<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Voo -->
<programme start="20230505030000 +0200" stop="20230505070000 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">Elections</title>
<desc lang="fr">Laura Kuenssberg is your guide as the votes are counted in 2023's bumper set of elections. BBC correspondents are at the key counts all around the country. In the studio, Reeta Chakrabarti crunches the numbers on her giant screens, and Professor Sir John Curtice assesses the underlying electoral trends. The BBC's political editor, Chris Mason, analyses what these elections mean for each political party, and senior politicians are on hand to give their verdict on the results.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/25/1752978_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230505070000 +0200" stop="20230505101500 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">Breakfast</title>
<desc lang="fr">The latest news, sport, business and weather from the BBC's Breakfast team.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine d'information</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/10/1672967_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230505101500 +0200" stop="20230505110000 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">Morning Live S5</title>
<desc lang="fr">Conversation, advice and great company to make your morning.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/20/17/1747401_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230505110000 +0200" stop="20230505114500 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">Scam Interceptors S2 (5/20)</title>
<desc lang="fr">Working with ethical hackers, Rav Wilding is hunting down the scammers plaguing our lives.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Documentaire</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/07/1752501_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230505114500 +0200" stop="20230505121500 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">Maximum Security S1 (5/10)</title>
<desc lang="fr">Dom Littlewood sees how security works at a premiership rugby match in Bristol.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/05/2122135_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230505121500 +0200" stop="20230505131500 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">Homes Under the Hammer S24 (69/80)</title>
<desc lang="fr">Featuring properties in Wolverhampton, Stoke-on-Trent and Dover.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Télé-Réalité</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/22/00/2157992_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230505131500 +0200" stop="20230505140000 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">Bargain Hunt</title>
<desc lang="fr">Christina Trevanion presents a right royal showdown to celebrate the coronation of King Charles III. Experts Raj Bisram and Roo Irvine are on hand to help two teams of royal enthusiasts as they race to be crowned winners. Christina also visits a pottery for an exclusive look at some new commemorative ware, and she makes her own royal plate fit for a king.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/58/1626268_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230505140000 +0200" stop="20230505144500 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">BBC News</title>
<desc lang="fr">The latest national and international news from the BBC.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Infos</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/20/22/1880115_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230505144500 +0200" stop="20230505173000 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">Politics Live</title>
<desc lang="fr">Jo Coburn is your guide as the votes are counted in 2023's bumper set of elections. BBC correspondents will be at all the key counts around the country. David Wallace Lockhart will crunch the numbers on his giant screen, and Professor Sir John Curtice will assess the underlying electoral trends. Senior politicians and commentators will be on hand to give their verdict on the results.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/22/02/2030147_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230505173000 +0200" stop="20230505181500 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">Unbeatable S2</title>
<desc lang="fr">Jason Manford hosts the quiz show where players try to find the unbeatable answer.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Jeu</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/24/32/2165230_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230505181500 +0200" stop="20230505190000 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">Pointless S29</title>
<desc lang="fr">The brainy quiz returns - but this time host Alexander Armstrong is joined by co-host Ria Lina. As always, contestants try to score as few points as possible by plumbing the depths of their general knowledge to come up with the answers no-one else could think of.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Jeu</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/47/1730372_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230505190000 +0200" stop="20230505200000 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">BBC News</title>
<desc lang="fr">The latest national and international news from the BBC.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Infos</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/20/22/1880115_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230505200000 +0200" stop="20230505210000 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">The Eve of the Coronation</title>
<desc lang="fr">As the nation prepares to mark a historic day, Kirsty Young is joined by a range of guests who give personal insights into the King and Queen Consort as they look ahead to the coronation. Some of the lucky invited guests attending the ceremony talk to the programme, along with those who have had close and personal connections with King Charles for many years. Kirsty speaks to celebrities who have spent time with the King, and hears from some of the people across the nation taking on once-in-a-lifetime roles in this historic ceremony. Sophie Raworth joins from outside Westminster Abbey, while JJ Chalmers speaks to members of the military as they prepare for one of the biggest military parades in British living memory.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/18/07/2185485_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230505210000 +0200" stop="20230505220000 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">Sing for the King: The Search for the Coronation Choir</title>
<desc lang="fr">Across the four corners of Britain, on stages and behind closed doors, hundreds of communities, friends, neighbours and colleagues are getting together to experience the power, joy and togetherness singing in a choir brings. As the nation prepares for the coronation of King Charles III, a very special choir is given the once-in-a-lifetime chance to sing their hearts out for the King and Queen Consort and the millions watching around the world at the Coronation Concert in Windsor Castle. The choir is made up of singing groups of all shapes and sizes; ordinary people who are passionate about the power of song to bring together their communities. Ready to roll up their sleeves and put the choirs through their paces are celebrity mentors Gareth Malone, Motsi Mabuse, Amanda Holden and Rose Ayling-Ellis.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/11/02/1790925_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230505220000 +0200" stop="20230505223000 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">Have I Got News for You S65</title>
<desc lang="fr">Alexander Armstrong is guest host, with panellists comedian Maisie Adam and journalist Helen Lewis joining team captains Paul Merton and Ian Hislop as they delve into the news.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Jeu</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/31/17/1858485_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230505223000 +0200" stop="20230505230000 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">Black Ops S1 (1/6)</title>
<desc lang="fr">Dom and Kay, two ordinary PCSOs, are recruited for a special undercover mission.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Série Comédie</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/56/1752524_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230505230000 +0200" stop="20230505234000 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">BBC News</title>
<desc lang="fr">The latest national and international news, with reports from BBC correspondents worldwide.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Infos</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/20/22/1880115_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230505234000 +0200" stop="20230506013500 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">Les gardiens de la galaxie</title>
<desc lang="fr">Peter Quill, a nerveless adventurer, becomes the galaxy's most wanted after stealing a mysterious orb.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Science-Fiction</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/31/10/1628710_A.jpg" />
</programme>