<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Voo -->
<programme start="20230520030500 +0200" stop="20230520070000 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">BBC News</title>
<desc lang="fr">BBC One joins the BBC's rolling news channel for a night of news.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Infos</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/20/22/1880115_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230520070000 +0200" stop="20230520110000 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">Breakfast</title>
<desc lang="fr">The latest news, sport, business and weather from the BBC's Breakfast team.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine d'information</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/10/1672967_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230520110000 +0200" stop="20230520123000 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">Saturday Kitchen</title>
<desc lang="fr">Host Matt Tebbutt is joined by chefs Sabrina Ghayour and Max La Manna. There are some great moments from the BBC food archive, including clips from Rick Stein, Marcus Wareing, Nigella Lawson and Keith Floyd. And drinks expert Olly Smith picks the wines to go with the studio dishes.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/56/1682723_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230520123000 +0200" stop="20230520130000 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">Mary Berry: Love to Cook S1</title>
<desc lang="fr">Mary's favourite way to show family and friends she cares is through her delicious food.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/08/05/2182094_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230520130000 +0200" stop="20230520140000 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">Football Focus</title>
<desc lang="fr">Alex Scott and guests reflect on the latest football headlines, including the Champions League semi-finals, and preview the penultimate weekend of the Premier League season. After hosting Real Madrid in midweek in the Champions League semi-final second leg, Manchester City continue their Premier League title defence with a home game against Chelsea. Arsenal visit relegation-threatened Nottingham Forest, with struggling Everton away at Wolves.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Football</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/20/1747376_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230520140000 +0200" stop="20230520141500 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">BBC News</title>
<desc lang="fr">The latest national and international news from the BBC.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Infos</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/20/22/1880115_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230520141500 +0200" stop="20230520150000 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">Bargain Hunt S52</title>
<desc lang="fr">Charlie Ross joins experts Tim Weeks and Charles Hanson at The Ardingly Antiques &amp; Collectors fair. The reds and blues go head to head to find some bargains that they hope will make a profit at auction. Meanwhile, Charlie learns about one of the bravest British Heroines of the 20th Century.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/58/1626268_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230520150000 +0200" stop="20230520173000 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">Leeds Rhinos v Wigan Warriors</title>
<desc lang="fr">Leeds Rhinos take on Wigan Warriors in the Rugby League Challenge Cup.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/06/39/1788807_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230520173000 +0200" stop="20230520181000 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">Final Score</title>
<desc lang="fr">Jason Mohammad keeps you up to date on developments in the afternoon's matches, with goal flashes and reports from across the country, as well as studio analysis and debate. Final Score can also be watched on the BBC Sport website plus mobile, tablet and connected TV.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Football</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/03/1776306_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230520181000 +0200" stop="20230520184000 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">Garden Rescue S6</title>
<desc lang="fr">Lionel and Paulette's garden in Droitwich Spa is an unusual shape, meaning it's heavily overlooked, and the couple find it uninspiring. Lionel loves firing up the barbecue, but they also want a tranquil space to relax in, and they want to create harmony between their indoor and outdoor spaces. Can Charlie and the Rich brothers create a zoned garden with plenty of screening that ticks all the boxes?</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/12/05/2195761_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230520184000 +0200" stop="20230520190000 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">BBC News</title>
<desc lang="fr">The latest national and international news from the BBC.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Infos</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/20/22/1880115_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230520190000 +0200" stop="20230520200000 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">Michael McIntyre's The Wheel S3</title>
<desc lang="fr">Michael McIntyre is back with his hit Saturday night game show that's packed with huge stars, big laughs and a colossal spinning wheel! Three contestants hope to answer their way to a fortune, with the help of seven celebrities, but it all depends on the spin of The Wheel. The celebrities on The Wheel tonight are: Anton Du Beke, Josie Gibson, Iain Stirling, Kadeena Cox, Nigel Ng, Tony Blackburn and Emma Barnett.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Jeu</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/14/2162907_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230520200000 +0200" stop="20230520203500 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">Blankety Blank S1</title>
<desc lang="fr">With Sally Lindsay, Andi Oliver, Jimmy Carr, Sophie Ellis-Bextor, and Melvin Odoom.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Jeu</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/24/15/1907356_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230520203500 +0200" stop="20230520212500 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">Pointless Celebrities S15</title>
<desc lang="fr">A celebrity special edition of the general knowledge quiz in which four teams try to come up with the answers that no-one else could think of. Presented by Alexander Armstrong and co-host Richard Osman and featuring Phil Tufnell, Mark Butcher, Cece Lightfoot, Pooja Shah, Chris McCausland, Sarah Keyworth, Ritchie Neville and Scott Robinson.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Jeu</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/47/1730372_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230520212500 +0200" stop="20230520221500 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">Casualty (Believe Me) S37 (n°31)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Believe Me»Jodie's night out turns into a nightmare, and Faith is given bad news.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Série Dramatique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/10/2125892_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230520221500 +0200" stop="20230520231000 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">Annika S1 (1/6)</title>
<desc lang="fr">Annika is called in to solve the murder of a man found with a harpoon in his head.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Série Policière</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/06/06/1912301_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230520231000 +0200" stop="20230520233000 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">BBC News</title>
<desc lang="fr">The latest national and international news from the BBC.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Infos</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/20/22/1880115_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230520233000 +0200" stop="20230521005000 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">Match of the Day 2</title>
<desc lang="fr">Gary Lineker presents highlights of the day's Premier League games, including relegation-threatened sides Nottingham Forest and Everton's matches against Arsenal and Wolves. Arsenal thrashed Forest 5-0 in October's reverse fixture to return to the top of the Premier League table, but indifferent results last month culminated in the Gunners' damaging defeat by title rivals Manchester City. Forest have struggled for much of the season in their quest to avoid an immediate return to the Championship. Sean Dyche's Everton headed to Molineux, seeking to end a run of three straight defeats against Wolves, who have impressed at home since the turn of the year. Elsewhere, Bournemouth welcomed Manchester United, Spurs hosted Brentford, Liverpool and Aston Villa met at Anfield and Crystal Palace made the short trip to Fulham.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Football</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/13/2125913_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521005000 +0200" stop="20230521012000 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">Dark Arts</title>
<desc lang="fr">Expect eye-watering tales as Gary Lineker, Micah Richards and Alan Shearer discuss the players in Premier League history most adept at using sly tactics to gain an advantage. Whether it be tactical fouls, time wasting, diving or even pinching, master manipulators of the Premier League era include former Liverpool forward Luis Suárez and midfielders Vinnie Jones and Joey Barton.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Football</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/29/1906477_A.jpg" />
</programme>