<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Voo -->
<programme start="20230521030000 +0200" stop="20230521070000 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">BBC News</title>
<desc lang="fr">BBC One joins the BBC's rolling news channel for a night of news.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Infos</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/20/22/1880115_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521070000 +0200" stop="20230521083500 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">Breakfast</title>
<desc lang="fr">The latest news, sport, business and weather from the BBC's Breakfast team.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine d'information</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/10/1672967_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521083500 +0200" stop="20230521100000 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">Match of the Day 2</title>
<desc lang="fr">Gary Lineker presents highlights of the day's Premier League games, including relegation-threatened sides Nottingham Forest and Everton's matches against Arsenal and Wolves. Arsenal thrashed Forest 5-0 in October's reverse fixture to return to the top of the Premier League table, but indifferent results last month culminated in the Gunners' damaging defeat by title rivals Manchester City. Forest have struggled for much of the season in their quest to avoid an immediate return to the Championship. Sean Dyche's Everton headed to Molineux, seeking to end a run of three straight defeats against Wolves, who have impressed at home since the turn of the year. Elsewhere, Bournemouth welcomed Manchester United, Spurs hosted Brentford, Liverpool and Aston Villa met at Anfield and Crystal Palace made the short trip to Fulham.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Football</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/13/2125913_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521100000 +0200" stop="20230521110000 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">Sunday with Laura Kuenssberg</title>
<desc lang="fr">Interviews with key politicians and public figures.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/54/1752485_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521110000 +0200" stop="20230521113000 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">Politics England</title>
<desc lang="fr">The latest political news, interviews and debate.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/47/1745775_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521113000 +0200" stop="20230521120000 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">Homes Under the Hammer S23 (10/10)</title>
<desc lang="fr">Featuring properties in County Durham, Cumbira and Worcestershire.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Télé-Réalité</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/43/2161497_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521120000 +0200" stop="20230521140000 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">Athlétisme : Great Manchester Run</title>
<desc lang="fr">Live coverage of the 2023 Great Manchester Run.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/27/1868371_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521140000 +0200" stop="20230521141500 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">BBC News</title>
<desc lang="fr">The latest national and international news from the BBC.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Infos</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/20/22/1880115_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521141500 +0200" stop="20230521145000 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">Songs of Praise (Christianity in County Down) (n°8)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Christianity in County Down»Claire McCollum meets the nuns who kayak on pilgrimage in County Down, Northern Ireland.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Documentaire</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/46/1978317_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521145000 +0200" stop="20230521150500 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">Points of View</title>
<desc lang="fr">Viewers have their say on the BBC's television shows. Email your thoughts to pov@bbc.co.uk.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/20/19/1790863_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521150500 +0200" stop="20230521155000 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">Escape to the Country S22 (22/55)</title>
<desc lang="fr">Jules Hudson is helping a couple from Middlesex to make a move to Norfolk or Suffolk.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Télé-Réalité</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/24/14/2125917_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521155000 +0200" stop="20230521173500 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">Les enfants du chemin de fer</title>
<desc lang="fr">After Charles Waterbury is mysteriously arrested on suspicion of being a spy, his family becomes impoverished and is forced to move from a stately townhouse to a small, shabby Yorkshire cottage near Oakworth railway station. When Mrs Waterbury and her three children arrive, they find the place in a complete mess, but do their best to make it more comfortable. While their mother learns how to perform household chores, Roberta, Phyllis and Peter find amusement in watching the trains and waving to the passengers. Along the way, they make new friends and try to discover the reason for their father's disappearance.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Comédie</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/17/2122503_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521173500 +0200" stop="20230521183500 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">Primates (Secrets of Survival) S1 (1/3)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Secrets of Survival»The strategies monkeys, apes and lemurs use to survive in the most unexpected places.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Animalier</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/07/2024050_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521183500 +0200" stop="20230521190000 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">BBC News</title>
<desc lang="fr">The latest national and international news from the BBC.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Infos</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/20/22/1880115_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521190000 +0200" stop="20230521200000 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">Chelsea Flower Show</title>
<desc lang="fr">Countdown to RHS Chelsea Flower Show 2023.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/08/16/2193915_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521200000 +0200" stop="20230521210000 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">Countryfile</title>
<desc lang="fr">For the first of three visits this year, Sammi Kinghorn is on a hill farm in Cumbria, as she catches up with a passionate young farmer, 16-year-old Katie. From dawn to dusk it's all go, as Katie and Sammi get stuck into all the daily chores and a surprise birth. But it's not just the farm keeping Katie busy this year - it's also GCSE year! Sammi will find out how this determined young lady is not fazed as she juggles her studies with caring for her animals. Adam looks into the dangers facing sheep and lambs from an increase in dog attacks this year, Charlotte investigates fears a 40-year-old chemical dump is threatening a village in Wales, and in a new strand, we meet four young farmers from around the country as we follow their trials and tribulations of farming over the next few months.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Mag Société</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/43/2161494_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521210000 +0200" stop="20230521220000 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">Antiques Roadshow S45</title>
<desc lang="fr">The roadshow comes from the beautiful grounds of Belmont House in sunny Kent, where Fiona opens the show with perfect timing amongst Belmont's world-famous collection of clocks. Alastair Dickenson is sweet on an immaculate silver honey pot, while Runjeet Singh explores a newly discovered photographic archive revealing the story of Sikh worship in this corner of the county. Raj Bisram is brought a humble piece of wood with links to one of the most notorious British ships in history - the HMS Bounty - and recounts this stirring tale of betrayal on the high seas. Cristian Beadman is surprised by a pair of bronze owls, each hiding a saucy secret within, and Fiona foxtrots her way through a chat with dancer and Strictly Come Dancing judge Anton Du Beke.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/14/2162908_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521220000 +0200" stop="20230521230000 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">Ten Pound Poms S1 (2/6)</title>
<desc lang="fr">A haunted Terry retraces his steps from the night before.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Série Dramatique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/20/28/1758829_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521230000 +0200" stop="20230521233000 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">BBC News</title>
<desc lang="fr">The latest national and international news from the BBC.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Infos</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/20/22/1880115_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521233000 +0200" stop="20230522004000 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">Match of the Day 2</title>
<desc lang="fr">Mark Chapman brings you the goals, drama and analysis from Sunday's three Premier League fixtures, including reigning champions Manchester City at home to fallen giants Chelsea. City, who were in Champions League semi-final action midweek, went into this game having already beaten Chelsea in three different competitions this season without conceding a goal. In the day's other matches, struggling sides Leeds United and Southampton were away to West Ham and Brighton &amp; Hove Albion.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Football</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/13/2125913_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230522004000 +0200" stop="20230522013000 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">The Women's Football Show</title>
<desc lang="fr">Highlights and analysis of all the action from the Women's Super League.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Football</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/57/1755436_A.jpg" />
</programme>