<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Voo -->
<programme start="20230603032000 +0200" stop="20230603070000 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">BBC News</title>
<desc lang="fr">BBC One joins the BBC's rolling news channel for a night of news.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Infos</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/20/27/1880115_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230603070000 +0200" stop="20230603110000 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">Breakfast</title>
<desc lang="fr">The latest news, sport, business and weather from the BBC's Breakfast team.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine d'information</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/10/1672967_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230603110000 +0200" stop="20230603123000 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">Saturday Kitchen</title>
<desc lang="fr">Host Matt Tebbutt is joined by chefs Ravinder Bhogal and Carlo Scotto, and special guest Dan Aykroyd. There are some great moments from the BBC food archive, including clips from Rick Stein, Marcus Wareing, Nadiya Hussain, and from the Two Greedy Italians, Gennaro Contaldo and Antonio Carluccio. Drinks expert Olly Smith picks the wines to go with the studio dishes.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/56/1682723_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230603123000 +0200" stop="20230603130000 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">Mary Berry: Love to Cook S1</title>
<desc lang="fr">Mary Berry proves watching the pennies does not mean having to sacrifice on flavour.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/08/05/2182094_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230603130000 +0200" stop="20230603140000 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">Football Focus</title>
<desc lang="fr">Alex Scott and guests look ahead to Wembley as city rivals Manchester City and Manchester United meet for the very first time in an FA Cup final. The classic showpiece concludes the domestic football season, and you can also look back on the standout highlights from a stellar campaign of Premier League action.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Football</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/20/1747376_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230603140000 +0200" stop="20230603141500 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">BBC News</title>
<desc lang="fr">The latest national and international news from the BBC.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Infos</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/20/27/1880115_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230603141500 +0200" stop="20230603145000 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">FA Cup: The Road to Wembley</title>
<desc lang="fr">A reimagined look back at the 2022/23 season's gripping FA Cup journey through a homage to classic video games. From incredible comebacks to tense ties settled at the penalty spot, this campaign has included its fair share of drama, culminating in a historic first meeting between Manchester City and Manchester United in the FA Cup final.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Football</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/19/06/2198632_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230603145000 +0200" stop="20230603183500 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">Manchester City / Manchester United</title>
<desc lang="fr">Manchester City meet local rivals Manchester United in a blockbuster contest at Wembley as football's oldest cup competition reaches its exhilarating climax. The two Manchester clubs have met 188 times in all competitions but never before in an FA Cup final. City have won the competition most recently, lifting the trophy for a sixth time after defeating Watford four years ago. United have won the FA Cup 12 times - a tally bettered only by Arsenal's 13 - with their last triumph coming against Crystal Palace in 2016.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Football</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/08/27/1799272_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230603183500 +0200" stop="20230603193500 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">Garden Rescue S3</title>
<desc lang="fr">In this episode, the team create two gardens for girls. The first is in the village of Liphook in East Hampshire, where Anne, Shaun and their daughter Joanne have lived in their comfortable home for many years. Their much-loved mid-sized family garden is looking the worse for wear, however, and the facelift the family envision includes a trampoline and a hot tub so that mum Anne will be able to see something &quot;wow&quot; whenever she looks out her windows. Meanwhile, in Aylesbury, Charlie and the Rich brothers pitch for the right to make over the garden of Michelle and Alistair and their two daughters, Tabitha and Jocelyn. They need to create a new sensory play and planting area for Tabitha and Jocelyn, who both have autism.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/11/19/2195336_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230603193500 +0200" stop="20230603195500 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">BBC News</title>
<desc lang="fr">The latest national and international news from the BBC.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Infos</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/20/27/1880115_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230603195500 +0200" stop="20230603203000 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">Blankety Blank S2</title>
<desc lang="fr">Bradley Walsh hosts as a panel of six celebrities fill in the missing blanks and help win some brilliant prizes for some very lucky contestants. This week, he's joined by Lorraine Kelly, Richard Madeley, Suzi Ruffell, Jimmy Carr, Su Pollard and Big Narstie.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Jeu</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/24/15/1907356_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230603203000 +0200" stop="20230603212000 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">Pointless Celebrities</title>
<desc lang="fr">A celebrity special edition of the general knowledge quiz in which four teams try to come up with the answers that no-one else could think of. Presented by Alexander Armstrong and co-host Richard Osman and featuring Kaye Adams, Kai Widdrington, Kelly Cates, Jill Douglas, Lucy Porter, Kevin Eldon, Dr Daniel Olaiya and Dr Raphael Olaiya.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Jeu</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/47/1730372_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230603212000 +0200" stop="20230603221000 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">Casualty (Amour-Plated) S37 (n°33)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Amour-Plated»Iain is forced to face a past trauma as Faith buckles under mounting pressure.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Série Dramatique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/20/01/2125892_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230603221000 +0200" stop="20230603230000 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">Annika S1 (3/6)</title>
<desc lang="fr">Annika investigates the death of a scientist found in Loch Katrine.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Série Policière</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/01/02/2160921_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230603230000 +0200" stop="20230603232000 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">BBC News</title>
<desc lang="fr">The latest national and international news from the BBC.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Infos</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/20/27/1880115_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230603232000 +0200" stop="20230604002000 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">Lionel Messi: Destiny</title>
<desc lang="fr">Behind-the-scenes documentary about how Lionel Messi finally won the World Cup.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Documentaire</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/10/1752533_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230604002000 +0200" stop="20230604005000 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">FA Cup Final Score</title>
<desc lang="fr">Watch the best of the action from Wembley as Manchester City face off Manchester United for the first time in an FA Cup final. Six-time winners City hope bto add to their trophy haul under manager Pep Guardiola after getting knocked out in last season's semi-finals, while United aim to add to their League Cup triumph earlier in this campaign and equal Arsenal's record of 13 FA Cup wins.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Football</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/08/27/1799272_A.jpg" />
</programme>