<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Voo -->
<programme start="20230408070000 +0200" stop="20230408110000 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">Breakfast</title>
<desc lang="fr">The latest news, sport, business and weather from the BBC's Breakfast team.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine d'information</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/10/1672967_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230408110000 +0200" stop="20230408123000 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">Saturday Kitchen</title>
<desc lang="fr">Matt Tebbutt and chefs Richard Bainbridge and Shivi Ramoutar are joined by special guest Judi Love, who faces her food heaven or food hell. There are great moments from the BBC food archive, including clips from Rick Stein, Marcus Wareing, Nigella Lawson and Keith Floyd, and drinks expert Helen McGinn picks the wines to go with the studio dishes.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/56/1682723_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230408123000 +0200" stop="20230408130000 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">Nadiya's Everyday Baking (Weekend Breakfasts) S1 (5/6)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Weekend Breakfasts»With a range of weekend breakfasts from granola cupcakes to an incredible breakfast pizza.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Documentaire</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/05/1752472_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230408130000 +0200" stop="20230408140000 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">Football Focus</title>
<desc lang="fr">Alex Scott and her guests reflect on the latest football headlines and preview the Easter weekend's matches, which include a trip to Liverpool for league leaders Arsenal. The Gunners have lost their past five league games at Anfield. Can they rise to the occasion in their quest for a first top-flight title since 2004? Liverpool were one of 12 teams in midweek Premier League action, with this weekend's fixtures also representing a quick turnaround for relegation candidates such as Leeds, West Ham, Bournemouth and Nottingham Forest.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Football</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/20/1747376_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230408140000 +0200" stop="20230408141500 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">BBC News</title>
<desc lang="fr">The latest national and international news from the BBC.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Infos</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/20/22/1880115_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230408141500 +0200" stop="20230408150000 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">Bargain Hunt</title>
<desc lang="fr">Join Charlie Ross for Bargain Hunt, which comes from the Royal Cornwall Showground in Wadebridge, where both the reds and blues with the help of experts Thomas Forrester and Tim Weeks hunt for bargains. Will it be a close call at auction in Plymouth? Charlie also gets a lesson in Cornish, as the Celtic language enjoys a revival.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/44/1745807_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230408150000 +0200" stop="20230408154500 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">Garden Rescue S7</title>
<desc lang="fr">Charlie and Flo go head-to-head with a budget of £4,000 to design a garden that takes inspiration from Crete, where Natalie and Matthew spent their honeymoon. Their L-shaped garden offers challenges for the designers, who also need to consider the couple's young toddler, Arthur. Charlie hopes her Greek-inspired planting scheme, pergola and water feature will appeal to the couple, while Flo is banking on the taverna-inspired seating area with colourful Mediterranean plants to sway the decision in her favour. But has Flo remembered a vital ingredient that Charlie may have overlooked?</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/31/01/2159493_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230408154500 +0200" stop="20230408164500 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">Escape to the Country S22 (11/20)</title>
<desc lang="fr">Suffolk is the destination for a couple from London who want a new life in the country.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Télé-Réalité</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/01/02/2153608_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230408164500 +0200" stop="20230408173000 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">Dodger (Special: Bad Egg) (n°3)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Special: Bad Egg»When a heist goes wrong, Dodger is given his harshest punishment yet - school!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Série Comédie</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/1752367_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230408173000 +0200" stop="20230408181500 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">Final Score</title>
<desc lang="fr">Kelly Somers with all the results, reports and reaction from the afternoon's big games.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Football</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/03/1776306_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230408181500 +0200" stop="20230408183500 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">BBC News</title>
<desc lang="fr">The latest national and international news from the BBC.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Infos</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/20/22/1880115_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230408183500 +0200" stop="20230408204500 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">Robin des Bois, prince des voleurs</title>
<desc lang="fr">Medieval adventure, starring Kevin Costner and Morgan Freeman. Nobleman Robert of Locksley returns to England from the Crusades with a Moor - who owes Locksley his life - in tow. They discover the evil Sheriff of Nottingham has stolen Locksley's lands and is running rampant across the country, and decide the time has come to fight back. Branded an outlaw, Locksley rallies the woodsmen around Nottingham and begins a rebellion.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Action/Aventures</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/28/33/2166893_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230408204500 +0200" stop="20230408213500 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">Pointless Celebrities S15</title>
<desc lang="fr">A special celebrity edition of the general knowledge quiz in which four teams try to come up with the answers that no-one else could think of. Presented by Alexander Armstrong and co-host Richard Osman, with contestants Lesley Garrett, Penny Lancaster, Noreen Khan, Eshaan Akbar, Laurie Brett, John Partridge, James King and Rosie Millard.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Jeu</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/47/1730372_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230408213500 +0200" stop="20230408222500 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">Casualty (Welcome to the Warzone) S37 (n°26)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Welcome to the Warzone»The paramedics welcome a recruit, and a new face in the ED turns Max's world upside down.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Série Dramatique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/10/2125892_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230408222500 +0200" stop="20230408231000 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">Comptine mortelle S1 (2/6)</title>
<desc lang="fr">Susan arrives in Suffolk, searching for the missing chapter.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Série Thriller</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/31/07/2170602_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230408231000 +0200" stop="20230408233000 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">BBC News</title>
<desc lang="fr">The latest national and international news from the BBC.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Infos</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/20/22/1880115_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230408233000 +0200" stop="20230409010000 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">Match of the Day</title>
<desc lang="fr">Gary Lineker introduces highlights and analysis of the day's eight Premier League games, including Manchester United v Everton and Spurs against surprise top-four rivals Brighton. Manchester United had already earned league and FA Cup victories this season against Everton, who have continued to struggle away from home since Sean Dyche was appointed as manager in January. Brighton &amp; Hove Albion are on course for the best top-flight season in the club's history, and they continued their unlikely charge for Champions League qualification with a trip to a talented but erratic Tottenham side.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Football</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/13/2125913_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230409010000 +0200" stop="20230409013000 +0200" channel="BBC1.uk">
<title lang="fr">Greatest Premier League Hat-Tricks</title>
<desc lang="fr">Gary Lineker, Alan Shearer and Micah Richards debate the greatest Premier League hat-tricks. The incredible list includes Dennis Bergkamp's sublime treble against Leicester, fellow Dutchman Robin van Persie's title-clinching effort for Manchester United at home to Aston Villa, and Luis Suarez's one-man demolition of Norwich. And what of Shearer - will any of his 11 Premier League hat-tricks make the top 10?</desc>
<category lang="fr">Football</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/57/1755436_A.jpg" />
</programme>