<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Telerama -->
<programme start="20230522074500 +0200" stop="20230522081500 +0200" channel="BBC2.uk">
<title lang="fr">Clive Myrie's Italian Road Trip</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Conegliano</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">The UK drinks a third of Italy's prosecco, but British visitors rarely make it to this corner of the Veneto region. After spending a night in a giant wine barrel, Clive learns why prosecco is just as good as champagne from one of the country's few female winegrowers, before jumping into the navigator's seat in a 70-year-old Maserati and hunting for antiques in the hilltop town of Asolo.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Documentaire voyage</category>
<icon src="https://focus.telerama.fr/1111x625/2021/07/13/6053caf4980caacb94184af0e78f86314e8efc4e.jpg" />
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230522081500 +0200" stop="20230522090000 +0200" channel="BBC2.uk">
<title lang="fr">Bargain Hunt</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Leominster 5</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">The market town of Leominster is the destination for today's show. Guiding the teams around an antiques centre in the Herefordshire town are Kate Bliss and Philip Serrell, but which team will make the biggest profit or the smallest loss at auction? Meanwhile, presenter Eric Knowles visits Hereford Cathedral's 17th-century library, where the books are kept under lock and key.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine des loisirs</category>
<icon src="https://focus.telerama.fr/1111x625/2021/07/19/5d8d00daa5463cdf2e2f319e6e717969bca63250.jpg" />
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230522090000 +0200" stop="20230522093000 +0200" channel="BBC2.uk">
<title lang="fr">Rick Stein's Cornwall</title>
<desc lang="fr">Rick drops in on the fishing port of Boscastle and finds a fabulous seafood restaurant in a building which once housed rockets used to fire safety ropes out to sinking ships. A trip to Cornwall's only dedicated organic mushroom farm inspires him to cook a stir fry with 'lion's mane' mushrooms, which are said to regrow your neurons! After a surreal afternoon spent watching a German film crew at work in the fishing village of Mousehole, he discovers that a major reason so many Germans love Cornwall is a long-running TV series, watched by millions, that is based on the romances written by Rosamunde Pilcher and set in Cornwall.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Documentaire voyage</category>
<icon src="https://focus.telerama.fr/1111x625/2022/01/31/6b28c90585f03c95465edbaefcfb0a5e15256cf6.jpg" />
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230522093000 +0200" stop="20230522100000 +0200" channel="BBC2.uk">
<title lang="fr">Banjo: Designing the Hebrides</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Book Shop</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Banjo and his team head north to the Isle of Skye and their biggest transformation to date. Owners of a remote café and bookshop are desperate to update their business, but with a vast space to fill, Banjo takes the bold decision to spend almost all his budget on a set of huge stained-glass windows. Far from home, and with tricky logistics, will this job push the team to their limits, and will Banjo's ambitious gamble payoff with his clients?</desc>
<category lang="fr">Documentaire fiction</category>
<icon src="https://focus.telerama.fr/1111x625/2022/12/26/00aca9ab7d6a4c7b887936d4835608970ebf5dfd.jpg" />
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230522100000 +0200" stop="20230522120000 +0200" channel="BBC2.uk">
<title lang="fr">Nicky Campbell BBC News Talk</title>
<desc lang="fr">Nicky Campbell takes your calls on the day's talking points, hearing views and experiences from across the UK. Call 08085 909693 between 9am and 11am on weekdays (calls are free from mobiles and landlines).</desc>
<category lang="fr">Interview</category>
<icon src="https://focus.telerama.fr/1111x625/2022/03/08/7b40309936178ee8c9f175e094a2c7c119b180e0.jpg" />
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230522120000 +0200" stop="20230522131500 +0200" channel="BBC2.uk">
<title lang="fr">BBC News</title>
<desc lang="fr">A suivre, les dernières actualités présentées par les équipes rédactionnelles de la BBC, le très réputé radiodiffuseur du service public britannique. Créée en 1922 à Londres, la British Broadcast Corporation est connue pour être la plus ancienne société diffusant des programmes de radio ou de télévision au monde.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Journal</category>
<icon src="https://focus.telerama.fr/1111x625/2021/11/29/85ace61f31e6c99dce97b4d2ed5ccf70ca270f0a.jpg" />
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230522131500 +0200" stop="20230522140000 +0200" channel="BBC2.uk">
<title lang="fr">Politics Live</title>
<desc lang="fr">Join presenter Jo Coburn as she discusses the latest political news and stories in a conversational format, covering the comings-and-goings from Westminster in the BBC's daily politics programme. Featuring opinions and arguments from all the sides of the political spectrum, the show invites informed and opinionated guests to share their views on the stories of the day.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Talk-show</category>
<icon src="https://focus.telerama.fr/1111x625/2022/03/12/9185c9e3ea617ca48429a852b2abf8713965f944.jpg" />
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230522140000 +0200" stop="20230522144500 +0200" channel="BBC2.uk">
<title lang="fr">Impossible</title>
<desc lang="fr">Entertaining and educational British quiz show, hosted by Rick Edwards, where 24 regular contestants compete throughout the series to answer tricky questions. But some of the optional answers are designed to be ''impossible'', or at the very least inconsistent with the information given. The participants must avoid selecting these booby trap answer and the best one wins the £10,000 jackpot.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Jeu</category>
<icon src="https://focus.telerama.fr/1111x625/2021/07/19/f75d1d2acfd3df0d4253e988ada41a790d3402d9.jpg" />
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230522144500 +0200" stop="20230522151500 +0200" channel="BBC2.uk">
<title lang="fr">Eggheads</title>
<desc lang="fr">Teams from all over the UK battle to beat the formidable Eggheads.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Jeu</category>
<icon src="https://focus.telerama.fr/1111x625/2021/11/29/8f93a93ddd7c3b42ba0540d2384df2da09736acc.jpg" />
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230522151500 +0200" stop="20230522154500 +0200" channel="BBC2.uk">
<title lang="fr">James Martin's Food Map of Britain</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">South East</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">James Martin visits the sunny south east to find out why Kent's cherries are so sweet.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://focus.telerama.fr/1111x625/2023/05/15/c16652d3cd4ca30a96dc78f8bc079571a6ce2618_06494D0DEB3AEA12A33CE6191757EC45.jpg" />
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230522154500 +0200" stop="20230522161500 +0200" channel="BBC2.uk">
<title lang="fr">A Countryside Summer</title>
<desc lang="fr">Gethin Jones delivers the ultimate guide to a countryside summer, aided by some familar faces. Chris Packham shows us the wildlife we can look out for, Nadiya Hussain cooks lamb with rhubarb glaze on the barbecue and Sean Fletcher takes to the great outdoors on a bike-packing adventure.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Documentaire nature</category>
<icon src="https://focus.telerama.fr/1111x625/2021/06/16/279dfbeb4ef2c9565f312ab0937c5cd246a26414.jpg" />
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230522161500 +0200" stop="20230522171500 +0200" channel="BBC2.uk">
<title lang="fr">Eat Well for Less?</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Students</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Gregg and Chris help the Drew family tackle their picky palates.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine du consommateur</category>
<icon src="https://focus.telerama.fr/1111x625/2022/05/02/f6dc2f9e535310a26423ac2a50f9b8ef98d399fb.jpg" />
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230522171500 +0200" stop="20230522181500 +0200" channel="BBC2.uk">
<title lang="fr">Mission déco</title>
<desc lang="fr">Saison 3 Episode 6
The final four designers renovate two cafes in the seaside town of Margate.
Année de réalisation : 2022</desc>
<category lang="fr">Documentaire téléréalité</category>
<icon src="https://focus.telerama.fr/1111x625/2022/02/07/6c7f5c0947a23c77aa4c6c6860f15ee50609a9e1.jpg" />
<episode-num system="xmltv_ns">2.5.</episode-num>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230522181500 +0200" stop="20230522190000 +0200" channel="BBC2.uk">
<title lang="fr">Flog It !</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Compilation - Ugbrooke 38</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Flog It! revisits some of the stunning locations from this series. The experts are hunting out antiques and collectibles at Greenwich Royal Naval College, Althorp House, Herstmonceux Castle and Reading Town Hall. Paul Martin visits Killerton in Devon and uncovers the fascinating story of Richard Acland, who gave away his fortune for his political beliefs.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://focus.telerama.fr/1111x625/2021/07/19/4756596759d48a5a8c2f5bc3deadf48916595e76.jpg" />
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230522190000 +0200" stop="20230522193000 +0200" channel="BBC2.uk">
<title lang="fr">Richard Osman's House of Games</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Week 13: Monday</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Mehreen Baig, Clare Balding, Jamie Laing and Mike Wozniak test their general knowledge.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Jeu</category>
<icon src="https://focus.telerama.fr/1111x625/2021/06/15/4960c8de813af5a7a3f04becd1f99eb04183561b.jpg" />
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230522193000 +0200" stop="20230522200000 +0200" channel="BBC2.uk">
<title lang="fr">Great Coastal Railway Journeys</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Douglas to Port Erin</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Michael Portillo embarks on another railway adventure across and beyond the United Kingdom, beginning on the self-governing Isle of Man - a paradise for rail lovers. He visits the Isle's ancient parliament, the Tynwald, which is older than Westminster; is taken down the east coast on the Isle of Man Steam Railway to the Norse castle of Rushen; testdrives the smallest production car ever made in Peel; joins a working fishing boat at Port St Mary; and meets two passionate advocates of the Manx language.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Documentaire voyage</category>
<icon src="https://focus.telerama.fr/1111x625/2023/05/15/75e0aa73579728be192673e56d429e348cc225f5_B35AD2164FBB12C0E5E66006464F77E9.jpg" />
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230522200000 +0200" stop="20230522203000 +0200" channel="BBC2.uk">
<title lang="fr">Grand Tours of Scotland's Rivers</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">A River of Invention</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Paul discovers the source of the remarkable River Nith, high in a remote forestry plantation. Heading downstream, he hears the story of the Knockshinnoch mining disaster - how 116 men were saved from entombment after a massive earth collapse. At Sanquhar, once famous for its unique and distinctive knitting pattern, Paul tries very hard to knit a glove before it all unravels. Kirkpatrick Macmillan was the man first credited with making a bicycle with pedals. Paul wobbles in his wake aboard a replica at Drumlanrig Castle, before heading south to Ellisland - once the riverside home of the poet Robert Burns. In Dumfries, Paul learns how astronaut Neil Armstrong might not have walked on the surface of the moon without the optical skills of a local man. Journey's end is at Caerlaverock Castle overlooking the shining sands of the Solway Firth.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Documentaire nature</category>
<icon src="https://focus.telerama.fr/1111x625/2023/05/08/2e1d5a0107f0bbe5df886c8dbc08a5f6966dae2c_AE4CB5E53E90769CDD63B2D664F60B22.jpg" />
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230522203000 +0200" stop="20230522213000 +0200" channel="BBC2.uk">
<title lang="fr">Chelsea Flower Show</title>
<desc lang="fr">Coverage of the RHS Chelsea Flower Show.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine des loisirs</category>
<icon src="https://focus.telerama.fr/1111x625/2023/05/15/35427168a783a5ecd68ee8baa5c66de8f6937b38_6A43A5E09264C4D7A0788F0B0C28AEA0.jpg" />
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230522213000 +0200" stop="20230522220000 +0200" channel="BBC2.uk">
<title lang="fr">University Challenge</title>
<desc lang="fr">In the second of the series semi-finals, Jeremy Paxman asks the questions.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Jeu</category>
<icon src="https://focus.telerama.fr/1111x625/2021/11/16/d0526e977a27dfc0739323feb3acb1170efdbd84.jpg" />
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230522220000 +0200" stop="20230522231500 +0200" channel="BBC2.uk">
<title lang="fr">Once Upon a Time Northern Ireland</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">It Wasn't Like a Movie Anymore</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">A time of relative peace in Northern Ireland escalates to full-blown conflict. As a civil rights movement gains pace, demanding equal rights for Catholics, the Provisional IRA comes to the fore, causing the British Army to be deployed. With the situation compounded by tactical mistakes, soldiers quickly find themselves caught up in violent clashes - leading to 13 unarmed Catholics being shot dead by British paratroopers in Derry on what becomes known as Bloody Sunday.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Documentaire histoire</category>
<icon src="https://focus.telerama.fr/1111x625/2021/06/16/ac3d61f24144608dcee5c41ebc9b290a3ab4dc53.jpg" />
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230522231500 +0200" stop="20230522233000 +0200" channel="BBC2.uk">
<title lang="fr">QI XS</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Quite Intrepid</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">A selection of classic clips from QI with travel in mind.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://focus.telerama.fr/1111x625/2022/10/24/01674cb2ed841966dcc342fdcfb1c0c779c8e2c3.jpg" />
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230522233000 +0200" stop="20230523001500 +0200" channel="BBC2.uk">
<title lang="fr">Newsnight</title>
<desc lang="fr">In-depth news and current affairs review of the main political and economic stories of the day, featuring robust interviews with senior government and opposition figures, business and trade union leaders.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Journal</category>
<icon src="https://focus.telerama.fr/1111x625/2021/07/19/08ec05a53a765eaab01e8ef11150cc0505bcc968.jpg" />
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230523001500 +0200" stop="20230523021000 +0200" channel="BBC2.uk">
<title lang="fr">Do the Right Thing</title>
<desc lang="fr">Malgré la canicule qui écrase la mégapole new-yorkaise, les habitants d'une rue du quartier de Bedford-Stuyvesant vaquent à leurs occupations habituelles. Il y a Sal, d'origine italienne, qui tient une pizzeria avec Vito et Pino, ses deux fils, Mookie, l'employé amoureux de Tina, Da Mayor, un vieil alcoolique qui traîne dans les rues et Smiley, un bègue qui tente de revendre des vieilles photos de Martin Luther King et de Malcolm X. La vie aurait pu continuer ainsi sans un banal incident qui déchaîne soudain les tensions raciales. En effet, un jour, Sal oblige un voyou du quartier à éteindre son radiocassette qu'il fait hurler à longueur de journées...
Année de réalisation : 1989</desc>
<category lang="fr">Drame</category>
<icon src="https://focus.telerama.fr/1111x625/2021/03/29/395c1aa8-9fc5-4202-b2cc-3074ba844c96.jpg" />
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230523021000 +0200" stop="20230523030500 +0200" channel="BBC2.uk">
<title lang="fr">Countryfile</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Mental Health Awareness</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Countryfile explores initiatives helping people to improve their mental wellbeing.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine de société</category>
<icon src="https://focus.telerama.fr/1111x625/2023/03/06/796f56a5b6ab189f20d50d2e7b11608d0a5b2a03.jpg" />
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230523030500 +0200" stop="20230523033500 +0200" channel="BBC2.uk">
<title lang="fr">Wrexham: Hollywood or Bust</title>
<desc lang="fr">Wrexham AFC are one of the oldest football clubs in the world, with a home in the Racecourse Ground that dates back virtually to the dawn of football as we know it. Theirs is a history that stretches back further than most, with drama and memorable moments to rival any club. A lot happened at Wrexham before they were taken over by two Hollywood actors. Ryan Reynolds and Rob McElhenney have put a shot in the arm of a sleeping giant. To the fans, promotion is more than just cause for celebration. This documentary tells the story of Wrexham, past and present, with a blend of archive footage, heart-warming testimonials and footage from the Racecourse Ground today.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Documentaire sport</category>
<icon src="https://focus.telerama.fr/1111x625/2021/08/09/26398fa3db94e67a43ff49d687aba6c97bab1ea6.jpg" />
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230523033500 +0200" stop="20230523043500 +0200" channel="BBC2.uk">
<title lang="fr">Turkey: Empire of Erdogan</title>
<desc lang="fr">Erdogan's rise to power and how his initial popularity turns to mass protests against him.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Documentaire politique</category>
<icon src="https://focus.telerama.fr/1111x625/2021/06/16/7008f91b432e9e21d598cff7abc92ed92df187f3.jpg" />
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230523043500 +0200" stop="20230523073000 +0200" channel="BBC2.uk">
<title lang="fr">This is BBC Two</title>
<desc lang="fr">This is BBC Two.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Emission spéciale</category>
<icon src="https://focus.telerama.fr/1111x625/2022/04/04/46aa775cca9a893a3168a0fd9ceb31194996fca1.jpg" />
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>