<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Voo -->
<programme start="20230407020000 +0200" stop="20230407023000 +0200" channel="CNBC.be">
<title lang="fr">Nick Jones S1</title>
<desc lang="fr">From just one private member's club a hospitality empire was born. Tania Bryer sits down with Nick Jones, Founder and CEO of Soho House to talk about expansion, exclusivity and his early career.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Autre</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/06/1790338_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230407023000 +0200" stop="20230407030000 +0200" channel="CNBC.be">
<title lang="fr">Kumar Mangalam Birla S1</title>
<desc lang="fr">He's the fourth generation to lead one of the largest conglomerates in India. A company whose history is closely tied to the late Mahatma Gandhi. Kumar Mangalam Birla, Chairman of the Aditya Birla Group, sits down for the CNBC Conversation.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Autre</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/06/1790338_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230407030000 +0200" stop="20230407033000 +0200" channel="CNBC.be">
<title lang="fr">US Closing Bell S2</title>
<desc lang="fr">Hosted by Sara Eisen and Wilfred Frost, Closing Bell brings you coverage of the final and most important hour of the trading day. The show provides insight to traders and investors by interviewing experts, CEOs and analysts, listening to their observations on the movements in the market. With live reports from stock exchanges across the USA, aspiring investors are given an informative platform from which to make informed and sensible decisions. Closing Bell also presents analysis of profit reports from a number of different corporations and speaks with wealthy executives who reveal how they spend their money and time.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/51/1680908_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230407033000 +0200" stop="20230407040000 +0200" channel="CNBC.be">
<title lang="fr">US Closing Bell S2</title>
<desc lang="fr">Hosted by Sara Eisen and Wilfred Frost, Closing Bell brings you coverage of the final and most important hour of the trading day. The show provides insight to traders and investors by interviewing experts, CEOs and analysts, listening to their observations on the movements in the market. With live reports from stock exchanges across the USA, aspiring investors are given an informative platform from which to make informed and sensible decisions. Closing Bell also presents analysis of profit reports from a number of different corporations and speaks with wealthy executives who reveal how they spend their money and time.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/51/1680908_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230407040000 +0200" stop="20230407050000 +0200" channel="CNBC.be">
<title lang="fr">La fièvre du dollar (The Art of the Steal / The Folsom Felon) S1 (n°47)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«The Art of the Steal / The Folsom Felon»&quot;The Art of the Steal&quot; Larry Salander is one of the biggest names in New York's art world. But collectors see red when he swipes more than $100 million from their pockets. &quot;The Folsom Felon&quot; Stefan Wilson says his investment fund is a sure-fire winner. Investors even mortgage their homes to join his fund. But business with Wilson comes at a very high price.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Documentaire</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/56/1805768_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230407050000 +0200" stop="20230407060000 +0200" channel="CNBC.be">
<title lang="fr">La fièvre du dollar (The Royal Scam: Kings of Counterfeit) S1 (n°46)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«The Royal Scam: Kings of Counterfeit»A tough guy from Chicago's South Side finds his way off the streets and into a lucrative life in counterfeiting. Art Williams Jr. prints millions in fake dollars.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Documentaire</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/56/1805768_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230407060000 +0200" stop="20230407063000 +0200" channel="CNBC.be">
<title lang="fr">Sue Kyung Lee, CEO, SK-II S1</title>
<desc lang="fr">Christine Tan travels to Japan for an exclusive look at the production process behind SK-II's famous skincare products. Global CEO, Sue Kyung Lee gives a guided tour as well as insight into what's next for the beauty brand.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Autre</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/04/1790342_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230407063000 +0200" stop="20230407070000 +0200" channel="CNBC.be">
<title lang="fr">Nanofilm Technologies S1</title>
<desc lang="fr">Nanofilm Technologies International's success is built on the company's proprietary wear-resistant carbon coating technology, which is used in electronic products for brands such as Microsoft, Hua Wei, Nikon, and Canon. Christine Tan speaks to founder and chairman, Shi Xu, to find out how the former professor turned a university research study into a multi-million-dollar business and himself into a billionaire.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Autre</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/04/1790342_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230407070000 +0200" stop="20230407080000 +0200" channel="CNBC.be">
<title lang="fr">La fièvre du dollar (Le gangster de l'opéra / Le flambeur des stades) (44/51)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Le gangster de l'opéra / Le flambeur des stades»&quot;Fraudster of the Opera&quot; Albert Vilar funds symphonies and operas around the world. But it's curtains for Vilar when he scams the mother of a Hollywood star. &quot;Frozen Assets - The Ice Capers&quot; William &quot;Boots&quot; Del Biaggio III is a hockey team owner skating on thin ice. His insatiable desire to be a sports mogul drives him to commit a multimillion-dollar fraud.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Documentaire</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/56/1805768_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230407080000 +0200" stop="20230407090000 +0200" channel="CNBC.be">
<title lang="fr">Last Call S1</title>
<desc lang="fr">Aucune description</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/09/1753801_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230407090000 +0200" stop="20230407093000 +0200" channel="CNBC.be">
<title lang="fr">Sustainable Future S1</title>
<desc lang="fr">Entrepreneur and environmentalist, Dale Vince speaks to CNBC's Tania Bryer about his green business portfolio, activism and why he thinks renewable energy will solve the European cost of living crisis.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/07/1790348_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230407093000 +0200" stop="20230407100000 +0200" channel="CNBC.be">
<title lang="fr">Sustainable Future S1</title>
<desc lang="fr">From the CNBC Davos Sanctuary, Tania Bryer sits down with John Kerry, the US Special Envoy on Climate to discuss what more needs to be done in the fight against climate change, including his &quot;loss and damage&quot; plans for developing nations.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/07/1790348_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230407100000 +0200" stop="20230407110000 +0200" channel="CNBC.be">
<title lang="fr">La fièvre du dollar (The Bling Ring / The Fraudster, the Ex-Stripper and the Missing Millions) S1 (n°43)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«The Bling Ring / The Fraudster, the Ex-Stripper and the Missing Millions»&quot;The Bling Ring&quot; They're called The Bling Ring. A fast crowd of celebrity wannabes. This gang of teenagers rob celebrity homes and steal millions in jewelry, clothing and artwork. How far will they go to be like their favorite Hollywood stars? &quot;The Fraudster, The Ex-Stripper and The Missing Millions&quot; Danny Pang is a high-rolling financier with a devil-may-care attitude. He makes millions betting on when people will die. But Pang has a shady past, a gambling habit and a murdered wife. Soon, this gambler's house of cards will collapse.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Documentaire</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/56/1805768_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230407110000 +0200" stop="20230407120000 +0200" channel="CNBC.be">
<title lang="fr">La fièvre du dollar (Pyramide de Ponzi et escroqueries en série) (42/51)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Pyramide de Ponzi et escroqueries en série»Scott Rothstein is a Ft. Lauderdale attorney making millions. He's the life of the party, a guy who wants the world to love him. But Rothstein is secretly a criminal mastermind.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Documentaire</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/56/1805768_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230407120000 +0200" stop="20230407123000 +0200" channel="CNBC.be">
<title lang="fr">Finding Purpose 1 S1</title>
<desc lang="fr">In the first episode in our Finding Purpose series, Christine Tan speaks to the leaders of Eu Yan Sang and Starhub to find out how they are steering their companies to, not only, build sustainable businesses but also ones with a corporate purpose to do good.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Autre</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/04/1790342_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230407123000 +0200" stop="20230407130000 +0200" channel="CNBC.be">
<title lang="fr">Finding Purpose 2 S1</title>
<desc lang="fr">Jewel Changi Airport and Gardens by the Bay are just two of the iconic sites in Singapore that Woh Hup has built. In the final episode of our Finding Purpose series, Christine Tan speaks to family members running one of the oldest construction companies in the country to find why they think giving back is an important business strategy.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Autre</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/04/1790342_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230407130000 +0200" stop="20230407140000 +0200" channel="CNBC.be">
<title lang="fr">La fièvre du dollar (L'escroc philanthrope) (41/51)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«L'escroc philanthrope»He's a trusted advisor. A philanthropist. Bob McLean runs a successful investment firm and donates millions to his favorite causes. But McLean has a dark, devastating secret.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Documentaire</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/56/1805768_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230407140000 +0200" stop="20230407150000 +0200" channel="CNBC.be">
<title lang="fr">La fièvre du dollar (Le roi des hackers) (40/51)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Le roi des hackers»A mysterious ring of social outcasts. Albert Gonzalez leads a gang with an insatiable appetite for sex, drugs...and your encrypted information. They steal credit card numbers and make a fortune by selling them on the black market. But the multi-million dollar scam has deadly consequences.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Documentaire</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/56/1805768_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230407150000 +0200" stop="20230407153000 +0200" channel="CNBC.be">
<title lang="fr">CNBC on Assignment S1</title>
<desc lang="fr">CNBC's Dan Murphy visits the Dubai street experts are calling &quot;Billionaires&quot; Row', goes inside a multimillion-dollar mega villa and investigates why Dubai's property market is seemingly defying an economic slowdown.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine d'information</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/10/1711242_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230407153000 +0200" stop="20230407160000 +0200" channel="CNBC.be">
<title lang="fr">CNBC on Assignment S1</title>
<desc lang="fr">CNBC's Dan Murphy goes behind the scenes at Arab Fashion Week in Dubai, meeting the global designers showcasing their latest collections, corporate partners and those working to put the Arab fashion industry on the map.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine d'information</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/10/1711242_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230407160000 +0200" stop="20230407170000 +0200" channel="CNBC.be">
<title lang="fr">La fièvre du dollar (Fools Gold) S1 (n°39)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Fools Gold»He's a philanthropist, a diplomat, and an international man of mystery. Dr. Henry Jones promises to get investors in on a secret gold deal. But Dr. Jones is leading a double life---a life unknown even to his partners in crime.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Documentaire</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/56/1805768_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230407170000 +0200" stop="20230407180000 +0200" channel="CNBC.be">
<title lang="fr">La fièvre du dollar (Le gourou de l'immobilier) (38/51)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Le gourou de l'immobilier»His pitch is irresistible: Troy Titus promises to make you rich. The self-proclaimed real estate guru travels the seminar circuit. Thousands attend his lectures, buy his DVDs and invest with the man who portrays himself as a moneymaking magician. It's true to an extent...Titus makes money disappear in a multi-million dollar Ponzi scheme!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Documentaire</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/56/1805768_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230407180000 +0200" stop="20230407183000 +0200" channel="CNBC.be">
<title lang="fr">The Edge (Dutch Water Tech) S1 (n°73)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Dutch Water Tech»As the climate changes, sea levels are predicted to rise, and extreme weather events are set to increase in frequency and intensity. In this episode of The Edge, CNBC's Julianna Tatelbaum travels to the Netherlands to explore Dutch innovations that help keep water at bay.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/02/1789416_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230407183000 +0200" stop="20230407190000 +0200" channel="CNBC.be">
<title lang="fr">The Edge (Fabrics of the Future) S1 (n°72)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Fabrics of the Future»From innovative materials to digital designs, CNBC's Tania Bryer explores the fabrics of the future.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/02/1789416_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230407190000 +0200" stop="20230407200000 +0200" channel="CNBC.be">
<title lang="fr">La fièvre du dollar (Gentleman cambrioleur) (37/51)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Gentleman cambrioleur»Stephen Trantel is a husband, a father...and a bank robber. He was once a broker making hundreds of thousands of dollars in the Manhattan trading pits. Unemployed, Trantel embarks on a new career?one of crime. His life -and the lives of those who love him?are changed forever.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Documentaire</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/56/1805768_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230407200000 +0200" stop="20230407210000 +0200" channel="CNBC.be">
<title lang="fr">La fièvre du dollar (Cybercrime) S1 (n°36)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Cybercrime»Max Butler is &quot;Iceman.&quot; He oversaw an underground Internet crime spree. Mysterious thugs steal information and access your financial life story. Billions are at stake.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Documentaire</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/56/1805768_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230407210000 +0200" stop="20230407213000 +0200" channel="CNBC.be">
<title lang="fr">Sustainable Future S1</title>
<desc lang="fr">Treating the climate crisis like a crisis. CNBC's Steve Sedgwick moderates a panel from the sidelines of the World Economic Forum. Speakers include climate activists: Greta Thunberg, Helena Gualinga, Vanessa Nakate, Luisa Neubauer and the IEA's Fatih Birol.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/07/1790348_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230407213000 +0200" stop="20230407220000 +0200" channel="CNBC.be">
<title lang="fr">Sustainable Future S1</title>
<desc lang="fr">They're the power couple of agriculture. Idris Elba and Sabrina Dhowre Elba talk to Tania Bryer just after they were honored with a Crystal Award from the World Economic Forum for their commitment and leadership in addressing food security, climate change and environmental conservation.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/07/1790348_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230407220000 +0200" stop="20230407230000 +0200" channel="CNBC.be">
<title lang="fr">La fièvre du dollar (Dr. Stokes) S1 (n°35)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Dr. Stokes»In Grand Rapids, Michigan, Dr. Robert Stokes runs a thriving dermatology practice. He's making millions. But Dr. Stokes has a dark secret. He's stealing patient's money. He reuses medical supplies and endangers patients.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Documentaire</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/56/1805768_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230407230000 +0200" stop="20230407233000 +0200" channel="CNBC.be">
<title lang="fr">Secret Lives of the Super Rich (Penthouse Secrets &amp; Mega-yacht Super Ship) S1 (n°202)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Penthouse Secrets &amp; Mega-yacht Super Ship»Uncover the secrets hidden inside the most incredible VIP Penthouse suite in America. Go aboard the ship that carries the mega-yachts of the super-rich. Plus, the race to sell a Gold Coast mansion filled with a shocking collection.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Documentaire</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/26/2123743_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230407233000 +0200" stop="20230408003000 +0200" channel="CNBC.be">
<title lang="fr">The Tonight Show Starring Jimmy Fallon S10</title>
<desc lang="fr">Jimmy Fallon with guests Molly Shannon and Ramón Rodríguez, and standup by Sophie Buddle . (US TX: 6 Apr 2023).</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/33/2161728_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230408003000 +0200" stop="20230408010000 +0200" channel="CNBC.be">
<title lang="fr">NBC Nightly News</title>
<desc lang="fr">Join American journalist Lester Holt as he provides a comprehensive report on the latest national and international stories, featuring interviews with the relevant persons involved in the day's news. Lester and his guests offer adept analysis to help you make sense of the frantic stories emerging from the world of politics, economics and social issues. Nightly News also features a segment titled Making a Difference, where we celebrate ordinary Americans doing extraordinary deeds to benefit their surrounding local communities.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Infos</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/20/42/1680909_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230408010000 +0200" stop="20230408020000 +0200" channel="CNBC.be">
<title lang="fr">La fièvre du dollar (Le calvaire des victimes du Fen-Phen) (34/51)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Le calvaire des victimes du Fen-Phen»Fen-Phen, the miracle weight loss drug of the 90's, turns out to have a serious side effect. When the story breaks, ambulance chasing lawyers rush in. They exploit the tragedy and pilfer their clients' money. How much they steal will shock you!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Documentaire</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/56/1805768_A.jpg" />
</programme>