<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Voo -->
<programme start="20230414030000 +0200" stop="20230414035500 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">WOMEX 2018</title>
<desc lang="fr">In 2018 WOMEX took place in Las Palmas in Gran Canaria. One of the participants was The Garifuna Collective. These young and old musicians from the Caribbean keep Andy Palacio's legacy alive.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/29/16/2143305_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230414035500 +0200" stop="20230414050200 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Trio Corrente</title>
<desc lang="fr">Trio Corrente - Da Pá Virada Sessions - Da Pá Virada sessions bring the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the bands taking part in this series is Trio Corrente, which was formed in 2001, consisting of Fabio Torres on piano, Paulo Paulelli on bass, and Edu Ribeiro on drums. Since then, the trio has been creating an original sound playing the classics of choro and Música Popular Brasileira.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/33/1798058_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230414050200 +0200" stop="20230414062900 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Ron Carter : Foursight</title>
<desc lang="fr">Ron Carter - Foursight - An evening with the &quot;Foursight&quot; quartet takes you on a tour of Ron Carter's discography, with two thousand five hundred albums, which is to say the consideration he has received since his debut in 1959. After accompanying Jacky Byard and Eric Dolphy, he joined Miles Davis' legendary VSOP with Herbie Hancock, Wayne Shorter, and Tony Williams, among others. Much more than an accompanist, the double bassist is above all a great soloist, as much in intimate trios as in advanced experimental formations or large orchestras. He will be remarkably surrounded here, during his &quot;Foursight&quot; show at Jazz sous les pommiers 2019.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230414062900 +0200" stop="20230414071200 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">WOMEX 2018</title>
<desc lang="fr">Kim So Ra - WOMEX 2018 - Since 1994, World Music Expo (WOMEX) has been attracting musicians, agents, a great number of press agencies, as well as media companies from all over the world. Its main exposition event has been held in various locations throughout Europe, including Berlin, Brussels, Marseille, Stockholm, Seville, Cardiff, and Budapest. In 2018, WOMEX was held in Las Palmas, Gran Canaria. One of its showcase participants, Korean percussionist Kim So Ra, has played the hourglass-shaped, two-headed drum known as janggu since she was a child. Quietly, she has been taking revolutionary steps to modernize perceptions within traditional Korean music.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/29/16/2143305_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230414071200 +0200" stop="20230414082700 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Monty Alexander &amp; The Harlem Kingston Express</title>
<desc lang="fr">With a career spanning five decades, jazz pianist Monty Alexander has played with the best of the best. An ambassador for Jamaican music, Alexander creates a unique blend of jazz and reggae with a group of exceptional American and Jamaican musicians called the &quot;Harlem Kingston Express.&quot; Together, they explore the two sides of Monty Alexander's musical legacy: the jazz of Harlem and the reggae of Kingston. Many great jazz musicians, including Dizzy Gillespie, have called on Alexander's exceptional sense of improvisation. Watch this 4K recording of his 2017 performance at Philharmonie de Paris, and you'll understand why.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/56/1752527_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230414082700 +0200" stop="20230414090000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Brian Bolger, Pat Brunnock, Tomas O'Durcain &amp; Chien Buggle</title>
<desc lang="fr">Classical:NEXT 2019 - Dublin Guitar Quartet - Strange to think that until the formation of The Dublin Guitar Quartet (DGQ) there had never been a guitar ensemble that specialised in contemporary classical music. The quartet consists of Brian Bolger, Pat Brunnock, Tomas O'Durcain, and Chien Buggle. Not deterred by the scarcity of repertoire, the DGQ set about creating their own collection of work by focusing on transcriptions and new commissions. Their performances now boast a dynamic mix of celebrated masterpieces by the likes of Philip Glass, Steve Reich, Arvo Pärt and Bryce Dessner alongside new commissions by composers such as Nico Muhly, Michael Gordon, and Marc Mellits.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/24/07/2123267_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230414090000 +0200" stop="20230414102200 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Alfredo Rodriguez &amp; Pedrito Martinez</title>
<desc lang="fr">Rodriguez &amp; Martinez - Jazz sous les Pommiers - Pianist Alfredo Rodriguez and percussionist Pedrito Martinez, both from Cuba, play an unforgettable Latin jazz performance at the 2019 edition of festival Jazz sous les Pommiers in Coutances, France. Although both musicians are originally from Havana, Cuba, their music careers are blooming in the USA. The duo's debut album &quot;Duologue&quot; was produced by legendary producer Quincy Jones and saw its release in 2019. Their Jazz sous les Pommiers concert features original compositions alongside Yoruba pieces in honor of the African diaspora to Cuba. Moreover, the duo plays an unexpected interpretation of the Super Mario theme during this varied performance.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/07/06/1769516_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230414102200 +0200" stop="20230414110800 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Bakolo Music International</title>
<desc lang="fr">In 2018 WOMEX took place in Las Palmas in Gran Canaria. One of the participants was the band Bakolo Music International. They represent the pioneers of the golden age of the Congolese rumba. Singer, guitarist and veteran Nzofu Moko Buele, called Bikunda by everyone, keeps the fire burning that &quot;Papa&quot; lit Wendolosoy, the &quot;father of the Congolese rumba&quot; in 1948 when his song &quot;Marie-Louise&quot; became an international hit.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/06/51/1642161_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230414110800 +0200" stop="20230414120300 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Audience Music</title>
<desc lang="fr">Enjoy ground-breaking concerts, in-depth artist interviews, and unique stories with host Ted Stryker. This concert series gives the audience an intimate view of music's most influential artists today. Shot in 4K, host Ted Stryker interviews musicians across all genres, creating one of the most unique music shows on TV today. This episode features singer/songwriter Skylar Grey, best known for her songwriting skills, as displayed in Eminem and Rihanna's &quot;Love The Way You Lie&quot; (2010). The five-time GRAMMY-nominee and Wisconsin-born pop artist takes the stage to perform some of her most popular songs, as well as some works of her forthcoming album &quot;Angel With Tattoos&quot;. Enjoy Skylar Grey's performance and interview at Audience Music 2019!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/04/2122118_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230414120300 +0200" stop="20230414133600 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Antonio Faraò</title>
<desc lang="fr">Jazz à Ramatuelle: Antonio Faraò - In 1998, Antonio Faraò won the prestigious Concours Martial Solal, awarded to him by Herbie Hancock! Since then, this talented Italian jazz pianist has made his mark as a player of elegance and lyricism, which has allowed him to collaborate with the best European and American musicians. On his last album &quot;Evan&quot;, recorded in the United States, he leads an all-star band starring Joe Lovano on tenor saxophone. On a beautiful summer night at the French Jazz à Ramatuelle festival, Faraò performs at the breathtaking Theatre de Verdure in the company of saxophone legend Dave Liebman. With refined ballads, a feline groove, elegance, and lyricism, this musical meeting sparkles - if you watch closely you might even see some bright new stars lighting up in the night sky above Ramatuelle!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230414133600 +0200" stop="20230414141000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">GayBird Leung et Zephyr Quartet</title>
<desc lang="fr">GayBird Leung &amp; Zephyr Quartet - GayBird Leung has worked in the Hong Kong music industry since 1996 as a music director, composer, and producer for over a hundred music productions, concerts and theatres. He continues to explore the realm of music creation, investigating potential formats of electronic music performance that enhance the music experience. The Zephyr Quartet, consisting of Emma Perkins (violin), Emily Tulloch (violin), Jason Thomas (viola) and Hilary Kleinig (cello) are Australia's leading genre-defying explorers of dynamic cross-art form music focused collaborations. During this showcase at Classical: NEXT 2019 in Rotterdam, they perform GayBird Leung's composition &quot;Music in Anticlockwise&quot; (2017).</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/49/1767496_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230414141000 +0200" stop="20230414150100 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Urban Cone</title>
<desc lang="fr">Urban Cone - Watch groundbreaking concerts, in-depth artist interviews, and stories with host Ted Stryker. This concert series gives the audience an intimate view of music's most influential artists today. Shot in 4K, Stryker interviews musicians across all genres, creating the most unique music show on TV today. This episode features the Swedish indie pop band Urban Cone. The band was formed in 2010 by Emil Gustafsson, Tim Formgren, Rasmus Flyckt, Jacob William Sjöberg, and Magnus Folkö. Their debut EP Our Youth came about when they were only 16 years old. The album was recorded in Flyckt's living room. The album's debut single &quot;Urban Photograph&quot; reached #2 on Hype Machine. A tour to the U.S. followed, with performances in New York City, Brooklyn, Los Angeles, and San Francisco.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/58/1754433_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230414150100 +0200" stop="20230414160900 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Hamilton e Laginha</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Da Pá Virada Sessions series portrays the best musicians in Brazilian jazz today. All sessions were recorded in São Paulo and offer a unique experience: they offer a fresh look at the Brazilian music scene. The artists have been selected together with the music editor of Stingray DJAZZ. One of the musical collaborations that can be seen in this series is the duo of Hamilton de Holanda and Mário Laginha. Grammy nominee De Holanda, who has given the ten-string mandolin a new place in Brazilian music, is entering into a collaboration with pianist Mário Laginha. Together they perform gems of Brazilian music that will make the viewer's heart beat faster.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230414160900 +0200" stop="20230414170900 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Nubiyan Twist : Music Meeting</title>
<desc lang="fr">Nubiyan Twist - Music Meeting - Since 1985, the Dutch city of Nijmegen has been welcoming the International Music Meeting Festival every Pentecost. Ranging from jazz and improvisational music to traditional music and unique crossovers, this adventurous festival is all about musical encounters and international collaborations. In 2019, the band Nubiyan Twist performs at the International Music Meeting Festival. This London-based group operates on the intersection of soul and jazz.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230414170900 +0200" stop="20230414184700 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Kyle Eastwood Quintet</title>
<desc lang="fr">Jazz à Ramatuelle: Kyle Eastwood Quintet - Bassist Kyle Eastwood (1968) is an explorer, equally at ease with jazz melodies as with pop songs. In the late 1970s, his father Clint took him to see his first jazz concert - a Count Basie performance. Eastwood Jr. was in awe of the drummer and wanted to play an instrument himself. It so happened he wasn't so much interested in jazz, preferring rhythm and blues, Motown and Stax records, funk groups, and North African and Indian music. Eastwood became a brilliant bassist and the composer of highly original soundtracks. His 2015 album &quot;Time Pieces&quot; is a collaboration with brilliant British musicians, such as trumpeter Quentin Collins and saxophonist Brandon Allen. In this broadcast, Eastwood and his fellow musicians revisit the hard bop legacy of Blue Note Records.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/19/1853106_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230414184700 +0200" stop="20230414192800 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">WOMEX 2018</title>
<desc lang="fr">Rob Thorne Toi Puo - WOMEX 2018 - Since 1994, World Music Expo (WOMEX) has been attracting musicians, agents, a great number of press agencies, as well as media companies from all over the world. Its main exposition event has been held in various locations throughout Europe, including Berlin, Brussels, Marseille, Stockholm, Seville, Cardiff, and Budapest. In 2018, WOMEX was held in Las Palmas, Gran Canaria. One of its showcase participants, composer/performer/anthropologist Rob Thorne, is a diverse explorer in the newly revived evolution of taonga puoro, traditional M?ori instruments, fusing these ancient voices with modern sounds and technology. He creates ethereal and immersive site-specific works as well as contemporary chamber music, born out of in-depth research and respect for tradition.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/29/16/2143305_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230414192800 +0200" stop="20230414203000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Frequencerz @ Airbeat One</title>
<desc lang="fr">Frequencerz @ Airbeat One - Frequencerz is a Dutch hardstyle duo formed by Pepijn Hol and Niels Koster. In 2009, they signed their contract with the Fusion Records label. Since then, they've released a good number of albums, such as Medium Rare, S.T.F.U. / G.T.F.O, and Phaser. With their performances for huge crowds at Defqon.1, Decibel Outdoor, and The Qontinent, they've established themselves as one of the biggest hardstyle acts of today. Their show at the German Airbeat One festival underlines their reputation. Expect nothing but spectacular light shows, non-stop jumpstyle, and a crazy crowd!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230414203000 +0200" stop="20230414210000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Rui Massena</title>
<desc lang="fr">CLASSICAL:Next 2019 - Rui Massena - A life-long pioneer and defender of classical music, a maestro and pianist by training, Rui Massena has performed in 14 countries with 30 orchestras, has conducted for José Carreras, Ute Lemper and Wim Mertens and was the main guest conductor of the Rome Symphony Orchestra for three seasons. He has also received several distinctions, both as maestro and as a TV personality. With his first album, Solo, in 2015, recorded entirely on solo piano, his remarkable talent as a melodist was revealed to the world. In 2016, he released 'Ensemble', partly recorded with the Czech National Symphony Orchestra. The record shot to #1 in the Portuguese charts.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/07/00/1647739_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230414210000 +0200" stop="20230414214500 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Fedde le Grand @ Pacha Festival</title>
<desc lang="fr">Pacha Festival - Fedde Le Grand is considered one of the most important artists of house music, a style in constant evolution. He is known around the world for his simple &quot;Put Your Hands Up For Detroit&quot;, &quot;Rhythm Of The Night&quot;, &quot;The Creeps&quot;, and &quot;Let Me Think About It&quot;. Fedde Le Grand has received countless awards and has offered remixes of the greatest international artists such as Coldplay, Madonna, Will.i.am, Robbie Williams and, more recently, Michael Jackson (&quot;Love Never Felt So Good&quot;) and Faithless (&quot;Insomnia&quot;). His electrifying DJ set at Bali's Pacha Festival thrills the view with his breathtaking lights, fireworks, and delirious crowd!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230414214500 +0200" stop="20230414224400 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">lovelytheband</title>
<desc lang="fr">Formed in West Hollywood in 2016, lovelytheband features former Oh Honey member Mitchy Collins along with guitarist Jordan Greenwald and drummer Sam Price. The band debuted in July 2017 with the Christian Medice-produced &quot;Broken,&quot; a sprightly and infectious single that quickly racked up over three million digital streams. Signing with Another Century Records, lovelytheband released their debut EP &quot;Everything I Could&quot; in September of that year and joined Vance Joy and AWOLNATION on tour. In April 2018, &quot;Broken&quot; was still going strong and hit number one on the Billboard Alternative Songs Airplay chart. That August, lovelytheband returned with their full-length debut album, Finding It Hard to Smile.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/58/1754433_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230414224400 +0200" stop="20230414234600 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Richie Hawtin at Family Piknik</title>
<desc lang="fr">Richie Hawtin at Family Piknik 2017 - Born in Britain and raised in Canada, Richie Hawtin is one of the biggest names in today's electro minimal and is one of the instigators of electro house. Hawtin, who rightly calls himself an artist, is always looking for new concepts and ways to push technological boundaries. Let yourself be carried away by the unique and dancing techno rhythms of this innovative DJ with this highly creative set delivered as part of the 2017 edition of the Family Piknik festival.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230414234600 +0200" stop="20230414235600 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam</title>
<desc lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam - New Cool Collective is one of the foremost Dutch jazz ensembles. Pioneering new blends of music styles since 1993, NCC has performed in various formations, from small combos to larger ensembles and even big bands! The ensemble's high energy is cut out for the dance floors, as dance, Latin, salsa, afrobeat and boogaloo all meet in a jazzy mix. NCC includes saxophonist Benjamin Herman, guitarist Rory Ronde, drummer Joost Kroon, percussionists Frank van Dok and Jos de Haas, pianist Willem Friede, bassist Leslie Lopez, and trumpeter David Rockefeller.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>