<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Voo -->
<programme start="20230421024000 +0200" stop="20230421030000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">José James</title>
<desc lang="fr">Songbook - &quot;I never heard anyone say that, and yeah, I know exactly what it means. It has to go in there, this has to be a song.&quot; Every song has its own story, and we all think it's a story we've heard before, but we haven't. Songbook finds and captures these intriguing stories by pulling you into the process of writing and composing. Known for its pristine sound, cinematic 4k video, and eye for detail, Songbook live-captured episodes emphasize the paramount importance of quality. It addresses the on-the-spot elements of blending song and location at the right moment. Both the magical location and remarkable music interaction will get the attention they deserve. Simply because Songbook isn't just a live music session, it lives. This episode of Songbook features eclectic R&amp;B artist José James.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230421030000 +0200" stop="20230421035300 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Giana Viscardi - New Year's Eve Special</title>
<desc lang="fr">Giana Viscardi - New Year's Eve Special - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the bands taking part in this series is the duo of Giana Viscardi and Gustavo Marques. After starting their career together, Giana Viscardi and Gustavo Marques released music in many places around the world. After returning to Brazil, they worked together on Giana's album &quot;ORUM&quot;, performing in Africa, Europe, and Brazil.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230421035300 +0200" stop="20230421045700 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">GusGus : Live at Sónar Reykjavik</title>
<desc lang="fr">Gusgus - GusGus was founded in 1995 as a collective of film music creators. After signing a contract with the 4AD label the following year, GusGus became one of the most popular electro formations in Iceland, a status that was cemented internationally by the release of Polydistortion in 1997 Over the next two decades, GusGus explored virtually every sub-genre of electronic music, from house to trance, to techno and trip-hop. Discover GusGus at the Sónar Reykjavík 2018 festival, where founding members Biggi Veira and Daníel Ágúst present the latest album from the band, Lies Are More Flexible. With his exceptional vocal talent, fascinating electronic hacks and subtle arrangements, GusGus promises to impress you.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230421045700 +0200" stop="20230421062300 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Ryan Porter &amp; The West Coast Get Down</title>
<desc lang="fr">Ryan Porter &amp; The West Coast Get Down - BIRD - Los Angeles-born saxophonist Kamasi Washington and trombonist Ryan Porter co-founded West Coast Get Down - a musical collective fusing jazz and funk with hip-hop. It is partly because of this collective that jazz saw a resurgence in Los Angeles, subtly eclipsing the long-established jazz mecca of the world, New York City. The two musicians join forces and take the vibes of Los Angeles to jazz club BIRD in Rotterdam, the Netherlands.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/02/23/19/1647737_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230421062300 +0200" stop="20230421070600 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Null + Void</title>
<desc lang="fr">Null + Void - While few people are familiar with the Null + Void project, many have already heard Kurt Uenala's music. After making his debut under the pseudonym Kap10Kurt in 2003, Uenala caught the attention of the world with the play &quot;Die Sleeping&quot;. This critical and popular success has led to collaborations with several big names in music, including Moby, The Kills, and Dave Gahan, singer of Depeche Mode, for whom Uenala has subsequently signed plays. Spending more and more time in his Manhattan studio, Uenala developed a unique sound made of angular beats and dark soundscapes, which gave rise to a new melancholy solo project called Null + Void. Cryosleep, Uenala's first album under this new banner, includes several titles inspired by retro science fiction, new wave and electronic innovators.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/06/2111709_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230421070600 +0200" stop="20230421082500 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Rocky Mountain Way</title>
<desc lang="fr">Rocky Mountain Way - The Colorado Music Hall of Fame hosted a concert for the induction of rock 'n' roll legends Joe Walsh and the late Dan Fogelberg, along with the honoring of the famed Caribou Ranch recording studio near Nederland, Colorado, where Walsh and Fogelberg both recorded some of their best work. The concert, dubbed &quot;The Rocky Mountain Way,&quot; took place on Sunday, August 13, 2017, at Fiddler's Green. It featured performances from an all-star list of musicians including The Lumineers, Garth Brooks, Amy Grant &amp; Vince Gill, The Nitty Gritty Dirt Band, Richie Furay, Randy Owen of Alabama, Todd Park Mohr, Michael Martin Murphey, and surprise guests paying tribute to Dan Fogelberg and Caribou Ranch. Joe Walsh reunited his Caribou recording band Barnstorm for the performance.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/02/14/03/2145504_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230421082500 +0200" stop="20230421090000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Nana Adjoa</title>
<desc lang="fr">Songbook - Nana Adjoa - &quot;I never heard anyone say that, and yeah, I know exactly what it means. It has to go in there, this has to be a song.&quot; Every song has its own story, and we all think it's a story we've heard before, but we haven't. Songbook finds and captures these intriguing stories by pulling you into the process of writing and composing. Known for its pristine sound, cinematic 4k video, and eye for detail, Songbook live-captured episodes emphasize the paramount importance of quality. It addresses the on-the-spot elements of blending song and location at the right moment. Both the magical location and remarkable music interaction will get the attention they deserve.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/04/2122118_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230421090000 +0200" stop="20230421102100 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">HVOB</title>
<desc lang="fr">HVOB - The two musicians behind HVOB are Anna Müller and Paul Wallner. Anna Müller composes, produces, and provides the captivating, hypnotic vocals. The final production of the tracks is done in collaboration with Paul Wallner in his Vienna studio. HVOB are carving their path not just with their distinctive sound but with their live performances as well. The duo always plays live and performs with a drummer - a concept as innovative as it is successful: HVOB has just been voted number two best live act by the most influential German electronic music magazine &quot;De:bug.&quot; Enjoy their 2019 show at Trabendo Paris!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Musique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/59/1769392_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230421102100 +0200" stop="20230421110500 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">City Beats</title>
<desc lang="fr">City Beats - Episode 6 - Europe - DJ-producer Carly Foxx is on a musical journey, immersing herself in the life of five iconic European cities to find inspiration for a series of new tracks. In this episode, Carly Foxx looks back at her journey to the music dance capitals of Europe to inspire her final track. She starts with the Balaeric beat that represents Ibiza while adding authentic bongo and guitar recordings. Then she shifts to London, where she discovers new areas and urban culture while talking to filmmaker DJ Don Letts. Carly captures the grime sound with the help of MC Yizzy and records vocals from a group of London women. Her next trip brings her to Berlin, where she produces an acid house flavored track with the 303 synthesizers.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Télé-Réalité</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/16/2123268_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230421110500 +0200" stop="20230421120300 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Jack Johnson</title>
<desc lang="fr">Jack Johnson - In an intimate performance at Manhattan's McKittrick Hotel in New York City, multi-instrumentalist and singer/songwriter Jack Johnson takes his harmonic Hawaiian soft-rock sound to the stage. Besides his critically-acclaimed music, the North Shore-born singer/songwriter has also received a variety of awards for his activism in environmental issues. Johnson's music reflects the former professional surfer's background: soft acoustic rock melodies accompany his smooth warm-sounding voice in harmonic compositions, taking audiences on a sensory journey to the dreamy shores of Hawaii.For this special performance, he is accompanied by special guest G. Love and Zach Gill of ALO on the keys.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230421120300 +0200" stop="20230421134000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Dickey Betts</title>
<desc lang="fr">Dickey Betts - Calling Dickey Betts the second guitarist in the Allman Brothers Band does him a disservice. After the tragic death of Duane Allman in 1971, Betts became co-captain with Gregg Allman, leading the group through ups and downs over the decades. Known as one of the most influential guitar players of all time, Betts has mastered a seamless style of lyrical melody and rhythm ? marrying country, jazz, blues, and rock into one sound. Betts has one of the most distinctive voices in music today, and on July 21, 2018, he brought down the house at the St. George's Theatre in Staten Island. Catch him performing the legendary Allman Brothers songs!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/42/1870646_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230421134000 +0200" stop="20230421141900 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Nilüfer Yanya - Echoes Series: Nilufer Yanya</title>
<desc lang="fr">Echoes Series: Emel Mathlouthi - Echoes is a modern live music show hosted by Jehnny Beth (lead singer in the British band Savages). It presents leading and emerging bands and artists from the contemporary scene. The show takes place underneath the Palais de Tokyo museum in Paris, in the club of brutalist architecture, the &quot;Yoyo.&quot; The live sets are 30 minutes long and take place on a customized stage, creating closeness with the audience. The intimate, immersive space lends to the atmosphere of the show. The artistic direction by Antoine Carlier follows a minimalist, refined and pure aesthetic, allowing the artists' energy and emotions to take center stage. This episode features Emel Mathlouthi. Her set includes the songs &quot;Rescuer,&quot; &quot;Something in the Way,&quot; and &quot;Holm.&quot;.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/03/1754401_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230421141900 +0200" stop="20230421150000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Rui Massena</title>
<desc lang="fr">CLASSICAL:Next 2019 - Rui Massena - A life-long pioneer and defender of classical music, a maestro and pianist by training, Rui Massena has performed in 14 countries with 30 orchestras, has conducted for José Carreras, Ute Lemper and Wim Mertens and was the main guest conductor of the Rome Symphony Orchestra for three seasons. He has also received several distinctions, both as maestro and as a TV personality. With his first album, Solo, in 2015, recorded entirely on solo piano, his remarkable talent as a melodist was revealed to the world. In 2016, he released 'Ensemble', partly recorded with the Czech National Symphony Orchestra. The record shot to #1 in the Portuguese charts.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/07/00/1647739_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230421150000 +0200" stop="20230421161100 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Les Vieilles Charrues</title>
<desc lang="fr">Les Vieilles Charrues - British alternative rock group Skunk Anansie celebrates its 25th anniversary with the album 25LIVE@25. These 90s rock scene icons, whose hair-raising shows have become legendary, celebrate their storied career with this 25-song project. With a selection of recordings taken from various 2017 live performances, Skunk Anansie once again proves its unbeatable power on stage. The setlist includes &quot;Because of You,&quot; &quot;The Skank Heads,&quot; and &quot;Tear the Place Up.&quot; Don't miss the triumphant return of these pillars of rock to the stage of the 28th edition of Les Vieilles Charrues in Carhaix, France, in 2019!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230421161100 +0200" stop="20230421171100 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Robin Schulz, Sam Feldt, Afrojack &amp; Alle Farben - Parookaville</title>
<desc lang="fr">Parookaville - Parookaville is a city that comes to life once a year to keep the legend of Bill Parooka alive. It was started as an artistic, free-flowing, wild, and musical place where people could connect with their pure selves, experience real connections, and feel a deep sense of bliss and fulfillment. Step into the darkness if you dare, follow your inner light and immerse yourself in a spectacular world of freedom and love! Only four years since the first event, this festival has already become one of Germany's most prevalent music festivals. This edition features Armin van Buuren, Showtek, Robin Schulz, and W&amp;W.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230421171100 +0200" stop="20230421184500 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Antonio Faraò</title>
<desc lang="fr">Jazz à Ramatuelle: Antonio Faraò - In 1998, Antonio Faraò won the prestigious Concours Martial Solal, awarded to him by Herbie Hancock! Since then, this talented Italian jazz pianist has made his mark as a player of elegance and lyricism, which has allowed him to collaborate with the best European and American musicians. On his last album &quot;Evan&quot;, recorded in the United States, he leads an all-star band starring Joe Lovano on tenor saxophone. On a beautiful summer night at the French Jazz à Ramatuelle festival, Faraò performs at the breathtaking Theatre de Verdure in the company of saxophone legend Dave Liebman. With refined ballads, a feline groove, elegance, and lyricism, this musical meeting sparkles - if you watch closely you might even see some bright new stars lighting up in the night sky above Ramatuelle!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230421184500 +0200" stop="20230421192800 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">WOMEX 2018</title>
<desc lang="fr">Kim So Ra - WOMEX 2018 - Since 1994, World Music Expo (WOMEX) has been attracting musicians, agents, a great number of press agencies, as well as media companies from all over the world. Its main exposition event has been held in various locations throughout Europe, including Berlin, Brussels, Marseille, Stockholm, Seville, Cardiff, and Budapest. In 2018, WOMEX was held in Las Palmas, Gran Canaria. One of its showcase participants, Korean percussionist Kim So Ra, has played the hourglass-shaped, two-headed drum known as janggu since she was a child. Quietly, she has been taking revolutionary steps to modernize perceptions within traditional Korean music.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/29/16/2143305_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230421192800 +0200" stop="20230421202300 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Oum 2018</title>
<desc lang="fr">Oum - Music Meeting Festival 2018 - Oum El Ghait Benessahraoui, who is better known as Oum, gives a unique glance at ethnic Morrocan musical esthetics. The singer-songwriter is considered to be the ambassador of Morrocan culture, too. Deeply influenced by gospel, jazz, soul and R&amp;B genres, today Oum mixes more and more African music genres, such as Sufi, Hassani, or Afrobeat. Yet, the singer's voice still echoes the colours of Aretha Franklin, Ella Fitzgerald or Whitney Houston. It is the African American vocal tradition that made a huge impact on Oum since her early days as the singer. Performing from Music Meeting Festival in Nijmegen, The Netherlands, Oum charms the stage with an exotic sonic journey to the undiscovered lands of North Africa.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/04/1754386_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230421202300 +0200" stop="20230421210000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Urban Cone</title>
<desc lang="fr">Urban Cone - Watch groundbreaking concerts, in-depth artist interviews, and stories with host Ted Stryker. This concert series gives the audience an intimate view of music's most influential artists today. Shot in 4K, Stryker interviews musicians across all genres, creating the most unique music show on TV today. This episode features the Swedish indie pop band Urban Cone. The band was formed in 2010 by Emil Gustafsson, Tim Formgren, Rasmus Flyckt, Jacob William Sjöberg, and Magnus Folkö. Their debut EP Our Youth came about when they were only 16 years old. The album was recorded in Flyckt's living room. The album's debut single &quot;Urban Photograph&quot; reached #2 on Hype Machine. A tour to the U.S. followed, with performances in New York City, Brooklyn, Los Angeles, and San Francisco.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/58/1754433_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230421210000 +0200" stop="20230421215100 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Lee Scratch Perry</title>
<desc lang="fr">Lee &quot;Scratch&quot; Perry is a Jamaican musician, a pioneer in the development of dub music in the 1970s. He remixes existing reggae tracks with studio effects, creating a new sound. During the early 2000s, Perry won a Grammy for Best Reggae album, and was ranked in the Rolling Stone list of 100 Greatest Artists of All Time. He has collaborated with a variety of great artists, most notably Bob Marley, whose compositions he still incorporates in his show. During his 2017 show at Philharmonie de Paris, you will enjoy well-known reggae songs like Punk Reggae Party, Sun Is Shining, and Soul Fire. Recorded in 4K, it promises to be a groovy and spectacular show!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/06/53/1998172_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230421215100 +0200" stop="20230421225000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Steve Vai</title>
<desc lang="fr">Steve Vai - The popular music performance series, Front and Center, which premiered nationwide on public television, in 2016, returns for Season 6. The series boasts 22, one-hour episodes and an all-star line-up. This episode features Steve Vai, the legendary guitarist who was voted the 10th Greatest Guitarist by Guitar World magazine, who treats fans to songs from his three-decade long career. As an independent guitarist he has won three Grammy Awards. Vai's solo sophomore release, Passion and Warfare, has earned gold certification in the US. At Front and Center he sits down and discusses his early interest in composing music and playing guitar as well as the many fortunes of his career.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Musique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/42/1870646_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230421225000 +0200" stop="20230421235300 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Jesse Cook - Follow the Road</title>
<desc lang="fr">Celebrated guitarist, composer, and music producer Jesse Cook has been delivering unforgettable concert experiences to audiences across the globe for over 25 years. As far as he has ventured, Jesse has always been fascinated with the mystique of the road that first led him out of Toronto. In his directorial debut, Cook shows us a concert from a rarely seen perspective: the musician's. Born to film director parents, guitarist Jesse Cook taps into this pedigree, and self-directed this story, his fifth Concert Special. The result is &quot;Follow the Road.&quot; Captured in 4K, during his 31-city cross-Canada tour, we follow the band down the TransCanada Highway, against a backdrop of majestic mountains and stunning natural beauty, as they traverse the scenic splendor of the second largest country in the world.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Musique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/04/2122118_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230421235300 +0200" stop="20230422000300 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam</title>
<desc lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam - New Cool Collective is one of the foremost Dutch jazz ensembles. Pioneering new blends of music styles since 1993, NCC has performed in various formations, from small combos to larger ensembles and even big bands! The ensemble's high energy is cut out for the dance floors, as dance, Latin, salsa, afrobeat and boogaloo all meet in a jazzy mix. NCC includes saxophonist Benjamin Herman, guitarist Rory Ronde, drummer Joost Kroon, percussionists Frank van Dok and Jos de Haas, pianist Willem Friede, bassist Leslie Lopez, and trumpeter David Rockefeller.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>