<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Voo -->
<programme start="20230504030000 +0200" stop="20230504041300 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Omer Avital Qantar - Jazz in Duketown</title>
<desc lang="fr">Jazz in Duketown is the largest free open-air jazz festival in the Netherlands. Jazz fanatics and other music lovers eagerly look forward to the performances of the many internationally renowned artists every year. In 2019 Israeli-American double bass player Omer Avital is one of them. Together with his quintet, consisting of saxophonists Asaf Yuria and Alexander Levin, drummer Ofri Nehemya and pianist Eden Ladin, he performs a strong repertoire from his album 'Qantar': vibrantly energetic, idiosyncratic jazz with oriental influences.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230504041300 +0200" stop="20230504045600 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">City Beats</title>
<desc lang="fr">City Beats - Episode 2 - Ibiza - DJ-producer Carly Foxx is on a musical journey, immersing herself in the life of five iconic European cities to find inspiration for a series of new tracks. In this episode, Carly Foxx travels to the world's clubbing capital to inspire her music track and discovers Ibiza's alternative spiritual side. She starts her journey in San Antonio but discovers this place is mainly about clubbing and drinking - not very inspiring for her music track. The next stop is Old Town, where Carly meets female Ibiza singer Sam Smith, who introduces her to DJ and producer Manu Gonzalez. While talking to him, Carly decides the base of her Ibiza-inspired track should be a Balearic beat, to which she plans to add bongos and castanet samples.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Télé-Réalité</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/12/00/2155262_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230504045600 +0200" stop="20230504055600 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Filo Machado - New Year's Eve Special</title>
<desc lang="fr">Filo Machado - New Year's Eve Special - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the artists taking part in this series is Filo Machado. Born in São Paulo, this singer, composer, instrumentalist, arranger and producer has celebrated many musical successes. Filo Machado took part in saxophonist Jane Bunnett's Canadian tour with her spectacular project 'Rendez-Vous Brazil/Cuba'. He has appeared at the jazz festivals of Córsega and Uzeste and opened for the one and only Nina Simone in Cannes.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230504055600 +0200" stop="20230504073200 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Dickey Betts</title>
<desc lang="fr">Dickey Betts - Calling Dickey Betts the second guitarist in the Allman Brothers Band does him a disservice. After the tragic death of Duane Allman in 1971, Betts became co-captain with Gregg Allman, leading the group through ups and downs over the decades. Known as one of the most influential guitar players of all time, Betts has mastered a seamless style of lyrical melody and rhythm ? marrying country, jazz, blues, and rock into one sound. Betts has one of the most distinctive voices in music today, and on July 21, 2018, he brought down the house at the St. George's Theatre in Staten Island. Catch him performing the legendary Allman Brothers songs!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/42/1870646_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230504073200 +0200" stop="20230504081000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Trio Zukan</title>
<desc lang="fr">Classical:NEXT 2019 - Trio Zukan - In 2014, Trio Zukan emerged from the combination of three uncommon instruments: accordion, percussion and txistu. The repertoire for this instrumental combination was non-existent at the beginning, so its members decided to promote a project with different composers, with the intention of creating a new repertoire. Today, Zukan has commissioned, revised and released more than a dozen pieces by national and international composers such as: María Eugenia Luc, Mikel Chamizo, Isabel Urrutia, Francisco José Domínguez, Vassilis Filippou, etc. The group is one of the most consolidated groups on the contemporary music scene in the Basque Country. They have performed in Quincena Musical Donostia, Bernaola Festival, Musikagileak Circuit, BBVA Cycle and Attacca Basel, among others.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/24/07/2123267_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230504081000 +0200" stop="20230504090000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Echoes Series: Fontaines DC</title>
<desc lang="fr">Echoes Series: Fontaines DC - Echoes is a modern live music show hosted by Jehnny Beth (lead singer in the British band Savages). It presents leading and emerging bands and artists from the contemporary scene. The show takes place underneath the Palais de Tokyo museum in Paris, in the club of brutalist architecture, the &quot;Yoyo.&quot; The live sets are 30 minutes long and take place on a customized stage, creating closeness with the audience. The intimate, immersive space lends to the atmosphere of the show. The artistic direction by Antoine Carlier follows a minimalist, refined and pure aesthetic, allowing the artists' energy and emotions to take center stage. This episode features the band Fontaines DC. Their set includes the songs &quot;A Hero's Death,&quot; &quot;Hurricane Laughter,&quot; and &quot;I Don't Belong.&quot;.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/04/2122118_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230504090000 +0200" stop="20230504102800 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Macha y el Bloque Depresivo</title>
<desc lang="fr">Macha y el Bloque Depresivo - With an arrangement of guitar and percussion players and Macha, the charismatic leader with the velvet voice, El Bloque Depresivo brings you an intensive tribute to South-American traditional music. This concert is brought to you by the &quot; Opéra Underground &quot; with the Opera de Lyon.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/02/07/27/1762648_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230504102800 +0200" stop="20230504112800 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">The Bloody Beetroots</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Bloody Beetroots - The Bloody Beetroots is the creation of Sir Bob Cornelius Rifo. Inspired by his lifelong love of punk rock and comic books, Rifo unleashed The Bloody Beetroots in late 2006 and has since crafted an intense sound that mixes his classical training, his punk rock obsession, and his passion for electronic music into an edgy rock-meets-dance hybrid sound. In 2019, The Bloody Beetroots released the Heavy EP, which sees Rifo revisiting his classic electro style and features collaborations with Ephwurd and Dr. Fresch, in addition to three new solo originals. Enjoy his show at Nameless Music Festival 2019!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230504112800 +0200" stop="20230504134100 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam</title>
<desc lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam - New Cool Collective is one of the foremost Dutch jazz ensembles. Pioneering new blends of music styles since 1993, NCC has performed in various formations, from small combos to larger ensembles and even big bands! The ensemble's high energy is cut out for the dance floors, as dance, Latin, salsa, afrobeat and boogaloo all meet in a jazzy mix. NCC includes saxophonist Benjamin Herman, guitarist Rory Ronde, drummer Joost Kroon, percussionists Frank van Dok and Jos de Haas, pianist Willem Friede, bassist Leslie Lopez, and trumpeter David Rockefeller.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230504134100 +0200" stop="20230504150200 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Steve Vai</title>
<desc lang="fr">Steve Vai - The popular music performance series, Front and Center, which premiered nationwide on public television, in 2016, returns for Season 6. The series boasts 22, one-hour episodes and an all-star line-up. This episode features Steve Vai, the legendary guitarist who was voted the 10th Greatest Guitarist by Guitar World magazine, who treats fans to songs from his three-decade long career. As an independent guitarist he has won three Grammy Awards. Vai's solo sophomore release, Passion and Warfare, has earned gold certification in the US. At Front and Center he sits down and discusses his early interest in composing music and playing guitar as well as the many fortunes of his career.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Musique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/42/1870646_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230504150200 +0200" stop="20230504171700 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam</title>
<desc lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam - New Cool Collective is one of the foremost Dutch jazz ensembles. Pioneering new blends of music styles since 1993, NCC has performed in various formations, from small combos to larger ensembles and even big bands! The ensemble's high energy is cut out for the dance floors, as dance, Latin, salsa, afrobeat and boogaloo all meet in a jazzy mix. NCC includes saxophonist Benjamin Herman, guitarist Rory Ronde, drummer Joost Kroon, percussionists Frank van Dok and Jos de Haas, pianist Willem Friede, bassist Leslie Lopez, and trumpeter David Rockefeller.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230504171700 +0200" stop="20230504181700 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Paulo Novaes - New Year's Eve Special</title>
<desc lang="fr">Paulo Novaes - New Year's Eve Special - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the artists taking part in this series is Paulo Novaes. Coming from a family of musicians, Paulo Novaes has already lived through a lifetime of music in spite of his young age. Paulo is the cousin of singer Bruna Caram, with whom he performed in São Paulo, Madrid, Barcelona, Lisbon, and other major cities. As a singer, composer, and instrumentalist, his creativity is enjoyed in many forms.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230504181700 +0200" stop="20230504192200 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Jungle By Night</title>
<desc lang="fr">Jungle By Night - Jazz in Duketown - Jazz in Duketown is the largest free outdoor jazz festival in the Netherlands. It's a real gathering for jazz addicts, inviting internationally renowned bands. In 2019, one of them is the Amsterdam-based Dutch instrumental collective Jungle by Night. The band plays a mix of various styles, inspired by funk, jazz, dub, rock, and others. The ensemble made its debut in 2010 and has played at numerous festivals. Their December 2010 performance with former backing musicians of Afrobeat founder Fela Kuti in Paris saw them hailed as &quot;the future of Afrobeat&quot;.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/10/1759031_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230504192200 +0200" stop="20230504203500 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">STUFF. Live at BIRD Rotterdam</title>
<desc lang="fr">With their inexhaustible energy, STUFF is impossible to get off the stage! The band was formed in 2012 when drummer Lander Gyselinck was asked by a local bar to make live music between sets of DJs, and he gathered a number of musician friends. The band is considered an avant-garde jazz band that plays a mix of funk, hip-hop and electro. Andrew Claes (saxophone), Dries Laheye (bass guitar), Lander Gyselinck (drummer), Mixmonster Menno (samples) and Joris Caluwaerts (keyboard) share a fabulous musical connection. The eagerness with which the musicians conquer every stage and the great pleasure with which they do so makes the heart of every music lover melt.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/04/2122118_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230504203500 +0200" stop="20230504210000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Wild Youth</title>
<desc lang="fr">Songbook - &quot;I never heard anyone say that, and yeah, I know exactly what it means. It has to go in there, this has to be a song.&quot; Every song has its own story, and we all think it's a story we've heard before, but we haven't. Songbook finds and captures these intriguing stories by pulling you into the process of writing and composing. Known for its pristine sound, cinematic 4k video and eye for detail, Songbook live-captured episodes emphasize the paramount importance of quality. It addresses the on-the-spot elements of blending song and location at the right moment. Both the magical location and remarkable music interaction will get the attention they deserve. Simply because Songbook isn't just a live music session, it lives. This episode of Songbook showcases the upbeat pop-rock sound of Dublin-based Wild Youth.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/04/2122118_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230504210000 +0200" stop="20230504213300 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Audience Music</title>
<desc lang="fr">Enjoy groundbreaking concerts, in-depth artist interviews, and unique stories with host Ted Stryker. This concert series gives the audience an intimate view of music's most influential artists today. Shot in 4K, host Ted Stryker interviews musicians across all genres, creating one of the most unique music shows on TV today. This episode features the multi-platinum, Grammy Award-winning band Imagine Dragons. They bring their passionately inventive alt-rock sound to a special, one-hour concert, just one month after releasing their hit song &quot;Natural.&quot; &quot;Living in a dog-eat-dog world can bring out the worst in you, and sometimes, the best,&quot; says the band's singer Dan Reynolds.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/35/1763357_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230504213300 +0200" stop="20230504223200 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Monty Alexander à La Seine Musicale</title>
<desc lang="fr">Monty Alexander - Kingston-born pianist Monty Alexander is a virtuoso with many secrets. He explores the world of jazz, swing, bebop, blues, calypso and reggae, and has created a style of his own. For him, music is a heartbeat. He plays with emotion, intelligence, humor and sensibility. During this unique performance, we are transported with his joyful swing and fizzing grooves, influenced by Afro-American jazz from Harlem, and reggae from Jamaica. This 2018 concert at the Seine Musical is exceptional. It is extremely rare for Monty Alexander to do a solo performance. We are in for an evening full of surprises.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/07/19/1995865_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230504223200 +0200" stop="20230504234900 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Bad Company : Live From Red Rocks</title>
<desc lang="fr">Soundstage, an innovative and prestigious program, achieved widespread critical acclaim while featuring artists that defined the era. On May 15, 2016, at Red Rocks Amphitheater in Colorado, Soundstage captured the legendary classic rock band Bad Company delivering their biggest hits. The band consists of bassist Boz Burrell, guitarist Mick Ralphs, singer Paul Rodgers, and drummer Simon Kirke. The setlist contains their greatest songs, such as &quot;Live for the Music,&quot; &quot;Ready for Love,&quot; &quot;Can't Get Enough&quot; and &quot;Rock Steady.&quot;.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230504234900 +0200" stop="20230505005500 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Panorama do Choro</title>
<desc lang="fr">Panorama do Choro - Da Pá Virada Sessions - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the bands taking part in this series is Panorama de Coro. This ensemble combines jazz and traditional Brazilian music. The resulting music has a festive, almost street-like atmosphere. Panorama de Coro consists of Roberta Valente (pandeiro and percussion), Alexandre Ribeiro (clarinet), Gian Correa (7-string guitar), Henrique Araujo (cavaquinho), João Poleto (flute and tenor saxophone) and Yves Finzetto (pandeiro and percussion).</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230505005500 +0200" stop="20230505015700 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Nilüfer Yanya - Echoes Series: Nilufer Yanya</title>
<desc lang="fr">Echoes Series - Episode 5 - Echoes is a modern live music show hosted by Jehnny Beth (lead singer in the British band Savages). It presents leading and emerging bands and artists from the contemporary scene. The show takes place underneath the Palais de Tokyo museum in Paris, in the club of brutalist architecture, the &quot;Yoyo.&quot; The live sets are 30 minutes long and take place on a customized stage, creating closeness with the audience. Once the bands have performed, Jehnny Beth invites everyone to sit at her roundtable for a group conversation. The open discussions in every episode allow the audience to understand the rapport, artistic exchange, and intellectual debates that run through this eclectic musical universe. The intimate, immersive space lends to the atmosphere of the show.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/03/1754401_A.jpg" />
</programme>