<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Voo -->
<programme start="20230503030000 +0200" stop="20230503034500 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">WOMEX 2018</title>
<desc lang="fr">Kim So Ra - WOMEX 2018 - Since 1994, World Music Expo (WOMEX) has been attracting musicians, agents, a great number of press agencies, as well as media companies from all over the world. Its main exposition event has been held in various locations throughout Europe, including Berlin, Brussels, Marseille, Stockholm, Seville, Cardiff, and Budapest. In 2018, WOMEX was held in Las Palmas, Gran Canaria. One of its showcase participants, Korean percussionist Kim So Ra, has played the hourglass-shaped, two-headed drum known as janggu since she was a child. Quietly, she has been taking revolutionary steps to modernize perceptions within traditional Korean music.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/29/16/2143305_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230503034500 +0200" stop="20230503044400 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Andre Marques</title>
<desc lang="fr">Andre Marques - Da Pá Virada Sessions - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the artists taking part in this series is pianist, composer, and arranger André Marques. He has been building a solid career, releasing his music with numerous groups: he is a member of the Latin Grammy-nominated Trio Curupira, the André Marques Sexteto, and he leads the Brazilian music orchestra Vintena Brasileira. In this episode of Da Pá Virada Sessions, André Marques performs an intimate solo piano recital.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230503044400 +0200" stop="20230503054600 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Liran Donin : Music Meeting</title>
<desc lang="fr">Nijmegen has been welcoming the International Music Meeting Festival, or Music Meeting for short, every spring since 1985. From jazz and improvised music to traditional music and unique crossovers: musical encounters and international collaborations are at the heart of this adventurous festival. In 2019, Tel Aviv-born bassist, producer and composer Liran Donin performed here.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230503054600 +0200" stop="20230503064800 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Marius Neset : Jazz in Duketown</title>
<desc lang="fr">Marius Neset - Jazz in Duketown - Jazz in Duketown is the largest free outdoor jazz festival in the Netherlands. It's a real gathering for jazz addicts, inviting internationally renowned artists. In 2019, one of them is Copenhagen-based Norwegian saxophonist Marius Neset, who is known internationally for his collaborations with People Are Machines, Kaktusch, JazzKamikaze, and Django Bates' projects StoRMChaser and Human Chain. Neset completed his Master's degree at the Copenhagen Rhythmic Music Conservatory in 2008.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/56/1752527_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230503064800 +0200" stop="20230503074700 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Roger Sanchez</title>
<desc lang="fr">Roger Sanchez - Self-made man and true legend of house music, Roger Sanchez perfectly embodies the spirit of Pacha Festival Bali. Sanchez had a humble debut in New York, but the days when he was spinning vinyls for his friends in Queens living rooms are far behind him. Today, he is the headliner of major festivals around the globe, and resident DJ of clubs in Ibiza's sights, such as the Pacha Club. With this DJ set at Pacha Festival, Sanchez brings some of the magic of Ibiza to the beaches of Bali. Expect lots of energy, breathtaking lights, and even fireworks!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230503074700 +0200" stop="20230503090000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Johnny Marr - Rock en Seine</title>
<desc lang="fr">Johnny Marr at Rock en Seine 2019 - English musician, songwriter, and singer Johnny Marr has enjoyed an exemplary career since his former band The Smiths split up in 1987. His distinctive guitar sound has been part of such varied groups as The Pretenders, The Cribs, Modest Mouse, and Electronic, the group he co-founded with Bernard Sumner of New Order. Now a living legend, Johnny Marr showcases his incredible singer-songwriter talents on each new album. His recent, hit-packed release Call The Comet (2018) gave us &quot;The Tracers&quot; and &quot;Hi Hello,&quot; and his live performances - which usually include some songs from his days with The Smiths - always hit the mark. Enjoy this 2019 show recorded at Rock en Seine in Paris!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/07/19/2123266_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230503090000 +0200" stop="20230503101700 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Lalah Hathaway</title>
<desc lang="fr">Lalah Hathaway - Sing Jazz 2018 - Winner of five Grammys in four consecutive years, including the Grammy for best R&amp;B album in 2017, Lalah Hathaway is a force impossible to ignore. The American artist has shared the scene with Prince, Snoop Dogg, Stevie Wonder, Anita Baker, Mary J. Blige, Frank Ocean and many others, an irrefutable proof of her keen musical sense and enormous talent. With a 26-year career, Hathaway is still highly sought after by the biggest names in music. See her transform the 2018 Sing Jazz festival scene into a real R&amp;B club, where she flaunts her voice and stage presence out of the ordinary.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/19/1853106_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230503101700 +0200" stop="20230503110500 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">WOMEX 2018</title>
<desc lang="fr">In 2018 WOMEX took place in Las Palmas in Gran Canaria. One of the participants was Ladama, five multi-instrumentalists from Venezuela, Brazil, Colombia and the United States. In addition to their performances as a band, the five women work with workshops and other collaborations to enthuse the youth for music, composition and audio editing. Ladama is a positive force in times when the need for tolerance and communication is greater than ever.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/29/16/2143305_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230503110500 +0200" stop="20230503120000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Altin Gün : Bird, Rotterdam</title>
<desc lang="fr">Mediterranean sounds meet western music in this performance by the band Altin Gün. Their unusual approach to traditional Turkish folk music produces an overall sound full of ethnic, funky, and even psychedelic influences. With their infinite energy, Altin Gün takes the audience on an amazing sonic roller coaster: a ride full of emotion and fun. Altin Gün consists of six talented musicians who share a great passion for Turkish music. In this live recording from BIRD Rotterdam, one of the Netherlands' most important music venues, the band presents their new album &quot;On&quot; to the enthusiastic audience.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/19/1975203_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230503120000 +0200" stop="20230503133700 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Moderat at Stereolux 2016</title>
<desc lang="fr">Moderat at Stereolux 2016 - Since the German bands Modeselektor (Gernot Bronsert and Sebastian Szary) and Apparat (Sascha Ring) joined forces in 2009, they have been hugely successful as the electronic music supergroup Moderat. In 2012, the formation produced the soundtrack of Xavier Dolan's film Laurence Anyways, released as A New Error. According to Les Inrockuptibles, their album II includes &quot;the rhythmic punch of the one (Modeselektor) and atmospheric finesse of the other (Apparat) combine perfectly.&quot; In 2016, the threesome returned with an eagerly anticipated third album, III, which they present in this program, live on stage at Stereolux in Nantes, France.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230503133700 +0200" stop="20230503141500 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">IDLES - Echoes Series: Idles</title>
<desc lang="fr">Echoes Series: Idles - Echoes is a modern live music show hosted by Jehnny Beth (lead singer in the British band Savages). It presents leading and emerging bands and artists from the contemporary scene. The show takes place underneath the Palais de Tokyo museum in Paris, in the club of brutalist architecture, the &quot;Yoyo.&quot; The live sets are 30 minutes long and take place on a customized stage, creating closeness with the audience. The intimate, immersive space lends to the atmosphere of the show. The artistic direction by Antoine Carlier follows a minimalist, refined and pure aesthetic, allowing the artists' energy and emotions to take center stage. This episode features the band Idles. Their set includes the songs &quot;Colossus,&quot; &quot;Love Song,&quot; and &quot;Television.&quot;.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230503141500 +0200" stop="20230503150000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Eleanor Dubinsky - Nublu 2019</title>
<desc lang="fr">The music of vocalist, guitarist and cellist Eleanor Dubinsky lives on the narrow ledge where jazz, international music and pop meet emotionally heartfelt songwriting. The musician and her versatile band deliver dynamic compositions that explore the fragile link between human emotions and human responsibility. The core of Eleanor's artistic mission is to enter into dialogue and achieve self-realization through music.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230503150000 +0200" stop="20230503155600 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">&quot;We Love Ella&quot; : The Amazing Keystone Big Band</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Amazing Keystone Big Band - &quot;We Love Ella&quot; - The Amazing Keystone Big Band performs material from their album &quot;We Love Ella&quot; at this 2019 recording from Salle Pleyel in Paris, France. Led by trombonist Bastien Ballaz, saxophonist Jon Boutellier, pianist Fred Nardin and trumpeter David Enhco, The Amazing Keystone Big Band helps young and adult audiences all over the world discover jazz in all its guises. &quot;We Love Ella&quot; is a reinvention of legendary vocalist Ella Fitzgerald's greatest successes.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/12/27/1889525_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230503155600 +0200" stop="20230503165900 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Tribute to Elis Regina</title>
<desc lang="fr">Tribute to Elis Regina - Da Pá Virada Sessions - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the bands taking part in this episode is a foursome that pays tribute to pioneering música popular brasileira vocalist Elis Regina: vocalist Vanessa Moreno, bassist Fi Marostica, Rhodes and keyboard player Tiago Costa, and drummer Jonatas Sansao honor the legendary Brazilian singer by performing famous pieces and hidden gems from her repertoire.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230503165900 +0200" stop="20230503182900 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Daucé conducts Charpentier and Du Mont</title>
<desc lang="fr">Daucé conducts Charpentier and Du Mont - Harpsichordist and organist Sébastien Daucé leads Ensemble Correspondances in this concert recorded as part of the Valletta International Baroque Festival of 2017 at the Co-Cathédrale de St-Jean de la Valette in Malta. The concert opens with a rendition of Marc-Antoine Charpentier's late-17th century composition Te Deum. The joyful and popular prelude of this piece is familiar to many as the Eurovision Anthem. Furthermore, the concert program is made up of motets by Henry du Mont (1610-1694), an organist and baroque composer of the French school, born in the Southern Netherlands. Among his musical heirs were Jean-Baptiste Lully (1632-1687) and François Couperin (1668-1733).</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/07/03/2143762_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230503182900 +0200" stop="20230503191100 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">WOMEX 2018</title>
<desc lang="fr">Norayr Kartashyan &amp; Menua - WOMEX 2018 - Since 1994, World Music Expo (WOMEX) has been attracting musicians, agents, a great number of press agencies, as well as media companies from all over the world. Its main exposition event has been held in various locations throughout Europe, including Berlin, Brussels, Marseille, Stockholm, Seville, Cardiff, and Budapest. In 2018, WOMEX was held in Las Palmas, Gran Canaria. One of its showcase participants, Norayr Kartashyan, is acclaimed as one of Armenia's finest woodwind masters and composers, an acknowledged virtuoso numerous traditional Armenian instruments. To name a few: the blul and shvi flutes, duduk, the double-reed zurna trumpet, the pku clarinet, and the parkapzuk bagpipe.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/29/16/2143305_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230503191100 +0200" stop="20230503202600 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Bixiga 70 - BIRD 2019</title>
<desc lang="fr">Bixiga 70 - BIRD 2019 - Stemming from Brazil's São Paulo, Bixiga 70 is an exciting brass and percussion-based instrumental dance ensemble that combines jazz, funk, and Afro-Brazilian music, incorporating elements from dub, reggae, electronics, cumbia, carimbo, Ethio-jazz, and samba. The name Bixiga 70 is taken from a vibrant neighbourhood in downtown São Paulo. Organic, ritualistic, and sometimes even primal, the band's music appeals to those who seek out mental and physical freedom.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/33/1977716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230503202600 +0200" stop="20230503210000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Nana Adjoa</title>
<desc lang="fr">Songbook - Nana Adjoa - &quot;I never heard anyone say that, and yeah, I know exactly what it means. It has to go in there, this has to be a song.&quot; Every song has its own story, and we all think it's a story we've heard before, but we haven't. Songbook finds and captures these intriguing stories by pulling you into the process of writing and composing. Known for its pristine sound, cinematic 4k video, and eye for detail, Songbook live-captured episodes emphasize the paramount importance of quality. It addresses the on-the-spot elements of blending song and location at the right moment. Both the magical location and remarkable music interaction will get the attention they deserve.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/04/2122118_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230503210000 +0200" stop="20230503220000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Liam Gallagher</title>
<desc lang="fr">Liam Gallagher - After leading iconic British rock band Oasis for nearly two decades, Manchester-born singer Liam Gallagher launched his solo career in 2016. He played his first ever U.S. solo show on July 28th of 2017 at Manhattan's McKittrick Hotel in New York City. The rather small venue is known to host the immersive theater experience &quot;Sleep No More&quot;, and its limited capacities made for an intense and intimate concert experience. In a 75-minute long show featuring thirteen songs, Gallagher performed tracks of his 2017 debut album As You Were, next to a list of Oasis fan favorites. Shot in phenomenally sharp 4K, this recording offers viewers the unique opportunity to become part of the audience of this secret session.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230503220000 +0200" stop="20230503230200 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Nilüfer Yanya - Echoes Series: Nilufer Yanya</title>
<desc lang="fr">Echoes Series - Episode 6 - Echoes is a modern live music show hosted by Jehnny Beth (lead singer in the British band Savages). It presents leading and emerging bands and artists from the contemporary scene. The show takes place underneath the Palais de Tokyo museum in Paris, in the club of brutalist architecture, the &quot;Yoyo.&quot; The live sets are 30 minutes long and take place on a customized stage, creating closeness with the audience. Once the bands have performed, Jehnny Beth invites everyone to sit at her roundtable for a group conversation. The open discussions in every episode allow the audience to understand the rapport, artistic exchange, and intellectual debates that run through this eclectic musical universe. The intimate, immersive space lends to the atmosphere of the show.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/03/1754401_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230503230200 +0200" stop="20230503235700 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Audience Music</title>
<desc lang="fr">Enjoy ground-breaking concerts, in-depth artist interviews, and unique stories with host Ted Stryker. This concert series gives the audience an intimate view of music's most influential artists today. Shot in 4K, host Ted Stryker interviews musicians across all genres, creating one of the most unique music shows on TV today. This episode features singer/songwriter Skylar Grey, best known for her songwriting skills, as displayed in Eminem and Rihanna's &quot;Love The Way You Lie&quot; (2010). The five-time GRAMMY-nominee and Wisconsin-born pop artist takes the stage to perform some of her most popular songs, as well as some works of her forthcoming album &quot;Angel With Tattoos&quot;. Enjoy Skylar Grey's performance and interview at Audience Music 2019!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/04/2122118_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230503235700 +0200" stop="20230504013400 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Hugh Coltman</title>
<desc lang="fr">The English singer and composer Hugh Coltman started in blues rock band The Hoax, after which he moved to Paris and released two pop and folk albums. Jazz was beckoning and his next project was a tribute to singer and pianist Nat &quot;King&quot; Cole. Coltman recorded his album 'Who's Happy?' in New Orleans. With this he makes music of an important life question.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/07/57/1642181_A.jpg" />
</programme>