<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Voo -->
<programme start="20230602022000 +0200" stop="20230602030000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Clarinet Factory</title>
<desc lang="fr">Classical:NEXT 2019 - Clarinet Factory - Considered to be one of the most unique ensembles to feature on the Czech scene in the last 25 years, the style of the Clarinet Factory hovers between contemporary and classical music, jazz and world music. As winners of the Classic Prague Awards in 2017 for 'Best Crossover Project', the quartet combines their classic music training and clarinet art with jazz, minimalism and improvisation to create their very own music without borders, capable of communicating directly with all audiences. The Clarinet Factory also experiment with electronics, both ambient and dance-oriented, and the four musicians remain ever fascinated with the possibilities of their instrument, considering their work as a music laboratory.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/24/07/2123267_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230602030000 +0200" stop="20230602042700 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Cirque Le Roux : La nuit du cerf</title>
<desc lang="fr">Cirque le Roux - A Deer in the Headlights - Cirque Le Roux, a reunion of six gifted artists, chooses glamour and eccentricity to dress up the acrobatic prowess of its creation. The acrobats master it all, from decor to costumes, and from the most perilous circus numbers to the slightest tremors of an intrigue which combines the eternal themes of love, friendship and the unsaid. Enter the strange and comical world of the Cirque Le Roux company with their disturbing story of A Deer in the Headlights performed on the stage of the Théâtre Libre de Paris. The story features three children, whose mother has died, who meet in the family home to prepare the funeral. The reunion is turned upside down by the irruption of a mysterious shaggy stranger. From now on, the funeral will take a completely different turn.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Evénement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/11/06/2096119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230602042700 +0200" stop="20230602051600 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">House of the Gipsies</title>
<desc lang="fr">House of the Gipsies - Sing Jazz 2018 - Since the Gypsy Kings made their triumphal debut on the music scene with their wild Spanish rumba four decades ago, no band has dared to follow in their footsteps ... until now! House of the Gipsies updates the raw rhythms of nomadic tribes in Rajasthan, India, collaborating with Manganiyar musicians Manjoor, Nehru and Dilawar Khan. The result is a unique sound that can be described as Indo-Gypsy fusion, which is part of the evolution of the Spanish rumba. Do not miss this eclectic performance sure to please music lovers of all generations, presented at the 2018 Sing Jazz Festival.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/03/2145502_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230602051600 +0200" stop="20230602054800 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Lifschitz &amp; Davidson</title>
<desc lang="fr">Lifschitz &amp; Davidson - Sonya Lifschitz is a pianist working across many contexts, with repertoire spanning from 15th century Faenza Codex to works written for her today. She is known for her fiercely imaginative, daring collaborations across film, animation, spoken word, visual and performance art. Robert Davidson has been making music from language since childhood. He has created music from the voices of Australia's prime ministers, from 100 years of radio broadcasts and from stories of asylum seekers and indigenous members of Australia's Stolen Generations. This performance is recorded during Classical:NEXT 2019 in Rotterdam, The Netherlands.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/49/1767496_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230602054800 +0200" stop="20230602070200 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Christian Scott - The Centennial Trilogy</title>
<desc lang="fr">In just a few years, young trumpet player Christian Scott has become synonymous with a new jazz generation. He shakes up the conventions of jazz by taking the genre to new horizons and reaching a wider audience. No doubt, at 33 years old, Christian Scott is already forging his own path. After each record release, he seems even more determined to challenge the rules of jazz with his own avant-garde style. At his 2018 show at La Coopérative de Mai, Christian Scott celebrates 100 years of jazz with the program &quot;The Centennial Trilogy.&quot; Expect a unique performance in an intimate theatre setting, shot in native 4K!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/04/1754386_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230602070200 +0200" stop="20230602074600 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Moonlight Benjamin : WOMEX 2018</title>
<desc lang="fr">Numerous musicians, booking agents, news agencies and media companies from all over the world have been attending the &quot;World Music Exhibition&quot; World Music Expo (WOMEX) since 1994. Over the years, this music fair has settled in several European cities, including Berlin, Brussels, Marseille, Stockholm, Seville, Cardiff and Budapest. In 2018 WOMEX took place in Las Palmas in Gran Canaria. One of the participants was the Haitian singer Moonlight Benjamin. With her band she mixes voodoo blues, Haitian rock and Creole roll into a swirling brew that is thrilling with exciting riffs and heavy grooves. Her powerful voice and fiery electric guitars do the rest.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/52/1752443_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230602074600 +0200" stop="20230602090000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Green Velvet, MK, Carl Cox &amp; deadmau5</title>
<desc lang="fr">Creamfields - Having burst onto the ever-growing festival scene two decades ago, Creamfields has secured its spot as being one of the - if not the - biggest weekend dedicated to electronic music in the UK. Currently, the clubbing and raving pilgrimage attracts an impressive 70,000 festival-goers over the weekend. Continuously offering up the very best in EDM, house, trance, drum and bass, grime, and more, Creamfields has hosted some massive names over the past twenty years. This 2019 edition of Creamfields presents Green Velvet, MK, Carl Cox, Deadmau5, Camelphat, Nicole Moudaber, Dimitri Vegas &amp; Like Mike, and many more!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230602090000 +0200" stop="20230602101800 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">The Opera Locos</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Opera Locos - In The Opera Locos (&quot;The Opera of Crazies&quot;), a comic opera show from the Spanish theater company Yllana and theatre producer Rami Eldar, five eccentric opera singers perform some of the greatest opera arias. Classical arias from George Bizet's Carmen, W. A. Mozart's The Magic Flute, and Giuseppe Verdi's Rigoletto are combined with classics from the pop and rock repertoire. During the performance, the five characters reveal their hidden passions, personalities, and desires, leading to unpredictable, hilarious situations that audiences of all ages will appreciate. The soloists are Florian Laconi (tenor), Margaux Toqué (mezzo soprano), Michaël Koné (countertenor), Laurent Arcaro (baritone), and Diane Fourès (soprano). This performance was recorded at Théâtre Libre in Paris, France.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Evénement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/02/07/27/1763355_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230602101800 +0200" stop="20230602112300 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Jungle By Night</title>
<desc lang="fr">Jungle By Night - Jazz in Duketown - Jazz in Duketown is the largest free outdoor jazz festival in the Netherlands. It's a real gathering for jazz addicts, inviting internationally renowned bands. In 2019, one of them is the Amsterdam-based Dutch instrumental collective Jungle by Night. The band plays a mix of various styles, inspired by funk, jazz, dub, rock, and others. The ensemble made its debut in 2010 and has played at numerous festivals. Their December 2010 performance with former backing musicians of Afrobeat founder Fela Kuti in Paris saw them hailed as &quot;the future of Afrobeat&quot;.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/10/1759031_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230602112300 +0200" stop="20230602133700 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Handel - Rinaldo</title>
<desc lang="fr">Handel - Rinaldo - Rinaldo (1711) is an opera by German-born composer George Frideric Handel, set during the First Crusade. With Rinaldo, Handel plunges us into a chivalrous, romantic world. With birds, dragons, lightning, and thunderbolts, this spectacular work demonstrates the dramatic mastery of the composer on a dreamlike and powerful score. Giacomo Rossi's libretto deals with Goffredo's Crusader army laying siege to Jerusalem, which king Argante defends. One of the Crusaders, knight Rinaldo, is promised to marry Goffredo's daughter Almirena if the Christians are victorious. Handel composed Rinaldo in just fourteen days, borrowing musical material from his earlier compositions. Rinaldo features &quot;Lascia ch'io pianga,&quot; one of Handel's best-known arias, in which Rinaldo's abducted lover Almirena bemoans her tragic fate.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/20/23/2199080_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230602133700 +0200" stop="20230602143900 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Nilüfer Yanya - Echoes Series: Nilufer Yanya</title>
<desc lang="fr">Echoes Series - Episode 4 - Echoes is a modern live music show hosted by Jehnny Beth (lead singer in the British band Savages). It presents leading and emerging bands and artists from the contemporary scene. The show takes place underneath the Palais de Tokyo museum in Paris, in the club of brutalist architecture, the &quot;Yoyo.&quot; The live sets are 30 minutes long and take place on a customized stage, creating closeness with the audience. Once the bands have performed, Jehnny Beth invites everyone to sit at her roundtable for a group conversation. The open discussions in every episode allow the audience to understand the rapport, artistic exchange, and intellectual debates that run through this eclectic musical universe. The intimate, immersive space lends to the atmosphere of the show.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/03/1754401_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230602143900 +0200" stop="20230602150500 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Violetta Zironi</title>
<desc lang="fr">Songbook - &quot;I never heard anyone say that, and yeah, I know exactly what it means. It has to go in there, this has to be a song.&quot; Every song has its own story, and we all think it's a story we've heard before, but we haven't. Songbook finds and captures these intriguing stories by pulling you into the process of writing and composing. Known for its pristine sound, cinematic 4k video and eye for detail, Songbook live-captured episodes emphasize the paramount importance of quality. It addresses the on-the-spot elements of blending song and location at the right moment. Both the magical location and remarkable music interaction will get the attention they deserve. Simply because Songbook isn't just a live music session, it lives. This episode of Songbook features Italian singer-songwriter Violetta Zironi.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230602150500 +0200" stop="20230602162500 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">HVOB</title>
<desc lang="fr">HVOB - The two musicians behind HVOB are Anna Müller and Paul Wallner. Anna Müller composes, produces, and provides the captivating, hypnotic vocals. The final production of the tracks is done in collaboration with Paul Wallner in his Vienna studio. HVOB are carving their path not just with their distinctive sound but with their live performances as well. The duo always plays live and performs with a drummer - a concept as innovative as it is successful: HVOB has just been voted number two best live act by the most influential German electronic music magazine &quot;De:bug.&quot; Enjoy their 2019 show at Trabendo Paris!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Musique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/59/1769392_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230602162500 +0200" stop="20230602174100 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Monty Alexander &amp; The Harlem Kingston Express</title>
<desc lang="fr">With a career spanning five decades, jazz pianist Monty Alexander has played with the best of the best. An ambassador for Jamaican music, Alexander creates a unique blend of jazz and reggae with a group of exceptional American and Jamaican musicians called the &quot;Harlem Kingston Express.&quot; Together, they explore the two sides of Monty Alexander's musical legacy: the jazz of Harlem and the reggae of Kingston. Many great jazz musicians, including Dizzy Gillespie, have called on Alexander's exceptional sense of improvisation. Watch this 4K recording of his 2017 performance at Philharmonie de Paris, and you'll understand why.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/56/1752527_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230602174100 +0200" stop="20230602180800 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Close Call</title>
<desc lang="fr">Classical:NEXT 2019 - Close Call - In Close Call your smartphone is a musical instrument. And you are not just an audience member, but a musician in a crazy band with three drummers! Arthur Wagenaar is a Dutch composer and musician. He has a deep love for rock bands, theatre, opera and classical music, and his music is usually a mixture of all of this. He also loves to invent his own instruments, mechanical or electronic, such as the &quot;rampaphone,&quot; a string instrument nine meters in length, the &quot;kleurwerper,&quot; played by juggling, and of course the Close Call Live app. In this performance from Classical:NEXT! in Rotterdam, he is supported by Joep Hendrickx, Tjalling Schrik, Marijn Korff de Gidts, Boy van Ooijen, Dodó Kis, Sarah Jeffery, Lotte Pen, Matthias Konrad, and Axel Schappert.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/24/07/2123267_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230602180800 +0200" stop="20230602190300 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Oum 2018</title>
<desc lang="fr">Oum El Ghait Benessahraoui, better known as Oum, provides a unique insight into Moroccan music. This singer-songwriter is considered an ambassador for Moroccan culture. Oum is strongly influenced by genres such as gospel, jazz, soul and R&amp;B, but also African genres such as sufi, hassani, and afrobeat inspire her. Yet the influences of Aretha Franklin, Ella Fitzgerald and Whitney Houston are also strongly present in Oum's powerful voice. As a young singer, the African American vocal tradition made a deep impression on her. During her performance at the Music Meeting Festival in Nijmegen, Oum shows her audience unexpected musical vistas.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/04/1754386_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230602190300 +0200" stop="20230602194500 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Null + Void</title>
<desc lang="fr">Null + Void - While few people are familiar with the Null + Void project, many have already heard Kurt Uenala's music. After making his debut under the pseudonym Kap10Kurt in 2003, Uenala caught the attention of the world with the play &quot;Die Sleeping&quot;. This critical and popular success has led to collaborations with several big names in music, including Moby, The Kills, and Dave Gahan, singer of Depeche Mode, for whom Uenala has subsequently signed plays. Spending more and more time in his Manhattan studio, Uenala developed a unique sound made of angular beats and dark soundscapes, which gave rise to a new melancholy solo project called Null + Void. Cryosleep, Uenala's first album under this new banner, includes several titles inspired by retro science fiction, new wave and electronic innovators.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/06/2111709_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230602194500 +0200" stop="20230602210000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">BIGYUKI : BIRD 2019</title>
<desc lang="fr">BIGYUKI - BIRD 2019 - BIGYUKI's is New York City's secret musical weapon! His unprecedented sound has attracted the attention of many, including Grammy Award-winning and nominated artists such as Q-Tip, Bilal, Talib Kweli, Harvey Mason, Marcus Strickland, Mark Giuliana, and Meshell Ndegeocello. BIGYUKI's music offers a soulful exploration into the wondrous soundscapes of his infinitely virtuosic mind. Infusing elements of jazz, classical music, hip-hop, soul, rock, dance, and electronica, BIGYUKI reaches a new and inspiring level, with support from guitarist Randy Runyon and drummer Smithsoneon. It is hard to believe that just three musicians can create a sound this massive.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/59/1769392_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230602210000 +0200" stop="20230602220900 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Skunk Anansie</title>
<desc lang="fr">Les Vieilles Charrues - British alternative rock group Skunk Anansie celebrates its 25th anniversary with the album 25LIVE@25. These 90s rock scene icons, whose hair-raising shows have become legendary, celebrate their storied career with this 25-song project. With a selection of recordings taken from various 2017 live performances, Skunk Anansie once again proves its unbeatable power on stage. The setlist includes &quot;Because of You,&quot; &quot;The Skank Heads,&quot; and &quot;Tear the Place Up.&quot; Don't miss the triumphant return of these pillars of rock to the stage of the 28th edition of Les Vieilles Charrues in Carhaix, France, in 2019!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/20/37/2008125_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230602220900 +0200" stop="20230602225300 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Sam Feldt, Mr. White, YAX.X &amp; Robin Schulz - Sensation</title>
<desc lang="fr">Sensation - What began fifteen years ago as a one-off in the Amsterdam ArenA is now a worldwide phenomenon that takes place in stadiums and arenas around the globe. All the attendees are required to wear white or black, and the Amsterdam ArenA is decorated to match. Sensation White's slogan is &quot;Be Part of the Night - Dress in White.&quot; Every event has around 40,000 to 45,000 tickets available. For the first time in history, Sensation Amsterdam had a black and white edition named &quot;Angels and Demons.&quot; The event, which had 20 000 people dressed in black and 20 000 in white, was sold out. Performing artists included David Guetta, Sam Feldt, Don Diablo, Yellow Claw, and Nicky Romero.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/35/1763357_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230602225300 +0200" stop="20230603004800 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Above &amp; Beyond Group Therapy 200</title>
<desc lang="fr">Above &amp; Beyond Group Therapy 300 - Above and Beyond recently made their mark on ABGT300 in an epic way. Live for the 300th edition of Group Therapy Radio, the group broadcast from The Asiaworld-Expo in Hong Kong on September 29, 2018. ABGT300 also saw live performances from Andrew Bayer, Ben Böhmer, Grum, Ilan Bluestone, and Spencer Brown, with the signature set from Above and Beyond as the main event. This year, they wanted to push Group Therapy to the next level. Get ready for some magic moments and excellent music.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/04/2122118_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230603004800 +0200" stop="20230603013100 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">City Beats</title>
<desc lang="fr">City Beats - Episode 2 - Ibiza - DJ-producer Carly Foxx is on a musical journey, immersing herself in the life of five iconic European cities to find inspiration for a series of new tracks. In this episode, Carly Foxx travels to the world's clubbing capital to inspire her music track and discovers Ibiza's alternative spiritual side. She starts her journey in San Antonio but discovers this place is mainly about clubbing and drinking - not very inspiring for her music track. The next stop is Old Town, where Carly meets female Ibiza singer Sam Smith, who introduces her to DJ and producer Manu Gonzalez. While talking to him, Carly decides the base of her Ibiza-inspired track should be a Balearic beat, to which she plans to add bongos and castanet samples.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Télé-Réalité</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/12/00/2155262_A.jpg" />
</programme>