<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Voo -->
<programme start="20230531030000 +0200" stop="20230531034600 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">BIRD</title>
<desc lang="fr">BIRD - Five promising musicians get together in Rotterdam jazz club BIRD's artists-in-residence project &quot;The Nest&quot;. In this first broadcast we get to know Lisette Ma Neza (slam poet), Peter Somuah (trumpet), Michelle Samba (drums), Huy Le (bass), and Brenn Luiten (piano). Over the course of seven sessions, they exchange ideas, work on their projects, and play music together. Following this period, during which record producer Jameszoo and music manager Jochem Tromp offer their coaching experience, BIRD and North Sea Jazz Festival's fringe festival DownTown organize a tryout performance. Enjoy this unique collaboration of upcoming musicians!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/02/18/24/2148521_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230531034600 +0200" stop="20230531044600 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Samba das Flores</title>
<desc lang="fr">Samba das Flores - Da Pá Virada Sessions - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the bands taking part in this series is the ensemble Samba das Flores, which dedicates itself to exploring the world's different rhythms, thus keeping the Brazilian heritage alive. The individual voices of the ensemble members color Samba das Flores's unique sound. Let Brazilian culture and global rhythms inspire you during this Samba das Flores performance!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230531044600 +0200" stop="20230531055700 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Salomao Soares Trio</title>
<desc lang="fr">Salomao Soares Trio - Da Pá Virada Sessions - Da Pá Virada sessions bring the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the bands taking part in this series is the Salomão Soares Trio, which consists of Salomão Soares on piano, Paulo Almeida on drums, and Thiago Alves on bass. Band leader Soares was a finalist of the 2017 Montreux Jazz Festival piano competition.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230531055700 +0200" stop="20230531070000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Tribute to Elis Regina</title>
<desc lang="fr">Tribute to Elis Regina - Da Pá Virada Sessions - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the bands taking part in this episode is a foursome that pays tribute to pioneering música popular brasileira vocalist Elis Regina: vocalist Vanessa Moreno, bassist Fi Marostica, Rhodes and keyboard player Tiago Costa, and drummer Jonatas Sansao honor the legendary Brazilian singer by performing famous pieces and hidden gems from her repertoire.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230531070000 +0200" stop="20230531075400 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">WOMEX 2018</title>
<desc lang="fr">In 2018 WOMEX took place in Las Palmas in Gran Canaria. One of the participants was The Garifuna Collective. These young and old musicians from the Caribbean keep Andy Palacio's legacy alive.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/29/16/2143305_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230531075400 +0200" stop="20230531090000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Sheryl Crow</title>
<desc lang="fr">Sheryl Crow - Missouri-born country mega-star Sheryl Crow celebrates her return to the stage in an intimate performance at New York City's Iridium. Having sold over million copies of her ten studio albums worldwide over the course of her over three decade-long career, Sheryl Crow has long-established a status of one of America's most successful musicians. With a warm sound made up of elements of country, pop, rock and Americana, Crow has received nine GRAMMY-awards and over thirty nominations.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/03/1853299_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230531090000 +0200" stop="20230531101600 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Chloé - Trabendo Paris</title>
<desc lang="fr">Chloé - Trabendo Paris - Chloé has, without a doubt, led an entire generation to her electronic music playground - one that goes beyond strictly club and techno. As much a film music enthusiast as an accomplished guitar player, she stumbled into the electronic scene early on, developing an unwavering curiosity for sound machines. Chloé is a composer, and she gives life to artistic ideas. The challenge is to stay unwavering in spite of self-doubt that arises throughout the creative process. It is precisely this inner questioning, this contradiction, that nourishes and motivates Chloé's work. Chloé dedicates a full set to her 2017 album Endless Revisions. At Trabendo Paris, she plays these brand-new songs only a few weeks after the album was released.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/59/1769392_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230531101600 +0200" stop="20230531110300 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Jacob Karlzon Trio - Open Waters</title>
<desc lang="fr">Together with the Danish bassist Morten Ramsbøl and the Swedish drummer Rasmus Kihlberg, the Swedish pianist Jacob Karlzon presents the album &quot;Open Waters&quot; in the Hamburg factory of piano builder Steinway. The trained pianist, who shared the stage with Kenny Wheeler, Norma Winstone and Billy Cobham, honors the rich tradition of eclectic Swedish jazz. In 2012 he explored heavy metal, then applied electronics to determine the beat.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/19/1853106_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230531110300 +0200" stop="20230531120200 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Paulo Novaes - New Year's Eve Special</title>
<desc lang="fr">Paulo Novaes - New Year's Eve Special - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the artists taking part in this series is Paulo Novaes. Coming from a family of musicians, Paulo Novaes has already lived through a lifetime of music in spite of his young age. Paulo is the cousin of singer Bruna Caram, with whom he performed in São Paulo, Madrid, Barcelona, Lisbon, and other major cities. As a singer, composer, and instrumentalist, his creativity is enjoyed in many forms.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230531120200 +0200" stop="20230531133900 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Hugh Coltman</title>
<desc lang="fr">The English singer and composer Hugh Coltman started in blues rock band The Hoax, after which he moved to Paris and released two pop and folk albums. Jazz was beckoning and his next project was a tribute to singer and pianist Nat &quot;King&quot; Cole. Coltman recorded his album 'Who's Happy?' in New Orleans. With this he makes music of an important life question.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/19/1853106_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230531133900 +0200" stop="20230531141100 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Audience Music</title>
<desc lang="fr">Yungblud - Watch groundbreaking concerts, in-depth artist interviews, and stories with host Ted Stryker. This concert series gives the audience an intimate view of music's most influential artists today. Shot in 4K, Stryker interviews musicians across all genres, creating the most unique music show on TV today. This episode features the English singer songwriter Yungblud. He grew up near Manchester in a musical family. His father owned a guitar shop, where he got his first guitar lessons. He released his first album, 21st Century Liability in 2018. In the same year, Yungblud recorded the song &quot;Falling Skies&quot; with Charlotte Lawrence, which was featured in the Netflix series 13 Reasons Why. Enjoy his exciting show at Audience Music 2019!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/58/1754433_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230531141100 +0200" stop="20230531150200 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Jeditah</title>
<desc lang="fr">Classical:NEXT 2019 - Jeditah - Jeditah is an experimental songwriter, producer and singer from Amsterdam. She works with Brendan Jan Walsh on cello and Jordy Pama on synths and electronics. From an early age on, Jeditah has been immersed in the world of music, travelling with her parents as a music collective. She finds inspiration in the works of acclaimed artists like Björk, James Blake, Laurie Anderson and PJ Harvey. When she began experimenting with making her own music, she first only utilized her own voice, lowering and altering it, and eventually adding electronic beats and synths. With Electric AlleyCat, Jeditah has established her position as a singer and songwriter. In between performing and recording with the band, she creates layered soundscapes from old recordings and homemade samples.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/24/07/2123267_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230531150200 +0200" stop="20230531160300 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Steve Vai</title>
<desc lang="fr">Steve Vai - The popular music performance series, Front and Center, which premiered nationwide on public television, in 2016, returns for Season 6. The series boasts 22, one-hour episodes and an all-star line-up. This episode features Steve Vai, the legendary guitarist who was voted the 10th Greatest Guitarist by Guitar World magazine, who treats fans to songs from his three-decade long career. As an independent guitarist he has won three Grammy Awards. Vai's solo sophomore release, Passion and Warfare, has earned gold certification in the US. At Front and Center he sits down and discusses his early interest in composing music and playing guitar as well as the many fortunes of his career.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Musique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/42/1870646_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230531160300 +0200" stop="20230531170400 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Mariana Aydar</title>
<desc lang="fr">Mariana Aydar - Da Pá Virada Sessions - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the artists taking part in this episode is vocalist Mariana Aydar, who masters the música popular brasileira repertoire (MPB) like no other. She was born in a family of musicians, and has been dubbed the &quot;hottest singer of the moment&quot; by Veja, one of Brazil's leading newsmagazines. For her performance at Da Pá Virada Sessions, Aydar (vocals and triangle) is joined by Cosme Vieira (accordion) and Feeh Silva (zabumba).</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230531170400 +0200" stop="20230531183400 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Clubbing Experience with Nina Kraviz @ Kappa FuturFestival</title>
<desc lang="fr">Nina Kraviz - When you're into techno, you're into Nina Kraviz. The Siberian DJ and producer has become one of the biggest names of the techno scene. From world famous stages, to intimate shows in smaller venues, Nina's hypnotic style of mixing, combined with her acid-like techno is loved by many. Kraviz went solo and made a splash in 2009, when she issued productions on Efdemin's Naïf, Jus-Ed's Underground Quality, and Matt Edwards' Rekids. Following additional singles on Rekids and Rosa, as well as the Mr. Jones EP in 2013, Kraviz founded the Trip label in 2014. Enjoy her show at Kappa FuturFestival 2019!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Clips</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/57/1752448_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230531183400 +0200" stop="20230531192300 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">House of the Gipsies</title>
<desc lang="fr">House of the Gipsies - Sing Jazz 2018 - Since the Gypsy Kings made their triumphal debut on the music scene with their wild Spanish rumba four decades ago, no band has dared to follow in their footsteps ... until now! House of the Gipsies updates the raw rhythms of nomadic tribes in Rajasthan, India, collaborating with Manganiyar musicians Manjoor, Nehru and Dilawar Khan. The result is a unique sound that can be described as Indo-Gypsy fusion, which is part of the evolution of the Spanish rumba. Do not miss this eclectic performance sure to please music lovers of all generations, presented at the 2018 Sing Jazz Festival.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/03/2145502_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230531192300 +0200" stop="20230531203700 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Bixiga 70 - BIRD 2019</title>
<desc lang="fr">Bixiga 70 - BIRD 2019 - Stemming from Brazil's São Paulo, Bixiga 70 is an exciting brass and percussion-based instrumental dance ensemble that combines jazz, funk, and Afro-Brazilian music, incorporating elements from dub, reggae, electronics, cumbia, carimbo, Ethio-jazz, and samba. The name Bixiga 70 is taken from a vibrant neighbourhood in downtown São Paulo. Organic, ritualistic, and sometimes even primal, the band's music appeals to those who seek out mental and physical freedom.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/33/1977716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230531203700 +0200" stop="20230531210000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Flaws</title>
<desc lang="fr">Songbook - &quot;I never heard anyone say that, and yeah, I know exactly what it means. It has to go in there, this has to be a song.&quot; Every song has its own story, and we all think it's a story we've heard before, but we haven't. Songbook finds and captures these intriguing stories by pulling you into the process of writing and composing. Known for its pristine sound, cinematic 4k video and eye for detail, Songbook live-captured episodes emphasize the paramount importance of quality. It addresses the on-the-spot elements of blending song and location at the right moment. Both the magical location and remarkable music interaction will get the attention they deserve. Simply because Songbook isn't just a live music session, it lives.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230531210000 +0200" stop="20230531220200 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Fedde Le Grand Ziggo Dome</title>
<desc lang="fr">Grand - Following his sold-out shows in 2015, top DJ Fedde Le Grand decided to make a comeback in a bigger and more spectacular environment, the Ziggo Dome. The goal was simple: take down the barriers and break all codes of a traditional dance party! Grand was a spectacular show, changing the dance landscape forever and creating a full crossover between dance and theater. Ballet dancers, singers, break dancers, actors, and live musicians all play their role to the beats of Fedde Le Grand. This show is impressive, and you will be surprised again and again.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230531220200 +0200" stop="20230531230700 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Jungle By Night</title>
<desc lang="fr">Jungle By Night - Jazz in Duketown - Jazz in Duketown is the largest free outdoor jazz festival in the Netherlands. It's a real gathering for jazz addicts, inviting internationally renowned bands. In 2019, one of them is the Amsterdam-based Dutch instrumental collective Jungle by Night. The band plays a mix of various styles, inspired by funk, jazz, dub, rock, and others. The ensemble made its debut in 2010 and has played at numerous festivals. Their December 2010 performance with former backing musicians of Afrobeat founder Fela Kuti in Paris saw them hailed as &quot;the future of Afrobeat&quot;.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/10/1759031_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230531230700 +0200" stop="20230601000100 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Audience Music</title>
<desc lang="fr">Enjoy ground-breaking concerts, in-depth artist interviews, and unique stories with host Ted Stryker. This concert series gives the audience an intimate view of music's most influential artists today. Shot in 4K, host Ted Stryker interviews musicians across all genres, creating one of the most unique music shows on TV today. This episode features singer/songwriter Skylar Grey, best known for her songwriting skills, as displayed in Eminem and Rihanna's &quot;Love The Way You Lie&quot; (2010). The five-time GRAMMY-nominee and Wisconsin-born pop artist takes the stage to perform some of her most popular songs, as well as some works of her forthcoming album &quot;Angel With Tattoos&quot;. Enjoy Skylar Grey's performance and interview at Audience Music 2019!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/04/2122118_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230601000100 +0200" stop="20230601013700 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Atys en folie</title>
<desc lang="fr">Atys en Folie - Atys en folie is a parody of Jean-Baptiste Lully's lyrical tragedy Atys (1676). Atys, Lully's most famous opera, was a constant subject of parody throughout the 18th century. Stage director Jean-Philippe Desrousseaux drew on several parodies to create this original production for singers, puppets, and musicians to revive the work. Princes, princesses, and kings are relegated to peasants, market gardeners, and fishmongers in the countryside. Among the performers are Alain Buet, Marie Lenormand, and Arnaud Marzorati. Gaëlle Trimardeau, Bruno Coulon and Jean-Philippe Desrousseaux feature as puppeteers. The music is performed by ensemble La Clique des Lunaisiens, conducted by Arnaud Marzorati. This performance was recorded at Teatru Manoel in Valletta, Malta, in 2017.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/02/04/18/1768814_A.jpg" />
</programme>