<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Voo -->
<programme start="20230324015900 +0100" stop="20230324024000 +0100" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Null + Void</title>
<desc lang="fr">Null + Void - While few people are familiar with the Null + Void project, many have already heard Kurt Uenala's music. After making his debut under the pseudonym Kap10Kurt in 2003, Uenala caught the attention of the world with the play &quot;Die Sleeping&quot;. This critical and popular success has led to collaborations with several big names in music, including Moby, The Kills, and Dave Gahan, singer of Depeche Mode, for whom Uenala has subsequently signed plays. Spending more and more time in his Manhattan studio, Uenala developed a unique sound made of angular beats and dark soundscapes, which gave rise to a new melancholy solo project called Null + Void. Cryosleep, Uenala's first album under this new banner, includes several titles inspired by retro science fiction, new wave and electronic innovators.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/06/2111709_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230324024000 +0100" stop="20230324030000 +0100" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">The Entrepeneurs</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Entrepeneurs - Songbook - &quot;I never heard anyone say that, and yeah, I know exactly what it means. It has to go in there, this has to be a song.&quot; Every song has its own story, and we all think it's a story we've heard before, but we haven't. Songbook finds and captures these intriguing stories by pulling you into the process of writing and composing. Known for its pristine sound, cinematic 4k video and eye for detail, Songbook live-captured episodes emphasize the paramount importance of quality. It addresses the on-the-spot elements of blending song and location at the right moment. Both the magical location and remarkable music interaction will get the attention they deserve. Simply because Songbook isn't just a live music session, it lives.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/35/1763357_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230324030000 +0100" stop="20230324040300 +0100" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Runtown : La Machine de Moulin Rouge</title>
<desc lang="fr">Runtown - La Machine de Moulin Rouge - Enjoy Runtown's first concert in Paris, where the Nigerian superstar brings many guests to his show. One of the most talented Nigerian afrobeat scenes will make you rediscover his greatest hits. Nigeria is a very creative country when it comes to the music scene. Runtown is no exception. His first single, &quot;Party Like It's 1980,&quot; paved the way for &quot;Gallardo,&quot; which caught the entire international scene's attention. Runtown's inspiration comes from the greats, from Salif Keita and Fela Kuti to Otis Redding and Bob Marley. An exceptional event not to be missed.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230324040300 +0100" stop="20230324050800 +0100" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Martina</title>
<desc lang="fr">Martina - Da Pá Virada Sessions - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the artists taking part in this series is Martina Marana. Vocalist, instrumentalist, and composer Martina Marana uses the power of irony to show how women instrumentalists are misjudged. In her music, Martina breaks free of sexist labels, reclaiming her own power as musician and composer. A gifted lyricist, Marana makes uncompromising, unique music.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230324050800 +0100" stop="20230324063900 +0100" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Mötley Crüe</title>
<desc lang="fr">Mötley Crüe, the American rock band formed in the 1980s, was founded by bassist Nikki Sixx and drummer Tommy Lee, who were later joined by guitarist Mick Mars, and vocalist Vince Neil. Mötley Crüe has sold more than 100 million records worldwide, including 25 million in the US. On December 31, 2015, legendary rock icons Mötley Crüe completed their 35-year touring career as a band with a spectacular final concert at Staples Center in their hometown of Los Angeles, CA, just 10 miles from the Sunset Strip where the band's infamous and decadent career first launched. The band thrilled the sold-out arena with performances of mega-hits &quot;Kickstart My Heart,&quot; &quot;Girls Girls Girls,&quot; &quot;Home Sweet Home,&quot; and &quot;Dr. Feelgood.&quot; Directed by Jeff Tremaine and Christian Lamb.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Société</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/03/1853299_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230324063900 +0100" stop="20230324072200 +0100" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">WOMEX 2018</title>
<desc lang="fr">Norayr Kartashyan &amp; Menua - WOMEX 2018 - Since 1994, World Music Expo (WOMEX) has been attracting musicians, agents, a great number of press agencies, as well as media companies from all over the world. Its main exposition event has been held in various locations throughout Europe, including Berlin, Brussels, Marseille, Stockholm, Seville, Cardiff, and Budapest. In 2018, WOMEX was held in Las Palmas, Gran Canaria. One of its showcase participants, Norayr Kartashyan, is acclaimed as one of Armenia's finest woodwind masters and composers, an acknowledged virtuoso numerous traditional Armenian instruments. To name a few: the blul and shvi flutes, duduk, the double-reed zurna trumpet, the pku clarinet, and the parkapzuk bagpipe.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/24/31/2143305_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230324072200 +0100" stop="20230324083500 +0100" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Chloé - Trabendo Paris</title>
<desc lang="fr">Chloé - Trabendo Paris - Chloé has, without a doubt, led an entire generation to her electronic music playground - one that goes beyond strictly club and techno. As much a film music enthusiast as an accomplished guitar player, she stumbled into the electronic scene early on, developing an unwavering curiosity for sound machines. Chloé is a composer, and she gives life to artistic ideas. The challenge is to stay unwavering in spite of self-doubt that arises throughout the creative process. It is precisely this inner questioning, this contradiction, that nourishes and motivates Chloé's work. Chloé dedicates a full set to her 2017 album Endless Revisions. At Trabendo Paris, she plays these brand-new songs only a few weeks after the album was released.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/59/1769392_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230324083500 +0100" stop="20230324090000 +0100" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Flaws</title>
<desc lang="fr">Songbook - &quot;I never heard anyone say that, and yeah, I know exactly what it means. It has to go in there, this has to be a song.&quot; Every song has its own story, and we all think it's a story we've heard before, but we haven't. Songbook finds and captures these intriguing stories by pulling you into the process of writing and composing. Known for its pristine sound, cinematic 4k video and eye for detail, Songbook live-captured episodes emphasize the paramount importance of quality. It addresses the on-the-spot elements of blending song and location at the right moment. Both the magical location and remarkable music interaction will get the attention they deserve. Simply because Songbook isn't just a live music session, it lives.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230324090000 +0100" stop="20230324101400 +0100" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Christine and the Queens</title>
<desc lang="fr">Live aux Vieilles Charrues - French singer Héloïse Létissier, aka Christine and the Queens, originates from Nantes, France. Her debut album Chaleur Humaine earned her a Victories of Music award in 2015, paving the way for future success. A versatile artist skilled in music and dance, she surrounds herself with the best. Among others, she collaborated with dancer and choreographer Marion Motin, who accompanied Madonna. In 2018, Christine and the Queens shortened her name to Chris and hit the international scene with a self-titled album. Her artistic work opens up a new perspective on femininity and masculinity, a hot topic today. In this concert, she inspires her audience at Les Vieilles Charrues in Carhaix, France, to dance all night long.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230324101400 +0100" stop="20230324110100 +0100" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Bakolo Music International</title>
<desc lang="fr">In 2018 WOMEX took place in Las Palmas in Gran Canaria. One of the participants was the band Bakolo Music International. They represent the pioneers of the golden age of the Congolese rumba. Singer, guitarist and veteran Nzofu Moko Buele, called Bikunda by everyone, keeps the fire burning that &quot;Papa&quot; lit Wendolosoy, the &quot;father of the Congolese rumba&quot; in 1948 when his song &quot;Marie-Louise&quot; became an international hit.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/24/25/1642161_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230324110100 +0100" stop="20230324120200 +0100" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Creamfields</title>
<desc lang="fr">Creamfields - Having burst onto the ever-growing festival scene two decades ago, Creamfields has secured its spot as being one of the - if not the - biggest weekend dedicated to electronic music in the UK. Currently, the clubbing and raving pilgrimage attracts an impressive 70,000 festival-goers over the weekend. Continuously offering up the very best in EDM, house, trance, drum and bass, grime, and more, Creamfields has hosted some massive names over the past twenty years. This 2019 edition of Creamfields presents Green Velvet, MK, Carl Cox, Deadmau5, Camelphat, Nicole Moudaber, Dimitri Vegas &amp; Like Mike, and many more!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/59/1769392_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230324120200 +0100" stop="20230324133500 +0100" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Antonio Faraò</title>
<desc lang="fr">Jazz à Ramatuelle: Antonio Faraò - In 1998, Antonio Faraò won the prestigious Concours Martial Solal, awarded to him by Herbie Hancock! Since then, this talented Italian jazz pianist has made his mark as a player of elegance and lyricism, which has allowed him to collaborate with the best European and American musicians. On his last album &quot;Evan&quot;, recorded in the United States, he leads an all-star band starring Joe Lovano on tenor saxophone. On a beautiful summer night at the French Jazz à Ramatuelle festival, Faraò performs at the breathtaking Theatre de Verdure in the company of saxophone legend Dave Liebman. With refined ballads, a feline groove, elegance, and lyricism, this musical meeting sparkles - if you watch closely you might even see some bright new stars lighting up in the night sky above Ramatuelle!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230324133500 +0100" stop="20230324141100 +0100" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Primal Scream - Echoes Series: Primal Scream</title>
<desc lang="fr">Echoes Series: Primal Scream - Echoes is a modern live music show hosted by Jehnny Beth (lead singer in the British band Savages). It presents leading and emerging bands and artists from the contemporary scene. The show takes place underneath the Palais de Tokyo museum in Paris, in the club of brutalist architecture, the &quot;Yoyo.&quot; The live sets are 30 minutes long and take place on a customized stage, creating closeness with the audience. The intimate, immersive space lends to the atmosphere of the show. The artistic direction by Antoine Carlier follows a minimalist, refined and pure aesthetic, allowing the artists' energy and emotions to take center stage. This episode features the band Primal Scream. Their set includes the songs &quot;Moving On Up,&quot; &quot;Svastika Eyes,&quot; and &quot;Country Girl.&quot;.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230324141100 +0100" stop="20230324150100 +0100" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Urban Cone</title>
<desc lang="fr">Urban Cone - Watch groundbreaking concerts, in-depth artist interviews, and stories with host Ted Stryker. This concert series gives the audience an intimate view of music's most influential artists today. Shot in 4K, Stryker interviews musicians across all genres, creating the most unique music show on TV today. This episode features the Swedish indie pop band Urban Cone. The band was formed in 2010 by Emil Gustafsson, Tim Formgren, Rasmus Flyckt, Jacob William Sjöberg, and Magnus Folkö. Their debut EP Our Youth came about when they were only 16 years old. The album was recorded in Flyckt's living room. The album's debut single &quot;Urban Photograph&quot; reached #2 on Hype Machine. A tour to the U.S. followed, with performances in New York City, Brooklyn, Los Angeles, and San Francisco.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/58/1754433_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230324150100 +0100" stop="20230324160900 +0100" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Hamilton e Laginha</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Da Pá Virada Sessions series portrays the best musicians in Brazilian jazz today. All sessions were recorded in São Paulo and offer a unique experience: they offer a fresh look at the Brazilian music scene. The artists have been selected together with the music editor of Stingray DJAZZ. One of the musical collaborations that can be seen in this series is the duo of Hamilton de Holanda and Mário Laginha. Grammy nominee De Holanda, who has given the ten-string mandolin a new place in Brazilian music, is entering into a collaboration with pianist Mário Laginha. Together they perform gems of Brazilian music that will make the viewer's heart beat faster.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230324160900 +0100" stop="20230324170900 +0100" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Audience Music</title>
<desc lang="fr">This series features groundbreaking concerts, in-depth artist interviews and unique stories with host Ted Stryker. This concert series gives the audience an intimate view of music's most influential artists today. Shot in 4K, host Ted Stryker interviews musicians across all genres, creating the most unique music show on TV today. This episode features The Band Perry, the famous country band consisting of siblings Kimberly, Reid and Neil Perry. Throughout high school they had different bands, but towards the end of high school the three came together as The Band Perry. After being signed to Republic Nashville, they released their first album, and conquered the charts with the song &quot;If I Die Young.&quot; Since then, they have scored numerous hits and have won various awards.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1757419_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230324170900 +0100" stop="20230324184100 +0100" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Banda Magda live at BIRD Rotterdam</title>
<desc lang="fr">Banda Magda: live at BIRD Rotterdam - An irresistible live act, Banda Magda is full of humour, unflagging energy, and quirky sensibility. A tight-knit group of musicians, they turn the songs of Greek-born founder, singer, and composer Magda Giannikou into engaging gems that have taken the band to legendary venues like Carnegie Hall and, for this performance, BIRD Rotterdam. Banda Magda moves from samba to French chanson, Greek folk music to Colombian cumbia and Afro-Peruvian landó. Their songs capture the best of mid-century ballads and cinematic arrangements, drawing from the band's global background and unrestrained musicality. A joy to experience, Banda Magda makes music for a new generation that's been inspired by ones before.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230324184100 +0100" stop="20230324192800 +0100" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Jacob Karlzon Trio - Open Waters</title>
<desc lang="fr">Together with the Danish bassist Morten Ramsbøl and the Swedish drummer Rasmus Kihlberg, the Swedish pianist Jacob Karlzon presents the album &quot;Open Waters&quot; in the Hamburg factory of piano builder Steinway. The trained pianist, who shared the stage with Kenny Wheeler, Norma Winstone and Billy Cobham, honors the rich tradition of eclectic Swedish jazz. In 2012 he explored heavy metal, then applied electronics to determine the beat.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/19/1853106_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230324192800 +0100" stop="20230324202200 +0100" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Live From the Kennedy Center</title>
<desc lang="fr">Live From the Kennedy Center - When Nas was just 19 years old, he composed what would become one of hip-hop's defining masterpieces, Illmatic. To mark its 20th anniversary, Nas delivers a standout performance alongside the National Symphony Orchestra at Washington DC's Kennedy Center. With conductor Steven Reineke taking the orchestra through arrangements of beats by DJ Premier and Large Professor, Nas delivers impassioned renditions of tracks like &quot;N.Y. State of Mind&quot;, &quot;The World Is Yours&quot;, and &quot;Memory Lane (Sittin' in Da Park)&quot;. Between songs, the program cuts away to both archival and new interview footage to document Nas' rise from Queensbridge upstart to influential rap icon.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/58/1754433_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230324202200 +0100" stop="20230324210000 +0100" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Audience Music</title>
<desc lang="fr">Sofi Tukker - Enjoy ground-breaking concerts, in-depth artist interviews, and unique stories with host Ted Stryker. This concert series gives the audience an intimate view of music's most influential artists today. Shot in 4K, host Ted Stryker interviews musicians across all genres, creating one of the most unique music shows on TV today. This episode features a playful performance of the New York City-based electro-pop duo Sofi Tukker. The duo's name is a stylized merge of the birth names of its members Sophie Hawley-Weld and Tucker Halpern. The two started producing music together in 2014, when they met at Rhode Island's Brown University.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230324210000 +0100" stop="20230324215000 +0100" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Johnny Osbourne &amp; The Homegrown Band</title>
<desc lang="fr">Johnny Osbourne &amp; The Homegrown Band - Johnny Osbourne is one of the most popular Jamaican reggae and dancehall singers of all time. His career began in the late 1960s and reached its peak about 15 years later. His legendary albums, such as Truth and Rights and Folly Rankingi, have cemented his success. After retreating to the shadows until the end of the 1990s, Johnny Osbourne delighted his fans with a big comeback that kicked off at the Garance Reggae Festival in 2012. Since then, his dancehall music has spread around the world, and he's developed compelling collaborations like for the song Independent Music, which he recorded with Chinese Man. Enjoy his 2017 show at Philharmonie de Paris, a high-end production recorded in 4K, and imagine yourself on Jamaican soil!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230324215000 +0100" stop="20230324224900 +0100" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Monty Alexander à La Seine Musicale</title>
<desc lang="fr">Monty Alexander - Kingston-born pianist Monty Alexander is a virtuoso with many secrets. He explores the world of jazz, swing, bebop, blues, calypso and reggae, and has created a style of his own. For him, music is a heartbeat. He plays with emotion, intelligence, humor and sensibility. During this unique performance, we are transported with his joyful swing and fizzing grooves, influenced by Afro-American jazz from Harlem, and reggae from Jamaica. This 2018 concert at the Seine Musical is exceptional. It is extremely rare for Monty Alexander to do a solo performance. We are in for an evening full of surprises.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/10/1995865_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230324224900 +0100" stop="20230324235100 +0100" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Kintsugi</title>
<desc lang="fr">Kintsugi - Kintsugi is made up of three musicians whose eclectic musical backgrounds mix Japanese stories drawn from the depths of time: the epic life of Yoshitsune, sung and played by Kakushin Nishihara, a Tokyo sub-modern and underground artist : the incredible collision between Serge Teyssot-Gay's electric guitar (Noir Désir), Gaspar Claus' cello and the indescribable art of the Japanese Kakushin Nishihara, traditional biwa virtuoso and shamanic singer.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/02/07/27/1762648_A.jpg" />
</programme>