<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Voo -->
<programme start="20230403030000 +0200" stop="20230403040400 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Bloco do O</title>
<desc lang="fr">Bloco do O - Da Pá Virada Sessions - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the bands taking part in this series is Bloco do Ó, a traditional street band associated with the Brazilian carnival. A &quot;bloco&quot; is a group of people who drive through the streets in trucks, playing music and providing fun to anyone who will listen. Immerse yourself in Bloco de Ó's world of cheerful melodies and spectacular costumes!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/19/1853106_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230403040400 +0200" stop="20230403050500 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Runtown : La Machine de Moulin Rouge</title>
<desc lang="fr">Runtown - La Machine de Moulin Rouge - Enjoy Runtown's first concert in Paris, where the Nigerian superstar brings many guests to his show. One of the most talented Nigerian afrobeat scenes will make you rediscover his greatest hits. Nigeria is a very creative country when it comes to the music scene. Runtown is no exception. His first single, &quot;Party Like It's 1980,&quot; paved the way for &quot;Gallardo,&quot; which caught the entire international scene's attention. Runtown's inspiration comes from the greats, from Salif Keita and Fela Kuti to Otis Redding and Bob Marley. An exceptional event not to be missed.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230403050500 +0200" stop="20230403064200 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Hugh Coltman</title>
<desc lang="fr">The English singer and composer Hugh Coltman started in blues rock band The Hoax, after which he moved to Paris and released two pop and folk albums. Jazz was beckoning and his next project was a tribute to singer and pianist Nat &quot;King&quot; Cole. Coltman recorded his album 'Who's Happy?' in New Orleans. With this he makes music of an important life question.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/24/1642181_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230403064200 +0200" stop="20230403073200 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Live with a Boom</title>
<desc lang="fr">Mn'JAM Experiment: Live with a Boom - Imagine that visual arts and music are no longer two separate fields; that musicians no longer focus on their instruments only, but also on the visuals of their performance. Such is the premise of Mn'JAM Experiment! Zoom in on their music and you'll find a mix between empirical and rationally constructed elements; between acoustic, electric and electronic instruments; urban rhythms and traditional melodies, vocal loops and guitar solos, turntables and acoustic drums. Zoom in on the visuals of the performance -they are analogously a product of pre-composed material and live manipulation, mostly carried out by the guy behind the turntables.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230403073200 +0200" stop="20230403082500 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">WOMEX 2018</title>
<desc lang="fr">In 2018 WOMEX took place in Las Palmas in Gran Canaria. One of the participants was The Garifuna Collective. These young and old musicians from the Caribbean keep Andy Palacio's legacy alive.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/28/13/2143305_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230403082500 +0200" stop="20230403090000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">?nied?</title>
<desc lang="fr">Classical:NEXT 2019 - ?nied? - ?nied? is a voice and electronics duo from Warsaw, Poland who combine extended vocal techniques with improvised, self-named &quot;glitchtronica.&quot; Singer, performer, and sound artist Aleksandra Klimczak frequently breaks boundaries between art genres through cooperating with young artists from different artistic fields. Her work has been awarded from scholarships from the Polish Ministry of Culture and the Capital City of Warsaw. Music curator Antoni Beksiak deals with contemporary crossover, ethnic, classical, jazz, and pop music in his work as an initiator, critic and creator. During this showcase recorded at Classical:NEXT 2019 in Rotterdam, The Netherlands the perform a set list of their own works.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/24/07/2123267_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230403090000 +0200" stop="20230403111500 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam</title>
<desc lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam - New Cool Collective is one of the foremost Dutch jazz ensembles. Pioneering new blends of music styles since 1993, NCC has performed in various formations, from small combos to larger ensembles and even big bands! The ensemble's high energy is cut out for the dance floors, as dance, Latin, salsa, afrobeat and boogaloo all meet in a jazzy mix. NCC includes saxophonist Benjamin Herman, guitarist Rory Ronde, drummer Joost Kroon, percussionists Frank van Dok and Jos de Haas, pianist Willem Friede, bassist Leslie Lopez, and trumpeter David Rockefeller.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230403111500 +0200" stop="20230403120900 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">&quot;We Love Ella&quot; : The Amazing Keystone Big Band</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Amazing Keystone Big Band - &quot;We Love Ella&quot; - The Amazing Keystone Big Band performs material from their album &quot;We Love Ella&quot; at this 2019 recording from Salle Pleyel in Paris, France. Led by trombonist Bastien Ballaz, saxophonist Jon Boutellier, pianist Fred Nardin and trumpeter David Enhco, The Amazing Keystone Big Band helps young and adult audiences all over the world discover jazz in all its guises. &quot;We Love Ella&quot; is a reinvention of legendary vocalist Ella Fitzgerald's greatest successes.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/02/1889525_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230403120900 +0200" stop="20230403131300 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">GusGus : Live at Sónar Reykjavik</title>
<desc lang="fr">Gusgus - GusGus was founded in 1995 as a collective of film music creators. After signing a contract with the 4AD label the following year, GusGus became one of the most popular electro formations in Iceland, a status that was cemented internationally by the release of Polydistortion in 1997 Over the next two decades, GusGus explored virtually every sub-genre of electronic music, from house to trance, to techno and trip-hop. Discover GusGus at the Sónar Reykjavík 2018 festival, where founding members Biggi Veira and Daníel Ágúst present the latest album from the band, Lies Are More Flexible. With his exceptional vocal talent, fascinating electronic hacks and subtle arrangements, GusGus promises to impress you.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230403131300 +0200" stop="20230403150100 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Chaka Khan</title>
<desc lang="fr">Chaka Khan - Chaka Khan, also known as the &quot;Queen of Funk,&quot; has sold about 70 million records worldwide in her nearly five-decade-long career. This unique singer masters many musical genres, including R&amp;B, pop, rock, gospel, country, international music, and classical music. For this concert, the 10-times Grammy Award-winning artist returns to her hometown, where she gives the performance of a lifetime to an appreciative audience. With her nine-piece band and three backing vocalists, she performs a smashing selection of her greatest hits, including &quot;I'm Every Woman,&quot; &quot;Ain't Nobody,&quot; and &quot;Tell Me Something Good.&quot; Join this world-famous superstar in this concert recorded at the Harris Theatre in Chicago, filmed in spectacular 4K.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Musique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230403150100 +0200" stop="20230403161700 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">STUFF. Live at BIRD Rotterdam</title>
<desc lang="fr">With their inexhaustible energy, STUFF is impossible to get off the stage! The band was formed in 2012 when drummer Lander Gyselinck was asked by a local bar to make live music between sets of DJs, and he gathered a number of musician friends. The band is considered an avant-garde jazz band that plays a mix of funk, hip-hop and electro. Andrew Claes (saxophone), Dries Laheye (bass guitar), Lander Gyselinck (drummer), Mixmonster Menno (samples) and Joris Caluwaerts (keyboard) share a fabulous musical connection. The eagerness with which the musicians conquer every stage and the great pleasure with which they do so makes the heart of every music lover melt.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/04/2122118_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230403161700 +0200" stop="20230403170000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Null + Void</title>
<desc lang="fr">Null + Void - While few people are familiar with the Null + Void project, many have already heard Kurt Uenala's music. After making his debut under the pseudonym Kap10Kurt in 2003, Uenala caught the attention of the world with the play &quot;Die Sleeping&quot;. This critical and popular success has led to collaborations with several big names in music, including Moby, The Kills, and Dave Gahan, singer of Depeche Mode, for whom Uenala has subsequently signed plays. Spending more and more time in his Manhattan studio, Uenala developed a unique sound made of angular beats and dark soundscapes, which gave rise to a new melancholy solo project called Null + Void. Cryosleep, Uenala's first album under this new banner, includes several titles inspired by retro science fiction, new wave and electronic innovators.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/06/2111709_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230403170000 +0200" stop="20230403175800 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Liam Gallagher</title>
<desc lang="fr">Liam Gallagher - After leading iconic British rock band Oasis for nearly two decades, Manchester-born singer Liam Gallagher launched his solo career in 2016. He played his first ever U.S. solo show on July 28th of 2017 at Manhattan's McKittrick Hotel in New York City. The rather small venue is known to host the immersive theater experience &quot;Sleep No More&quot;, and its limited capacities made for an intense and intimate concert experience. In a 75-minute long show featuring thirteen songs, Gallagher performed tracks of his 2017 debut album As You Were, next to a list of Oasis fan favorites. Shot in phenomenally sharp 4K, this recording offers viewers the unique opportunity to become part of the audience of this secret session.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230403175800 +0200" stop="20230403193800 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Au Théâtre de Villefranche-sur-Saône</title>
<desc lang="fr">Omar Sosa - Quarteto Afrocubano - While always keeping one foot firmly anchored in the traditions of his home country, Cuba, Omar Sosa tirelessly explores music from the Caribbean to India, and West Africa to the Arab world. Since he left Cuba in 1993, the pianist has been blending his Afro-Cuban roots with jazz, hip hop, electro and world music. For his 2018 performance at Théâtre de Villefranche-sur-Saône, he brings to stage his Quarteto Afrocubano members Childo Tomas (electric bass &amp; vocals), Ernesto Simpson (drums), and Leandro Saint-Hill (saxophones, flute, percussion &amp; vocals). Together, they create a riveting instrumental dialogue. Celebrating rhythm in all its forms, this Omar Sosa concert is an intense and mystical experience.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/19/1853106_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230403193800 +0200" stop="20230403201500 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Tagg &amp; Petersen</title>
<desc lang="fr">Classical:NEXT 2019 - Tagg &amp; Petersen - The Kathleen Tagg / Andre Petersen piano duo brings together two of South Africa's most celebrated pianists: one eclectic-experimental classical and one jazz artist, in a unique and highly personal collaboration. Drawing inspiration from the rich sonic tapestries of classical music, nuances of South African jazz and traditional musics from sub-Saharan Africa, this duo explodes the concept of what two pianos can sound like: a bass guitar, goema drum, marimba and uhadi-plus mixing fully composed scores with improvisation in a bold, vital and highly entertaining mix with performances of original compositions and works by iconic South African jazz composers such as Abdullah Ibrahim, Bheki Mseleku and Moses Molelekwa.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/24/07/2123267_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230403201500 +0200" stop="20230403210000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Nilufer Yanya</title>
<desc lang="fr">Echoes Series: Nilufer Yanya - Echoes is a modern live music show hosted by Jehnny Beth (lead singer in the British band Savages). It presents leading and emerging bands and artists from the contemporary scene. The show takes place underneath the Palais de Tokyo museum in Paris, in the club of brutalist architecture, the &quot;Yoyo.&quot; The live sets are 30 minutes long and take place on a customized stage, creating closeness with the audience. The intimate, immersive space lends to the atmosphere of the show. The artistic direction by Antoine Carlier follows a minimalist, refined and pure aesthetic, allowing the artists' energy and emotions to take center stage. This episode features Nilüfer Yanya. Her set includes the songs &quot;The Florist,&quot; &quot;Angels,&quot; and &quot;The Unordained.&quot;.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230403210000 +0200" stop="20230403230900 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Above &amp; Beyond Group Therapy 300</title>
<desc lang="fr">Above &amp; Beyond Group Therapy 300 - Above and Beyond recently made their mark on ABGT300 in an epic way. Live for the 300th edition of Group Therapy Radio, the group broadcast from The Asiaworld-Expo in Hong Kong on September 29, 2018. ABGT300 also saw live performances from Andrew Bayer, Ben Böhmer, Grum, Ilan Bluestone, and Spencer Brown, with the signature set from Above and Beyond as the main event. This year, they wanted to push Group Therapy to the next level. Get ready for some magic moments and excellent music.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230403230900 +0200" stop="20230404000000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Giana Viscardi - New Year's Eve Special</title>
<desc lang="fr">Giana Viscardi - New Year's Eve Special - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the bands taking part in this series is the duo of Giana Viscardi and Gustavo Marques. After starting their career together, Giana Viscardi and Gustavo Marques released music in many places around the world. After returning to Brazil, they worked together on Giana's album &quot;ORUM&quot;, performing in Africa, Europe, and Brazil.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230404000000 +0200" stop="20230404015900 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Tower of Power</title>
<desc lang="fr">Tower of Power - Tower of Power is an American R&amp;B-based horn section and band that has been performing since 1968. The concert shows the legendary band's return to where it all started. Recorded live over two performances at The Fox Theatre in Oakland, Tower of Power celebrates their 50th anniversary with their life-long fans, friends, and family. The lead vocalist in this performance is the electrifying, soulful and compelling Marcus Scott. The show also includes an augmented horn and string section and alumni guests, including Lenny Pickett, Bruce Conte, Chester Thompson, Ray Greene, and Francis &quot;Rocco&quot; Prestia. Celebrate the music of Tower of Power and join these memorable evenings where the band performs their full spectrum of life-affirming funk and soul hits.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>