<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Voo -->
<programme start="20230418030000 +0200" stop="20230418041700 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Bixiga 70 - BIRD 2019</title>
<desc lang="fr">Bixiga 70 - BIRD 2019 - Stemming from Brazil's São Paulo, Bixiga 70 is an exciting brass and percussion-based instrumental dance ensemble that combines jazz, funk, and Afro-Brazilian music, incorporating elements from dub, reggae, electronics, cumbia, carimbo, Ethio-jazz, and samba. The name Bixiga 70 is taken from a vibrant neighbourhood in downtown São Paulo. Organic, ritualistic, and sometimes even primal, the band's music appeals to those who seek out mental and physical freedom.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/33/1977716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230418041700 +0200" stop="20230418050000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">City Beats</title>
<desc lang="fr">City Beats - Episode 1 - London - DJ-producer Carly Foxx is on a musical journey, immersing herself in the life of five iconic European cities to find inspiration for a series of new tracks. In this episode, Carly Foxx steps outside of her comfort zone to draw inspiration for her music track from urban youths in London's grime scene. With fresh eyes, she explores what makes this city unique to the people who live there. Carly interviews people on the street and asks them about the London music scene, which is very lively and diverse. To better understand the urban music scene, Carly pays a visit to RepreZent Radio, where she interviews grime artists. She records street sounds such as a bus driving by, the ticking against a metal door, and police sirens.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Télé-Réalité</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/29/01/2134738_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230418050000 +0200" stop="20230418060100 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Frequencerz @ Airbeat One</title>
<desc lang="fr">Frequencerz @ Airbeat One - Frequencerz is a Dutch hardstyle duo formed by Pepijn Hol and Niels Koster. In 2009, they signed their contract with the Fusion Records label. Since then, they've released a good number of albums, such as Medium Rare, S.T.F.U. / G.T.F.O, and Phaser. With their performances for huge crowds at Defqon.1, Decibel Outdoor, and The Qontinent, they've established themselves as one of the biggest hardstyle acts of today. Their show at the German Airbeat One festival underlines their reputation. Expect nothing but spectacular light shows, non-stop jumpstyle, and a crazy crowd!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230418060100 +0200" stop="20230418073900 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Kyle Eastwood Quintet</title>
<desc lang="fr">Jazz à Ramatuelle: Kyle Eastwood Quintet - Bassist Kyle Eastwood (1968) is an explorer, equally at ease with jazz melodies as with pop songs. In the late 1970s, his father Clint took him to see his first jazz concert - a Count Basie performance. Eastwood Jr. was in awe of the drummer and wanted to play an instrument himself. It so happened he wasn't so much interested in jazz, preferring rhythm and blues, Motown and Stax records, funk groups, and North African and Indian music. Eastwood became a brilliant bassist and the composer of highly original soundtracks. His 2015 album &quot;Time Pieces&quot; is a collaboration with brilliant British musicians, such as trumpeter Quentin Collins and saxophonist Brandon Allen. In this broadcast, Eastwood and his fellow musicians revisit the hard bop legacy of Blue Note Records.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/19/1853106_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230418073900 +0200" stop="20230418081200 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Ruben Hein &amp; NJJO : Jazz in Duketown</title>
<desc lang="fr">Ruben Hein &amp; NJJO - Jazz in Duketown - Jazz in Duketown is the largest free outdoor jazz festival in the Netherlands. It's a real gathering for jazz addicts, inviting internationally renowned artists. One of them is Dutch singer, pianist, composer and bandleader Ruben Hein. Widely praised for his warm and characteristic voice and his offbeat piano playing, Ruben Hein is the artistic director and conductor of the National Youth Jazz Orchestra (NJJO). At Jazz in Duketown he performs a jazzy set, accompanied by his 18 finest proteges.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/01/01/2153368_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230418081200 +0200" stop="20230418090000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">WOMEX 2018</title>
<desc lang="fr">Mario Batkovic - WOMEX 2018 - Since 1994, World Music Expo (WOMEX) has been attracting musicians, agents, a great number of press agencies, as well as media companies from all over the world. Its main exposition event has been held in various locations throughout Europe, including Berlin, Brussels, Marseille, Stockholm, Seville, Cardiff, and Budapest. The 2018 edition of WOMEX was held in Las Palmas, Gran Canaria. One of its showcase participants, Mario Batkovic, aims to explore the sonic possibilities of the accordion, without effects or loops, rather through a mutualist symbiotic relationship between man and instrument. Challenging, hypnotic, and grandiose, Batkovic's single-handed symphonic vision is certainly unique.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/29/16/2143305_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230418090000 +0200" stop="20230418100200 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Maceo Plex - Audio Obscura x Rijksmuseum</title>
<desc lang="fr">Audio Obscura x Rijksmuseum - The American DJ/producer - known for his enigmatic combinations of grooving, melancholic and ecstatic house and techno - visited the museum for some ground-level inspiration, and will share this during this once a lifetime event under the ever so stunning Rijksmuseum. This is the first time the museum collaborates on a project that revolves around electronic music, matching its vision to inspire visitors and to let them experience art in exciting new ways Initiated by Audio Obscura, this is the next step in connecting world-class artists with legendary, historical locations.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230418100200 +0200" stop="20230418105400 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Giana Viscardi</title>
<desc lang="fr">Giana Viscardi - Da Pá Virada Sessions - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the bands taking part in this series is the duo of Giana Viscardi and Gustavo Marques. After starting their career together, Giana Viscardi and Gustavo Marques released music in many places around the world. After returning to Brazil, they worked together on Giana's album &quot;ORUM&quot;, performing in Africa, Europe, and Brazil. In this episode, Giana Viscardi and Gustavo Marques perform conductor and arranger Letieres Leite's arrangements of their work.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230418105400 +0200" stop="20230418123100 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Moderat at Stereolux 2016</title>
<desc lang="fr">Moderat at Stereolux 2016 - Since the German bands Modeselektor (Gernot Bronsert and Sebastian Szary) and Apparat (Sascha Ring) joined forces in 2009, they have been hugely successful as the electronic music supergroup Moderat. In 2012, the formation produced the soundtrack of Xavier Dolan's film Laurence Anyways, released as A New Error. According to Les Inrockuptibles, their album II includes &quot;the rhythmic punch of the one (Modeselektor) and atmospheric finesse of the other (Apparat) combine perfectly.&quot; In 2016, the threesome returned with an eagerly anticipated third album, III, which they present in this program, live on stage at Stereolux in Nantes, France.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230418123100 +0200" stop="20230418131900 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">WOMEX 2018</title>
<desc lang="fr">In 2018 WOMEX took place in Las Palmas in Gran Canaria. One of the participants was Ladama, five multi-instrumentalists from Venezuela, Brazil, Colombia and the United States. In addition to their performances as a band, the five women work with workshops and other collaborations to enthuse the youth for music, composition and audio editing. Ladama is a positive force in times when the need for tolerance and communication is greater than ever.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/29/16/2143305_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230418131900 +0200" stop="20230418142000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Mestrinho</title>
<desc lang="fr">Mestrinho - Da Pá Virada Sessions - Da Pá Virada sessions bring the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the artists taking part in this series is accordionist Mestrinho, seen in performance with Cainã Cavalcante on guitar, Alex Buck on drums, and Carlinhos Noronha on bass. They combine the subtle rhythms of Brazilian music with the leader's instrumental virtuosity.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/19/1853106_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230418142000 +0200" stop="20230418150300 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Jeditah</title>
<desc lang="fr">Classical:NEXT 2019 - Jeditah - Jeditah is an experimental songwriter, producer and singer from Amsterdam. She works with Brendan Jan Walsh on cello and Jordy Pama on synths and electronics. From an early age on, Jeditah has been immersed in the world of music, travelling with her parents as a music collective. She finds inspiration in the works of acclaimed artists like Björk, James Blake, Laurie Anderson and PJ Harvey. When she began experimenting with making her own music, she first only utilized her own voice, lowering and altering it, and eventually adding electronic beats and synths. With Electric AlleyCat, Jeditah has established her position as a singer and songwriter. In between performing and recording with the band, she creates layered soundscapes from old recordings and homemade samples.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/24/07/2123267_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230418150300 +0200" stop="20230418163300 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Lee Ranaldo</title>
<desc lang="fr">Lee Ranaldo - After being one of the pillars of Sonic Youth, Lee Ranaldo released the solo album Electric Trim. The album was recorded in Barcelona and New York, with a dream-team including producer Raul Refree Fernandez, singer Sharon Van Etten, and guitarist/composer Nels Cline. To top it off, Lee Ranaldo collaborated with New York author Jonathan Lethem for the lyrics of most of the album's songs. Enjoy this special occasion and watch the 4K recording of Electric Trim at the French theatre L'Epicerie Moderne in 2018. This free-minded musician will surprise you with a unique blend of psychedelic music and folk rock!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230418163300 +0200" stop="20230418173300 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Paulo Novaes</title>
<desc lang="fr">Paulo Novaes - Da Pá Virada Sessions - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the artists taking part in this series is Paulo Novaes. Coming from a family of musicians, Paulo Novaes has already lived through a lifetime of music in spite of his young age. Paulo is the cousin of singer Bruna Caram, with whom he performed in São Paulo, Madrid, Barcelona, Lisbon, and other major cities. As a singer, composer, and instrumentalist, his creativity is enjoyed in many forms.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230418173300 +0200" stop="20230418194600 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam</title>
<desc lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam - New Cool Collective is one of the foremost Dutch jazz ensembles. Pioneering new blends of music styles since 1993, NCC has performed in various formations, from small combos to larger ensembles and even big bands! The ensemble's high energy is cut out for the dance floors, as dance, Latin, salsa, afrobeat and boogaloo all meet in a jazzy mix. NCC includes saxophonist Benjamin Herman, guitarist Rory Ronde, drummer Joost Kroon, percussionists Frank van Dok and Jos de Haas, pianist Willem Friede, bassist Leslie Lopez, and trumpeter David Rockefeller.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230418194600 +0200" stop="20230418210000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Altin Gün : Bird, Rotterdam</title>
<desc lang="fr">Mediterranean sounds meet western music in this performance by the band Altin Gün. Their unusual approach to traditional Turkish folk music produces an overall sound full of ethnic, funky, and even psychedelic influences. With their infinite energy, Altin Gün takes the audience on an amazing sonic roller coaster: a ride full of emotion and fun. Altin Gün consists of six talented musicians who share a great passion for Turkish music. In this live recording from BIRD Rotterdam, one of the Netherlands' most important music venues, the band presents their new album &quot;On&quot; to the enthusiastic audience.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/19/1975203_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230418210000 +0200" stop="20230418223700 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Opera Imaginaire</title>
<desc lang="fr">Opera Imaginaire - To celebrate Le Concert Spirituel's 30th anniversary, conductor Hervé Niquet collaborated with the Baroque Music Center of Versailles to build his opéra imaginaire. For this unique project, Le Concert Spirituel presents an original performance of unpublished operas by Lully, Rameau, Charpentier, and many other French baroque composers. You will find yourself captivated by a tearful lover, intrigued by the passage to the underworld, and fascinated by the descents of the Gods. The program includes many favorite passages, such as Lully's Armide, Charpentier's Medea, and Campra's Carnaval de Venise. Experience all the magic of Louis XIV's French opera as Le Concert Spirituel transforms the Théâtre des Champs-Elysées into a true French baroque scene.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/03/1781759_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230418223700 +0200" stop="20230418233800 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Johnny Marr - Rock en Seine</title>
<desc lang="fr">Johnny Marr at Rock en Seine 2019 - English musician, songwriter, and singer Johnny Marr has enjoyed an exemplary career since his former band The Smiths split up in 1987. His distinctive guitar sound has been part of such varied groups as The Pretenders, The Cribs, Modest Mouse, and Electronic, the group he co-founded with Bernard Sumner of New Order. Now a living legend, Johnny Marr showcases his incredible singer-songwriter talents on each new album. His recent, hit-packed release Call The Comet (2018) gave us &quot;The Tracers&quot; and &quot;Hi Hello,&quot; and his live performances - which usually include some songs from his days with The Smiths - always hit the mark. Enjoy this 2019 show recorded at Rock en Seine in Paris!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/07/19/2123266_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230418233800 +0200" stop="20230419004200 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Frederico Heliodoro</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Da Pá Virada Sessions series portrays the best musicians in Brazilian jazz today. All sessions were recorded in São Paulo and offer a unique experience, offering a fresh look at the Brazilian music scene. The artists have been selected together with the music editor of Stingray DJAZZ. Among the bands featured in this series is Caixa Cubo. Typically, this versatile trio explores the rhythmically rich Brazilian landscapes, combining them with modern Brazilian jazz trends. For this program, however, Caixa Cubo works together with vocalist Zé Leônidas, with a special repertoire that has been put together with Dani Gurgel from Da Pá Virada Sessions and Rokas Ku?inskas from Stingray DJAZZ.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/07/54/1626400_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230419004200 +0200" stop="20230419015300 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Omer Avital Qantar - Jazz in Duketown</title>
<desc lang="fr">Jazz in Duketown is the largest free open-air jazz festival in the Netherlands. Jazz fanatics and other music lovers eagerly look forward to the performances of the many internationally renowned artists every year. In 2019 Israeli-American double bass player Omer Avital is one of them. Together with his quintet, consisting of saxophonists Asaf Yuria and Alexander Levin, drummer Ofri Nehemya and pianist Eden Ladin, he performs a strong repertoire from his album 'Qantar': vibrantly energetic, idiosyncratic jazz with oriental influences.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>