<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Voo -->
<programme start="20230522030000 +0200" stop="20230522040700 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Amilton Godoy</title>
<desc lang="fr">Amilton Godoy - Da Pá Virada Sessions - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the artists taking part in this series is pianist Amilton Godoy. He is not only a well-known soloist in his homeland Brazil, but he is also considered one of the world's greatest pianists today, regularly guesting with international top orchestras and conductors. Godoy frequently teaches workshops throughout Brazil and abroad.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230522040700 +0200" stop="20230522045900 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Cabaret Contemporain</title>
<desc lang="fr">Cabaret Contemporain - &quot;Cabaret Contemporain&quot;: an explosive performance by musicians, composers, and improvisers who cross all musical boundaries with an innovative approach to the world of sound. Transforming life into dream and music into dance, the acoustic instruments are processed through an electronic filter which combines musical genres and codes. This performance is animated by the search for a new vocabulary of sounds. Enjoy this stunning live performance at the Suona Francese Festival in Rome's amazing Maxxi museum! Featuring Fabrizio Rat (piano), Giani Caserotto (guitar), Ronan Courty (bass), and Simon Drappier (bass).</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230522045900 +0200" stop="20230522063800 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Jazz à Ramatuelle : Omar Sosa</title>
<desc lang="fr">Jazz à Ramatuelle: Omar Sosa - Experience the incredible richness of our world's music in this performance by the unparalleled Afro-Cuban pianist Omar Sosa! Whilst staying true to Cuban music traditions, Sosa shows an insatiable curiosity: tirelessly exploring music from around the world - from the Caribbean to India and from West Africa to the Arab World - nothing seems to escape his thirst for discovery. A celebration of rhythm in all its forms, this Omar Sosa concert from the French Ramatuelle Jazz Festival promises an intense mystical experience!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230522063800 +0200" stop="20230522072000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">City Beats</title>
<desc lang="fr">City Beats - Episode 2 - Ibiza - DJ-producer Carly Foxx is on a musical journey, immersing herself in the life of five iconic European cities to find inspiration for a series of new tracks. In this episode, Carly Foxx travels to the world's clubbing capital to inspire her music track and discovers Ibiza's alternative spiritual side. She starts her journey in San Antonio but discovers this place is mainly about clubbing and drinking - not very inspiring for her music track. The next stop is Old Town, where Carly meets female Ibiza singer Sam Smith, who introduces her to DJ and producer Manu Gonzalez. While talking to him, Carly decides the base of her Ibiza-inspired track should be a Balearic beat, to which she plans to add bongos and castanet samples.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Télé-Réalité</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/12/00/2155262_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230522072000 +0200" stop="20230522082100 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Robin Schulz, Sam Feldt, Afrojack &amp; Alle Farben - Parookaville</title>
<desc lang="fr">Parookaville - Parookaville is a city that comes to life once a year to keep the legend of Bill Parooka alive. It was started as an artistic, free-flowing, wild, and musical place where people could connect with their pure selves, experience real connections, and feel a deep sense of bliss and fulfillment. Step into the darkness if you dare, follow your inner light and immerse yourself in a spectacular world of freedom and love! Only four years since the first event, this festival has already become one of Germany's most prevalent music festivals. This edition features Armin van Buuren, Showtek, Robin Schulz, and W&amp;W.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230522082100 +0200" stop="20230522090000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Audience Music</title>
<desc lang="fr">Urban Cone - Watch groundbreaking concerts, in-depth artist interviews, and stories with host Ted Stryker. This concert series gives the audience an intimate view of music's most influential artists today. Shot in 4K, Stryker interviews musicians across all genres, creating the most unique music show on TV today. This episode features the Swedish indie pop band Urban Cone. The band was formed in 2010 by Emil Gustafsson, Tim Formgren, Rasmus Flyckt, Jacob William Sjöberg, and Magnus Folkö. Their debut EP Our Youth came about when they were only 16 years old. The album was recorded in Flyckt's living room. The album's debut single &quot;Urban Photograph&quot; reached #2 on Hype Machine. A tour to the U.S. followed, with performances in New York City, Brooklyn, Los Angeles, and San Francisco.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/58/1754433_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230522090000 +0200" stop="20230522111500 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam</title>
<desc lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam - New Cool Collective is one of the foremost Dutch jazz ensembles. Pioneering new blends of music styles since 1993, NCC has performed in various formations, from small combos to larger ensembles and even big bands! The ensemble's high energy is cut out for the dance floors, as dance, Latin, salsa, afrobeat and boogaloo all meet in a jazzy mix. NCC includes saxophonist Benjamin Herman, guitarist Rory Ronde, drummer Joost Kroon, percussionists Frank van Dok and Jos de Haas, pianist Willem Friede, bassist Leslie Lopez, and trumpeter David Rockefeller.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230522111500 +0200" stop="20230522121400 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">The Bloody Beetroots</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Bloody Beetroots - The Bloody Beetroots is the creation of Sir Bob Cornelius Rifo. Inspired by his lifelong love of punk rock and comic books, Rifo unleashed The Bloody Beetroots in late 2006 and has since crafted an intense sound that mixes his classical training, his punk rock obsession, and his passion for electronic music into an edgy rock-meets-dance hybrid sound. In 2019, The Bloody Beetroots released the Heavy EP, which sees Rifo revisiting his classic electro style and features collaborations with Ephwurd and Dr. Fresch, in addition to three new solo originals. Enjoy his show at Nameless Music Festival 2019!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230522121400 +0200" stop="20230522131500 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Fedde Le Grand</title>
<desc lang="fr">Fedde Le Grand - DJ Fedde Le Grand plays his set at the Keukenhof, the Netherlands' exhibition of tulips, during the SLAM! Quarantaine Festival. This festival is a collaboration between the biggest Dutch DJs and radio channel SLAM. The DJs play on extraordinary locations, such as the Keukenhof, where Fedde Le Grand presents his set. The setlist features songs such as &quot;Deep In My Soul,&quot; &quot;JB's The Man,&quot; &quot;Smoke Machine,&quot; and &quot;You Should Know.&quot; Shots of Fedde Le Grand and his DJ table alternate with images of the beautiful colorful tulip fields at the Keukenhof.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230522131500 +0200" stop="20230522150600 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Chaka Khan</title>
<desc lang="fr">Chaka Khan - Chaka Khan, also known as the &quot;Queen of Funk,&quot; has sold about 70 million records worldwide in her nearly five-decade-long career. This unique singer masters many musical genres, including R&amp;B, pop, rock, gospel, country, international music, and classical music. For this concert, the 10-times Grammy Award-winning artist returns to her hometown, where she gives the performance of a lifetime to an appreciative audience. With her nine-piece band and three backing vocalists, she performs a smashing selection of her greatest hits, including &quot;I'm Every Woman,&quot; &quot;Ain't Nobody,&quot; and &quot;Tell Me Something Good.&quot; Join this world-famous superstar in this concert recorded at the Harris Theatre in Chicago, filmed in spectacular 4K.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Musique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230522150600 +0200" stop="20230522162200 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Chloé - Trabendo Paris</title>
<desc lang="fr">Chloé - Trabendo Paris - Chloé has, without a doubt, led an entire generation to her electronic music playground - one that goes beyond strictly club and techno. As much a film music enthusiast as an accomplished guitar player, she stumbled into the electronic scene early on, developing an unwavering curiosity for sound machines. Chloé is a composer, and she gives life to artistic ideas. The challenge is to stay unwavering in spite of self-doubt that arises throughout the creative process. It is precisely this inner questioning, this contradiction, that nourishes and motivates Chloé's work. Chloé dedicates a full set to her 2017 album Endless Revisions. At Trabendo Paris, she plays these brand-new songs only a few weeks after the album was released.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/59/1769392_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230522162200 +0200" stop="20230522170600 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">BIRD</title>
<desc lang="fr">BIRD - Five promising musicians get together in Rotterdam jazz club BIRD's artists-in-residence project &quot;The Nest&quot;. In this first broadcast we get to know Lisette Ma Neza (slam poet), Peter Somuah (trumpet), Michelle Samba (drums), Huy Le (bass), and Brenn Luiten (piano). Over the course of seven sessions, they exchange ideas, work on their projects, and play music together. Following this period, during which record producer Jameszoo and music manager Jochem Tromp offer their coaching experience, BIRD and North Sea Jazz Festival's fringe festival DownTown organize a tryout performance. Enjoy this unique collaboration of upcoming musicians!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/02/18/24/2148521_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230522170600 +0200" stop="20230522180500 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Nile Rodgers</title>
<desc lang="fr">The popular music performance series Front and Center premiered nationwide on public television in 2016, and now returns for Season 6. The series boasts 22, one-hour episodes and an all-star line-up. This episode features Nile Rodgers. He started his musical career by the end of the '60s. A decade later, he scored a hit with Chic's debut single &quot;Dance Dance Dance,&quot; followed by &quot;Le Freak&quot; from the second album C'est Chic. At Front and Center, Nile Rodgers performs his most well-known songs such as &quot;Get Lucky&quot; and &quot;We Are Family.&quot; In between the songs, Nile Rodgers shares personal stories about his dreams and how they have come true. Enjoy this intimate Front and Center show!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/58/1754433_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230522180500 +0200" stop="20230522194300 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Meute</title>
<desc lang="fr">Meute - When the bass sounds and the confetti explodes, there is no doubt that Meute is a different kind of band. The band creates a whole new genre by mixing fanfare music with hypnotic techno. Meute liberates electronic music of the classic model of the DJ console. This group breaks the codes by provoking a real interaction with the audience, who will be unable to do anything but stomp their feet. This brass and percussion ensemble revolutionizes techno music while ultimately bringing it back to its roots. The eleven musicians in their iconic red jackets have already taken over the biggest festivals in Europe! Watch them on Festival 4K with their show at Trianon Paris, 2019.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230522194300 +0200" stop="20230522201700 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Nilüfer Yanya - Echoes Series: Nilufer Yanya</title>
<desc lang="fr">Echoes Series: Billy Nomates - Echoes is a modern live music show hosted by Jehnny Beth (lead singer in the British band Savages). It presents leading and emerging bands and artists from the contemporary scene. The show takes place underneath the Palais de Tokyo museum in Paris, in the club of brutalist architecture, the &quot;Yoyo.&quot; The live sets are 30 minutes long and take place on a customized stage, creating closeness with the audience. The intimate, immersive space lends to the atmosphere of the show. The artistic direction by Antoine Carlier follows a minimalist, refined and pure aesthetic, allowing the artists' energy and emotions to take center stage. This episode features Billy Nomates. Her set includes the songs &quot;Happy Misery,&quot; &quot;Wild Arena,&quot; and &quot;Call in Sick.&quot;.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/03/1754401_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230522201700 +0200" stop="20230522210000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Ensemble Offspring</title>
<desc lang="fr">Ensemble Offspring - Ensemble Offspring is Australia's foremost new music ensemble, based in Sydney, made up of flute, clarinet, violin, cello, piano, and percussion. At Classical:NEXT, the ensemble features a line-up of internationally acclaimed core instrumentalists, Claire Edwardes (percussionist/artistic director), Zubin Kanga (piano), Jason Noble (clarinet), and Lamorna Nightingale (flute). With a 23-year history, the group embraces all modes of adventurous music making, which has brought to fruition the creation of over 200 new works. The 2019 Classical:Next showcase programme Solitude features two works written for the ensemble by Kate Moore (&quot;Fern&quot;) and Andrea Keller (&quot;Love in Solitude&quot;).</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/49/1767496_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230522210000 +0200" stop="20230522230800 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Hardwell and the Metropole Orchestra - Symphony</title>
<desc lang="fr">Hardwell and the Metropole Orchestra - Symphony - During &quot;Symphony: The Global Revolution of Dance,&quot; the global sensation DJ Hardwell, with the world's leading pop and jazz orchestra, The Metropole Orchestra, take the audience on a musical journey through the history of dance music. The spectacular show of legendary DJ and the Metropole Orchestra is characterized by the composition of different music periods, from the '80s to the present. The show features hits from various world stars like Donna Summer, Tiësto, Carl Cox, and Daft Punk.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/21/1756184_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230522230800 +0200" stop="20230523000900 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Isle of Wight 2018: Part II</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Isle of Wight Festival, held in Newport, England is a rock-pop music festival that annually serves as the first major event opening the British festival summer. The tradition of the festival first saw the light of day in 1969, opening eleven days after the closing of legendary Woodstock and was regarded as the European counterpart to the legendary &quot;counterculture&quot; festival. In 1970, its line-up was stars-studded with gigs by Jimi Hendrix, The Who, The Doors, Joni Mitchell, Supertramp, Leonard Cohen and many more, establishing the name of the festival. In 2002, the festival was revived after 30 years of silence and brought back the sounds of contemporary musical legends to the Isle of Wight.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/42/1870646_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230523000900 +0200" stop="20230523015400 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Leçons de ténèbres, de Michel-Richard de Lalande</title>
<desc lang="fr">Lalande - Leçons de ténèbres - Harpsichordist and organist Sébastien Daucé conducts Ensemble Correspondances and soloist Sophie Karthäuser (soprano) in a performance of Michel-Richard de Lalande's (1657-1726) sacred music piece Les Leçons des Ténèbres ('lessons of darkness'). To round off the period of Lent leading up to Easter, the congregation sings these Lamentations of Jeremiah in church. With each psalm, one of the candles is extinguished until complete darkness and silence ensues. Whatever one's faith, this tradition is a unique spiritual experience. French baroque composer Michel-Richard de Lalande, an important composer of &quot;grands&quot; motets of unprecedented length, was one of many who wrote music for this religious practice. This performance was recorded at Chapelle Corneille in Rouen, France in 2016.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/21/1756184_A.jpg" />
</programme>