<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Voo -->
<programme start="20230529030000 +0200" stop="20230529040400 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">La Fraîcheur</title>
<desc lang="fr">La Fraîcheur - For over a decade now, first in Paris, then Montreal and now in Berlin, La Fraîcheur has been brewing her blend of deep house and techno beats, making a name for herself with her signature sound of emotionally charged and acid techno sets. The queer feminist-activist is a marathon DJ who can go on for countless hours, running the gamut from classics to new songs released just hours earlier. Her craft expanded by producing music ranging from ravy epic techno to dark pumping electro, spacious open-air deep house to melancholic electronica. She wrote her critically acclaimed debut album during an artist residency with the Berlin-Detroit Connection.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/59/1769392_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230529040400 +0200" stop="20230529050300 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Andre Marques</title>
<desc lang="fr">Andre Marques - Da Pá Virada Sessions - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the artists taking part in this series is pianist, composer, and arranger André Marques. He has been building a solid career, releasing his music with numerous groups: he is a member of the Latin Grammy-nominated Trio Curupira, the André Marques Sexteto, and he leads the Brazilian music orchestra Vintena Brasileira. In this episode of Da Pá Virada Sessions, André Marques performs an intimate solo piano recital.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230529050300 +0200" stop="20230529064000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Moderat at Stereolux 2016</title>
<desc lang="fr">Moderat at Stereolux 2016 - Since the German bands Modeselektor (Gernot Bronsert and Sebastian Szary) and Apparat (Sascha Ring) joined forces in 2009, they have been hugely successful as the electronic music supergroup Moderat. In 2012, the formation produced the soundtrack of Xavier Dolan's film Laurence Anyways, released as A New Error. According to Les Inrockuptibles, their album II includes &quot;the rhythmic punch of the one (Modeselektor) and atmospheric finesse of the other (Apparat) combine perfectly.&quot; In 2016, the threesome returned with an eagerly anticipated third album, III, which they present in this program, live on stage at Stereolux in Nantes, France.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230529064000 +0200" stop="20230529072300 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">WOMEX 2018</title>
<desc lang="fr">Kim So Ra - WOMEX 2018 - Since 1994, World Music Expo (WOMEX) has been attracting musicians, agents, a great number of press agencies, as well as media companies from all over the world. Its main exposition event has been held in various locations throughout Europe, including Berlin, Brussels, Marseille, Stockholm, Seville, Cardiff, and Budapest. In 2018, WOMEX was held in Las Palmas, Gran Canaria. One of its showcase participants, Korean percussionist Kim So Ra, has played the hourglass-shaped, two-headed drum known as janggu since she was a child. Quietly, she has been taking revolutionary steps to modernize perceptions within traditional Korean music.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/29/16/2143305_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230529072300 +0200" stop="20230529082500 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Frequencerz @ Airbeat One</title>
<desc lang="fr">Frequencerz @ Airbeat One - Frequencerz is a Dutch hardstyle duo formed by Pepijn Hol and Niels Koster. In 2009, they signed their contract with the Fusion Records label. Since then, they've released a good number of albums, such as Medium Rare, S.T.F.U. / G.T.F.O, and Phaser. With their performances for huge crowds at Defqon.1, Decibel Outdoor, and The Qontinent, they've established themselves as one of the biggest hardstyle acts of today. Their show at the German Airbeat One festival underlines their reputation. Expect nothing but spectacular light shows, non-stop jumpstyle, and a crazy crowd!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230529082500 +0200" stop="20230529090000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Eleanor Dubinsky - Nublu 2019</title>
<desc lang="fr">The music of vocalist, guitarist and cellist Eleanor Dubinsky lives on the narrow ledge where jazz, international music and pop meet emotionally heartfelt songwriting. The musician and her versatile band deliver dynamic compositions that explore the fragile link between human emotions and human responsibility. The core of Eleanor's artistic mission is to enter into dialogue and achieve self-realization through music.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230529090000 +0200" stop="20230529111500 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam</title>
<desc lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam - New Cool Collective is one of the foremost Dutch jazz ensembles. Pioneering new blends of music styles since 1993, NCC has performed in various formations, from small combos to larger ensembles and even big bands! The ensemble's high energy is cut out for the dance floors, as dance, Latin, salsa, afrobeat and boogaloo all meet in a jazzy mix. NCC includes saxophonist Benjamin Herman, guitarist Rory Ronde, drummer Joost Kroon, percussionists Frank van Dok and Jos de Haas, pianist Willem Friede, bassist Leslie Lopez, and trumpeter David Rockefeller.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230529111500 +0200" stop="20230529121500 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Isle of Wight 2018: Part I</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Isle of Wight Festival, held in Newport, England is a rock-pop music festival that annually serves as the first major event opening the British festival summer. The tradition of the festival first saw the light of day in 1969, opening eleven days after the closing of legendary Woodstock and was regarded as the European counterpart to the legendary &quot;counterculture&quot; festival. In 1970, its line-up was stars-studded with gigs by Jimi Hendrix, The Who, The Doors, Joni Mitchell, Supertramp, Leonard Cohen and many more, establishing the name of the festival. In 2002, the festival was revived after 30 years of silence and brought back the sounds of contemporary musical legends to the Isle of Wight.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/42/1870646_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230529121500 +0200" stop="20230529131700 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Trio Macaiba</title>
<desc lang="fr">Trio Macaiba - Da Pá Virada Sessions - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the bands taking part in this series is Trio Macaíba, consisting of Beto Corrêa (accordion), Cléber Almeida (zabumba, a type of bass drum), and Ramon Vieira (triangle). Their use of a traditional instrument combination, as well as cultural research, which all members of the group are dedicated to, contributes to the authenticity of the music and their experience as musicians.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230529131700 +0200" stop="20230529143200 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Oumou Sangaré @ Jazz Sous Les Pommiers</title>
<desc lang="fr">Salif Keita described her as the &quot;Tina Turner of Mali.&quot; Indeed, Oumou Sangaré is one of Africa's most important female voices. While maintaining her political views as a champion of women's rights in Africa, her vocal talent has brought this singer to shine at some of the most important venues around the world. At Jazz Sous Les Pommiers 2017, Oumou Sangaré presents her latest album, Mogoya. She is accompanied by a group that combines traditional African instruments with a modern band set-up, featuring young French musicians. Recorded in spectacular 4K in a beautiful musical setting, Sangaré will surely make you sing and dance!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230529143200 +0200" stop="20230529150300 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Wild Youth</title>
<desc lang="fr">Songbook - &quot;I never heard anyone say that, and yeah, I know exactly what it means. It has to go in there, this has to be a song.&quot; Every song has its own story, and we all think it's a story we've heard before, but we haven't. Songbook finds and captures these intriguing stories by pulling you into the process of writing and composing. Known for its pristine sound, cinematic 4k video and eye for detail, Songbook live-captured episodes emphasize the paramount importance of quality. It addresses the on-the-spot elements of blending song and location at the right moment. Both the magical location and remarkable music interaction will get the attention they deserve. Simply because Songbook isn't just a live music session, it lives. This episode of Songbook showcases the upbeat pop-rock sound of Dublin-based Wild Youth.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/04/2122118_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230529150300 +0200" stop="20230529162100 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Lalah Hathaway</title>
<desc lang="fr">Lalah Hathaway - Sing Jazz 2018 - Winner of five Grammys in four consecutive years, including the Grammy for best R&amp;B album in 2017, Lalah Hathaway is a force impossible to ignore. The American artist has shared the scene with Prince, Snoop Dogg, Stevie Wonder, Anita Baker, Mary J. Blige, Frank Ocean and many others, an irrefutable proof of her keen musical sense and enormous talent. With a 26-year career, Hathaway is still highly sought after by the biggest names in music. See her transform the 2018 Sing Jazz festival scene into a real R&amp;B club, where she flaunts her voice and stage presence out of the ordinary.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/19/1853106_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230529162100 +0200" stop="20230529170800 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Etenesh Wassie Trio : WOMEX 2018</title>
<desc lang="fr">In 2018 WOMEX took place in Las Palmas in Gran Canaria. One of the participants was the Ethiopian diva Etenesh Wassie with her trio. She mixes the contemporary energy of jazz and punk with her in-depth knowledge of the Ethiopian repertoire. The result is compelling, inspired, and truly unique.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/29/16/2143305_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230529170800 +0200" stop="20230529180100 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Tribute to Gilberto Gil</title>
<desc lang="fr">Tribute to Gilberto Gil - Da Pá Virada Sessions - The series Da Pá Virada sessions presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the bands taking part in this series is Caixa Cubo. This trio usually explores Brazil's rhythmically rich landscapes, combining them with modern Brazilian jazz trends. Yet in this singular performance, Caixa Cubo teams up with vocalist Zé Leônidas, selecting special repertoire together with Dani Gurgel from Da Pá Virada Sessions and Rokas Ku?inskas from Stingray DJAZZ.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230529180100 +0200" stop="20230529193400 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Antonio Faraò</title>
<desc lang="fr">Jazz à Ramatuelle: Antonio Faraò - In 1998, Antonio Faraò won the prestigious Concours Martial Solal, awarded to him by Herbie Hancock! Since then, this talented Italian jazz pianist has made his mark as a player of elegance and lyricism, which has allowed him to collaborate with the best European and American musicians. On his last album &quot;Evan&quot;, recorded in the United States, he leads an all-star band starring Joe Lovano on tenor saxophone. On a beautiful summer night at the French Jazz à Ramatuelle festival, Faraò performs at the breathtaking Theatre de Verdure in the company of saxophone legend Dave Liebman. With refined ballads, a feline groove, elegance, and lyricism, this musical meeting sparkles - if you watch closely you might even see some bright new stars lighting up in the night sky above Ramatuelle!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/35/1763357_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230529193400 +0200" stop="20230529201500 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">City Beats</title>
<desc lang="fr">City Beats - Episode 5 - Amsterdam - DJ-producer Carly Foxx is on a musical journey, immersing herself in the life of five iconic European cities to find inspiration for a series of new tracks. In this episode, Carly Foxx travels to Amsterdam to influence her music track and discovers it is a lot more experimental than she imagined. After exploring the streets of Amsterdam and interviewing passersby, Carly meets up with Steim director Dick Rijken. He and his students design electronic instruments that encourage experimentation. She records various instruments and adds them to her track. Then, in the central library, Carly finds a young pianist who plays his compositions for her to record. After that, Carly travels to the North of Amsterdam to meet with DJ David Leese, who introduces her to the Amsterdam clubbing scene.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Télé-Réalité</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/20/02/2135485_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230529201500 +0200" stop="20230529210000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">WOMEX 2018</title>
<desc lang="fr">Mario Batkovic - WOMEX 2018 - Since 1994, World Music Expo (WOMEX) has been attracting musicians, agents, a great number of press agencies, as well as media companies from all over the world. Its main exposition event has been held in various locations throughout Europe, including Berlin, Brussels, Marseille, Stockholm, Seville, Cardiff, and Budapest. The 2018 edition of WOMEX was held in Las Palmas, Gran Canaria. One of its showcase participants, Mario Batkovic, aims to explore the sonic possibilities of the accordion, without effects or loops, rather through a mutualist symbiotic relationship between man and instrument. Challenging, hypnotic, and grandiose, Batkovic's single-handed symphonic vision is certainly unique.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/29/16/2143305_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230529210000 +0200" stop="20230529230800 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Hardwell and the Metropole Orchestra - Symphony</title>
<desc lang="fr">Hardwell and the Metropole Orchestra - Symphony - During &quot;Symphony: The Global Revolution of Dance,&quot; the global sensation DJ Hardwell, with the world's leading pop and jazz orchestra, The Metropole Orchestra, take the audience on a musical journey through the history of dance music. The spectacular show of legendary DJ and the Metropole Orchestra is characterized by the composition of different music periods, from the '80s to the present. The show features hits from various world stars like Donna Summer, Tiësto, Carl Cox, and Daft Punk.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/21/1756184_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230529230800 +0200" stop="20230530000900 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Green Velvet, MK, Carl Cox &amp; deadmau5</title>
<desc lang="fr">Creamfields - Having burst onto the ever-growing festival scene two decades ago, Creamfields has secured its spot as being one of the - if not the - biggest weekend dedicated to electronic music in the UK. Currently, the clubbing and raving pilgrimage attracts an impressive 70,000 festival-goers over the weekend. Continuously offering up the very best in EDM, house, trance, drum and bass, grime, and more, Creamfields has hosted some massive names over the past twenty years. This 2019 edition of Creamfields presents Green Velvet, MK, Carl Cox, Deadmau5, Camelphat, Nicole Moudaber, Dimitri Vegas &amp; Like Mike, and many more!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/59/1769392_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230530000900 +0200" stop="20230530015500 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Leçons de ténèbres, de Michel-Richard de Lalande</title>
<desc lang="fr">Lalande - Leçons de ténèbres - Harpsichordist and organist Sébastien Daucé conducts Ensemble Correspondances and soloist Sophie Karthäuser (soprano) in a performance of Michel-Richard de Lalande's (1657-1726) sacred music piece Les Leçons des Ténèbres ('lessons of darkness'). To round off the period of Lent leading up to Easter, the congregation sings these Lamentations of Jeremiah in church. With each psalm, one of the candles is extinguished until complete darkness and silence ensues. Whatever one's faith, this tradition is a unique spiritual experience. French baroque composer Michel-Richard de Lalande, an important composer of &quot;grands&quot; motets of unprecedented length, was one of many who wrote music for this religious practice. This performance was recorded at Chapelle Corneille in Rouen, France in 2016.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/21/1756184_A.jpg" />
</programme>