<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Voo -->
<programme start="20230401030000 +0200" stop="20230401051500 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam</title>
<desc lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam - New Cool Collective is one of the foremost Dutch jazz ensembles. Pioneering new blends of music styles since 1993, NCC has performed in various formations, from small combos to larger ensembles and even big bands! The ensemble's high energy is cut out for the dance floors, as dance, Latin, salsa, afrobeat and boogaloo all meet in a jazzy mix. NCC includes saxophonist Benjamin Herman, guitarist Rory Ronde, drummer Joost Kroon, percussionists Frank van Dok and Jos de Haas, pianist Willem Friede, bassist Leslie Lopez, and trumpeter David Rockefeller.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230401051500 +0200" stop="20230401060600 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Giana Viscardi</title>
<desc lang="fr">Giana Viscardi - Da Pá Virada Sessions - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the bands taking part in this series is the duo of Giana Viscardi and Gustavo Marques. After starting their career together, Giana Viscardi and Gustavo Marques released music in many places around the world. After returning to Brazil, they worked together on Giana's album &quot;ORUM&quot;, performing in Africa, Europe, and Brazil. In this episode, Giana Viscardi and Gustavo Marques perform conductor and arranger Letieres Leite's arrangements of their work.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230401060600 +0200" stop="20230401071000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Quartabe</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Da Pá Virada Sessions series portrays the best musicians in Brazilian jazz today. All sessions were recorded in São Paulo and offer a unique experience: they offer a fresh look at the Brazilian music scene. The artists have been selected together with the music editor of Stingray DJAZZ. Among the bands featured in this series is Quartabê, a unique Brazilian quartet that draws from a wide variety of influences, including São Paulo's avant-garde movement, free improvisation, pop, and electronic music. Each of these influences is reflected in Quartabê's rousing live performances! Joana Queiroz (tenor saxophone and clarinets), Maria Beraldo Bastos (clarinets), Mariá Portugal (drums), and Chicão (keys) write, arrange, improvise and sing music that is all theirs.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230401071000 +0200" stop="20230401082900 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Rocky Mountain Way</title>
<desc lang="fr">Rocky Mountain Way - The Colorado Music Hall of Fame hosted a concert for the induction of rock 'n' roll legends Joe Walsh and the late Dan Fogelberg, along with the honoring of the famed Caribou Ranch recording studio near Nederland, Colorado, where Walsh and Fogelberg both recorded some of their best work. The concert, dubbed &quot;The Rocky Mountain Way,&quot; took place on Sunday, August 13, 2017, at Fiddler's Green. It featured performances from an all-star list of musicians including The Lumineers, Garth Brooks, Amy Grant &amp; Vince Gill, The Nitty Gritty Dirt Band, Richie Furay, Randy Owen of Alabama, Todd Park Mohr, Michael Martin Murphey, and surprise guests paying tribute to Dan Fogelberg and Caribou Ranch. Joe Walsh reunited his Caribou recording band Barnstorm for the performance.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/02/14/03/2145504_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230401082900 +0200" stop="20230401090000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">San Holo</title>
<desc lang="fr">Songbook - &quot;I never heard anyone say that, and yeah, I know exactly what it means. It has to go in there, this has to be a song.&quot; Every song has its own story, and we all think it's a story we've heard before, but we haven't. Songbook finds and captures these intriguing stories by pulling you into the process of writing and composing. Known for its pristine sound, cinematic 4k video and eye for detail, Songbook live-captured episodes emphasize the paramount importance of quality. It addresses the on-the-spot elements of blending song and location at the right moment. Both the magical location and remarkable music interaction will get the attention they deserve. Simply because Songbook isn't just a live music session, it lives. This episode of Songbook features Dutch producer, DJ and innovator San Holo, born Sander van Dijck.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230401090000 +0200" stop="20230401094600 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Moonlight Benjamin : WOMEX 2018</title>
<desc lang="fr">Numerous musicians, booking agents, news agencies and media companies from all over the world have been attending the &quot;World Music Exhibition&quot; World Music Expo (WOMEX) since 1994. Over the years, this music fair has settled in several European cities, including Berlin, Brussels, Marseille, Stockholm, Seville, Cardiff and Budapest. In 2018 WOMEX took place in Las Palmas in Gran Canaria. One of the participants was the Haitian singer Moonlight Benjamin. With her band she mixes voodoo blues, Haitian rock and Creole roll into a swirling brew that is thrilling with exciting riffs and heavy grooves. Her powerful voice and fiery electric guitars do the rest.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/52/1752443_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230401094600 +0200" stop="20230401104700 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Johnny Marr - Rock en Seine</title>
<desc lang="fr">Johnny Marr at Rock en Seine 2019 - English musician, songwriter, and singer Johnny Marr has enjoyed an exemplary career since his former band The Smiths split up in 1987. His distinctive guitar sound has been part of such varied groups as The Pretenders, The Cribs, Modest Mouse, and Electronic, the group he co-founded with Bernard Sumner of New Order. Now a living legend, Johnny Marr showcases his incredible singer-songwriter talents on each new album. His recent, hit-packed release Call The Comet (2018) gave us &quot;The Tracers&quot; and &quot;Hi Hello,&quot; and his live performances - which usually include some songs from his days with The Smiths - always hit the mark. Enjoy this 2019 show recorded at Rock en Seine in Paris!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/15/2123266_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230401104700 +0200" stop="20230401115800 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Mondriaan Jazz 2017 : FORQ</title>
<desc lang="fr">Mondriaan Jazz 2017: FORQ - Forq is an instrumental quartet with an aggressive sound and a penchant for sonic exploration. Originally founded by keyboardist Henry Hey (David Bowie, Empire of the Sun, and Jeff &quot;Tain&quot; Watts) and bassist Michael League (Grammy-winning founder of Snarky Puppy), Forq is joined by guitarist Chris McQueen and drummer Jason &quot;JT&quot; Thomas. Their group sound draws from various musical paths of its members, whether it's Jason's swampy grooves and shuffles, Chris' singular sonic approach to guitar, Henry's zeal for unique keyboard sounds and twisted ear candy, or Michael's driving world-influenced grooves. The band pushes further down the sonic rabbit hole with their stunning music. This concert was filmed during Mondriaan Jazz Festival 2017, The Hague.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/35/1763357_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230401115800 +0200" stop="20230401125900 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Trio Macaiba</title>
<desc lang="fr">Trio Macaiba - Da Pá Virada Sessions - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the bands taking part in this series is Trio Macaíba, consisting of Beto Corrêa (accordion), Cléber Almeida (zabumba, a type of bass drum), and Ramon Vieira (triangle). Their use of a traditional instrument combination, as well as cultural research, which all members of the group are dedicated to, contributes to the authenticity of the music and their experience as musicians.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230401125900 +0200" stop="20230401135100 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Ramón Valle &amp; Reinier Baas : Music Meeting 2020</title>
<desc lang="fr">Ramón Valle &amp; Reinier Baas - Music Meeting 2020 - Since 1985, the Dutch city of Nijmegen has been welcoming the International Music Meeting Festival every Pentecost. Ranging from jazz and improvisational music to traditional music and unique crossovers, this adventurous festival is all about musical encounters and international collaborations. Disrupted by COVID-19, the festival's 2020 edition had to adapt to new challenges. It now presents this exclusive concert by pianist Ramón Valle and guitarist Reinier Baas, filmed at Concertgebouw De Vereeniging in Nijmegen.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/49/1767496_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230401135100 +0200" stop="20230401150200 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Roger Sanchez</title>
<desc lang="fr">Roger Sanchez - Self-made man and true legend of house music, Roger Sanchez perfectly embodies the spirit of Pacha Festival Bali. Sanchez had a humble debut in New York, but the days when he was spinning vinyls for his friends in Queens living rooms are far behind him. Today, he is the headliner of major festivals around the globe, and resident DJ of clubs in Ibiza's sights, such as the Pacha Club. With this DJ set at Pacha Festival, Sanchez brings some of the magic of Ibiza to the beaches of Bali. Expect lots of energy, breathtaking lights, and even fireworks!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230401150200 +0200" stop="20230401163600 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">&quot;Whatever&quot; at Jazz à Ramatuelle</title>
<desc lang="fr">China Moses: &quot;Whatever&quot; at Jazz à Ramatuelle - In 1988, Dee Dee Bridgewater was one of the first great jazz singers to perform at the Jazz Festival in Ramatuelle. In 2016, the story seems to repeat itself as her daughter China Moses took the stage at Ramatuelle. Over the years, China Moses has become a mature performer with a unique style: rocky voice, sharp sense of swing, and intense/energetic stage presence. After signing compilations dedicated to Dinah Washington and blues, Moses released in 2016 an album of his own compositions, entitled &quot;Whatever&quot;. Get ready for a most entertaining performance combining jazz, soul, and hip-hop.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230401163600 +0200" stop="20230401173500 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Andre Marques</title>
<desc lang="fr">Andre Marques - Da Pá Virada Sessions - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the artists taking part in this series is pianist, composer, and arranger André Marques. He has been building a solid career, releasing his music with numerous groups: he is a member of the Latin Grammy-nominated Trio Curupira, the André Marques Sexteto, and he leads the Brazilian music orchestra Vintena Brasileira. In this episode of Da Pá Virada Sessions, André Marques performs an intimate solo piano recital.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230401173500 +0200" stop="20230401183700 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Marius Neset : Jazz in Duketown</title>
<desc lang="fr">Marius Neset - Jazz in Duketown - Jazz in Duketown is the largest free outdoor jazz festival in the Netherlands. It's a real gathering for jazz addicts, inviting internationally renowned artists. In 2019, one of them is Copenhagen-based Norwegian saxophonist Marius Neset, who is known internationally for his collaborations with People Are Machines, Kaktusch, JazzKamikaze, and Django Bates' projects StoRMChaser and Human Chain. Neset completed his Master's degree at the Copenhagen Rhythmic Music Conservatory in 2008.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/56/1752527_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230401183700 +0200" stop="20230401195300 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Monty Alexander &amp; The Harlem Kingston Express</title>
<desc lang="fr">With a career spanning five decades, jazz pianist Monty Alexander has played with the best of the best. An ambassador for Jamaican music, Alexander creates a unique blend of jazz and reggae with a group of exceptional American and Jamaican musicians called the &quot;Harlem Kingston Express.&quot; Together, they explore the two sides of Monty Alexander's musical legacy: the jazz of Harlem and the reggae of Kingston. Many great jazz musicians, including Dizzy Gillespie, have called on Alexander's exceptional sense of improvisation. Watch this 4K recording of his 2017 performance at Philharmonie de Paris, and you'll understand why.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/56/1752527_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230401195300 +0200" stop="20230401210000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Audience Music</title>
<desc lang="fr">This series features groundbreaking concerts, in-depth artist interviews and unique stories with host Ted Stryker. This concert series gives the audience an intimate view of music's most influential artists today. Shot in 4K, host Ted Stryker interviews musicians across all genres, creating the most unique music show on TV today. This episode features The Band Perry, the famous country band consisting of siblings Kimberly, Reid and Neil Perry. Throughout high school they had different bands, but towards the end of high school the three came together as The Band Perry. After being signed to Republic Nashville, they released their first album, and conquered the charts with the song &quot;If I Die Young.&quot; Since then, they have scored numerous hits and have won various awards.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1757419_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230401210000 +0200" stop="20230401215800 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Hozier, Alex Ryan, Rory Doyle &amp; Cormac Curran The Gramercy Theatre</title>
<desc lang="fr">Hozier - The popular music performance series Front and Center, which premiered nationwide on public television in 2016, returns for Season 6. The series boasts 22, one-hour episodes and an all-star line-up. This episode features the Irish singer-songwriter Hozier. From 2009 to 2012, he toured with an Irish choral group, Anuna. 2013 saw his breakthrough, with the hit song &quot;Take Me to Church.&quot; A successful international tour followed, as well as his albums Hozier (2014) and Wasteland, Baby (2019). At Front and Center, he showcases his unique sound, blending blues, gospel and soul.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/04/1754386_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230401215800 +0200" stop="20230401230500 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">The Driver - Trabendo Paris</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Driver - Trabendo Paris - The Driver is especially known by his pseudonym Manu le Malin. Since the emergence of rave in France in the early 1990s, he has become a true icon of hardcore techno and underground. The Driver is renowned all over the world as one of the most important representatives of the underground scene, taking over major festivals and clubs. During his 2017 show at Trabendo Paris, this living legend presents a previously unreleased set. While the crowd goes wild, you'll be blown away by powerful beats and a high-end visual show. Enjoy his unforgettable tribute to French electro!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/19/1849379_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230401230500 +0200" stop="20230402000500 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Paulo Novaes</title>
<desc lang="fr">Paulo Novaes - Da Pá Virada Sessions - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the artists taking part in this series is Paulo Novaes. Coming from a family of musicians, Paulo Novaes has already lived through a lifetime of music in spite of his young age. Paulo is the cousin of singer Bruna Caram, with whom he performed in São Paulo, Madrid, Barcelona, Lisbon, and other major cities. As a singer, composer, and instrumentalist, his creativity is enjoyed in many forms.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230402000500 +0200" stop="20230402013700 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Charlie Parker : &quot;Bird with Strings&quot; revisited à la Philharmonie de Paris</title>
<desc lang="fr">Charlie Parker - Bird with Strings Revisited - In the late 1940s, jazz saxophonist Charlie &quot;Bird&quot; Parker expressed his wish to record with a classical string section rather than his usual jazz quintet. This desire was fulfilled in 1949 and 1950 when he recorded two albums with oboe, harp, string section and a jazz rhythm section, released as 'Charlie Parker with Strings'. Fast forward 70 years, when saxophonists Olivier Bogé, Géraldine Laurent, Pierrick Pédron, Thomas de Pourquery, and Jaleel Shaw follow in the jazz legend's footsteps, revisiting the repertoire of those original albums in this 2019 concert at The Philharmonie de Paris. Bastien Stil conducts Christophe Dal Sasso's new orchestral arrangements in this genre-blending concert, which opens with Dal Sasso's very own Overture pour cinq saxophones et orchestra.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/24/33/2164871_A.jpg" />
</programme>