<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Voo -->
<programme start="20230515030000 +0200" stop="20230515040300 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Marius Neset : Jazz in Duketown</title>
<desc lang="fr">Marius Neset - Jazz in Duketown - Jazz in Duketown is the largest free outdoor jazz festival in the Netherlands. It's a real gathering for jazz addicts, inviting internationally renowned artists. In 2019, one of them is Copenhagen-based Norwegian saxophonist Marius Neset, who is known internationally for his collaborations with People Are Machines, Kaktusch, JazzKamikaze, and Django Bates' projects StoRMChaser and Human Chain. Neset completed his Master's degree at the Copenhagen Rhythmic Music Conservatory in 2008.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/56/1752527_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230515040300 +0200" stop="20230515050200 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Roger Sanchez</title>
<desc lang="fr">Roger Sanchez - Self-made man and true legend of house music, Roger Sanchez perfectly embodies the spirit of Pacha Festival Bali. Sanchez had a humble debut in New York, but the days when he was spinning vinyls for his friends in Queens living rooms are far behind him. Today, he is the headliner of major festivals around the globe, and resident DJ of clubs in Ibiza's sights, such as the Pacha Club. With this DJ set at Pacha Festival, Sanchez brings some of the magic of Ibiza to the beaches of Bali. Expect lots of energy, breathtaking lights, and even fireworks!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230515050200 +0200" stop="20230515063800 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Atys en folie</title>
<desc lang="fr">Atys en Folie - Atys en folie is a parody of Jean-Baptiste Lully's lyrical tragedy Atys (1676). Atys, Lully's most famous opera, was a constant subject of parody throughout the 18th century. Stage director Jean-Philippe Desrousseaux drew on several parodies to create this original production for singers, puppets, and musicians to revive the work. Princes, princesses, and kings are relegated to peasants, market gardeners, and fishmongers in the countryside. Among the performers are Alain Buet, Marie Lenormand, and Arnaud Marzorati. Gaëlle Trimardeau, Bruno Coulon and Jean-Philippe Desrousseaux feature as puppeteers. The music is performed by ensemble La Clique des Lunaisiens, conducted by Arnaud Marzorati. This performance was recorded at Teatru Manoel in Valletta, Malta, in 2017.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/02/04/18/1768814_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230515063800 +0200" stop="20230515072800 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">WOMEX 2018</title>
<desc lang="fr">Numerous musicians, booking agents, news agencies and media companies from all over the world have been attending the &quot;World Music Exhibition&quot; World Music Expo (WOMEX) since 1994. Over the years, this music fair has settled in several European cities, including Berlin, Brussels, Marseille, Stockholm, Seville, Cardiff and Budapest. In 2018 WOMEX took place in Las Palmas in Gran Canaria. One of the participants was singer Lucibela, from the Cape Verde island of São Nicolau.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/53/1759065_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230515072800 +0200" stop="20230515082700 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Paulo Novaes</title>
<desc lang="fr">Paulo Novaes - Da Pá Virada Sessions - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the artists taking part in this series is Paulo Novaes. Coming from a family of musicians, Paulo Novaes has already lived through a lifetime of music in spite of his young age. Paulo is the cousin of singer Bruna Caram, with whom he performed in São Paulo, Madrid, Barcelona, Lisbon, and other major cities. As a singer, composer, and instrumentalist, his creativity is enjoyed in many forms.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230515082700 +0200" stop="20230515090000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Close Call</title>
<desc lang="fr">Classical:NEXT 2019 - Close Call - In Close Call your smartphone is a musical instrument. And you are not just an audience member, but a musician in a crazy band with three drummers! Arthur Wagenaar is a Dutch composer and musician. He has a deep love for rock bands, theatre, opera and classical music, and his music is usually a mixture of all of this. He also loves to invent his own instruments, mechanical or electronic, such as the &quot;rampaphone,&quot; a string instrument nine meters in length, the &quot;kleurwerper,&quot; played by juggling, and of course the Close Call Live app. In this performance from Classical:NEXT! in Rotterdam, he is supported by Joep Hendrickx, Tjalling Schrik, Marijn Korff de Gidts, Boy van Ooijen, Dodó Kis, Sarah Jeffery, Lotte Pen, Matthias Konrad, and Axel Schappert.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/24/07/2123267_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230515090000 +0200" stop="20230515111500 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam</title>
<desc lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam - New Cool Collective is one of the foremost Dutch jazz ensembles. Pioneering new blends of music styles since 1993, NCC has performed in various formations, from small combos to larger ensembles and even big bands! The ensemble's high energy is cut out for the dance floors, as dance, Latin, salsa, afrobeat and boogaloo all meet in a jazzy mix. NCC includes saxophonist Benjamin Herman, guitarist Rory Ronde, drummer Joost Kroon, percussionists Frank van Dok and Jos de Haas, pianist Willem Friede, bassist Leslie Lopez, and trumpeter David Rockefeller.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230515111500 +0200" stop="20230515121500 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Robin Schulz, Sam Feldt, Afrojack &amp; Alle Farben - Parookaville</title>
<desc lang="fr">Parookaville - Parookaville is a city that comes to life once a year to keep the legend of Bill Parooka alive. It was started as an artistic, free-flowing, wild, and musical place where people could connect with their pure selves, experience real connections, and feel a deep sense of bliss and fulfillment. Step into the darkness if you dare, follow your inner light and immerse yourself in a spectacular world of freedom and love! Only four years since the first event, this festival has already become one of Germany's most prevalent music festivals. This edition features Armin van Buuren, Showtek, Robin Schulz, and W&amp;W.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230515121500 +0200" stop="20230515132200 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">The Driver - Trabendo Paris</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Driver - Trabendo Paris - The Driver is especially known by his pseudonym Manu le Malin. Since the emergence of rave in France in the early 1990s, he has become a true icon of hardcore techno and underground. The Driver is renowned all over the world as one of the most important representatives of the underground scene, taking over major festivals and clubs. During his 2017 show at Trabendo Paris, this living legend presents a previously unreleased set. While the crowd goes wild, you'll be blown away by powerful beats and a high-end visual show. Enjoy his unforgettable tribute to French electro!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/19/1849379_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230515132200 +0200" stop="20230515150100 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Monty Alexander &amp; The Harlem Kingston Express</title>
<desc lang="fr">With a career spanning five decades, jazz pianist Monty Alexander has played with the best of the best. An ambassador for Jamaican music, Alexander creates a unique blend of jazz and reggae with a group of exceptional American and Jamaican musicians called the &quot;Harlem Kingston Express.&quot; Together, they explore the two sides of Monty Alexander's musical legacy: the jazz of Harlem and the reggae of Kingston. Many great jazz musicians, including Dizzy Gillespie, have called on Alexander's exceptional sense of improvisation. Watch this 4K recording of his 2017 performance at Philharmonie de Paris, and you'll understand why.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/56/1752527_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230515150100 +0200" stop="20230515161900 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Beth Ditto live at L'Aéronef Lille 2017</title>
<desc lang="fr">At L'Aéronef Lille 2017 - Gossip fans, rejoice: Beth Ditto makes a big comeback! With her new album, the fiery singer launches into a solo career. With the boundless energy, undeniable humor, and legendary generosity that characterize her, the American phenomenon presents brand-new songs. Beth Ditto is more than a singer: she is an inescapable figure of the world's pop culture. As the lead singer of indie rock band Gossip (1999-2016), this young woman pulled off spectacular stage performances and gave hilarious interviews, greatly contributing to her sympathy capital. Her 2017 album mixes blues, pop, country, and rock, paying tribute to her native Arkansas in twelve eclectic and unifying pieces. Experience Beth Ditto as never before in this appearance at L'Aéronef Lille 2017!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Musique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/15/1838343_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230515161900 +0200" stop="20230515170800 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Ben Frost</title>
<desc lang="fr">Ben Frost - Australian Ben Frost produces under his Bedroom Community label albums inspired by post-classical electronic music, structured sound art and minimalism. His numerous collaborations testify to his desire to develop an artistic form combining music, texts, technology and performance. In this fascinating concert delivered at the Sónar Reykjavík 2018 festival, Frost once again displays his ingenuity as he presents the pieces of the album The Centre Cannot Hold. The award-winning visual artist MFO signs visual effects and lighting.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/59/1769392_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230515170800 +0200" stop="20230515180900 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Johnny Marr - Rock en Seine</title>
<desc lang="fr">Johnny Marr at Rock en Seine 2019 - English musician, songwriter, and singer Johnny Marr has enjoyed an exemplary career since his former band The Smiths split up in 1987. His distinctive guitar sound has been part of such varied groups as The Pretenders, The Cribs, Modest Mouse, and Electronic, the group he co-founded with Bernard Sumner of New Order. Now a living legend, Johnny Marr showcases his incredible singer-songwriter talents on each new album. His recent, hit-packed release Call The Comet (2018) gave us &quot;The Tracers&quot; and &quot;Hi Hello,&quot; and his live performances - which usually include some songs from his days with The Smiths - always hit the mark. Enjoy this 2019 show recorded at Rock en Seine in Paris!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/07/19/2123266_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230515180900 +0200" stop="20230515194200 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Fred Hersch Trio</title>
<desc lang="fr">Since awakening from a months-long coma in 2008, Fred Hersch has experienced a spectacular physical and artistic rebirth. He filled numerous albums with his piano playing and his own compositions.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230515194200 +0200" stop="20230515201500 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Lost Heritage</title>
<desc lang="fr">Classical:NEXT 2019 - Lost Heritage - François Vasseur and Pierre Chataignon make up the French electronic and contemporary music duo Lost Heritage. Living in the region of Geneva, they are two music lovers interested in jazz, classical, urban, and electronic music. François Vasseur is an electronic composer and pianist. He has been working on electronics for many years, starting as a DJ, then as a musician and composer, while also working in the field of cultural mediation and public engagement for organisations like the Verbier Festival, the Geneva Opera and the Lyon Baroque Music Festival. Pierre Chataignon works on various projects across many musical styles, from world music to electronic, as well as in film sound production and voice-over projects that require high quality sound recording, mixing, and production.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/24/07/2123267_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230515201500 +0200" stop="20230515210000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Nilufer Yanya</title>
<desc lang="fr">Echoes Series: Nilufer Yanya - Echoes is a modern live music show hosted by Jehnny Beth (lead singer in the British band Savages). It presents leading and emerging bands and artists from the contemporary scene. The show takes place underneath the Palais de Tokyo museum in Paris, in the club of brutalist architecture, the &quot;Yoyo.&quot; The live sets are 30 minutes long and take place on a customized stage, creating closeness with the audience. The intimate, immersive space lends to the atmosphere of the show. The artistic direction by Antoine Carlier follows a minimalist, refined and pure aesthetic, allowing the artists' energy and emotions to take center stage. This episode features Nilüfer Yanya. Her set includes the songs &quot;The Florist,&quot; &quot;Angels,&quot; and &quot;The Unordained.&quot;.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230515210000 +0200" stop="20230515230800 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Hardwell and the Metropole Orchestra - Symphony</title>
<desc lang="fr">Hardwell and the Metropole Orchestra - Symphony - During &quot;Symphony: The Global Revolution of Dance,&quot; the global sensation DJ Hardwell, with the world's leading pop and jazz orchestra, The Metropole Orchestra, take the audience on a musical journey through the history of dance music. The spectacular show of legendary DJ and the Metropole Orchestra is characterized by the composition of different music periods, from the '80s to the present. The show features hits from various world stars like Donna Summer, Tiësto, Carl Cox, and Daft Punk.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/21/1756184_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230515230800 +0200" stop="20230516000900 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Green Velvet, MK, Carl Cox &amp; deadmau5</title>
<desc lang="fr">Creamfields - Having burst onto the ever-growing festival scene two decades ago, Creamfields has secured its spot as being one of the - if not the - biggest weekend dedicated to electronic music in the UK. Currently, the clubbing and raving pilgrimage attracts an impressive 70,000 festival-goers over the weekend. Continuously offering up the very best in EDM, house, trance, drum and bass, grime, and more, Creamfields has hosted some massive names over the past twenty years. This 2019 edition of Creamfields presents Green Velvet, MK, Carl Cox, Deadmau5, Camelphat, Nicole Moudaber, Dimitri Vegas &amp; Like Mike, and many more!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/59/1769392_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230516000900 +0200" stop="20230516015500 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Leçons de ténèbres, de Michel-Richard de Lalande</title>
<desc lang="fr">Lalande - Leçons de ténèbres - Harpsichordist and organist Sébastien Daucé conducts Ensemble Correspondances and soloist Sophie Karthäuser (soprano) in a performance of Michel-Richard de Lalande's (1657-1726) sacred music piece Les Leçons des Ténèbres ('lessons of darkness'). To round off the period of Lent leading up to Easter, the congregation sings these Lamentations of Jeremiah in church. With each psalm, one of the candles is extinguished until complete darkness and silence ensues. Whatever one's faith, this tradition is a unique spiritual experience. French baroque composer Michel-Richard de Lalande, an important composer of &quot;grands&quot; motets of unprecedented length, was one of many who wrote music for this religious practice. This performance was recorded at Chapelle Corneille in Rouen, France in 2016.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/21/1756184_A.jpg" />
</programme>