<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Voo -->
<programme start="20230327030000 +0200" stop="20230327040300 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Marius Neset : Jazz in Duketown</title>
<desc lang="fr">Marius Neset - Jazz in Duketown - Jazz in Duketown is the largest free outdoor jazz festival in the Netherlands. It's a real gathering for jazz addicts, inviting internationally renowned artists. In 2019, one of them is Copenhagen-based Norwegian saxophonist Marius Neset, who is known internationally for his collaborations with People Are Machines, Kaktusch, JazzKamikaze, and Django Bates' projects StoRMChaser and Human Chain. Neset completed his Master's degree at the Copenhagen Rhythmic Music Conservatory in 2008.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/56/1752527_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230327040300 +0200" stop="20230327050400 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Frequencerz @ Airbeat One</title>
<desc lang="fr">Frequencerz @ Airbeat One - Frequencerz is a Dutch hardstyle duo formed by Pepijn Hol and Niels Koster. In 2009, they signed their contract with the Fusion Records label. Since then, they've released a good number of albums, such as Medium Rare, S.T.F.U. / G.T.F.O, and Phaser. With their performances for huge crowds at Defqon.1, Decibel Outdoor, and The Qontinent, they've established themselves as one of the biggest hardstyle acts of today. Their show at the German Airbeat One festival underlines their reputation. Expect nothing but spectacular light shows, non-stop jumpstyle, and a crazy crowd!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230327050400 +0200" stop="20230327063700 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">&quot;Whatever&quot; at Jazz à Ramatuelle</title>
<desc lang="fr">China Moses: &quot;Whatever&quot; at Jazz à Ramatuelle - In 1988, Dee Dee Bridgewater was one of the first great jazz singers to perform at the Jazz Festival in Ramatuelle. In 2016, the story seems to repeat itself as her daughter China Moses took the stage at Ramatuelle. Over the years, China Moses has become a mature performer with a unique style: rocky voice, sharp sense of swing, and intense/energetic stage presence. After signing compilations dedicated to Dinah Washington and blues, Moses released in 2016 an album of his own compositions, entitled &quot;Whatever&quot;. Get ready for a most entertaining performance combining jazz, soul, and hip-hop.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230327063700 +0200" stop="20230327072300 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Invisible World : WOMEX 2018</title>
<desc lang="fr">One of the participants was the band Invisible World, which operates at the crossroads where Eastern European and Mediterranean influences come together and break new ground. Invisible World is led by the inventive Czech bassist Tomá? Li?ka, together with the Turkish violinist Efe Turumtay, the Serbian accordionist Nikola Zari? and the Moravian drummer Kamil Slezák.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/24/31/2143305_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230327072300 +0200" stop="20230327082200 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Paulo Novaes</title>
<desc lang="fr">Paulo Novaes - Da Pá Virada Sessions - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the artists taking part in this series is Paulo Novaes. Coming from a family of musicians, Paulo Novaes has already lived through a lifetime of music in spite of his young age. Paulo is the cousin of singer Bruna Caram, with whom he performed in São Paulo, Madrid, Barcelona, Lisbon, and other major cities. As a singer, composer, and instrumentalist, his creativity is enjoyed in many forms.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230327082200 +0200" stop="20230327090000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">WOMEX 2018</title>
<desc lang="fr">Mario Batkovic - WOMEX 2018 - Since 1994, World Music Expo (WOMEX) has been attracting musicians, agents, a great number of press agencies, as well as media companies from all over the world. Its main exposition event has been held in various locations throughout Europe, including Berlin, Brussels, Marseille, Stockholm, Seville, Cardiff, and Budapest. The 2018 edition of WOMEX was held in Las Palmas, Gran Canaria. One of its showcase participants, Mario Batkovic, aims to explore the sonic possibilities of the accordion, without effects or loops, rather through a mutualist symbiotic relationship between man and instrument. Challenging, hypnotic, and grandiose, Batkovic's single-handed symphonic vision is certainly unique.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/24/31/2143305_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230327090000 +0200" stop="20230327111500 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam</title>
<desc lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam - New Cool Collective is one of the foremost Dutch jazz ensembles. Pioneering new blends of music styles since 1993, NCC has performed in various formations, from small combos to larger ensembles and even big bands! The ensemble's high energy is cut out for the dance floors, as dance, Latin, salsa, afrobeat and boogaloo all meet in a jazzy mix. NCC includes saxophonist Benjamin Herman, guitarist Rory Ronde, drummer Joost Kroon, percussionists Frank van Dok and Jos de Haas, pianist Willem Friede, bassist Leslie Lopez, and trumpeter David Rockefeller.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230327111500 +0200" stop="20230327120700 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Cabaret Contemporain</title>
<desc lang="fr">Cabaret Contemporain - &quot;Cabaret Contemporain&quot;: an explosive performance by musicians, composers, and improvisers who cross all musical boundaries with an innovative approach to the world of sound. Transforming life into dream and music into dance, the acoustic instruments are processed through an electronic filter which combines musical genres and codes. This performance is animated by the search for a new vocabulary of sounds. Enjoy this stunning live performance at the Suona Francese Festival in Rome's amazing Maxxi museum! Featuring Fabrizio Rat (piano), Giani Caserotto (guitar), Ronan Courty (bass), and Simon Drappier (bass).</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230327120700 +0200" stop="20230327131300 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Trio Corrente</title>
<desc lang="fr">Trio Corrente - Da Pá Virada Sessions - Da Pá Virada sessions bring the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the bands taking part in this series is Trio Corrente, which was formed in 2001, consisting of Fabio Torres on piano, Paulo Paulelli on bass, and Edu Ribeiro on drums. Since then, the trio has been creating an original sound playing the classics of choro and Música Popular Brasileira.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/24/38/1798058_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230327131300 +0200" stop="20230327142900 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Bad Company : Live From Red Rocks</title>
<desc lang="fr">Soundstage, an innovative and prestigious program, achieved widespread critical acclaim while featuring artists that defined the era. On May 15, 2016, at Red Rocks Amphitheater in Colorado, Soundstage captured the legendary classic rock band Bad Company delivering their biggest hits. The band consists of bassist Boz Burrell, guitarist Mick Ralphs, singer Paul Rodgers, and drummer Simon Kirke. The setlist contains their greatest songs, such as &quot;Live for the Music,&quot; &quot;Ready for Love,&quot; &quot;Can't Get Enough&quot; and &quot;Rock Steady.&quot;.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230327142900 +0200" stop="20230327150200 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Sorcha Richardson</title>
<desc lang="fr">Songbook - &quot;I never heard anyone say that, and yeah, I know exactly what it means. It has to go in there, this has to be a song.&quot; Every song has its own story, and we all think it's a story we've heard before, but we haven't. Songbook finds and captures these intriguing stories by pulling you into the process of writing and composing. Known for its pristine sound, cinematic 4k video and eye for detail, Songbook live-captured episodes emphasize the paramount importance of quality. It addresses the on-the-spot elements of blending song and location at the right moment. Both the magical location and remarkable music interaction will get the attention they deserve. Simply because Songbook isn't just a live music session, it lives. This episode of Songbook features Irish singer-songwriter Sorcha Richardson.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/04/2122118_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230327150200 +0200" stop="20230327162400 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Alfredo Rodriguez &amp; Pedrito Martinez</title>
<desc lang="fr">Rodriguez &amp; Martinez - Jazz sous les Pommiers - Pianist Alfredo Rodriguez and percussionist Pedrito Martinez, both from Cuba, play an unforgettable Latin jazz performance at the 2019 edition of festival Jazz sous les Pommiers in Coutances, France. Although both musicians are originally from Havana, Cuba, their music careers are blooming in the USA. The duo's debut album &quot;Duologue&quot; was produced by legendary producer Quincy Jones and saw its release in 2019. Their Jazz sous les Pommiers concert features original compositions alongside Yoruba pieces in honor of the African diaspora to Cuba. Moreover, the duo plays an unexpected interpretation of the Super Mario theme during this varied performance.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/45/1769516_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230327162400 +0200" stop="20230327171200 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">James Arthur</title>
<desc lang="fr">James Arthur - British pop singer James Arthur, best known for his power ballads &quot;Impossible&quot; (2013) and &quot;Say You Won't Let Go&quot; (2016), gives an intimate concert at New York City's Iridium. After winning the ninth season of UK's The X Factor in 2011, his powerful voice quickly helped him rise to the top of international pop charts.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230327171200 +0200" stop="20230327181000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Steve Vai</title>
<desc lang="fr">Steve Vai - The popular music performance series, Front and Center, which premiered nationwide on public television, in 2016, returns for Season 6. The series boasts 22, one-hour episodes and an all-star line-up. This episode features Steve Vai, the legendary guitarist who was voted the 10th Greatest Guitarist by Guitar World magazine, who treats fans to songs from his three-decade long career. As an independent guitarist he has won three Grammy Awards. Vai's solo sophomore release, Passion and Warfare, has earned gold certification in the US. At Front and Center he sits down and discusses his early interest in composing music and playing guitar as well as the many fortunes of his career.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Musique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/42/1870646_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230327181000 +0200" stop="20230327194600 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Atys en Folie</title>
<desc lang="fr">Atys en Folie - Atys en folie is a parody of Jean-Baptiste Lully's lyrical tragedy Atys (1676). Atys, Lully's most famous opera, was a constant subject of parody throughout the 18th century. Stage director Jean-Philippe Desrousseaux drew on several parodies to create this original production for singers, puppets, and musicians to revive the work. Princes, princesses, and kings are relegated to peasants, market gardeners, and fishmongers in the countryside. Among the performers are Alain Buet, Marie Lenormand, and Arnaud Marzorati. Gaëlle Trimardeau, Bruno Coulon and Jean-Philippe Desrousseaux feature as puppeteers. The music is performed by ensemble La Clique des Lunaisiens, conducted by Arnaud Marzorati. This performance was recorded at Teatru Manoel in Valletta, Malta, in 2017.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/02/04/18/1768814_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230327194600 +0200" stop="20230327201900 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Ruben Hein &amp; NJJO : Jazz in Duketown</title>
<desc lang="fr">Ruben Hein &amp; NJJO - Jazz in Duketown - Jazz in Duketown is the largest free outdoor jazz festival in the Netherlands. It's a real gathering for jazz addicts, inviting internationally renowned artists. One of them is Dutch singer, pianist, composer and bandleader Ruben Hein. Widely praised for his warm and characteristic voice and his offbeat piano playing, Ruben Hein is the artistic director and conductor of the National Youth Jazz Orchestra (NJJO). At Jazz in Duketown he performs a jazzy set, accompanied by his 18 finest proteges.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/01/01/2153368_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230327201900 +0200" stop="20230327210000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">reConvert Project</title>
<desc lang="fr">Classical:NEXT 2019 - reConvert Project - The concept of percussion has been altered significantly by the evolution of the instrument. The methods of the innovative reConvert Project are unique and dedicated to changing the face of the percussionist world, by working actively with composers such as Georges Aperghis, Simon Steen Andersen, Michael Maierhof and Jorge Sánchez-Chiong and premiering over a dozen works written to help train emerging young composers. The reConvert philosophy is based on the re-examination of the aesthetic use of percussion instruments, where musical discourse is analysed and adapted to their creative needs. With numerous works using unconventional instruments and staging, a whole new experience is created for the listener.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/24/07/2123267_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230327210000 +0200" stop="20230327230800 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Hardwell and the Metropole Orchestra - Symphony</title>
<desc lang="fr">Hardwell and the Metropole Orchestra - Symphony - During &quot;Symphony: The Global Revolution of Dance,&quot; the global sensation DJ Hardwell, with the world's leading pop and jazz orchestra, The Metropole Orchestra, take the audience on a musical journey through the history of dance music. The spectacular show of legendary DJ and the Metropole Orchestra is characterized by the composition of different music periods, from the '80s to the present. The show features hits from various world stars like Donna Summer, Tiësto, Carl Cox, and Daft Punk.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/21/1756184_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230327230800 +0200" stop="20230328000800 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Filo Machado</title>
<desc lang="fr">Filo Machado - Da Pá Virada Sessions - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the artists taking part in this series is Filo Machado. Born in São Paulo, this singer, composer, instrumentalist, arranger, and producer has celebrated many musical successes. Filo Machado took part in saxophonist Jane Bunnett's Canadian tour with her spectacular project 'Rendez-Vous Brazil/Cuba'. He has appeared at the jazz festivals of Córsega and Uzeste and opened for the one and only Nina Simone in Cannes.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230328000800 +0200" stop="20230328015100 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">RSO (Richie Sambora &amp; Orianthi)</title>
<desc lang="fr">RSO (Richie Sambora &amp; Orianthi) - Long before music television filled the airwaves, the series Soundstage sparked the nation. This innovative and prestigious program achieved widespread critical acclaim and featured the artists that defined the era, such as RSO, which stands for Richie Sambora and Orianthi. The American guitarist Richie Sambora has been the lead guitarist of rock band Bon Jovi for 30 years. He was, together with Bon Jovi, responsible for most of the songwriting of the band. Orianthi is most known for her rehearsals in 2009 with Michael Jackson for his ill-fated This Is It concert series. She has also performed with Alice Cooper's touring band. Richie Sambora and Orianthi have been performing together as RSO since 2014. Enjoy their 2018 Soundstage show at WTTW Chicago!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/42/1870646_A.jpg" />
</programme>