<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Voo -->
<programme start="20230527020200 +0200" stop="20230527030000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">IDLES - Echoes Series: Idles</title>
<desc lang="fr">Echoes Series: Idles - Echoes is a modern live music show hosted by Jehnny Beth (lead singer in the British band Savages). It presents leading and emerging bands and artists from the contemporary scene. The show takes place underneath the Palais de Tokyo museum in Paris, in the club of brutalist architecture, the &quot;Yoyo.&quot; The live sets are 30 minutes long and take place on a customized stage, creating closeness with the audience. The intimate, immersive space lends to the atmosphere of the show. The artistic direction by Antoine Carlier follows a minimalist, refined and pure aesthetic, allowing the artists' energy and emotions to take center stage. This episode features the band Idles. Their set includes the songs &quot;Colossus,&quot; &quot;Love Song,&quot; and &quot;Television.&quot;.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230527030000 +0200" stop="20230527051500 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam</title>
<desc lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam - New Cool Collective is one of the foremost Dutch jazz ensembles. Pioneering new blends of music styles since 1993, NCC has performed in various formations, from small combos to larger ensembles and even big bands! The ensemble's high energy is cut out for the dance floors, as dance, Latin, salsa, afrobeat and boogaloo all meet in a jazzy mix. NCC includes saxophonist Benjamin Herman, guitarist Rory Ronde, drummer Joost Kroon, percussionists Frank van Dok and Jos de Haas, pianist Willem Friede, bassist Leslie Lopez, and trumpeter David Rockefeller.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230527051500 +0200" stop="20230527060600 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Giana Viscardi - New Year's Eve Special</title>
<desc lang="fr">Giana Viscardi - New Year's Eve Special - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the bands taking part in this series is the duo of Giana Viscardi and Gustavo Marques. After starting their career together, Giana Viscardi and Gustavo Marques released music in many places around the world. After returning to Brazil, they worked together on Giana's album &quot;ORUM&quot;, performing in Africa, Europe, and Brazil.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230527060600 +0200" stop="20230527070900 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Joris Voorn</title>
<desc lang="fr">Joris Voorn - The Royal Concertgebouw is a night full of the best house and techno, hosted by one of the biggest names from the underground at one of the prettiest locations in the world. Renown as one of the most stunning sites dedicated to music, the Royal Concertgebouw has been transformed into a glorious cathedral of techno for one night only. Audio Obscura is a movement born out of love for cutting-edge underground dance music. Today, Audio Obscura has grown into one of the most sought-after destinations for leading DJs to play, and for partygoers, both young and old, to dance the night (and day) away.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/19/1849379_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230527070900 +0200" stop="20230527082800 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Alfredo Rodriguez &amp; Pedrito Martinez</title>
<desc lang="fr">Rodriguez &amp; Martinez - Jazz sous les Pommiers - Pianist Alfredo Rodriguez and percussionist Pedrito Martinez, both from Cuba, play an unforgettable Latin jazz performance at the 2019 edition of festival Jazz sous les Pommiers in Coutances, France. Although both musicians are originally from Havana, Cuba, their music careers are blooming in the USA. The duo's debut album &quot;Duologue&quot; was produced by legendary producer Quincy Jones and saw its release in 2019. Their Jazz sous les Pommiers concert features original compositions alongside Yoruba pieces in honor of the African diaspora to Cuba. Moreover, the duo plays an unexpected interpretation of the Super Mario theme during this varied performance.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/07/06/1769516_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230527082800 +0200" stop="20230527090000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Half Moon Run</title>
<desc lang="fr">Songbook - Half Moon Run - &quot;I never heard anyone say that, and yeah, I know exactly what it means. It has to go in there, this has to be a song.&quot; Every song has its own story, and we all think it's a story we've heard before, but we haven't. Songbook finds and captures these intriguing stories by pulling you into the process of writing and composing. Known for its pristine sound, cinematic 4k video and eye for detail, Songbook live-captured episodes emphasize the paramount importance of quality. It addresses the on-the-spot elements of blending song and location at the right moment. Both the magical location and remarkable music interaction will get the attention they deserve. Simply because Songbook isn't just a live music session, it lives.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/04/1754386_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230527090000 +0200" stop="20230527094800 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Bakolo Music International</title>
<desc lang="fr">In 2018 WOMEX took place in Las Palmas in Gran Canaria. One of the participants was the band Bakolo Music International. They represent the pioneers of the golden age of the Congolese rumba. Singer, guitarist and veteran Nzofu Moko Buele, called Bikunda by everyone, keeps the fire burning that &quot;Papa&quot; lit Wendolosoy, the &quot;father of the Congolese rumba&quot; in 1948 when his song &quot;Marie-Louise&quot; became an international hit.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/06/51/1642161_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230527094800 +0200" stop="20230527104800 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Isle of Wight 2018: Part II</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Isle of Wight Festival, held in Newport, England is a rock-pop music festival that annually serves as the first major event opening the British festival summer. The tradition of the festival first saw the light of day in 1969, opening eleven days after the closing of legendary Woodstock and was regarded as the European counterpart to the legendary &quot;counterculture&quot; festival. In 1970, its line-up was stars-studded with gigs by Jimi Hendrix, The Who, The Doors, Joni Mitchell, Supertramp, Leonard Cohen and many more, establishing the name of the festival. In 2002, the festival was revived after 30 years of silence and brought back the sounds of contemporary musical legends to the Isle of Wight.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/42/1870646_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230527104800 +0200" stop="20230527115100 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Sven Väth at Family Piknik</title>
<desc lang="fr">Sven Väth at Family Piknik 2017 - Active on the music scene for more than 30 years, Sven Väth is a true icon of techno. He was one of the first DJs to host a weekly event in Ibiza, and his &quot;Cocoon&quot; nights have quickly become a staple for fans of underground music in all its forms. Väth has been involved in all major developments of the techno movement, but even after three decades, this living legend is not ready to take the backstage and continues to dance crowds on five continents. Experience the unique sounds of Sven Väth with this performance recorded at the 2017 Family Piknik Festival!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230527115100 +0200" stop="20230527125400 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Popa Chubby : It's A Mighty Hard Road</title>
<desc lang="fr">Popa Chubby - It's A Mighty Hard Road - Popa Chubby, born as Ted Horowitz, is an American blues singer and guitarist, who has become one of the most popular figures of New York's blues scene. Early on in his career he released the album &quot;Booty and the Beast&quot; (1995), which became one of the 1990s's best-selling blues albums. Chubby describes his own style as &quot;The Stooges meets Buddy Guy, Motörhead meets Muddy Waters, and Jimi Hendrix meets Robert Johnson&quot;. As part of the French music festival Blues sur Seine, Chubby and his band played a great blues rock concert, showcasing the artist's powerful and soulful guitar playing. This performance was recorded at Théâtre Simone Signoret on November 8, 2019.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230527125400 +0200" stop="20230527135000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Oum 2018</title>
<desc lang="fr">Oum El Ghait Benessahraoui, better known as Oum, provides a unique insight into Moroccan music. This singer-songwriter is considered an ambassador for Moroccan culture. Oum is strongly influenced by genres such as gospel, jazz, soul and R&amp;B, but also African genres such as sufi, hassani, and afrobeat inspire her. Yet the influences of Aretha Franklin, Ella Fitzgerald and Whitney Houston are also strongly present in Oum's powerful voice. As a young singer, the African American vocal tradition made a deep impression on her. During her performance at the Music Meeting Festival in Nijmegen, Oum shows her audience unexpected musical vistas.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/04/1754386_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230527135000 +0200" stop="20230527150300 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Roger Sanchez</title>
<desc lang="fr">Roger Sanchez - Self-made man and true legend of house music, Roger Sanchez perfectly embodies the spirit of Pacha Festival Bali. Sanchez had a humble debut in New York, but the days when he was spinning vinyls for his friends in Queens living rooms are far behind him. Today, he is the headliner of major festivals around the globe, and resident DJ of clubs in Ibiza's sights, such as the Pacha Club. With this DJ set at Pacha Festival, Sanchez brings some of the magic of Ibiza to the beaches of Bali. Expect lots of energy, breathtaking lights, and even fireworks!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230527150300 +0200" stop="20230527163700 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Charlie Parker : &quot;Bird with Strings&quot; revisited à la Philharmonie de Paris</title>
<desc lang="fr">Charlie Parker - Bird with Strings Revisited - In the late 1940s, jazz saxophonist Charlie &quot;Bird&quot; Parker expressed his wish to record with a classical string section rather than his usual jazz quintet. This desire was fulfilled in 1949 and 1950 when he recorded two albums with oboe, harp, string section and a jazz rhythm section, released as 'Charlie Parker with Strings'. Fast forward 70 years, when saxophonists Olivier Bogé, Géraldine Laurent, Pierrick Pédron, Thomas de Pourquery, and Jaleel Shaw follow in the jazz legend's footsteps, revisiting the repertoire of those original albums in this 2019 concert at The Philharmonie de Paris. Bastien Stil conducts Christophe Dal Sasso's new orchestral arrangements in this genre-blending concert, which opens with Dal Sasso's very own Overture pour cinq saxophones et orchestra.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/07/19/2123265_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230527163700 +0200" stop="20230527173200 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Altin Gün : Bird, Rotterdam</title>
<desc lang="fr">Mediterranean sounds meet western music in this performance by the band Altin Gün. Their unusual approach to traditional Turkish folk music produces an overall sound full of ethnic, funky, and even psychedelic influences. With their infinite energy, Altin Gün takes the audience on an amazing sonic roller coaster: a ride full of emotion and fun. Altin Gün consists of six talented musicians who share a great passion for Turkish music. In this live recording from BIRD Rotterdam, one of the Netherlands' most important music venues, the band presents their new album &quot;On&quot; to the enthusiastic audience.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/19/1975203_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230527173200 +0200" stop="20230527183700 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Sgt. Pepper Tribute at Philharmonie de Paris</title>
<desc lang="fr">Sgt. Pepper Tribute at Philharmonie de Paris 2017 - Celebrated as one of the most influential albums of all times, The Beatles' 1967 Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band marked its time and inspired generations of artists. While the album was purely a recording studio product, Beatles' fans continue to be frustrated by not hearing it live. British musician and composer Ed Harcourt, author of six highly acclaimed albums and collaborator of vocalists Marianne Faithfull, Patti Smith, and trumpeter Erik Truffaz, gathered a supergroup for this occasion with top artists from the British independent rock scene. Join Ed Harcourt and members of The Libertines, Supergrass, The Coral, the Beta Band, and Primal Scream for this special tribute.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230527183700 +0200" stop="20230527195500 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Bad Company : Live From Red Rocks</title>
<desc lang="fr">Soundstage, an innovative and prestigious program, achieved widespread critical acclaim while featuring artists that defined the era. On May 15, 2016, at Red Rocks Amphitheater in Colorado, Soundstage captured the legendary classic rock band Bad Company delivering their biggest hits. The band consists of bassist Boz Burrell, guitarist Mick Ralphs, singer Paul Rodgers, and drummer Simon Kirke. The setlist contains their greatest songs, such as &quot;Live for the Music,&quot; &quot;Ready for Love,&quot; &quot;Can't Get Enough&quot; and &quot;Rock Steady.&quot;.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230527195500 +0200" stop="20230527210000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Frequencerz @ Airbeat One</title>
<desc lang="fr">Frequencerz @ Airbeat One - Frequencerz is a Dutch hardstyle duo formed by Pepijn Hol and Niels Koster. In 2009, they signed their contract with the Fusion Records label. Since then, they've released a good number of albums, such as Medium Rare, S.T.F.U. / G.T.F.O, and Phaser. With their performances for huge crowds at Defqon.1, Decibel Outdoor, and The Qontinent, they've established themselves as one of the biggest hardstyle acts of today. Their show at the German Airbeat One festival underlines their reputation. Expect nothing but spectacular light shows, non-stop jumpstyle, and a crazy crowd!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230527210000 +0200" stop="20230527220200 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Isle of Wight 2018: Part I</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Isle of Wight Festival, held in Newport, England is a rock-pop music festival that annually serves as the first major event opening the British festival summer. The tradition of the festival first saw the light of day in 1969, opening eleven days after the closing of legendary Woodstock and was regarded as the European counterpart to the legendary &quot;counterculture&quot; festival. In 1970, its line-up was stars-studded with gigs by Jimi Hendrix, The Who, The Doors, Joni Mitchell, Supertramp, Leonard Cohen and many more, establishing the name of the festival. In 2002, the festival was revived after 30 years of silence and brought back the sounds of contemporary musical legends to the Isle of Wight.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/42/1870646_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230527220200 +0200" stop="20230527230400 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Marius Neset : Jazz in Duketown</title>
<desc lang="fr">Marius Neset - Jazz in Duketown - Jazz in Duketown is the largest free outdoor jazz festival in the Netherlands. It's a real gathering for jazz addicts, inviting internationally renowned artists. In 2019, one of them is Copenhagen-based Norwegian saxophonist Marius Neset, who is known internationally for his collaborations with People Are Machines, Kaktusch, JazzKamikaze, and Django Bates' projects StoRMChaser and Human Chain. Neset completed his Master's degree at the Copenhagen Rhythmic Music Conservatory in 2008.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/56/1752527_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230527230400 +0200" stop="20230528000300 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Jack Johnson</title>
<desc lang="fr">Jack Johnson - In an intimate performance at Manhattan's McKittrick Hotel in New York City, multi-instrumentalist and singer/songwriter Jack Johnson takes his harmonic Hawaiian soft-rock sound to the stage. Besides his critically-acclaimed music, the North Shore-born singer/songwriter has also received a variety of awards for his activism in environmental issues. Johnson's music reflects the former professional surfer's background: soft acoustic rock melodies accompany his smooth warm-sounding voice in harmonic compositions, taking audiences on a sensory journey to the dreamy shores of Hawaii.For this special performance, he is accompanied by special guest G. Love and Zach Gill of ALO on the keys.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230528000300 +0200" stop="20230528013900 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Dickey Betts</title>
<desc lang="fr">Dickey Betts - Calling Dickey Betts the second guitarist in the Allman Brothers Band does him a disservice. After the tragic death of Duane Allman in 1971, Betts became co-captain with Gregg Allman, leading the group through ups and downs over the decades. Known as one of the most influential guitar players of all time, Betts has mastered a seamless style of lyrical melody and rhythm ? marrying country, jazz, blues, and rock into one sound. Betts has one of the most distinctive voices in music today, and on July 21, 2018, he brought down the house at the St. George's Theatre in Staten Island. Catch him performing the legendary Allman Brothers songs!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/42/1870646_A.jpg" />
</programme>