<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Voo -->
<programme start="20230412030000 +0200" stop="20230412035100 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Lucibela - WOMEX 2018</title>
<desc lang="fr">Numerous musicians, booking agents, news agencies and media companies from all over the world have been attending the &quot;World Music Exhibition&quot; World Music Expo (WOMEX) since 1994. Over the years, this music fair has settled in several European cities, including Berlin, Brussels, Marseille, Stockholm, Seville, Cardiff and Budapest. In 2018 WOMEX took place in Las Palmas in Gran Canaria. One of the participants was singer Lucibela, from the Cape Verde island of São Nicolau.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/53/1759065_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230412035100 +0200" stop="20230412045200 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Johnny Marr - Rock en Seine</title>
<desc lang="fr">Johnny Marr at Rock en Seine 2019 - English musician, songwriter, and singer Johnny Marr has enjoyed an exemplary career since his former band The Smiths split up in 1987. His distinctive guitar sound has been part of such varied groups as The Pretenders, The Cribs, Modest Mouse, and Electronic, the group he co-founded with Bernard Sumner of New Order. Now a living legend, Johnny Marr showcases his incredible singer-songwriter talents on each new album. His recent, hit-packed release Call The Comet (2018) gave us &quot;The Tracers&quot; and &quot;Hi Hello,&quot; and his live performances - which usually include some songs from his days with The Smiths - always hit the mark. Enjoy this 2019 show recorded at Rock en Seine in Paris!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/07/19/2123266_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230412045200 +0200" stop="20230412055700 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Sleaford Mods</title>
<desc lang="fr">Sleaford Mods - Perhaps you know Sleaford Mods from their collaboration with The Prodigy on The Day Is My Enemy album for which they recorded the track &quot;Ibiza&quot; together. Jason Williamson and Andrew Fearn are Sleaford Mods, the electronic punk duo hailing from Nottingham. Up until 2012, Jason Williamson worked together with Simon Parfrement, who left the music production to Andrew Fearn. In 2015, Sleaford Mods was nominated for the IMPALA Album of the Year Award for their album Key Markets. At the 2019 We Love Green festival in Paris, they play tracks from their latest album Eton Alive.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230412055700 +0200" stop="20230412065900 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Liran Donin : Music Meeting</title>
<desc lang="fr">Nijmegen has been welcoming the International Music Meeting Festival, or Music Meeting for short, every spring since 1985. From jazz and improvised music to traditional music and unique crossovers: musical encounters and international collaborations are at the heart of this adventurous festival. In 2019, Tel Aviv-born bassist, producer and composer Liran Donin performed here.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230412065900 +0200" stop="20230412075100 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Karin Fernandes</title>
<desc lang="fr">Karin Fernandes - Da Pá Virada Sessions - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the artists taking part in this series is pianist Karin Fernandes. She is dedicated to the performance of 20th and 21st century piano repertoire and has premiered numerous new compositions. As a soloist, Karin Fernandes has performed with prestigious Brazilian orchestras.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230412075100 +0200" stop="20230412090000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">The Bloody Beetroots</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Bloody Beetroots - The Bloody Beetroots is the creation of Sir Bob Cornelius Rifo. Inspired by his lifelong love of punk rock and comic books, Rifo unleashed The Bloody Beetroots in late 2006 and has since crafted an intense sound that mixes his classical training, his punk rock obsession, and his passion for electronic music into an edgy rock-meets-dance hybrid sound. In 2019, The Bloody Beetroots released the Heavy EP, which sees Rifo revisiting his classic electro style and features collaborations with Ephwurd and Dr. Fresch, in addition to three new solo originals. Enjoy his show at Nameless Music Festival 2019!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230412090000 +0200" stop="20230412102000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">The Opera Locos</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Opera Locos - In The Opera Locos (&quot;The Opera of Crazies&quot;), a comic opera show from the Spanish theater company Yllana and theatre producer Rami Eldar, five eccentric opera singers perform some of the greatest opera arias. Classical arias from George Bizet's Carmen, W. A. Mozart's The Magic Flute, and Giuseppe Verdi's Rigoletto are combined with classics from the pop and rock repertoire. During the performance, the five characters reveal their hidden passions, personalities, and desires, leading to unpredictable, hilarious situations that audiences of all ages will appreciate. The soloists are Florian Laconi (tenor), Margaux Toqué (mezzo soprano), Michaël Koné (countertenor), Laurent Arcaro (baritone), and Diane Fourès (soprano). This performance was recorded at Théâtre Libre in Paris, France.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Evénement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/02/07/27/1763355_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230412102000 +0200" stop="20230412110300 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Null + Void</title>
<desc lang="fr">Null + Void - While few people are familiar with the Null + Void project, many have already heard Kurt Uenala's music. After making his debut under the pseudonym Kap10Kurt in 2003, Uenala caught the attention of the world with the play &quot;Die Sleeping&quot;. This critical and popular success has led to collaborations with several big names in music, including Moby, The Kills, and Dave Gahan, singer of Depeche Mode, for whom Uenala has subsequently signed plays. Spending more and more time in his Manhattan studio, Uenala developed a unique sound made of angular beats and dark soundscapes, which gave rise to a new melancholy solo project called Null + Void. Cryosleep, Uenala's first album under this new banner, includes several titles inspired by retro science fiction, new wave and electronic innovators.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/06/2111709_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230412110300 +0200" stop="20230412115800 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Altin Gün : Bird, Rotterdam</title>
<desc lang="fr">Mediterranean sounds meet western music in this performance by the band Altin Gün. Their unusual approach to traditional Turkish folk music produces an overall sound full of ethnic, funky, and even psychedelic influences. With their infinite energy, Altin Gün takes the audience on an amazing sonic roller coaster: a ride full of emotion and fun. Altin Gün consists of six talented musicians who share a great passion for Turkish music. In this live recording from BIRD Rotterdam, one of the Netherlands' most important music venues, the band presents their new album &quot;On&quot; to the enthusiastic audience.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/19/1975203_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230412115800 +0200" stop="20230412133700 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Au Théâtre de Villefranche-sur-Saône</title>
<desc lang="fr">Omar Sosa - Quarteto Afrocubano - While always keeping one foot firmly anchored in the traditions of his home country, Cuba, Omar Sosa tirelessly explores music from the Caribbean to India, and West Africa to the Arab world. Since he left Cuba in 1993, the pianist has been blending his Afro-Cuban roots with jazz, hip hop, electro and world music. For his 2018 performance at Théâtre de Villefranche-sur-Saône, he brings to stage his Quarteto Afrocubano members Childo Tomas (electric bass &amp; vocals), Ernesto Simpson (drums), and Leandro Saint-Hill (saxophones, flute, percussion &amp; vocals). Together, they create a riveting instrumental dialogue. Celebrating rhythm in all its forms, this Omar Sosa concert is an intense and mystical experience.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/19/1853106_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230412133700 +0200" stop="20230412141000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Nilüfer Yanya - Echoes Series: Nilufer Yanya</title>
<desc lang="fr">Echoes Series: Billy Nomates - Echoes is a modern live music show hosted by Jehnny Beth (lead singer in the British band Savages). It presents leading and emerging bands and artists from the contemporary scene. The show takes place underneath the Palais de Tokyo museum in Paris, in the club of brutalist architecture, the &quot;Yoyo.&quot; The live sets are 30 minutes long and take place on a customized stage, creating closeness with the audience. The intimate, immersive space lends to the atmosphere of the show. The artistic direction by Antoine Carlier follows a minimalist, refined and pure aesthetic, allowing the artists' energy and emotions to take center stage. This episode features Billy Nomates. Her set includes the songs &quot;Happy Misery,&quot; &quot;Wild Arena,&quot; and &quot;Call in Sick.&quot;.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/03/1754401_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230412141000 +0200" stop="20230412150200 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Clarinet Factory</title>
<desc lang="fr">Classical:NEXT 2019 - Clarinet Factory - Considered to be one of the most unique ensembles to feature on the Czech scene in the last 25 years, the style of the Clarinet Factory hovers between contemporary and classical music, jazz and world music. As winners of the Classic Prague Awards in 2017 for 'Best Crossover Project', the quartet combines their classic music training and clarinet art with jazz, minimalism and improvisation to create their very own music without borders, capable of communicating directly with all audiences. The Clarinet Factory also experiment with electronics, both ambient and dance-oriented, and the four musicians remain ever fascinated with the possibilities of their instrument, considering their work as a music laboratory.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/24/07/2123267_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230412150200 +0200" stop="20230412160400 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Isle of Wight 2018: Part II</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Isle of Wight Festival, held in Newport, England is a rock-pop music festival that annually serves as the first major event opening the British festival summer. The tradition of the festival first saw the light of day in 1969, opening eleven days after the closing of legendary Woodstock and was regarded as the European counterpart to the legendary &quot;counterculture&quot; festival. In 1970, its line-up was stars-studded with gigs by Jimi Hendrix, The Who, The Doors, Joni Mitchell, Supertramp, Leonard Cohen and many more, establishing the name of the festival. In 2002, the festival was revived after 30 years of silence and brought back the sounds of contemporary musical legends to the Isle of Wight.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/42/1870646_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230412160400 +0200" stop="20230412170900 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Martina</title>
<desc lang="fr">Martina - Da Pá Virada Sessions - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the artists taking part in this series is Martina Marana. Vocalist, instrumentalist, and composer Martina Marana uses the power of irony to show how women instrumentalists are misjudged. In her music, Martina breaks free of sexist labels, reclaiming her own power as musician and composer. A gifted lyricist, Marana makes uncompromising, unique music.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230412170900 +0200" stop="20230412183900 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Daucé conducts Charpentier and Du Mont</title>
<desc lang="fr">Daucé conducts Charpentier and Du Mont - Harpsichordist and organist Sébastien Daucé leads Ensemble Correspondances in this concert recorded as part of the Valletta International Baroque Festival of 2017 at the Co-Cathédrale de St-Jean de la Valette in Malta. The concert opens with a rendition of Marc-Antoine Charpentier's late-17th century composition Te Deum. The joyful and popular prelude of this piece is familiar to many as the Eurovision Anthem. Furthermore, the concert program is made up of motets by Henry du Mont (1610-1694), an organist and baroque composer of the French school, born in the Southern Netherlands. Among his musical heirs were Jean-Baptiste Lully (1632-1687) and François Couperin (1668-1733).</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/07/03/2143762_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230412183900 +0200" stop="20230412192200 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">City Beats</title>
<desc lang="fr">City Beats - Episode 6 - Europe - DJ-producer Carly Foxx is on a musical journey, immersing herself in the life of five iconic European cities to find inspiration for a series of new tracks. In this episode, Carly Foxx looks back at her journey to the music dance capitals of Europe to inspire her final track. She starts with the Balaeric beat that represents Ibiza while adding authentic bongo and guitar recordings. Then she shifts to London, where she discovers new areas and urban culture while talking to filmmaker DJ Don Letts. Carly captures the grime sound with the help of MC Yizzy and records vocals from a group of London women. Her next trip brings her to Berlin, where she produces an acid house flavored track with the 303 synthesizers.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Télé-Réalité</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/16/2123268_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230412192200 +0200" stop="20230412203700 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Oumou Sangaré @ Jazz Sous Les Pommiers</title>
<desc lang="fr">Salif Keita described her as the &quot;Tina Turner of Mali.&quot; Indeed, Oumou Sangaré is one of Africa's most important female voices. While maintaining her political views as a champion of women's rights in Africa, her vocal talent has brought this singer to shine at some of the most important venues around the world. At Jazz Sous Les Pommiers 2017, Oumou Sangaré presents her latest album, Mogoya. She is accompanied by a group that combines traditional African instruments with a modern band set-up, featuring young French musicians. Recorded in spectacular 4K in a beautiful musical setting, Sangaré will surely make you sing and dance!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230412203700 +0200" stop="20230412210000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Cold Storage</title>
<desc lang="fr">Cold Storage - The Finnish dancer and film maker Thomas Freundlich created 'Cold Storage', a short dance film that pays homage to the virtuosic physical performances and melancholy comedy of the classic silent screen. As a lonely ice fisherman discovers his frozen prehistoric soul brother in the ice, multiple levels of time and reality blend together into a cinematic and kinetic exploration of alienation, dependency and friendship. In this choreography by Valtteri Raekallio, Eero Vesterinen and Valtteri Raekallio dance to the music of the internationally renowned avant-garde accordionist Kimmo Pohjonen.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Court-métrage</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/56/1752524_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230412210000 +0200" stop="20230412220300 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Jose James : Jazz à Vienne</title>
<desc lang="fr">José James - Jazz a Vienne - Since bursting onto the international scene in the late 2000s, José James and his honeyed voice are as bewitching as ever in this 2019 performance at Jazz à Vienne. Flitting between raw soul, soul-folk, hip-hop, and jazz, James is one of the few vocalists capable of keeping the crossover created by Ray Charles in the '50s alive. After sensitive and intelligent odes to Billie Holiday and John Coltrane, this time James pays tribute to a living legend of American popular music: soul man Bill Withers. James performs Bill Withers's unforgettable songs, accompanied by Marcus Machado (guitar), Aneesa Strings (bass, vocals), and Aaron Steele (drums).</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/07/01/1691820_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230412220300 +0200" stop="20230412230500 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Trio Macaiba</title>
<desc lang="fr">Trio Macaiba - Da Pá Virada Sessions - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the bands taking part in this series is Trio Macaíba, consisting of Beto Corrêa (accordion), Cléber Almeida (zabumba, a type of bass drum), and Ramon Vieira (triangle). Their use of a traditional instrument combination, as well as cultural research, which all members of the group are dedicated to, contributes to the authenticity of the music and their experience as musicians.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/53/1759065_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230412230500 +0200" stop="20230413000400 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Paulo Novaes - New Year's Eve Special</title>
<desc lang="fr">Paulo Novaes - New Year's Eve Special - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the artists taking part in this series is Paulo Novaes. Coming from a family of musicians, Paulo Novaes has already lived through a lifetime of music in spite of his young age. Paulo is the cousin of singer Bruna Caram, with whom he performed in São Paulo, Madrid, Barcelona, Lisbon, and other major cities. As a singer, composer, and instrumentalist, his creativity is enjoyed in many forms.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230413000400 +0200" stop="20230413014100 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Hugh Coltman</title>
<desc lang="fr">The English singer and composer Hugh Coltman started in blues rock band The Hoax, after which he moved to Paris and released two pop and folk albums. Jazz was beckoning and his next project was a tribute to singer and pianist Nat &quot;King&quot; Cole. Coltman recorded his album 'Who's Happy?' in New Orleans. With this he makes music of an important life question.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/07/57/1642181_A.jpg" />
</programme>