<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Voo -->
<programme start="20230405030000 +0200" stop="20230405034600 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">BIRD</title>
<desc lang="fr">BIRD - Five promising musicians get together in Rotterdam jazz club BIRD's artists-in-residence project &quot;The Nest&quot;. In this first broadcast we get to know Lisette Ma Neza (slam poet), Peter Somuah (trumpet), Michelle Samba (drums), Huy Le (bass), and Brenn Luiten (piano). Over the course of seven sessions, they exchange ideas, work on their projects, and play music together. Following this period, during which record producer Jameszoo and music manager Jochem Tromp offer their coaching experience, BIRD and North Sea Jazz Festival's fringe festival DownTown organize a tryout performance. Enjoy this unique collaboration of upcoming musicians!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/02/18/24/2148521_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230405034600 +0200" stop="20230405044500 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Monty Alexander à La Seine Musicale</title>
<desc lang="fr">Monty Alexander - Kingston-born pianist Monty Alexander is a virtuoso with many secrets. He explores the world of jazz, swing, bebop, blues, calypso and reggae, and has created a style of his own. For him, music is a heartbeat. He plays with emotion, intelligence, humor and sensibility. During this unique performance, we are transported with his joyful swing and fizzing grooves, influenced by Afro-American jazz from Harlem, and reggae from Jamaica. This 2018 concert at the Seine Musical is exceptional. It is extremely rare for Monty Alexander to do a solo performance. We are in for an evening full of surprises.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/10/1995865_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230405044500 +0200" stop="20230405054600 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Fedde Le Grand</title>
<desc lang="fr">Fedde Le Grand - DJ Fedde Le Grand plays his set at the Keukenhof, the Netherlands' exhibition of tulips, during the SLAM! Quarantaine Festival. This festival is a collaboration between the biggest Dutch DJs and radio channel SLAM. The DJs play on extraordinary locations, such as the Keukenhof, where Fedde Le Grand presents his set. The setlist features songs such as &quot;Deep In My Soul,&quot; &quot;JB's The Man,&quot; &quot;Smoke Machine,&quot; and &quot;You Should Know.&quot; Shots of Fedde Le Grand and his DJ table alternate with images of the beautiful colorful tulip fields at the Keukenhof.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230405054600 +0200" stop="20230405065400 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">BIGYUKI : BIRD 2019</title>
<desc lang="fr">BIGYUKI - BIRD 2019 - BIGYUKI's is New York City's secret musical weapon! His unprecedented sound has attracted the attention of many, including Grammy Award-winning and nominated artists such as Q-Tip, Bilal, Talib Kweli, Harvey Mason, Marcus Strickland, Mark Giuliana, and Meshell Ndegeocello. BIGYUKI's music offers a soulful exploration into the wondrous soundscapes of his infinitely virtuosic mind. Infusing elements of jazz, classical music, hip-hop, soul, rock, dance, and electronica, BIGYUKI reaches a new and inspiring level, with support from guitarist Randy Runyon and drummer Smithsoneon. It is hard to believe that just three musicians can create a sound this massive.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/59/1769392_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230405065400 +0200" stop="20230405074900 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Oum 2018</title>
<desc lang="fr">Oum - Music Meeting Festival 2018 - Oum El Ghait Benessahraoui, who is better known as Oum, gives a unique glance at ethnic Morrocan musical esthetics. The singer-songwriter is considered to be the ambassador of Morrocan culture, too. Deeply influenced by gospel, jazz, soul and R&amp;B genres, today Oum mixes more and more African music genres, such as Sufi, Hassani, or Afrobeat. Yet, the singer's voice still echoes the colours of Aretha Franklin, Ella Fitzgerald or Whitney Houston. It is the African American vocal tradition that made a huge impact on Oum since her early days as the singer. Performing from Music Meeting Festival in Nijmegen, The Netherlands, Oum charms the stage with an exotic sonic journey to the undiscovered lands of North Africa.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/04/1754386_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230405074900 +0200" stop="20230405090000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Frequencerz @ Airbeat One</title>
<desc lang="fr">Frequencerz @ Airbeat One - Frequencerz is a Dutch hardstyle duo formed by Pepijn Hol and Niels Koster. In 2009, they signed their contract with the Fusion Records label. Since then, they've released a good number of albums, such as Medium Rare, S.T.F.U. / G.T.F.O, and Phaser. With their performances for huge crowds at Defqon.1, Decibel Outdoor, and The Qontinent, they've established themselves as one of the biggest hardstyle acts of today. Their show at the German Airbeat One festival underlines their reputation. Expect nothing but spectacular light shows, non-stop jumpstyle, and a crazy crowd!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230405090000 +0200" stop="20230405101500 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Christian Scott - The Centennial Trilogy</title>
<desc lang="fr">In just a few years, young trumpet player Christian Scott has become synonymous with a new jazz generation. He shakes up the conventions of jazz by taking the genre to new horizons and reaching a wider audience. No doubt, at 33 years old, Christian Scott is already forging his own path. After each record release, he seems even more determined to challenge the rules of jazz with his own avant-garde style. At his 2018 show at La Coopérative de Mai, Christian Scott celebrates 100 years of jazz with the program &quot;The Centennial Trilogy.&quot; Expect a unique performance in an intimate theatre setting, shot in native 4K!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/04/1754386_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230405101500 +0200" stop="20230405110400 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">House of the Gipsies</title>
<desc lang="fr">House of the Gipsies - Sing Jazz 2018 - Since the Gypsy Kings made their triumphal debut on the music scene with their wild Spanish rumba four decades ago, no band has dared to follow in their footsteps ... until now! House of the Gipsies updates the raw rhythms of nomadic tribes in Rajasthan, India, collaborating with Manganiyar musicians Manjoor, Nehru and Dilawar Khan. The result is a unique sound that can be described as Indo-Gypsy fusion, which is part of the evolution of the Spanish rumba. Do not miss this eclectic performance sure to please music lovers of all generations, presented at the 2018 Sing Jazz Festival.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/28/02/2145502_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230405110400 +0200" stop="20230405120400 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Filo Machado</title>
<desc lang="fr">Filo Machado - Da Pá Virada Sessions - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the artists taking part in this series is Filo Machado. Born in São Paulo, this singer, composer, instrumentalist, arranger, and producer has celebrated many musical successes. Filo Machado took part in saxophonist Jane Bunnett's Canadian tour with her spectacular project 'Rendez-Vous Brazil/Cuba'. He has appeared at the jazz festivals of Córsega and Uzeste and opened for the one and only Nina Simone in Cannes.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230405120400 +0200" stop="20230405133600 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Fred Hersch Trio</title>
<desc lang="fr">Fred Hersch Trio - Jazz à Ramatuelle - At the age of 63, Fred Hersch is unquestionably one of today's key figures in jazz piano. His music touches upon millions of nuances, contains a keen sense of harmony, and displays an intrinsic knowledge of the standard repertoire. What else made him the teacher of Brad Mehldau and sideman of Stan Getz, Joe Henderson and Art Farmer? Since his recovery from a long coma in 2008, Fred Hersch has experienced a spectacular artistic renaissance. With numerous albums as composer as well as interpreter, he has managed to establish himself as a role model of jazz piano. Supported by John Hebert (double bass) and Eric McPherson (drums), Fred Hersch showcases his unparalleled technique and sensitivity at Jazz à Ramatuelle 2018.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230405133600 +0200" stop="20230405140900 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Lost Heritage</title>
<desc lang="fr">Classical:NEXT 2019 - Lost Heritage - François Vasseur and Pierre Chataignon make up the French electronic and contemporary music duo Lost Heritage. Living in the region of Geneva, they are two music lovers interested in jazz, classical, urban, and electronic music. François Vasseur is an electronic composer and pianist. He has been working on electronics for many years, starting as a DJ, then as a musician and composer, while also working in the field of cultural mediation and public engagement for organisations like the Verbier Festival, the Geneva Opera and the Lyon Baroque Music Festival. Pierre Chataignon works on various projects across many musical styles, from world music to electronic, as well as in film sound production and voice-over projects that require high quality sound recording, mixing, and production.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/24/07/2123267_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230405140900 +0200" stop="20230405150000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Life</title>
<desc lang="fr">Echoes Series: Life - Echoes is a modern live music show hosted by Jehnny Beth (lead singer in the British band Savages). It presents leading and emerging bands and artists from the contemporary scene. The show takes place underneath the Palais de Tokyo museum in Paris, in the club of brutalist architecture, the &quot;Yoyo.&quot; The live sets are 30 minutes long and take place on a customized stage, creating closeness with the audience. The intimate, immersive space lends to the atmosphere of the show. The artistic direction by Antoine Carlier follows a minimalist, refined and pure aesthetic, allowing the artists' energy and emotions to take center stage. This episode features the band Life. Their set includes the songs &quot;Excites Me,&quot; &quot;Hollow Thing,&quot; and &quot;Moral Fibre.&quot;.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230405150000 +0200" stop="20230405160100 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">The Bloody Beetroots</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Bloody Beetroots - The Bloody Beetroots is the creation of Sir Bob Cornelius Rifo. Inspired by his lifelong love of punk rock and comic books, Rifo unleashed The Bloody Beetroots in late 2006 and has since crafted an intense sound that mixes his classical training, his punk rock obsession, and his passion for electronic music into an edgy rock-meets-dance hybrid sound. In 2019, The Bloody Beetroots released the Heavy EP, which sees Rifo revisiting his classic electro style and features collaborations with Ephwurd and Dr. Fresch, in addition to three new solo originals. Enjoy his show at Nameless Music Festival 2019!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230405160100 +0200" stop="20230405171100 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Michelle David - Jazz in Duketown</title>
<desc lang="fr">Michelle David - Jazz in Duketown - Jazz in Duketown is the largest free outdoor jazz festival in the Netherlands. It's a real gathering for jazz addicts, inviting internationally renowned artists. The talented American singer Michelle David performs pop and gospel music that feeds the heart and soothes the soul. Having grown up with the church, she started singing at the age of four. A year later she joined her first band, The Mission of Love. In 1980 she enrolled at Fiorello H. LaGuardia High School of Music &amp; Art and Performing Arts in New York City, known from the film 'Fame'. During this time, she appeared as an extra in the legendary comedy film 'Ghostbusters'. Musicals and tours with the bands of Diana Ross and Michael Bolton followed.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/19/1853106_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230405171100 +0200" stop="20230405184100 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">La Mambanegra : Music Meeting Festival</title>
<desc lang="fr">La Mambanegra - Music Meeting Festival 2018 - The latin music orchestra, La Mambanegra, combines many musical elements, such as Jamaican or Colombian music, as well as Funk and Hip Hop. Yet, their main musical influence comes from 1970s New York, where during the time Salsa was born. The magic of the genre, however, is given new colours by La Mambanegra: with a series of fantastic adventures in Cali, La Habana and New York, the band's music is inspired by an anonymous and even mythical hero of the Cali's popular neighborhood Barrio Obrero. Consisting of 8 talented musicians, La Mambanegra presents their charming showcase at the Music Meeting Festival in Nijmegen, The Netherlands.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/13/1750348_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230405184100 +0200" stop="20230405192200 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">WOMEX 2018</title>
<desc lang="fr">Rob Thorne Toi Puo - WOMEX 2018 - Since 1994, World Music Expo (WOMEX) has been attracting musicians, agents, a great number of press agencies, as well as media companies from all over the world. Its main exposition event has been held in various locations throughout Europe, including Berlin, Brussels, Marseille, Stockholm, Seville, Cardiff, and Budapest. In 2018, WOMEX was held in Las Palmas, Gran Canaria. One of its showcase participants, composer/performer/anthropologist Rob Thorne, is a diverse explorer in the newly revived evolution of taonga puoro, traditional M?ori instruments, fusing these ancient voices with modern sounds and technology. He creates ethereal and immersive site-specific works as well as contemporary chamber music, born out of in-depth research and respect for tradition.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/29/16/2143305_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230405192200 +0200" stop="20230405203500 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Chloé - Trabendo Paris</title>
<desc lang="fr">Chloé - Trabendo Paris - Chloé has, without a doubt, led an entire generation to her electronic music playground - one that goes beyond strictly club and techno. As much a film music enthusiast as an accomplished guitar player, she stumbled into the electronic scene early on, developing an unwavering curiosity for sound machines. Chloé is a composer, and she gives life to artistic ideas. The challenge is to stay unwavering in spite of self-doubt that arises throughout the creative process. It is precisely this inner questioning, this contradiction, that nourishes and motivates Chloé's work. Chloé dedicates a full set to her 2017 album Endless Revisions. At Trabendo Paris, she plays these brand-new songs only a few weeks after the album was released.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/59/1769392_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230405203500 +0200" stop="20230405210000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Flaws</title>
<desc lang="fr">Songbook - &quot;I never heard anyone say that, and yeah, I know exactly what it means. It has to go in there, this has to be a song.&quot; Every song has its own story, and we all think it's a story we've heard before, but we haven't. Songbook finds and captures these intriguing stories by pulling you into the process of writing and composing. Known for its pristine sound, cinematic 4k video and eye for detail, Songbook live-captured episodes emphasize the paramount importance of quality. It addresses the on-the-spot elements of blending song and location at the right moment. Both the magical location and remarkable music interaction will get the attention they deserve. Simply because Songbook isn't just a live music session, it lives.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230405210000 +0200" stop="20230405220300 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Jose James : Jazz à Vienne</title>
<desc lang="fr">José James - Jazz a Vienne - Since bursting onto the international scene in the late 2000s, José James and his honeyed voice are as bewitching as ever in this 2019 performance at Jazz à Vienne. Flitting between raw soul, soul-folk, hip-hop, and jazz, James is one of the few vocalists capable of keeping the crossover created by Ray Charles in the '50s alive. After sensitive and intelligent odes to Billie Holiday and John Coltrane, this time James pays tribute to a living legend of American popular music: soul man Bill Withers. James performs Bill Withers's unforgettable songs, accompanied by Marcus Machado (guitar), Aneesa Strings (bass, vocals), and Aaron Steele (drums).</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/20/48/1691820_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230405220300 +0200" stop="20230405230600 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Tribute to Elis Regina</title>
<desc lang="fr">Tribute to Elis Regina - Da Pá Virada Sessions - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the bands taking part in this episode is a foursome that pays tribute to pioneering música popular brasileira vocalist Elis Regina: vocalist Vanessa Moreno, bassist Fi Marostica, Rhodes and keyboard player Tiago Costa, and drummer Jonatas Sansao honor the legendary Brazilian singer by performing famous pieces and hidden gems from her repertoire.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230405230600 +0200" stop="20230406000100 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Altin Gün : Bird, Rotterdam</title>
<desc lang="fr">Mediterranean sounds meet western music in this performance by the band Altin Gün. Their unusual approach to traditional Turkish folk music produces an overall sound full of ethnic, funky, and even psychedelic influences. With their infinite energy, Altin Gün takes the audience on an amazing sonic roller coaster: a ride full of emotion and fun. Altin Gün consists of six talented musicians who share a great passion for Turkish music. In this live recording from BIRD Rotterdam, one of the Netherlands' most important music venues, the band presents their new album &quot;On&quot; to the enthusiastic audience.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/19/1975203_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230406000100 +0200" stop="20230406013900 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Moderat at Stereolux 2016</title>
<desc lang="fr">Moderat at Stereolux 2016 - Since the German bands Modeselektor (Gernot Bronsert and Sebastian Szary) and Apparat (Sascha Ring) joined forces in 2009, they have been hugely successful as the electronic music supergroup Moderat. In 2012, the formation produced the soundtrack of Xavier Dolan's film Laurence Anyways, released as A New Error. According to Les Inrockuptibles, their album II includes &quot;the rhythmic punch of the one (Modeselektor) and atmospheric finesse of the other (Apparat) combine perfectly.&quot; In 2016, the threesome returned with an eagerly anticipated third album, III, which they present in this program, live on stage at Stereolux in Nantes, France.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>