<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Voo -->
<programme start="20230411030000 +0200" stop="20230411042100 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">HVOB</title>
<desc lang="fr">HVOB - The two musicians behind HVOB are Anna Müller and Paul Wallner. Anna Müller composes, produces, and provides the captivating, hypnotic vocals. The final production of the tracks is done in collaboration with Paul Wallner in his Vienna studio. HVOB are carving their path not just with their distinctive sound but with their live performances as well. The duo always plays live and performs with a drummer - a concept as innovative as it is successful: HVOB has just been voted number two best live act by the most influential German electronic music magazine &quot;De:bug.&quot; Enjoy their 2019 show at Trabendo Paris!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Musique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/59/1769392_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230411042100 +0200" stop="20230411050800 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Etenesh Wassie Trio : WOMEX 2018</title>
<desc lang="fr">In 2018 WOMEX took place in Las Palmas in Gran Canaria. One of the participants was the Ethiopian diva Etenesh Wassie with her trio. She mixes the contemporary energy of jazz and punk with her in-depth knowledge of the Ethiopian repertoire. The result is compelling, inspired, and truly unique.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/29/16/2143305_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230411050800 +0200" stop="20230411060000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Giana Viscardi - New Year's Eve Special</title>
<desc lang="fr">Giana Viscardi - New Year's Eve Special - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the bands taking part in this series is the duo of Giana Viscardi and Gustavo Marques. After starting their career together, Giana Viscardi and Gustavo Marques released music in many places around the world. After returning to Brazil, they worked together on Giana's album &quot;ORUM&quot;, performing in Africa, Europe, and Brazil.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230411060000 +0200" stop="20230411073500 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Opera Imaginaire</title>
<desc lang="fr">Opera Imaginaire - To celebrate Le Concert Spirituel's 30th anniversary, conductor Hervé Niquet collaborated with the Baroque Music Center of Versailles to build his opéra imaginaire. For this unique project, Le Concert Spirituel presents an original performance of unpublished operas by Lully, Rameau, Charpentier, and many other French baroque composers. You will find yourself captivated by a tearful lover, intrigued by the passage to the underworld, and fascinated by the descents of the Gods. The program includes many favorite passages, such as Lully's Armide, Charpentier's Medea, and Campra's Carnaval de Venise. Experience all the magic of Louis XIV's French opera as Le Concert Spirituel transforms the Théâtre des Champs-Elysées into a true French baroque scene.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/03/1781759_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230411073500 +0200" stop="20230411081600 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">City Beats</title>
<desc lang="fr">City Beats - Episode 3 - Berlin - DJ-producer Carly Foxx is on a musical journey, immersing herself in the life of five iconic European cities to find inspiration for a series of new tracks. In this episode, Carly Foxx journeys to Berlin, one of the world's undisputed techno capitals, and discovers the sound of freedom buried in its history. She starts her journey at the heart of the city: Alexanderplatz. Passersby tell her the music scene is very alternative, and there is a big techno scene, which is why Carly decides to meet up with techno producer Mijk van Dijk. Inspired by his interview, she records some sounds that characterize the city. Carly also records a vocalist and adds the sound of a classic '80s synthesizer: the 303. She finalizes her mix in the studio and presents it to a wild Berlin audience in the club.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Télé-Réalité</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/07/29/2180892_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230411081600 +0200" stop="20230411090000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">reConvert Project</title>
<desc lang="fr">Classical:NEXT 2019 - reConvert Project - The concept of percussion has been altered significantly by the evolution of the instrument. The methods of the innovative reConvert Project are unique and dedicated to changing the face of the percussionist world, by working actively with composers such as Georges Aperghis, Simon Steen Andersen, Michael Maierhof and Jorge Sánchez-Chiong and premiering over a dozen works written to help train emerging young composers. The reConvert philosophy is based on the re-examination of the aesthetic use of percussion instruments, where musical discourse is analysed and adapted to their creative needs. With numerous works using unconventional instruments and staging, a whole new experience is created for the listener.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/24/07/2123267_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230411090000 +0200" stop="20230411100400 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">La Fraîcheur</title>
<desc lang="fr">La Fraîcheur - For over a decade now, first in Paris, then Montreal and now in Berlin, La Fraîcheur has been brewing her blend of deep house and techno beats, making a name for herself with her signature sound of emotionally charged and acid techno sets. The queer feminist-activist is a marathon DJ who can go on for countless hours, running the gamut from classics to new songs released just hours earlier. Her craft expanded by producing music ranging from ravy epic techno to dark pumping electro, spacious open-air deep house to melancholic electronica. She wrote her critically acclaimed debut album during an artist residency with the Berlin-Detroit Connection.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/59/1769392_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230411100400 +0200" stop="20230411110200 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Nile Rodgers</title>
<desc lang="fr">The popular music performance series Front and Center premiered nationwide on public television in 2016, and now returns for Season 6. The series boasts 22, one-hour episodes and an all-star line-up. This episode features Nile Rodgers. He started his musical career by the end of the '60s. A decade later, he scored a hit with Chic's debut single &quot;Dance Dance Dance,&quot; followed by &quot;Le Freak&quot; from the second album C'est Chic. At Front and Center, Nile Rodgers performs his most well-known songs such as &quot;Get Lucky&quot; and &quot;We Are Family.&quot; In between the songs, Nile Rodgers shares personal stories about his dreams and how they have come true. Enjoy this intimate Front and Center show!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/58/1754433_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230411110200 +0200" stop="20230411123800 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Atys en folie</title>
<desc lang="fr">Atys en Folie - Atys en folie is a parody of Jean-Baptiste Lully's lyrical tragedy Atys (1676). Atys, Lully's most famous opera, was a constant subject of parody throughout the 18th century. Stage director Jean-Philippe Desrousseaux drew on several parodies to create this original production for singers, puppets, and musicians to revive the work. Princes, princesses, and kings are relegated to peasants, market gardeners, and fishmongers in the countryside. Among the performers are Alain Buet, Marie Lenormand, and Arnaud Marzorati. Gaëlle Trimardeau, Bruno Coulon and Jean-Philippe Desrousseaux feature as puppeteers. The music is performed by ensemble La Clique des Lunaisiens, conducted by Arnaud Marzorati. This performance was recorded at Teatru Manoel in Valletta, Malta, in 2017.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/02/04/18/1768814_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230411123800 +0200" stop="20230411132500 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Jacob Karlzon Trio - Open Waters</title>
<desc lang="fr">Together with the Danish bassist Morten Ramsbøl and the Swedish drummer Rasmus Kihlberg, the Swedish pianist Jacob Karlzon presents the album &quot;Open Waters&quot; in the Hamburg factory of piano builder Steinway. The trained pianist, who shared the stage with Kenny Wheeler, Norma Winstone and Billy Cobham, honors the rich tradition of eclectic Swedish jazz. In 2012 he explored heavy metal, then applied electronics to determine the beat.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/19/1853106_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230411132500 +0200" stop="20230411142400 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Roger Sanchez</title>
<desc lang="fr">Roger Sanchez - Self-made man and true legend of house music, Roger Sanchez perfectly embodies the spirit of Pacha Festival Bali. Sanchez had a humble debut in New York, but the days when he was spinning vinyls for his friends in Queens living rooms are far behind him. Today, he is the headliner of major festivals around the globe, and resident DJ of clubs in Ibiza's sights, such as the Pacha Club. With this DJ set at Pacha Festival, Sanchez brings some of the magic of Ibiza to the beaches of Bali. Expect lots of energy, breathtaking lights, and even fireworks!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230411142400 +0200" stop="20230411150200 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Nilufer Yanya</title>
<desc lang="fr">Echoes Series: Nilufer Yanya - Echoes is a modern live music show hosted by Jehnny Beth (lead singer in the British band Savages). It presents leading and emerging bands and artists from the contemporary scene. The show takes place underneath the Palais de Tokyo museum in Paris, in the club of brutalist architecture, the &quot;Yoyo.&quot; The live sets are 30 minutes long and take place on a customized stage, creating closeness with the audience. The intimate, immersive space lends to the atmosphere of the show. The artistic direction by Antoine Carlier follows a minimalist, refined and pure aesthetic, allowing the artists' energy and emotions to take center stage. This episode features Nilüfer Yanya. Her set includes the songs &quot;The Florist,&quot; &quot;Angels,&quot; and &quot;The Unordained.&quot;.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230411150200 +0200" stop="20230411162900 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Incognito</title>
<desc lang="fr">Incognito - Sing Jazz 2018 - An acid jazz project rooted in the 1970s jazz/funk/soul world, Incognito was originally formed by Jean-Paul &quot;Bluey&quot; Maunick and Paul &quot;Tubbs&quot; Williams. Both were original members of the late 1970s disco/funk group Light of the World. They decided to take a couple of their jams into the studio and debuted with the single Parisienne Girl. Decades later, Incognito's cover of Boz Scaggs' classic Lowdown with Chaka Khan and Mario Biondi saw the band's international status grow more and more popular. At Sing Jazz 2018, Incognito takes a fresh direction on classic musical themes, giving their fans an unforgettable live show!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/03/2145502_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230411162900 +0200" stop="20230411172700 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Steve Vai</title>
<desc lang="fr">Steve Vai - The popular music performance series, Front and Center, which premiered nationwide on public television, in 2016, returns for Season 6. The series boasts 22, one-hour episodes and an all-star line-up. This episode features Steve Vai, the legendary guitarist who was voted the 10th Greatest Guitarist by Guitar World magazine, who treats fans to songs from his three-decade long career. As an independent guitarist he has won three Grammy Awards. Vai's solo sophomore release, Passion and Warfare, has earned gold certification in the US. At Front and Center he sits down and discusses his early interest in composing music and playing guitar as well as the many fortunes of his career.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Musique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/42/1870646_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230411172700 +0200" stop="20230411194000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam</title>
<desc lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam - New Cool Collective is one of the foremost Dutch jazz ensembles. Pioneering new blends of music styles since 1993, NCC has performed in various formations, from small combos to larger ensembles and even big bands! The ensemble's high energy is cut out for the dance floors, as dance, Latin, salsa, afrobeat and boogaloo all meet in a jazzy mix. NCC includes saxophonist Benjamin Herman, guitarist Rory Ronde, drummer Joost Kroon, percussionists Frank van Dok and Jos de Haas, pianist Willem Friede, bassist Leslie Lopez, and trumpeter David Rockefeller.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230411194000 +0200" stop="20230411210000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Robin Schulz, Sam Feldt, Afrojack &amp; Alle Farben - Parookaville</title>
<desc lang="fr">Parookaville - Parookaville is a city that comes to life once a year to keep the legend of Bill Parooka alive. It was started as an artistic, free-flowing, wild, and musical place where people could connect with their pure selves, experience real connections, and feel a deep sense of bliss and fulfillment. Step into the darkness if you dare, follow your inner light and immerse yourself in a spectacular world of freedom and love! Only four years since the first event, this festival has already become one of Germany's most prevalent music festivals. This edition features Armin van Buuren, Showtek, Robin Schulz, and W&amp;W.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230411210000 +0200" stop="20230411222400 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Mosè in Egitto</title>
<desc lang="fr">Mosè in Egitto - The spectacular Milan Cathedral - the fifth-largest church in the world, which took six centuries to build - provides the setting for this lavish performance of Gioachino Rossini's opera &quot;Mosè&quot;. Rossini created &quot;Mosè in Egitto&quot; for the Teatro San Carlo in Naples in 1818-19 but later revised and expanded it for the Paris Opera. The French opera &quot;Moïse et Pharaon&quot;, of which Mosè is the Italian transcript, is a dropsical affair, decked out with ballet sequences, and embellished with the kind of effects Cecil B de Mille would later favor when dealing with Biblical epics. There is nothing of that here. In this pared-down Mosè, the action focuses on Moses's confrontations with the Egyptians and Amenofi's (Pharaoh's son) love for Moses's niece Anaide.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/07/36/1871763_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230411222400 +0200" stop="20230411231900 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Oum 2018</title>
<desc lang="fr">Oum - Music Meeting Festival 2018 - Oum El Ghait Benessahraoui, who is better known as Oum, gives a unique glance at ethnic Morrocan musical esthetics. The singer-songwriter is considered to be the ambassador of Morrocan culture, too. Deeply influenced by gospel, jazz, soul and R&amp;B genres, today Oum mixes more and more African music genres, such as Sufi, Hassani, or Afrobeat. Yet, the singer's voice still echoes the colours of Aretha Franklin, Ella Fitzgerald or Whitney Houston. It is the African American vocal tradition that made a huge impact on Oum since her early days as the singer. Performing from Music Meeting Festival in Nijmegen, The Netherlands, Oum charms the stage with an exotic sonic journey to the undiscovered lands of North Africa.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/04/1754386_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230411231900 +0200" stop="20230412002800 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Skunk Anansie</title>
<desc lang="fr">Les Vieilles Charrues - British alternative rock group Skunk Anansie celebrates its 25th anniversary with the album 25LIVE@25. These 90s rock scene icons, whose hair-raising shows have become legendary, celebrate their storied career with this 25-song project. With a selection of recordings taken from various 2017 live performances, Skunk Anansie once again proves its unbeatable power on stage. The setlist includes &quot;Because of You,&quot; &quot;The Skank Heads,&quot; and &quot;Tear the Place Up.&quot; Don't miss the triumphant return of these pillars of rock to the stage of the 28th edition of Les Vieilles Charrues in Carhaix, France, in 2019!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/20/00/2008125_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230412002800 +0200" stop="20230412014700 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Chaka Khan</title>
<desc lang="fr">Chaka Khan - Chaka Khan, also known as the &quot;Queen of Funk,&quot; has sold about 70 million records worldwide in her nearly five-decade-long career. This unique singer masters many musical genres, including R&amp;B, pop, rock, gospel, country, international music, and classical music. For this concert, the 10-times Grammy Award-winning artist returns to her hometown, where she gives the performance of a lifetime to an appreciative audience. With her nine-piece band and three backing vocalists, she performs a smashing selection of her greatest hits, including &quot;I'm Every Woman,&quot; &quot;Ain't Nobody,&quot; and &quot;Tell Me Something Good.&quot; Join this world-famous superstar in this concert recorded at the Harris Theatre in Chicago, filmed in spectacular 4K.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Musique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>