<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Voo -->
<programme start="20230512024000 +0200" stop="20230512030000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">José James</title>
<desc lang="fr">Songbook - &quot;I never heard anyone say that, and yeah, I know exactly what it means. It has to go in there, this has to be a song.&quot; Every song has its own story, and we all think it's a story we've heard before, but we haven't. Songbook finds and captures these intriguing stories by pulling you into the process of writing and composing. Known for its pristine sound, cinematic 4k video, and eye for detail, Songbook live-captured episodes emphasize the paramount importance of quality. It addresses the on-the-spot elements of blending song and location at the right moment. Both the magical location and remarkable music interaction will get the attention they deserve. Simply because Songbook isn't just a live music session, it lives. This episode of Songbook features eclectic R&amp;B artist José James.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230512030000 +0200" stop="20230512040300 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Fabrizio Rat : Artemix</title>
<desc lang="fr">Fabrizio Rat - Since his teenage years, Fabrizio has worked simultaneously on both classical and electronic music productions. He's definitely not the classical music guy who has just discovered techno. Throughout his apprentice years at the musical academy in Turin, he was working as a producer in dance music studios at the same time, hiding his &quot;double life&quot; to both the professors and the DJs. Arriving in Paris in 2007, his objective starts to take shape. Fabrizio combines the acoustic sounds and weird harmonics of his prepared piano with the acid loops of the TB-303 and the beats of the TR-909. Unsurprisingly, it's in front of the dancefloor, in clubs or festivals, that Fabrizio plays his live sets. With the right hand, he plays repetitive rhythmical patterns while the left one handles the machines and manipulates the piano strings.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/43/1767478_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230512040300 +0200" stop="20230512050700 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Dipha Barus</title>
<desc lang="fr">Dipha Barus - Dipha Barus has received several career awards, including the 2014 DJ of The Year at the Paranoia Awards and has been recognized by Rolling Stone Magazine. He has produced several popular hits in Indonesia, and recently released the amazing &quot;No One Can Stop Us&quot; with local star Kallula. Discover this Indonesian platinum star at the Pacha Festival in Bali, with a cocktail in hand, and let yourself be transported under the tropical sun.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/59/1769392_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230512050700 +0200" stop="20230512063500 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Ron Carter : Foursight</title>
<desc lang="fr">Ron Carter - Foursight - An evening with the &quot;Foursight&quot; quartet takes you on a tour of Ron Carter's discography, with two thousand five hundred albums, which is to say the consideration he has received since his debut in 1959. After accompanying Jacky Byard and Eric Dolphy, he joined Miles Davis' legendary VSOP with Herbie Hancock, Wayne Shorter, and Tony Williams, among others. Much more than an accompanist, the double bassist is above all a great soloist, as much in intimate trios as in advanced experimental formations or large orchestras. He will be remarkably surrounded here, during his &quot;Foursight&quot; show at Jazz sous les pommiers 2019.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230512063500 +0200" stop="20230512071800 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Null + Void</title>
<desc lang="fr">Null + Void - While few people are familiar with the Null + Void project, many have already heard Kurt Uenala's music. After making his debut under the pseudonym Kap10Kurt in 2003, Uenala caught the attention of the world with the play &quot;Die Sleeping&quot;. This critical and popular success has led to collaborations with several big names in music, including Moby, The Kills, and Dave Gahan, singer of Depeche Mode, for whom Uenala has subsequently signed plays. Spending more and more time in his Manhattan studio, Uenala developed a unique sound made of angular beats and dark soundscapes, which gave rise to a new melancholy solo project called Null + Void. Cryosleep, Uenala's first album under this new banner, includes several titles inspired by retro science fiction, new wave and electronic innovators.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/06/2111709_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230512071800 +0200" stop="20230512090000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Oumou Sangaré @ Jazz Sous Les Pommiers</title>
<desc lang="fr">Salif Keita described her as the &quot;Tina Turner of Mali.&quot; Indeed, Oumou Sangaré is one of Africa's most important female voices. While maintaining her political views as a champion of women's rights in Africa, her vocal talent has brought this singer to shine at some of the most important venues around the world. At Jazz Sous Les Pommiers 2017, Oumou Sangaré presents her latest album, Mogoya. She is accompanied by a group that combines traditional African instruments with a modern band set-up, featuring young French musicians. Recorded in spectacular 4K in a beautiful musical setting, Sangaré will surely make you sing and dance!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230512090000 +0200" stop="20230512101900 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Bad Company : Live From Red Rocks</title>
<desc lang="fr">Soundstage, an innovative and prestigious program, achieved widespread critical acclaim while featuring artists that defined the era. On May 15, 2016, at Red Rocks Amphitheater in Colorado, Soundstage captured the legendary classic rock band Bad Company delivering their biggest hits. The band consists of bassist Boz Burrell, guitarist Mick Ralphs, singer Paul Rodgers, and drummer Simon Kirke. The setlist contains their greatest songs, such as &quot;Live for the Music,&quot; &quot;Ready for Love,&quot; &quot;Can't Get Enough&quot; and &quot;Rock Steady.&quot;.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230512101900 +0200" stop="20230512110400 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Invisible World : WOMEX 2018</title>
<desc lang="fr">One of the participants was the band Invisible World, which operates at the crossroads where Eastern European and Mediterranean influences come together and break new ground. Invisible World is led by the inventive Czech bassist Tomá? Li?ka, together with the Turkish violinist Efe Turumtay, the Serbian accordionist Nikola Zari? and the Moravian drummer Kamil Slezák.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/29/16/2143305_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230512110400 +0200" stop="20230512120000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">The Go! Team @ Route du Rock Hivers</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Go! Team @ Route du Rock Hivers - Originating from Brighton, UK, The Go! Team blends garage/indie rock with distorted guitars and a popping brass section. The creative force behind this six-piece band is Ian Parton. According to him, the band samples everything from Bollywood to hip-hop. Although the samples are at the heart of the band's sound, every song is kicked off by the melody. At Route du Rock Hivers 2018, The Go! Team presents its latest album, Semicircle. Its opening track Mayday is built around a drum loop based on Morse code. This is only the beginning of the endless variety of sound effects The Go! Team experiments with. At their 4K show at Rock Hivers 2018, you will enjoy a blend of noisy pop, hip-hop collages, awesome grooves, irresistible soul arrangements and much more!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/42/1870646_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230512120000 +0200" stop="20230512133700 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Hugh Coltman</title>
<desc lang="fr">The English singer and composer Hugh Coltman started in blues rock band The Hoax, after which he moved to Paris and released two pop and folk albums. Jazz was beckoning and his next project was a tribute to singer and pianist Nat &quot;King&quot; Cole. Coltman recorded his album 'Who's Happy?' in New Orleans. With this he makes music of an important life question.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/07/57/1642181_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230512133700 +0200" stop="20230512141000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Ensemble HOPE</title>
<desc lang="fr">Classical:NEXT 2019 - Ensemble HOPE - The Ensemble HOPE is dedicated to the performance and creation of music of today. As well as exploring new forms of contemporary electro-acoustic technology, it integrates written musical tradition, improvisation and an adapted classical repertoire. The &quot;Cristal Baschet&quot; and the &quot;Euphone&quot; form the basis of the ensemble's sophisticated instrumental collection. The new works reflect these neglected and little-known instruments. The Ensemble HOPE, consisting of Frederic Bousquet (Euphone), Marc Antoine Millon (Bass Cristal) and Armelle Marq (soprano voice), is also actively engaged in developing a new generation of Euphones. In this concert from 2019's Classical:NEXT!, the ensemble performs Frederic Bousquet's &quot;Vénus&quot;, &quot;Epilogue&quot; and &quot;en transit,&quot; Henry Purcell's &quot;Dido's lament,&quot; arranged by M.A.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/24/07/2123267_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230512141000 +0200" stop="20230512150000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Echoes Series: Fontaines DC</title>
<desc lang="fr">Echoes Series: Fontaines DC - Echoes is a modern live music show hosted by Jehnny Beth (lead singer in the British band Savages). It presents leading and emerging bands and artists from the contemporary scene. The show takes place underneath the Palais de Tokyo museum in Paris, in the club of brutalist architecture, the &quot;Yoyo.&quot; The live sets are 30 minutes long and take place on a customized stage, creating closeness with the audience. The intimate, immersive space lends to the atmosphere of the show. The artistic direction by Antoine Carlier follows a minimalist, refined and pure aesthetic, allowing the artists' energy and emotions to take center stage. This episode features the band Fontaines DC. Their set includes the songs &quot;A Hero's Death,&quot; &quot;Hurricane Laughter,&quot; and &quot;I Don't Belong.&quot;.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/04/2122118_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230512150000 +0200" stop="20230512160400 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Nilüfer Yanya - Echoes Series: Nilufer Yanya</title>
<desc lang="fr">Echoes Series - Episode 6 - Echoes is a modern live music show hosted by Jehnny Beth (lead singer in the British band Savages). It presents leading and emerging bands and artists from the contemporary scene. The show takes place underneath the Palais de Tokyo museum in Paris, in the club of brutalist architecture, the &quot;Yoyo.&quot; The live sets are 30 minutes long and take place on a customized stage, creating closeness with the audience. Once the bands have performed, Jehnny Beth invites everyone to sit at her roundtable for a group conversation. The open discussions in every episode allow the audience to understand the rapport, artistic exchange, and intellectual debates that run through this eclectic musical universe. The intimate, immersive space lends to the atmosphere of the show.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/03/1754401_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230512160400 +0200" stop="20230512170200 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Liam Gallagher</title>
<desc lang="fr">Liam Gallagher - After leading iconic British rock band Oasis for nearly two decades, Manchester-born singer Liam Gallagher launched his solo career in 2016. He played his first ever U.S. solo show on July 28th of 2017 at Manhattan's McKittrick Hotel in New York City. The rather small venue is known to host the immersive theater experience &quot;Sleep No More&quot;, and its limited capacities made for an intense and intimate concert experience. In a 75-minute long show featuring thirteen songs, Gallagher performed tracks of his 2017 debut album As You Were, next to a list of Oasis fan favorites. Shot in phenomenally sharp 4K, this recording offers viewers the unique opportunity to become part of the audience of this secret session.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230512170200 +0200" stop="20230512183800 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Opera Imaginaire</title>
<desc lang="fr">Opera Imaginaire - To celebrate Le Concert Spirituel's 30th anniversary, conductor Hervé Niquet collaborated with the Baroque Music Center of Versailles to build his opéra imaginaire. For this unique project, Le Concert Spirituel presents an original performance of unpublished operas by Lully, Rameau, Charpentier, and many other French baroque composers. You will find yourself captivated by a tearful lover, intrigued by the passage to the underworld, and fascinated by the descents of the Gods. The program includes many favorite passages, such as Lully's Armide, Charpentier's Medea, and Campra's Carnaval de Venise. Experience all the magic of Louis XIV's French opera as Le Concert Spirituel transforms the Théâtre des Champs-Elysées into a true French baroque scene.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/03/1781759_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230512183800 +0200" stop="20230512192600 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">WOMEX 2018</title>
<desc lang="fr">In 2018 WOMEX took place in Las Palmas in Gran Canaria. One of the participants was Ladama, five multi-instrumentalists from Venezuela, Brazil, Colombia and the United States. In addition to their performances as a band, the five women work with workshops and other collaborations to enthuse the youth for music, composition and audio editing. Ladama is a positive force in times when the need for tolerance and communication is greater than ever.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/29/16/2143305_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230512192600 +0200" stop="20230512202500 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Paulo Novaes</title>
<desc lang="fr">Paulo Novaes - Da Pá Virada Sessions - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the artists taking part in this series is Paulo Novaes. Coming from a family of musicians, Paulo Novaes has already lived through a lifetime of music in spite of his young age. Paulo is the cousin of singer Bruna Caram, with whom he performed in São Paulo, Madrid, Barcelona, Lisbon, and other major cities. As a singer, composer, and instrumentalist, his creativity is enjoyed in many forms.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230512202500 +0200" stop="20230512210000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">?nied?</title>
<desc lang="fr">Classical:NEXT 2019 - ?nied? - ?nied? is a voice and electronics duo from Warsaw, Poland who combine extended vocal techniques with improvised, self-named &quot;glitchtronica.&quot; Singer, performer, and sound artist Aleksandra Klimczak frequently breaks boundaries between art genres through cooperating with young artists from different artistic fields. Her work has been awarded from scholarships from the Polish Ministry of Culture and the Capital City of Warsaw. Music curator Antoni Beksiak deals with contemporary crossover, ethnic, classical, jazz, and pop music in his work as an initiator, critic and creator. During this showcase recorded at Classical:NEXT 2019 in Rotterdam, The Netherlands the perform a set list of their own works.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/24/07/2123267_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230512210000 +0200" stop="20230512215100 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Lee Scratch Perry</title>
<desc lang="fr">Lee &quot;Scratch&quot; Perry is a Jamaican musician, a pioneer in the development of dub music in the 1970s. He remixes existing reggae tracks with studio effects, creating a new sound. During the early 2000s, Perry won a Grammy for Best Reggae album, and was ranked in the Rolling Stone list of 100 Greatest Artists of All Time. He has collaborated with a variety of great artists, most notably Bob Marley, whose compositions he still incorporates in his show. During his 2017 show at Philharmonie de Paris, you will enjoy well-known reggae songs like Punk Reggae Party, Sun Is Shining, and Soul Fire. Recorded in 4K, it promises to be a groovy and spectacular show!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230512215100 +0200" stop="20230512224400 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Ramón Valle &amp; Reinier Baas : Music Meeting 2020</title>
<desc lang="fr">Ramón Valle &amp; Reinier Baas - Music Meeting 2020 - Since 1985, the Dutch city of Nijmegen has been welcoming the International Music Meeting Festival every Pentecost. Ranging from jazz and improvisational music to traditional music and unique crossovers, this adventurous festival is all about musical encounters and international collaborations. Disrupted by COVID-19, the festival's 2020 edition had to adapt to new challenges. It now presents this exclusive concert by pianist Ramón Valle and guitarist Reinier Baas, filmed at Concertgebouw De Vereeniging in Nijmegen.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/49/1767496_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230512224400 +0200" stop="20230512235300 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Skunk Anansie</title>
<desc lang="fr">Les Vieilles Charrues - British alternative rock group Skunk Anansie celebrates its 25th anniversary with the album 25LIVE@25. These 90s rock scene icons, whose hair-raising shows have become legendary, celebrate their storied career with this 25-song project. With a selection of recordings taken from various 2017 live performances, Skunk Anansie once again proves its unbeatable power on stage. The setlist includes &quot;Because of You,&quot; &quot;The Skank Heads,&quot; and &quot;Tear the Place Up.&quot; Don't miss the triumphant return of these pillars of rock to the stage of the 28th edition of Les Vieilles Charrues in Carhaix, France, in 2019!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/20/00/2008125_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230512235300 +0200" stop="20230513000300 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam</title>
<desc lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam - New Cool Collective is one of the foremost Dutch jazz ensembles. Pioneering new blends of music styles since 1993, NCC has performed in various formations, from small combos to larger ensembles and even big bands! The ensemble's high energy is cut out for the dance floors, as dance, Latin, salsa, afrobeat and boogaloo all meet in a jazzy mix. NCC includes saxophonist Benjamin Herman, guitarist Rory Ronde, drummer Joost Kroon, percussionists Frank van Dok and Jos de Haas, pianist Willem Friede, bassist Leslie Lopez, and trumpeter David Rockefeller.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>