<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Voo -->
<programme start="20230528030000 +0200" stop="20230528040600 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Sleaford Mods</title>
<desc lang="fr">Sleaford Mods - Perhaps you know Sleaford Mods from their collaboration with The Prodigy on The Day Is My Enemy album for which they recorded the track &quot;Ibiza&quot; together. Jason Williamson and Andrew Fearn are Sleaford Mods, the electronic punk duo hailing from Nottingham. Up until 2012, Jason Williamson worked together with Simon Parfrement, who left the music production to Andrew Fearn. In 2015, Sleaford Mods was nominated for the IMPALA Album of the Year Award for their album Key Markets. At the 2019 We Love Green festival in Paris, they play tracks from their latest album Eton Alive.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230528040600 +0200" stop="20230528050600 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Robin Schulz, Sam Feldt, Afrojack &amp; Alle Farben - Parookaville</title>
<desc lang="fr">Parookaville - Parookaville is a city that comes to life once a year to keep the legend of Bill Parooka alive. It was started as an artistic, free-flowing, wild, and musical place where people could connect with their pure selves, experience real connections, and feel a deep sense of bliss and fulfillment. Step into the darkness if you dare, follow your inner light and immerse yourself in a spectacular world of freedom and love! Only four years since the first event, this festival has already become one of Germany's most prevalent music festivals. This edition features Armin van Buuren, Showtek, Robin Schulz, and W&amp;W.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230528050600 +0200" stop="20230528063900 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">&quot;Whatever&quot; at Jazz à Ramatuelle</title>
<desc lang="fr">China Moses: &quot;Whatever&quot; at Jazz à Ramatuelle - In 1988, Dee Dee Bridgewater was one of the first great jazz singers to perform at the Jazz Festival in Ramatuelle. In 2016, the story seems to repeat itself as her daughter China Moses took the stage at Ramatuelle. Over the years, China Moses has become a mature performer with a unique style: rocky voice, sharp sense of swing, and intense/energetic stage presence. After signing compilations dedicated to Dinah Washington and blues, Moses released in 2016 an album of his own compositions, entitled &quot;Whatever&quot;. Get ready for a most entertaining performance combining jazz, soul, and hip-hop.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230528063900 +0200" stop="20230528072400 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Invisible World : WOMEX 2018</title>
<desc lang="fr">One of the participants was the band Invisible World, which operates at the crossroads where Eastern European and Mediterranean influences come together and break new ground. Invisible World is led by the inventive Czech bassist Tomá? Li?ka, together with the Turkish violinist Efe Turumtay, the Serbian accordionist Nikola Zari? and the Moravian drummer Kamil Slezák.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/29/16/2143305_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230528072400 +0200" stop="20230528082600 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Johnny Marr - Rock en Seine</title>
<desc lang="fr">Johnny Marr at Rock en Seine 2019 - English musician, songwriter, and singer Johnny Marr has enjoyed an exemplary career since his former band The Smiths split up in 1987. His distinctive guitar sound has been part of such varied groups as The Pretenders, The Cribs, Modest Mouse, and Electronic, the group he co-founded with Bernard Sumner of New Order. Now a living legend, Johnny Marr showcases his incredible singer-songwriter talents on each new album. His recent, hit-packed release Call The Comet (2018) gave us &quot;The Tracers&quot; and &quot;Hi Hello,&quot; and his live performances - which usually include some songs from his days with The Smiths - always hit the mark. Enjoy this 2019 show recorded at Rock en Seine in Paris!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/07/19/2123266_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230528082600 +0200" stop="20230528090000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Nilufer Yanya</title>
<desc lang="fr">Echoes Series: Nilufer Yanya - Echoes is a modern live music show hosted by Jehnny Beth (lead singer in the British band Savages). It presents leading and emerging bands and artists from the contemporary scene. The show takes place underneath the Palais de Tokyo museum in Paris, in the club of brutalist architecture, the &quot;Yoyo.&quot; The live sets are 30 minutes long and take place on a customized stage, creating closeness with the audience. The intimate, immersive space lends to the atmosphere of the show. The artistic direction by Antoine Carlier follows a minimalist, refined and pure aesthetic, allowing the artists' energy and emotions to take center stage. This episode features Nilüfer Yanya. Her set includes the songs &quot;The Florist,&quot; &quot;Angels,&quot; and &quot;The Unordained.&quot;.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230528090000 +0200" stop="20230528111500 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam</title>
<desc lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam - New Cool Collective is one of the foremost Dutch jazz ensembles. Pioneering new blends of music styles since 1993, NCC has performed in various formations, from small combos to larger ensembles and even big bands! The ensemble's high energy is cut out for the dance floors, as dance, Latin, salsa, afrobeat and boogaloo all meet in a jazzy mix. NCC includes saxophonist Benjamin Herman, guitarist Rory Ronde, drummer Joost Kroon, percussionists Frank van Dok and Jos de Haas, pianist Willem Friede, bassist Leslie Lopez, and trumpeter David Rockefeller.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230528111500 +0200" stop="20230528121000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Beth Hart - Front And Center</title>
<desc lang="fr">The popular music performance series Front and Center premiered nationwide on public television in 2016, and now returns for Season 6. The series boasts 22, one-hour episodes and an all-star line-up. Today's guest is Beth Hart, active in the music scene since the '90s, releasing her third live album. Her intimate show showcases her amazing voice, and her piano playing skills, which she proves with the song &quot;Jazz Man.&quot; One of the performance's highlights includes the ballad &quot;Leave the Light On,&quot; as well as the final song &quot;No Place Like Home.&quot; During her performance, Beth Hart is supported by Jon Nichols, Bill Ransom, Bob Marinelli, and Sonny Landreth.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/19/1853106_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230528121000 +0200" stop="20230528131400 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Hercules Gomes</title>
<desc lang="fr">Hercules Gomes - Da Pá Virada Sessions - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the artists taking part in this series is pianist Hércules Gomes. Due to his impressive technical skill and expressive choice of repertoire he is considered one of Brazil's foremost pianists today. Hércules has performed with numerous renowned Brazilian musicians, including Arismar do Espirito Santo, Letieres Leite, Alessandro Penezzi, Wilson das Neves, and Banda Mantiqueira.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/19/1853106_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230528131400 +0200" stop="20230528142900 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Arsenik à l'Olympia</title>
<desc lang="fr">Arsenik - Olympia, Paris - The mythical duo Arsenik is a rap group from France, made up of two brothers, Lino and Calbo. The team performs at Olympia Paris to celebrate their 20 years since their first album, Quelques gouttes suffisent... It's a unique concert: Arsenik plays the entire album with numerous special guests for the first time. The album has sold over 300,000 copies in France. Today it's being considered a classic, and it continues to be cited in the top five of the best French rap albums of all generations. Enjoy Arsenik's live show in Olympia Paris!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230528142900 +0200" stop="20230528150300 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Sorcha Richardson</title>
<desc lang="fr">Songbook - &quot;I never heard anyone say that, and yeah, I know exactly what it means. It has to go in there, this has to be a song.&quot; Every song has its own story, and we all think it's a story we've heard before, but we haven't. Songbook finds and captures these intriguing stories by pulling you into the process of writing and composing. Known for its pristine sound, cinematic 4k video and eye for detail, Songbook live-captured episodes emphasize the paramount importance of quality. It addresses the on-the-spot elements of blending song and location at the right moment. Both the magical location and remarkable music interaction will get the attention they deserve. Simply because Songbook isn't just a live music session, it lives. This episode of Songbook features Irish singer-songwriter Sorcha Richardson.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230528150300 +0200" stop="20230528161700 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Omer Avital Qantar - Jazz in Duketown</title>
<desc lang="fr">Jazz in Duketown is the largest free open-air jazz festival in the Netherlands. Jazz fanatics and other music lovers eagerly look forward to the performances of the many internationally renowned artists every year. In 2019 Israeli-American double bass player Omer Avital is one of them. Together with his quintet, consisting of saxophonists Asaf Yuria and Alexander Levin, drummer Ofri Nehemya and pianist Eden Ladin, he performs a strong repertoire from his album 'Qantar': vibrantly energetic, idiosyncratic jazz with oriental influences.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230528161700 +0200" stop="20230528171400 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Shawn Mendes</title>
<desc lang="fr">Shawn Mendes - Having been discovered via social media, Shawn Mendes is the youngest artist to debut his album in the top 25. The Canadian singer, songwriter and model, rose to fame by posting cover videos on Vine. Since then he became known for hits such as &quot;Stitches&quot; and &quot;There's Nothing Holdin' Me Back.&quot; On July 9, 2016, the singer, songwriter and performer surprised his fans with a free pop-up show at the Melrose Ballroom in Astoria, NYC. Enjoy this intimate concert and witness how Shawn Mendes enthralls his audience with his amazing songs!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/58/1754433_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230528171400 +0200" stop="20230528181400 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Samba das Flores</title>
<desc lang="fr">Samba das Flores - Da Pá Virada Sessions - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the bands taking part in this series is the ensemble Samba das Flores, which dedicates itself to exploring the world's different rhythms, thus keeping the Brazilian heritage alive. The individual voices of the ensemble members color Samba das Flores's unique sound. Let Brazilian culture and global rhythms inspire you during this Samba das Flores performance!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230528181400 +0200" stop="20230528194900 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Opera Imaginaire</title>
<desc lang="fr">Opera Imaginaire - To celebrate Le Concert Spirituel's 30th anniversary, conductor Hervé Niquet collaborated with the Baroque Music Center of Versailles to build his opéra imaginaire. For this unique project, Le Concert Spirituel presents an original performance of unpublished operas by Lully, Rameau, Charpentier, and many other French baroque composers. You will find yourself captivated by a tearful lover, intrigued by the passage to the underworld, and fascinated by the descents of the Gods. The program includes many favorite passages, such as Lully's Armide, Charpentier's Medea, and Campra's Carnaval de Venise. Experience all the magic of Louis XIV's French opera as Le Concert Spirituel transforms the Théâtre des Champs-Elysées into a true French baroque scene.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/03/1781759_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230528194900 +0200" stop="20230528202200 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">BIRD</title>
<desc lang="fr">BIRD - Five promising musicians get together in Rotterdam jazz club BIRD's artists-in-residence project &quot;The Nest&quot;. In this first broadcast we get to know Lisette Ma Neza (slam poet), Peter Somuah (trumpet), Michelle Samba (drums), Huy Le (bass), and Brenn Luiten (piano). Over the course of seven sessions, they exchange ideas, work on their projects, and play music together. Following this period, during which record producer Jameszoo and music manager Jochem Tromp offer their coaching experience, BIRD and North Sea Jazz Festival's fringe festival DownTown organize a tryout performance. Enjoy this unique collaboration of upcoming musicians!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/02/18/24/2148521_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230528202200 +0200" stop="20230528210000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Rui Massena</title>
<desc lang="fr">CLASSICAL:Next 2019 - Rui Massena - A life-long pioneer and defender of classical music, a maestro and pianist by training, Rui Massena has performed in 14 countries with 30 orchestras, has conducted for José Carreras, Ute Lemper and Wim Mertens and was the main guest conductor of the Rome Symphony Orchestra for three seasons. He has also received several distinctions, both as maestro and as a TV personality. With his first album, Solo, in 2015, recorded entirely on solo piano, his remarkable talent as a melodist was revealed to the world. In 2016, he released 'Ensemble', partly recorded with the Czech National Symphony Orchestra. The record shot to #1 in the Portuguese charts.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/07/00/1647739_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230528210000 +0200" stop="20230528230900 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Above &amp; Beyond Group Therapy 300</title>
<desc lang="fr">Above &amp; Beyond Group Therapy 300 - Above and Beyond recently made their mark on ABGT300 in an epic way. Live for the 300th edition of Group Therapy Radio, the group broadcast from The Asiaworld-Expo in Hong Kong on September 29, 2018. ABGT300 also saw live performances from Andrew Bayer, Ben Böhmer, Grum, Ilan Bluestone, and Spencer Brown, with the signature set from Above and Beyond as the main event. This year, they wanted to push Group Therapy to the next level. Get ready for some magic moments and excellent music.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>