<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Voo -->
<programme start="20230402030000 +0200" stop="20230402041200 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Irène Drésel</title>
<desc lang="fr">Irène Drésel - The world of Irène Drésel can be described as high-colored techno, sensual, and bold. It's a hypnotic world where languid and sporty BPMs rub shoulders with crystalline melodies, foiling the expectations of techno listeners. A polymorphic artist who has left the frenzy of Paris for the calm of the countryside, Irène Drésel tends to her universe down to the smallest details, as evidenced on stage by the roses that gracefully overhang the cold steel of her machines. Irène Drésel composes alone, but she is accompanied live by a percussionist, Sizo Del Givry. Enjoy their 2019 show at Trabendo Paris!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/19/1849379_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230402041200 +0200" stop="20230402050400 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Karin Fernandes</title>
<desc lang="fr">Karin Fernandes - Da Pá Virada Sessions - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the artists taking part in this series is pianist Karin Fernandes. She is dedicated to the performance of 20th and 21st century piano repertoire and has premiered numerous new compositions. As a soloist, Karin Fernandes has performed with prestigious Brazilian orchestras.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230402050400 +0200" stop="20230402064000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Atys en Folie</title>
<desc lang="fr">Atys en Folie - Atys en folie is a parody of Jean-Baptiste Lully's lyrical tragedy Atys (1676). Atys, Lully's most famous opera, was a constant subject of parody throughout the 18th century. Stage director Jean-Philippe Desrousseaux drew on several parodies to create this original production for singers, puppets, and musicians to revive the work. Princes, princesses, and kings are relegated to peasants, market gardeners, and fishmongers in the countryside. Among the performers are Alain Buet, Marie Lenormand, and Arnaud Marzorati. Gaëlle Trimardeau, Bruno Coulon and Jean-Philippe Desrousseaux feature as puppeteers. The music is performed by ensemble La Clique des Lunaisiens, conducted by Arnaud Marzorati. This performance was recorded at Teatru Manoel in Valletta, Malta, in 2017.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/02/04/18/1768814_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230402064000 +0200" stop="20230402073000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Lucibela - WOMEX 2018</title>
<desc lang="fr">Numerous musicians, booking agents, news agencies and media companies from all over the world have been attending the &quot;World Music Exhibition&quot; World Music Expo (WOMEX) since 1994. Over the years, this music fair has settled in several European cities, including Berlin, Brussels, Marseille, Stockholm, Seville, Cardiff and Budapest. In 2018 WOMEX took place in Las Palmas in Gran Canaria. One of the participants was singer Lucibela, from the Cape Verde island of São Nicolau.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/53/1759065_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230402073000 +0200" stop="20230402082400 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Tribute to Gilberto Gil</title>
<desc lang="fr">Tribute to Gilberto Gil - Da Pá Virada Sessions - The series Da Pá Virada sessions presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the bands taking part in this series is Caixa Cubo. This trio usually explores Brazil's rhythmically rich landscapes, combining them with modern Brazilian jazz trends. Yet in this singular performance, Caixa Cubo teams up with vocalist Zé Leônidas, selecting special repertoire together with Dani Gurgel from Da Pá Virada Sessions and Rokas Ku?inskas from Stingray DJAZZ.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230402082400 +0200" stop="20230402090000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Clarinet Factory</title>
<desc lang="fr">Classical:NEXT 2019 - Clarinet Factory - Considered to be one of the most unique ensembles to feature on the Czech scene in the last 25 years, the style of the Clarinet Factory hovers between contemporary and classical music, jazz and world music. As winners of the Classic Prague Awards in 2017 for 'Best Crossover Project', the quartet combines their classic music training and clarinet art with jazz, minimalism and improvisation to create their very own music without borders, capable of communicating directly with all audiences. The Clarinet Factory also experiment with electronics, both ambient and dance-oriented, and the four musicians remain ever fascinated with the possibilities of their instrument, considering their work as a music laboratory.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/24/07/2123267_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230402090000 +0200" stop="20230402111500 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam</title>
<desc lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam - New Cool Collective is one of the foremost Dutch jazz ensembles. Pioneering new blends of music styles since 1993, NCC has performed in various formations, from small combos to larger ensembles and even big bands! The ensemble's high energy is cut out for the dance floors, as dance, Latin, salsa, afrobeat and boogaloo all meet in a jazzy mix. NCC includes saxophonist Benjamin Herman, guitarist Rory Ronde, drummer Joost Kroon, percussionists Frank van Dok and Jos de Haas, pianist Willem Friede, bassist Leslie Lopez, and trumpeter David Rockefeller.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230402111500 +0200" stop="20230402121400 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Filo Machado - New Year's Eve Special</title>
<desc lang="fr">Filo Machado - New Year's Eve Special - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the artists taking part in this series is Filo Machado. Born in São Paulo, this singer, composer, instrumentalist, arranger and producer has celebrated many musical successes. Filo Machado took part in saxophonist Jane Bunnett's Canadian tour with her spectacular project 'Rendez-Vous Brazil/Cuba'. He has appeared at the jazz festivals of Córsega and Uzeste and opened for the one and only Nina Simone in Cannes.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230402121400 +0200" stop="20230402131700 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Liran Donin : Music Meeting</title>
<desc lang="fr">Nijmegen has been welcoming the International Music Meeting Festival, or Music Meeting for short, every spring since 1985. From jazz and improvised music to traditional music and unique crossovers: musical encounters and international collaborations are at the heart of this adventurous festival. In 2019, Tel Aviv-born bassist, producer and composer Liran Donin performed here.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230402131700 +0200" stop="20230402142700 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Omer Avital Qantar - Jazz in Duketown</title>
<desc lang="fr">Jazz in Duketown is the largest free open-air jazz festival in the Netherlands. Jazz fanatics and other music lovers eagerly look forward to the performances of the many internationally renowned artists every year. In 2019 Israeli-American double bass player Omer Avital is one of them. Together with his quintet, consisting of saxophonists Asaf Yuria and Alexander Levin, drummer Ofri Nehemya and pianist Eden Ladin, he performs a strong repertoire from his album 'Qantar': vibrantly energetic, idiosyncratic jazz with oriental influences.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230402142700 +0200" stop="20230402150000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Beak</title>
<desc lang="fr">Echoes Series: Beak - Echoes is a modern live music show hosted by Jehnny Beth (lead singer in the British band Savages). It presents leading and emerging bands and artists from the contemporary scene. The show takes place underneath the Palais de Tokyo museum in Paris, in the club of brutalist architecture, the &quot;Yoyo.&quot; The live sets are 30 minutes long and take place on a customized stage, creating closeness with the audience. The intimate, immersive space lends to the atmosphere of the show. The artistic direction by Antoine Carlier follows a minimalist, refined and pure aesthetic, allowing the artists' energy and emotions to take center stage. This episode features the electronic project Beak. Their set includes the songs &quot;The Brazilian,&quot; &quot;Brean Down,&quot; and &quot;Allé Sauvage.&quot;.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/56/1752527_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230402150000 +0200" stop="20230402161800 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Oumou Sangaré @ Jazz Sous Les Pommiers</title>
<desc lang="fr">Salif Keita described her as the &quot;Tina Turner of Mali.&quot; Indeed, Oumou Sangaré is one of Africa's most important female voices. While maintaining her political views as a champion of women's rights in Africa, her vocal talent has brought this singer to shine at some of the most important venues around the world. At Jazz Sous Les Pommiers 2017, Oumou Sangaré presents her latest album, Mogoya. She is accompanied by a group that combines traditional African instruments with a modern band set-up, featuring young French musicians. Recorded in spectacular 4K in a beautiful musical setting, Sangaré will surely make you sing and dance!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230402161800 +0200" stop="20230402170100 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">City Beats</title>
<desc lang="fr">City Beats - Episode 2 - Ibiza - DJ-producer Carly Foxx is on a musical journey, immersing herself in the life of five iconic European cities to find inspiration for a series of new tracks. In this episode, Carly Foxx travels to the world's clubbing capital to inspire her music track and discovers Ibiza's alternative spiritual side. She starts her journey in San Antonio but discovers this place is mainly about clubbing and drinking - not very inspiring for her music track. The next stop is Old Town, where Carly meets female Ibiza singer Sam Smith, who introduces her to DJ and producer Manu Gonzalez. While talking to him, Carly decides the base of her Ibiza-inspired track should be a Balearic beat, to which she plans to add bongos and castanet samples.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Télé-Réalité</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/04/09/2155262_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230402170100 +0200" stop="20230402180200 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Fabrizio Rat : Artemix</title>
<desc lang="fr">Fabrizio Rat - Since his teenage years, Fabrizio has worked simultaneously on both classical and electronic music productions. He's definitely not the classical music guy who has just discovered techno. Throughout his apprentice years at the musical academy in Turin, he was working as a producer in dance music studios at the same time, hiding his &quot;double life&quot; to both the professors and the DJs. Arriving in Paris in 2007, his objective starts to take shape. Fabrizio combines the acoustic sounds and weird harmonics of his prepared piano with the acid loops of the TB-303 and the beats of the TR-909. Unsurprisingly, it's in front of the dancefloor, in clubs or festivals, that Fabrizio plays his live sets. With the right hand, he plays repetitive rhythmical patterns while the left one handles the machines and manipulates the piano strings.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/43/1767478_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230402180200 +0200" stop="20230402193700 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Opera Imaginaire</title>
<desc lang="fr">Opera Imaginaire - To celebrate Le Concert Spirituel's 30th anniversary, conductor Hervé Niquet collaborated with the Baroque Music Center of Versailles to build his opéra imaginaire. For this unique project, Le Concert Spirituel presents an original performance of unpublished operas by Lully, Rameau, Charpentier, and many other French baroque composers. You will find yourself captivated by a tearful lover, intrigued by the passage to the underworld, and fascinated by the descents of the Gods. The program includes many favorite passages, such as Lully's Armide, Charpentier's Medea, and Campra's Carnaval de Venise. Experience all the magic of Louis XIV's French opera as Le Concert Spirituel transforms the Théâtre des Champs-Elysées into a true French baroque scene.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/03/1781759_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230402193700 +0200" stop="20230402201100 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">GayBird Leung et Zephyr Quartet</title>
<desc lang="fr">GayBird Leung &amp; Zephyr Quartet - GayBird Leung has worked in the Hong Kong music industry since 1996 as a music director, composer, and producer for over a hundred music productions, concerts and theatres. He continues to explore the realm of music creation, investigating potential formats of electronic music performance that enhance the music experience. The Zephyr Quartet, consisting of Emma Perkins (violin), Emily Tulloch (violin), Jason Thomas (viola) and Hilary Kleinig (cello) are Australia's leading genre-defying explorers of dynamic cross-art form music focused collaborations. During this showcase at Classical: NEXT 2019 in Rotterdam, they perform GayBird Leung's composition &quot;Music in Anticlockwise&quot; (2017).</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/49/1767496_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230402201100 +0200" stop="20230402210000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Echoes Series: Fontaines DC</title>
<desc lang="fr">Echoes Series: Fontaines DC - Echoes is a modern live music show hosted by Jehnny Beth (lead singer in the British band Savages). It presents leading and emerging bands and artists from the contemporary scene. The show takes place underneath the Palais de Tokyo museum in Paris, in the club of brutalist architecture, the &quot;Yoyo.&quot; The live sets are 30 minutes long and take place on a customized stage, creating closeness with the audience. The intimate, immersive space lends to the atmosphere of the show. The artistic direction by Antoine Carlier follows a minimalist, refined and pure aesthetic, allowing the artists' energy and emotions to take center stage. This episode features the band Fontaines DC. Their set includes the songs &quot;A Hero's Death,&quot; &quot;Hurricane Laughter,&quot; and &quot;I Don't Belong.&quot;.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/04/2122118_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230402210000 +0200" stop="20230402230800 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Hardwell and the Metropole Orchestra - Symphony</title>
<desc lang="fr">Hardwell and the Metropole Orchestra - Symphony - During &quot;Symphony: The Global Revolution of Dance,&quot; the global sensation DJ Hardwell, with the world's leading pop and jazz orchestra, The Metropole Orchestra, take the audience on a musical journey through the history of dance music. The spectacular show of legendary DJ and the Metropole Orchestra is characterized by the composition of different music periods, from the '80s to the present. The show features hits from various world stars like Donna Summer, Tiësto, Carl Cox, and Daft Punk.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/21/1756184_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230402230800 +0200" stop="20230403000700 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">lovelytheband</title>
<desc lang="fr">Formed in West Hollywood in 2016, lovelytheband features former Oh Honey member Mitchy Collins along with guitarist Jordan Greenwald and drummer Sam Price. The band debuted in July 2017 with the Christian Medice-produced &quot;Broken,&quot; a sprightly and infectious single that quickly racked up over three million digital streams. Signing with Another Century Records, lovelytheband released their debut EP &quot;Everything I Could&quot; in September of that year and joined Vance Joy and AWOLNATION on tour. In April 2018, &quot;Broken&quot; was still going strong and hit number one on the Billboard Alternative Songs Airplay chart. That August, lovelytheband returned with their full-length debut album, Finding It Hard to Smile.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/58/1754433_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230403000700 +0200" stop="20230403015300 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Leçons de ténèbres, de Michel-Richard de Lalande</title>
<desc lang="fr">Lalande - Leçons de ténèbres - Harpsichordist and organist Sébastien Daucé conducts Ensemble Correspondances and soloist Sophie Karthäuser (soprano) in a performance of Michel-Richard de Lalande's (1657-1726) sacred music piece Les Leçons des Ténèbres ('lessons of darkness'). To round off the period of Lent leading up to Easter, the congregation sings these Lamentations of Jeremiah in church. With each psalm, one of the candles is extinguished until complete darkness and silence ensues. Whatever one's faith, this tradition is a unique spiritual experience. French baroque composer Michel-Richard de Lalande, an important composer of &quot;grands&quot; motets of unprecedented length, was one of many who wrote music for this religious practice. This performance was recorded at Chapelle Corneille in Rouen, France in 2016.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/21/1756184_A.jpg" />
</programme>