<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Voo -->
<programme start="20230525030000 +0200" stop="20230525041400 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Christine &amp; the Queens</title>
<desc lang="fr">Live aux Vieilles Charrues - French singer Héloïse Létissier, aka Christine and the Queens, originates from Nantes, France. Her debut album Chaleur Humaine earned her a Victories of Music award in 2015, paving the way for future success. A versatile artist skilled in music and dance, she surrounds herself with the best. Among others, she collaborated with dancer and choreographer Marion Motin, who accompanied Madonna. In 2018, Christine and the Queens shortened her name to Chris and hit the international scene with a self-titled album. Her artistic work opens up a new perspective on femininity and masculinity, a hot topic today. In this concert, she inspires her audience at Les Vieilles Charrues in Carhaix, France, to dance all night long.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230525041400 +0200" stop="20230525050400 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Live with a Boom</title>
<desc lang="fr">Mn'JAM Experiment: Live with a Boom - Imagine that visual arts and music are no longer two separate fields; that musicians no longer focus on their instruments only, but also on the visuals of their performance. Such is the premise of Mn'JAM Experiment! Zoom in on their music and you'll find a mix between empirical and rationally constructed elements; between acoustic, electric and electronic instruments; urban rhythms and traditional melodies, vocal loops and guitar solos, turntables and acoustic drums. Zoom in on the visuals of the performance -they are analogously a product of pre-composed material and live manipulation, mostly carried out by the guy behind the turntables.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230525050400 +0200" stop="20230525060000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">The Go! Team @ Route du Rock Hivers</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Go! Team @ Route du Rock Hivers - Originating from Brighton, UK, The Go! Team blends garage/indie rock with distorted guitars and a popping brass section. The creative force behind this six-piece band is Ian Parton. According to him, the band samples everything from Bollywood to hip-hop. Although the samples are at the heart of the band's sound, every song is kicked off by the melody. At Route du Rock Hivers 2018, The Go! Team presents its latest album, Semicircle. Its opening track Mayday is built around a drum loop based on Morse code. This is only the beginning of the endless variety of sound effects The Go! Team experiments with. At their 4K show at Rock Hivers 2018, you will enjoy a blend of noisy pop, hip-hop collages, awesome grooves, irresistible soul arrangements and much more!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/42/1870646_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230525060000 +0200" stop="20230525073800 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Kyle Eastwood Quintet</title>
<desc lang="fr">Jazz à Ramatuelle: Kyle Eastwood Quintet - Bassist Kyle Eastwood (1968) is an explorer, equally at ease with jazz melodies as with pop songs. In the late 1970s, his father Clint took him to see his first jazz concert - a Count Basie performance. Eastwood Jr. was in awe of the drummer and wanted to play an instrument himself. It so happened he wasn't so much interested in jazz, preferring rhythm and blues, Motown and Stax records, funk groups, and North African and Indian music. Eastwood became a brilliant bassist and the composer of highly original soundtracks. His 2015 album &quot;Time Pieces&quot; is a collaboration with brilliant British musicians, such as trumpeter Quentin Collins and saxophonist Brandon Allen. In this broadcast, Eastwood and his fellow musicians revisit the hard bop legacy of Blue Note Records.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230525073800 +0200" stop="20230525081100 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Ensemble HOPE</title>
<desc lang="fr">Classical:NEXT 2019 - Ensemble HOPE - The Ensemble HOPE is dedicated to the performance and creation of music of today. As well as exploring new forms of contemporary electro-acoustic technology, it integrates written musical tradition, improvisation and an adapted classical repertoire. The &quot;Cristal Baschet&quot; and the &quot;Euphone&quot; form the basis of the ensemble's sophisticated instrumental collection. The new works reflect these neglected and little-known instruments. The Ensemble HOPE, consisting of Frederic Bousquet (Euphone), Marc Antoine Millon (Bass Cristal) and Armelle Marq (soprano voice), is also actively engaged in developing a new generation of Euphones. In this concert from 2019's Classical:NEXT!, the ensemble performs Frederic Bousquet's &quot;Vénus&quot;, &quot;Epilogue&quot; and &quot;en transit,&quot; Henry Purcell's &quot;Dido's lament,&quot; arranged by M.A.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/24/07/2123267_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230525081100 +0200" stop="20230525090000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Life</title>
<desc lang="fr">Echoes Series: Life - Echoes is a modern live music show hosted by Jehnny Beth (lead singer in the British band Savages). It presents leading and emerging bands and artists from the contemporary scene. The show takes place underneath the Palais de Tokyo museum in Paris, in the club of brutalist architecture, the &quot;Yoyo.&quot; The live sets are 30 minutes long and take place on a customized stage, creating closeness with the audience. The intimate, immersive space lends to the atmosphere of the show. The artistic direction by Antoine Carlier follows a minimalist, refined and pure aesthetic, allowing the artists' energy and emotions to take center stage. This episode features the band Life. Their set includes the songs &quot;Excites Me,&quot; &quot;Hollow Thing,&quot; and &quot;Moral Fibre.&quot;.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230525090000 +0200" stop="20230525102800 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Macha y el Bloque Depresivo</title>
<desc lang="fr">Macha y el Bloque Depresivo - With an arrangement of guitar and percussion players and Macha, the charismatic leader with the velvet voice, El Bloque Depresivo brings you an intensive tribute to South-American traditional music. This concert is brought to you by the &quot; Opéra Underground &quot; with the Opera de Lyon.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/02/07/27/1762648_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230525102800 +0200" stop="20230525112800 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Paulo Novaes</title>
<desc lang="fr">Paulo Novaes - Da Pá Virada Sessions - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the artists taking part in this series is Paulo Novaes. Coming from a family of musicians, Paulo Novaes has already lived through a lifetime of music in spite of his young age. Paulo is the cousin of singer Bruna Caram, with whom he performed in São Paulo, Madrid, Barcelona, Lisbon, and other major cities. As a singer, composer, and instrumentalist, his creativity is enjoyed in many forms.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230525112800 +0200" stop="20230525134100 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam</title>
<desc lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam - New Cool Collective is one of the foremost Dutch jazz ensembles. Pioneering new blends of music styles since 1993, NCC has performed in various formations, from small combos to larger ensembles and even big bands! The ensemble's high energy is cut out for the dance floors, as dance, Latin, salsa, afrobeat and boogaloo all meet in a jazzy mix. NCC includes saxophonist Benjamin Herman, guitarist Rory Ronde, drummer Joost Kroon, percussionists Frank van Dok and Jos de Haas, pianist Willem Friede, bassist Leslie Lopez, and trumpeter David Rockefeller.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230525134100 +0200" stop="20230525150100 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Liam Gallagher</title>
<desc lang="fr">Liam Gallagher - After leading iconic British rock band Oasis for nearly two decades, Manchester-born singer Liam Gallagher launched his solo career in 2016. He played his first ever U.S. solo show on July 28th of 2017 at Manhattan's McKittrick Hotel in New York City. The rather small venue is known to host the immersive theater experience &quot;Sleep No More&quot;, and its limited capacities made for an intense and intimate concert experience. In a 75-minute long show featuring thirteen songs, Gallagher performed tracks of his 2017 debut album As You Were, next to a list of Oasis fan favorites. Shot in phenomenally sharp 4K, this recording offers viewers the unique opportunity to become part of the audience of this secret session.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230525150100 +0200" stop="20230525171600 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam</title>
<desc lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam - New Cool Collective is one of the foremost Dutch jazz ensembles. Pioneering new blends of music styles since 1993, NCC has performed in various formations, from small combos to larger ensembles and even big bands! The ensemble's high energy is cut out for the dance floors, as dance, Latin, salsa, afrobeat and boogaloo all meet in a jazzy mix. NCC includes saxophonist Benjamin Herman, guitarist Rory Ronde, drummer Joost Kroon, percussionists Frank van Dok and Jos de Haas, pianist Willem Friede, bassist Leslie Lopez, and trumpeter David Rockefeller.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230525171600 +0200" stop="20230525181600 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Nubiyan Twist : Music Meeting</title>
<desc lang="fr">Nubiyan Twist - Music Meeting - Since 1985, the Dutch city of Nijmegen has been welcoming the International Music Meeting Festival every Pentecost. Ranging from jazz and improvisational music to traditional music and unique crossovers, this adventurous festival is all about musical encounters and international collaborations. In 2019, the band Nubiyan Twist performs at the International Music Meeting Festival. This London-based group operates on the intersection of soul and jazz.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230525181600 +0200" stop="20230525191800 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Matthew Dear</title>
<desc lang="fr">Matthew Dear - Matthew Dear is a shapeshifter, oscillating seamlessly between DJ, dance-music producer, and experimental pop auteur. He writes, produces, and mixes all of his work. He maintains four aliases (Audion, False, Jabberjaw, and Matthew Dear), each with its own style and distinct visual identity. He straddles multiple musical worlds and belongs to none, now nearly 20 years into his kaleidoscopic career, with five albums and two dozen EPs plus millions of miles in the rearview of his biography. Bunny, his fifth full-length released October 2018, parades down a rabbit hole of unhinged phrasings, dreams, and interludes. Bunny further confirms that Matthew Dear occupies a rarified corner of the musical universe: no longer tethered to any one genre, respected by his peers, and blessed with a bottomless well of creative energy.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/19/1849379_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230525191800 +0200" stop="20230525203300 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Beth Ditto live at L'Aéronef Lille 2017</title>
<desc lang="fr">At L'Aéronef Lille 2017 - Gossip fans, rejoice: Beth Ditto makes a big comeback! With her new album, the fiery singer launches into a solo career. With the boundless energy, undeniable humor, and legendary generosity that characterize her, the American phenomenon presents brand-new songs. Beth Ditto is more than a singer: she is an inescapable figure of the world's pop culture. As the lead singer of indie rock band Gossip (1999-2016), this young woman pulled off spectacular stage performances and gave hilarious interviews, greatly contributing to her sympathy capital. Her 2017 album mixes blues, pop, country, and rock, paying tribute to her native Arkansas in twelve eclectic and unifying pieces. Experience Beth Ditto as never before in this appearance at L'Aéronef Lille 2017!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Musique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/15/1838343_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230525203300 +0200" stop="20230525210000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Violetta Zironi</title>
<desc lang="fr">Songbook - &quot;I never heard anyone say that, and yeah, I know exactly what it means. It has to go in there, this has to be a song.&quot; Every song has its own story, and we all think it's a story we've heard before, but we haven't. Songbook finds and captures these intriguing stories by pulling you into the process of writing and composing. Known for its pristine sound, cinematic 4k video and eye for detail, Songbook live-captured episodes emphasize the paramount importance of quality. It addresses the on-the-spot elements of blending song and location at the right moment. Both the magical location and remarkable music interaction will get the attention they deserve. Simply because Songbook isn't just a live music session, it lives. This episode of Songbook features Italian singer-songwriter Violetta Zironi.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230525210000 +0200" stop="20230525213200 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Audience Music</title>
<desc lang="fr">X Ambassadors - Enjoy ground-breaking concerts, in-depth artist interviews, and unique stories with host Ted Stryker. This concert series gives the audience an intimate view of music's most influential artists today. Shot in 4K, host Ted Stryker interviews musicians across all genres, creating one of the most unique music shows on TV today. This episode features the alternative rock band X Ambassadors, founded in 2009. After self-releasing the debut EP &quot;Ambassadors EP&quot;, which featured &quot;Litost&quot;, a song that would later be added to the soundtrack of sci-fi blockbuster The Host, the band had its break-through when Imagine Dragons lead singer Dan Reynolds initiated their signage to a major music label.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/58/1754433_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230525213200 +0200" stop="20230525223300 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Audience Music</title>
<desc lang="fr">This series features groundbreaking concerts, in-depth artist interviews and unique stories with host Ted Stryker. This concert series gives the audience an intimate view of music's most influential artists today. Shot in 4K, host Ted Stryker interviews musicians across all genres, creating the most unique music show on TV today. This episode features The Band Perry, the famous country band consisting of siblings Kimberly, Reid and Neil Perry. Throughout high school they had different bands, but towards the end of high school the three came together as The Band Perry. After being signed to Republic Nashville, they released their first album, and conquered the charts with the song &quot;If I Die Young.&quot; Since then, they have scored numerous hits and have won various awards.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1757419_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230525223300 +0200" stop="20230525234900 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Lalah Hathaway</title>
<desc lang="fr">Lalah Hathaway - Sing Jazz 2018 - Winner of five Grammys in four consecutive years, including the Grammy for best R&amp;B album in 2017, Lalah Hathaway is a force impossible to ignore. The American artist has shared the scene with Prince, Snoop Dogg, Stevie Wonder, Anita Baker, Mary J. Blige, Frank Ocean and many others, an irrefutable proof of her keen musical sense and enormous talent. With a 26-year career, Hathaway is still highly sought after by the biggest names in music. See her transform the 2018 Sing Jazz festival scene into a real R&amp;B club, where she flaunts her voice and stage presence out of the ordinary.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/19/1853106_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230525234900 +0200" stop="20230526005100 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Bloco do O</title>
<desc lang="fr">Bloco do O - Da Pá Virada Sessions - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the bands taking part in this series is Bloco do Ó, a traditional street band associated with the Brazilian carnival. A &quot;bloco&quot; is a group of people who drive through the streets in trucks, playing music and providing fun to anyone who will listen. Immerse yourself in Bloco de Ó's world of cheerful melodies and spectacular costumes!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/19/1853106_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230526005100 +0200" stop="20230526015400 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Nilüfer Yanya - Echoes Series: Nilufer Yanya</title>
<desc lang="fr">Echoes Series - Episode 3 - Echoes is a modern live music show hosted by Jehnny Beth (lead singer in the British band Savages). It presents leading and emerging bands and artists from the contemporary scene. The show takes place underneath the Palais de Tokyo museum in Paris, in the club of brutalist architecture, the &quot;Yoyo.&quot; The live sets are 30 minutes long and take place on a customized stage, creating closeness with the audience. Once the bands have performed, Jehnny Beth invites everyone to sit at her roundtable for a group conversation. The open discussions in every episode allow the audience to understand the rapport, artistic exchange, and intellectual debates that run through this eclectic musical universe. The intimate, immersive space lends to the atmosphere of the show.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/03/1754401_A.jpg" />
</programme>