<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Voo -->
<programme start="20230507030000 +0200" stop="20230507041100 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Michelle David - Jazz in Duketown</title>
<desc lang="fr">Michelle David - Jazz in Duketown - Jazz in Duketown is the largest free outdoor jazz festival in the Netherlands. It's a real gathering for jazz addicts, inviting internationally renowned artists. The talented American singer Michelle David performs pop and gospel music that feeds the heart and soothes the soul. Having grown up with the church, she started singing at the age of four. A year later she joined her first band, The Mission of Love. In 1980 she enrolled at Fiorello H. LaGuardia High School of Music &amp; Art and Performing Arts in New York City, known from the film 'Fame'. During this time, she appeared as an extra in the legendary comedy film 'Ghostbusters'. Musicals and tours with the bands of Diana Ross and Michael Bolton followed.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/19/1853106_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507041100 +0200" stop="20230507051200 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Runtown : La Machine de Moulin Rouge</title>
<desc lang="fr">Runtown - La Machine de Moulin Rouge - Enjoy Runtown's first concert in Paris, where the Nigerian superstar brings many guests to his show. One of the most talented Nigerian afrobeat scenes will make you rediscover his greatest hits. Nigeria is a very creative country when it comes to the music scene. Runtown is no exception. His first single, &quot;Party Like It's 1980,&quot; paved the way for &quot;Gallardo,&quot; which caught the entire international scene's attention. Runtown's inspiration comes from the greats, from Salif Keita and Fela Kuti to Otis Redding and Bob Marley. An exceptional event not to be missed.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507051200 +0200" stop="20230507064500 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Antonio Faraò</title>
<desc lang="fr">Jazz à Ramatuelle: Antonio Faraò - In 1998, Antonio Faraò won the prestigious Concours Martial Solal, awarded to him by Herbie Hancock! Since then, this talented Italian jazz pianist has made his mark as a player of elegance and lyricism, which has allowed him to collaborate with the best European and American musicians. On his last album &quot;Evan&quot;, recorded in the United States, he leads an all-star band starring Joe Lovano on tenor saxophone. On a beautiful summer night at the French Jazz à Ramatuelle festival, Faraò performs at the breathtaking Theatre de Verdure in the company of saxophone legend Dave Liebman. With refined ballads, a feline groove, elegance, and lyricism, this musical meeting sparkles - if you watch closely you might even see some bright new stars lighting up in the night sky above Ramatuelle!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507064500 +0200" stop="20230507072900 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">City Beats</title>
<desc lang="fr">City Beats - Episode 6 - Europe - DJ-producer Carly Foxx is on a musical journey, immersing herself in the life of five iconic European cities to find inspiration for a series of new tracks. In this episode, Carly Foxx looks back at her journey to the music dance capitals of Europe to inspire her final track. She starts with the Balaeric beat that represents Ibiza while adding authentic bongo and guitar recordings. Then she shifts to London, where she discovers new areas and urban culture while talking to filmmaker DJ Don Letts. Carly captures the grime sound with the help of MC Yizzy and records vocals from a group of London women. Her next trip brings her to Berlin, where she produces an acid house flavored track with the 303 synthesizers.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Télé-Réalité</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/16/2123268_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507072900 +0200" stop="20230507082200 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Live From the Kennedy Center</title>
<desc lang="fr">Live From the Kennedy Center - When Nas was just 19 years old, he composed what would become one of hip-hop's defining masterpieces, Illmatic. To mark its 20th anniversary, Nas delivers a standout performance alongside the National Symphony Orchestra at Washington DC's Kennedy Center. With conductor Steven Reineke taking the orchestra through arrangements of beats by DJ Premier and Large Professor, Nas delivers impassioned renditions of tracks like &quot;N.Y. State of Mind&quot;, &quot;The World Is Yours&quot;, and &quot;Memory Lane (Sittin' in Da Park)&quot;. Between songs, the program cuts away to both archival and new interview footage to document Nas' rise from Queensbridge upstart to influential rap icon.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/58/1754433_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507082200 +0200" stop="20230507090000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">?nied?</title>
<desc lang="fr">Classical:NEXT 2019 - ?nied? - ?nied? is a voice and electronics duo from Warsaw, Poland who combine extended vocal techniques with improvised, self-named &quot;glitchtronica.&quot; Singer, performer, and sound artist Aleksandra Klimczak frequently breaks boundaries between art genres through cooperating with young artists from different artistic fields. Her work has been awarded from scholarships from the Polish Ministry of Culture and the Capital City of Warsaw. Music curator Antoni Beksiak deals with contemporary crossover, ethnic, classical, jazz, and pop music in his work as an initiator, critic and creator. During this showcase recorded at Classical:NEXT 2019 in Rotterdam, The Netherlands the perform a set list of their own works.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/24/07/2123267_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507090000 +0200" stop="20230507111500 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam</title>
<desc lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam - New Cool Collective is one of the foremost Dutch jazz ensembles. Pioneering new blends of music styles since 1993, NCC has performed in various formations, from small combos to larger ensembles and even big bands! The ensemble's high energy is cut out for the dance floors, as dance, Latin, salsa, afrobeat and boogaloo all meet in a jazzy mix. NCC includes saxophonist Benjamin Herman, guitarist Rory Ronde, drummer Joost Kroon, percussionists Frank van Dok and Jos de Haas, pianist Willem Friede, bassist Leslie Lopez, and trumpeter David Rockefeller.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507111500 +0200" stop="20230507121400 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Filo Machado</title>
<desc lang="fr">Filo Machado - Da Pá Virada Sessions - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the artists taking part in this series is Filo Machado. Born in São Paulo, this singer, composer, instrumentalist, arranger, and producer has celebrated many musical successes. Filo Machado took part in saxophonist Jane Bunnett's Canadian tour with her spectacular project 'Rendez-Vous Brazil/Cuba'. He has appeared at the jazz festivals of Córsega and Uzeste and opened for the one and only Nina Simone in Cannes.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507121400 +0200" stop="20230507132300 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Les Vieilles Charrues</title>
<desc lang="fr">Les Vieilles Charrues - British alternative rock group Skunk Anansie celebrates its 25th anniversary with the album 25LIVE@25. These 90s rock scene icons, whose hair-raising shows have become legendary, celebrate their storied career with this 25-song project. With a selection of recordings taken from various 2017 live performances, Skunk Anansie once again proves its unbeatable power on stage. The setlist includes &quot;Because of You,&quot; &quot;The Skank Heads,&quot; and &quot;Tear the Place Up.&quot; Don't miss the triumphant return of these pillars of rock to the stage of the 28th edition of Les Vieilles Charrues in Carhaix, France, in 2019!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507132300 +0200" stop="20230507150200 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Christian Scott - The Centennial Trilogy</title>
<desc lang="fr">In just a few years, young trumpet player Christian Scott has become synonymous with a new jazz generation. He shakes up the conventions of jazz by taking the genre to new horizons and reaching a wider audience. No doubt, at 33 years old, Christian Scott is already forging his own path. After each record release, he seems even more determined to challenge the rules of jazz with his own avant-garde style. At his 2018 show at La Coopérative de Mai, Christian Scott celebrates 100 years of jazz with the program &quot;The Centennial Trilogy.&quot; Expect a unique performance in an intimate theatre setting, shot in native 4K!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/04/1754386_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507150200 +0200" stop="20230507162000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Monty Alexander &amp; The Harlem Kingston Express</title>
<desc lang="fr">With a career spanning five decades, jazz pianist Monty Alexander has played with the best of the best. An ambassador for Jamaican music, Alexander creates a unique blend of jazz and reggae with a group of exceptional American and Jamaican musicians called the &quot;Harlem Kingston Express.&quot; Together, they explore the two sides of Monty Alexander's musical legacy: the jazz of Harlem and the reggae of Kingston. Many great jazz musicians, including Dizzy Gillespie, have called on Alexander's exceptional sense of improvisation. Watch this 4K recording of his 2017 performance at Philharmonie de Paris, and you'll understand why.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/56/1752527_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507162000 +0200" stop="20230507170900 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Ben Frost</title>
<desc lang="fr">Ben Frost - Australian Ben Frost produces under his Bedroom Community label albums inspired by post-classical electronic music, structured sound art and minimalism. His numerous collaborations testify to his desire to develop an artistic form combining music, texts, technology and performance. In this fascinating concert delivered at the Sónar Reykjavík 2018 festival, Frost once again displays his ingenuity as he presents the pieces of the album The Centre Cannot Hold. The award-winning visual artist MFO signs visual effects and lighting.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/59/1769392_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507170900 +0200" stop="20230507180300 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Os Capoeira</title>
<desc lang="fr">Os Capoeira - Da Pá Virada Sessions - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the bands taking part in this series is Os Capoeira. This ensemble practices the traditional Brazilian martial art from Bahia it is named after, combining elements of dance, acrobatics, and percussive music. Moreover, Os Capoeira runs a cultural center in São Paulo. Let yourself be inspired by Os Capoeira's unique take on Brazilian culture!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507180300 +0200" stop="20230507194300 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Au Théâtre de Villefranche-sur-Saône</title>
<desc lang="fr">Omar Sosa - Quarteto Afrocubano - While always keeping one foot firmly anchored in the traditions of his home country, Cuba, Omar Sosa tirelessly explores music from the Caribbean to India, and West Africa to the Arab world. Since he left Cuba in 1993, the pianist has been blending his Afro-Cuban roots with jazz, hip hop, electro and world music. For his 2018 performance at Théâtre de Villefranche-sur-Saône, he brings to stage his Quarteto Afrocubano members Childo Tomas (electric bass &amp; vocals), Ernesto Simpson (drums), and Leandro Saint-Hill (saxophones, flute, percussion &amp; vocals). Together, they create a riveting instrumental dialogue. Celebrating rhythm in all its forms, this Omar Sosa concert is an intense and mystical experience.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/19/1853106_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507194300 +0200" stop="20230507201600 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Nilüfer Yanya - Echoes Series: Nilufer Yanya</title>
<desc lang="fr">Echoes Series: Billy Nomates - Echoes is a modern live music show hosted by Jehnny Beth (lead singer in the British band Savages). It presents leading and emerging bands and artists from the contemporary scene. The show takes place underneath the Palais de Tokyo museum in Paris, in the club of brutalist architecture, the &quot;Yoyo.&quot; The live sets are 30 minutes long and take place on a customized stage, creating closeness with the audience. The intimate, immersive space lends to the atmosphere of the show. The artistic direction by Antoine Carlier follows a minimalist, refined and pure aesthetic, allowing the artists' energy and emotions to take center stage. This episode features Billy Nomates. Her set includes the songs &quot;Happy Misery,&quot; &quot;Wild Arena,&quot; and &quot;Call in Sick.&quot;.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/03/1754401_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507201600 +0200" stop="20230507210000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Close Call</title>
<desc lang="fr">Classical:NEXT 2019 - Close Call - In Close Call your smartphone is a musical instrument. And you are not just an audience member, but a musician in a crazy band with three drummers! Arthur Wagenaar is a Dutch composer and musician. He has a deep love for rock bands, theatre, opera and classical music, and his music is usually a mixture of all of this. He also loves to invent his own instruments, mechanical or electronic, such as the &quot;rampaphone,&quot; a string instrument nine meters in length, the &quot;kleurwerper,&quot; played by juggling, and of course the Close Call Live app. In this performance from Classical:NEXT! in Rotterdam, he is supported by Joep Hendrickx, Tjalling Schrik, Marijn Korff de Gidts, Boy van Ooijen, Dodó Kis, Sarah Jeffery, Lotte Pen, Matthias Konrad, and Axel Schappert.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/24/07/2123267_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507210000 +0200" stop="20230507230900 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Above &amp; Beyond Group Therapy 300</title>
<desc lang="fr">Above &amp; Beyond Group Therapy 300 - Above and Beyond recently made their mark on ABGT300 in an epic way. Live for the 300th edition of Group Therapy Radio, the group broadcast from The Asiaworld-Expo in Hong Kong on September 29, 2018. ABGT300 also saw live performances from Andrew Bayer, Ben Böhmer, Grum, Ilan Bluestone, and Spencer Brown, with the signature set from Above and Beyond as the main event. This year, they wanted to push Group Therapy to the next level. Get ready for some magic moments and excellent music.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507230900 +0200" stop="20230508000800 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Paulo Novaes</title>
<desc lang="fr">Paulo Novaes - Da Pá Virada Sessions - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the artists taking part in this series is Paulo Novaes. Coming from a family of musicians, Paulo Novaes has already lived through a lifetime of music in spite of his young age. Paulo is the cousin of singer Bruna Caram, with whom he performed in São Paulo, Madrid, Barcelona, Lisbon, and other major cities. As a singer, composer, and instrumentalist, his creativity is enjoyed in many forms.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230508000800 +0200" stop="20230508015100 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">RSO (Richie Sambora &amp; Orianthi)</title>
<desc lang="fr">RSO (Richie Sambora &amp; Orianthi) - Long before music television filled the airwaves, the series Soundstage sparked the nation. This innovative and prestigious program achieved widespread critical acclaim and featured the artists that defined the era, such as RSO, which stands for Richie Sambora and Orianthi. The American guitarist Richie Sambora has been the lead guitarist of rock band Bon Jovi for 30 years. He was, together with Bon Jovi, responsible for most of the songwriting of the band. Orianthi is most known for her rehearsals in 2009 with Michael Jackson for his ill-fated This Is It concert series. She has also performed with Alice Cooper's touring band. Richie Sambora and Orianthi have been performing together as RSO since 2014. Enjoy their 2018 Soundstage show at WTTW Chicago!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/42/1870646_A.jpg" />
</programme>