<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Voo -->
<programme start="20230603022500 +0200" stop="20230603030000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Brian Bolger, Pat Brunnock, Tomas O'Durcain &amp; Chien Buggle</title>
<desc lang="fr">Classical:NEXT 2019 - Dublin Guitar Quartet - Strange to think that until the formation of The Dublin Guitar Quartet (DGQ) there had never been a guitar ensemble that specialised in contemporary classical music. The quartet consists of Brian Bolger, Pat Brunnock, Tomas O'Durcain, and Chien Buggle. Not deterred by the scarcity of repertoire, the DGQ set about creating their own collection of work by focusing on transcriptions and new commissions. Their performances now boast a dynamic mix of celebrated masterpieces by the likes of Philip Glass, Steve Reich, Arvo Pärt and Bryce Dessner alongside new commissions by composers such as Nico Muhly, Michael Gordon, and Marc Mellits.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/24/07/2123267_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230603030000 +0200" stop="20230603043100 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Banda Magda live at BIRD Rotterdam</title>
<desc lang="fr">Banda Magda: live at BIRD Rotterdam - An irresistible live act, Banda Magda is full of humour, unflagging energy, and quirky sensibility. A tight-knit group of musicians, they turn the songs of Greek-born founder, singer, and composer Magda Giannikou into engaging gems that have taken the band to legendary venues like Carnegie Hall and, for this performance, BIRD Rotterdam. Banda Magda moves from samba to French chanson, Greek folk music to Colombian cumbia and Afro-Peruvian landó. Their songs capture the best of mid-century ballads and cinematic arrangements, drawing from the band's global background and unrestrained musicality. A joy to experience, Banda Magda makes music for a new generation that's been inspired by ones before.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230603043100 +0200" stop="20230603053200 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Isle of Wight 2018: Part I</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Isle of Wight Festival, held in Newport, England is a rock-pop music festival that annually serves as the first major event opening the British festival summer. The tradition of the festival first saw the light of day in 1969, opening eleven days after the closing of legendary Woodstock and was regarded as the European counterpart to the legendary &quot;counterculture&quot; festival. In 1970, its line-up was stars-studded with gigs by Jimi Hendrix, The Who, The Doors, Joni Mitchell, Supertramp, Leonard Cohen and many more, establishing the name of the festival. In 2002, the festival was revived after 30 years of silence and brought back the sounds of contemporary musical legends to the Isle of Wight.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/42/1870646_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230603053200 +0200" stop="20230603073900 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Above &amp; Beyond Group Therapy 300</title>
<desc lang="fr">Above &amp; Beyond Group Therapy 300 - Above and Beyond recently made their mark on ABGT300 in an epic way. Live for the 300th edition of Group Therapy Radio, the group broadcast from The Asiaworld-Expo in Hong Kong on September 29, 2018. ABGT300 also saw live performances from Andrew Bayer, Ben Böhmer, Grum, Ilan Bluestone, and Spencer Brown, with the signature set from Above and Beyond as the main event. This year, they wanted to push Group Therapy to the next level. Get ready for some magic moments and excellent music.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230603073900 +0200" stop="20230603090000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Nilüfer Yanya - Echoes Series: Nilufer Yanya</title>
<desc lang="fr">Echoes Series - Episode 2 - Echoes is a modern live music show hosted by Jehnny Beth (lead singer in the British band Savages). It presents leading and emerging bands and artists from the contemporary scene. The show takes place underneath the Palais de Tokyo museum in Paris, in the club of brutalist architecture, the &quot;Yoyo.&quot; The live sets are 30 minutes long and take place on a customized stage, creating closeness with the audience. Once the bands have performed, Jehnny Beth invites everyone to sit at her roundtable for a group conversation. The open discussions in every episode allow the audience to understand the rapport, artistic exchange, and intellectual debates that run through this eclectic musical universe. The intimate, immersive space lends to the atmosphere of the show.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/03/1754401_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230603090000 +0200" stop="20230603102600 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Ryan Porter &amp; The West Coast Get Down</title>
<desc lang="fr">Ryan Porter &amp; The West Coast Get Down - BIRD - Los Angeles-born saxophonist Kamasi Washington and trombonist Ryan Porter co-founded West Coast Get Down - a musical collective fusing jazz and funk with hip-hop. It is partly because of this collective that jazz saw a resurgence in Los Angeles, subtly eclipsing the long-established jazz mecca of the world, New York City. The two musicians join forces and take the vibes of Los Angeles to jazz club BIRD in Rotterdam, the Netherlands.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/02/23/19/1647737_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230603102600 +0200" stop="20230603114100 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Lalah Hathaway</title>
<desc lang="fr">Lalah Hathaway - Sing Jazz 2018 - Winner of five Grammys in four consecutive years, including the Grammy for best R&amp;B album in 2017, Lalah Hathaway is a force impossible to ignore. The American artist has shared the scene with Prince, Snoop Dogg, Stevie Wonder, Anita Baker, Mary J. Blige, Frank Ocean and many others, an irrefutable proof of her keen musical sense and enormous talent. With a 26-year career, Hathaway is still highly sought after by the biggest names in music. See her transform the 2018 Sing Jazz festival scene into a real R&amp;B club, where she flaunts her voice and stage presence out of the ordinary.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/19/1853106_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230603114100 +0200" stop="20230603121800 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Tagg &amp; Petersen</title>
<desc lang="fr">Classical:NEXT 2019 - Tagg &amp; Petersen - The Kathleen Tagg / Andre Petersen piano duo brings together two of South Africa's most celebrated pianists: one eclectic-experimental classical and one jazz artist, in a unique and highly personal collaboration. Drawing inspiration from the rich sonic tapestries of classical music, nuances of South African jazz and traditional musics from sub-Saharan Africa, this duo explodes the concept of what two pianos can sound like: a bass guitar, goema drum, marimba and uhadi-plus mixing fully composed scores with improvisation in a bold, vital and highly entertaining mix with performances of original compositions and works by iconic South African jazz composers such as Abdullah Ibrahim, Bheki Mseleku and Moses Molelekwa.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/24/07/2123267_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230603121800 +0200" stop="20230603131200 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Tribute to Gilberto Gil</title>
<desc lang="fr">Tribute to Gilberto Gil - Da Pá Virada Sessions - The series Da Pá Virada sessions presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the bands taking part in this series is Caixa Cubo. This trio usually explores Brazil's rhythmically rich landscapes, combining them with modern Brazilian jazz trends. Yet in this singular performance, Caixa Cubo teams up with vocalist Zé Leônidas, selecting special repertoire together with Dani Gurgel from Da Pá Virada Sessions and Rokas Ku?inskas from Stingray DJAZZ.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230603131200 +0200" stop="20230603134300 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Ensemble Offspring</title>
<desc lang="fr">Ensemble Offspring - Ensemble Offspring is Australia's foremost new music ensemble, based in Sydney, made up of flute, clarinet, violin, cello, piano, and percussion. At Classical:NEXT, the ensemble features a line-up of internationally acclaimed core instrumentalists, Claire Edwardes (percussionist/artistic director), Zubin Kanga (piano), Jason Noble (clarinet), and Lamorna Nightingale (flute). With a 23-year history, the group embraces all modes of adventurous music making, which has brought to fruition the creation of over 200 new works. The 2019 Classical:Next showcase programme Solitude features two works written for the ensemble by Kate Moore (&quot;Fern&quot;) and Andrea Keller (&quot;Love in Solitude&quot;).</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/49/1767496_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230603134300 +0200" stop="20230603150000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Hamilton e Laginha</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Da Pá Virada Sessions series portrays the best musicians in Brazilian jazz today. All sessions were recorded in São Paulo and offer a unique experience: they offer a fresh look at the Brazilian music scene. The artists have been selected together with the music editor of Stingray DJAZZ. One of the musical collaborations that can be seen in this series is the duo of Hamilton de Holanda and Mário Laginha. Grammy nominee De Holanda, who has given the ten-string mandolin a new place in Brazilian music, is entering into a collaboration with pianist Mário Laginha. Together they perform gems of Brazilian music that will make the viewer's heart beat faster.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230603150000 +0200" stop="20230603162700 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Lucky Chops - Live at BIRD</title>
<desc lang="fr">Lucky Chops - Live at BIRD - The NYC band Lucky Chops rose to fame when a video of their performance at a subway station went viral on YouTube in 2015. Since then, the energetic quintet has been entertaining audiences all over the world. The band was formed in 2006, when trumpeter Joshua Gawel, saxophonist Daro Behroozi, trombonist Josh Holcomb, tubist Raphael Buyo, and drummer Charles Sams, met during their education at Fiorello H. LaGuardia High School of Music &amp; Art and Performing Arts. Besides touring globally, Lucky Chops also aspires to inspire new generations of musicians by regularly performing at clinics and educational outreaches. In August 2018, they performed their high-energy brassy funk at BIRD, in Rotterdam.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/52/1752443_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230603162700 +0200" stop="20230603172500 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">The O'Jays</title>
<desc lang="fr">The O'Jays - The O'Jays, who started in 1958, have grown into one of the most important vocal groups singing Philadelphia soul. They received the RIAA Platinum Record Award for several of their albums and Gold Discs for singles and other albums. Eddie Levert, Walter Williams, and Eric Grant shine in this live performance at the beautiful St. George Theatre in New York City. The concert features some of their most famous songs, such as &quot;Love Train,&quot; &quot;Use Ta Be My Girl,&quot; &quot;Enjoy Yourself,&quot; and more. Expect to see the same vibrant energy these men have had for over 50 years because The O'Jays give the people what they want in this concert!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/35/1763357_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230603172500 +0200" stop="20230603175800 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Ruben Hein &amp; NJJO : Jazz in Duketown</title>
<desc lang="fr">Ruben Hein &amp; NJJO - Jazz in Duketown - Jazz in Duketown is the largest free outdoor jazz festival in the Netherlands. It's a real gathering for jazz addicts, inviting internationally renowned artists. One of them is Dutch singer, pianist, composer and bandleader Ruben Hein. Widely praised for his warm and characteristic voice and his offbeat piano playing, Ruben Hein is the artistic director and conductor of the National Youth Jazz Orchestra (NJJO). At Jazz in Duketown he performs a jazzy set, accompanied by his 18 finest proteges.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/24/00/2153368_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230603175800 +0200" stop="20230603190000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">La Fraîcheur</title>
<desc lang="fr">La Fraîcheur - For over a decade now, first in Paris, then Montreal and now in Berlin, La Fraîcheur has been brewing her blend of deep house and techno beats, making a name for herself with her signature sound of emotionally charged and acid techno sets. The queer feminist-activist is a marathon DJ who can go on for countless hours, running the gamut from classics to new songs released just hours earlier. Her craft expanded by producing music ranging from ravy epic techno to dark pumping electro, spacious open-air deep house to melancholic electronica. She wrote her critically acclaimed debut album during an artist residency with the Berlin-Detroit Connection.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/59/1769392_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230603190000 +0200" stop="20230603193800 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Trio Zukan</title>
<desc lang="fr">Classical:NEXT 2019 - Trio Zukan - In 2014, Trio Zukan emerged from the combination of three uncommon instruments: accordion, percussion and txistu. The repertoire for this instrumental combination was non-existent at the beginning, so its members decided to promote a project with different composers, with the intention of creating a new repertoire. Today, Zukan has commissioned, revised and released more than a dozen pieces by national and international composers such as: María Eugenia Luc, Mikel Chamizo, Isabel Urrutia, Francisco José Domínguez, Vassilis Filippou, etc. The group is one of the most consolidated groups on the contemporary music scene in the Basque Country. They have performed in Quincena Musical Donostia, Bernaola Festival, Musikagileak Circuit, BBVA Cycle and Attacca Basel, among others.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/24/07/2123267_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230603193800 +0200" stop="20230603210000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Michelle David - Jazz in Duketown</title>
<desc lang="fr">Michelle David - Jazz in Duketown - Jazz in Duketown is the largest free outdoor jazz festival in the Netherlands. It's a real gathering for jazz addicts, inviting internationally renowned artists. The talented American singer Michelle David performs pop and gospel music that feeds the heart and soothes the soul. Having grown up with the church, she started singing at the age of four. A year later she joined her first band, The Mission of Love. In 1980 she enrolled at Fiorello H. LaGuardia High School of Music &amp; Art and Performing Arts in New York City, known from the film 'Fame'. During this time, she appeared as an extra in the legendary comedy film 'Ghostbusters'. Musicals and tours with the bands of Diana Ross and Michael Bolton followed.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/19/1853106_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230603210000 +0200" stop="20230603215900 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Stone Temple Pilots</title>
<desc lang="fr">Stone Temple Pilots - Enjoy ground-breaking concerts, in-depth artist interviews, and unique stories with host Ted Stryker. This concert series gives the audience an intimate view of music's most influential artists today. Shot in 4K, host Ted Stryker interviews musicians across all genres, creating one of the most unique music shows on TV today. This episode features the San Diego rock band Stone Temple Pilots, known for its timeless grungy rock sound.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/35/1763357_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230603215900 +0200" stop="20230603233000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Mötley Crüe</title>
<desc lang="fr">Mötley Crüe, the American rock band formed in the 1980s, was founded by bassist Nikki Sixx and drummer Tommy Lee, who were later joined by guitarist Mick Mars, and vocalist Vince Neil. Mötley Crüe has sold more than 100 million records worldwide, including 25 million in the US. On December 31, 2015, legendary rock icons Mötley Crüe completed their 35-year touring career as a band with a spectacular final concert at Staples Center in their hometown of Los Angeles, CA, just 10 miles from the Sunset Strip where the band's infamous and decadent career first launched. The band thrilled the sold-out arena with performances of mega-hits &quot;Kickstart My Heart,&quot; &quot;Girls Girls Girls,&quot; &quot;Home Sweet Home,&quot; and &quot;Dr. Feelgood.&quot; Directed by Jeff Tremaine and Christian Lamb.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Société</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/03/1853299_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230603233000 +0200" stop="20230604003300 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Gary Clark Jr.</title>
<desc lang="fr">Gary Clark Jr. - Texas guitarist Gary Clark Jr. has been compared to guitar icons like Jimi Hendrix and Stevie Ray Vaughan, and his playing is a powerful and inspired mix of blues, contemporary soul, and hip-hop. He sounds like a natural hybrid of both the past and the future of the blues. Born and raised in Austin, Texas, Clark first picked up a guitar at the age of 12 and spent his teens playing whatever gig he could get in the Austin area. In 2011, Clark signed with Warner Brothers' Records and released The Bright Lights EP. It was followed by the albums Blak and Blu and The Story of Sonny Boy Slim, both of which reached the Top Ten on the US charts. Throughout his career Clark has been a prolific live performer, and this intimate 2017 performance at The Village Studios is not one to be missed!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/03/1853299_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230604003300 +0200" stop="20230604013400 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">De La Soul - Garorock</title>
<desc lang="fr">De La Soul - Garorock - There is a packed crowd for this De La Soul set at the 2019 Garorock Festival, and with good reason: they witness an unmissable concert by an incomparable group! Having released regular albums since 1989's 3 Feet High and Rising, the Long Island hip-hop stalwarts of De La Soul have been doing the rounds on a suitably named Gods of Rap tour alongside Public Enemy and the Wu-Tang Clan. With an opening that includes call and response, mic checks and arms waving in the air, the audience gets more than a touch of vintage appeal, something that has led to terms like &quot;heritage rap&quot; being associated with the group. But despite their long and influential career, the De La Soul impact has perennial relevance for much of contemporary music. They pushed boundaries back then and they continue to venture out further.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>