<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Voo -->
<programme start="20230406030000 +0200" stop="20230406042200 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Alfredo Rodriguez &amp; Pedrito Martinez</title>
<desc lang="fr">Rodriguez &amp; Martinez - Jazz sous les Pommiers - Pianist Alfredo Rodriguez and percussionist Pedrito Martinez, both from Cuba, play an unforgettable Latin jazz performance at the 2019 edition of festival Jazz sous les Pommiers in Coutances, France. Although both musicians are originally from Havana, Cuba, their music careers are blooming in the USA. The duo's debut album &quot;Duologue&quot; was produced by legendary producer Quincy Jones and saw its release in 2019. Their Jazz sous les Pommiers concert features original compositions alongside Yoruba pieces in honor of the African diaspora to Cuba. Moreover, the duo plays an unexpected interpretation of the Super Mario theme during this varied performance.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/45/1769516_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230406042200 +0200" stop="20230406050800 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Bakolo Music International</title>
<desc lang="fr">In 2018 WOMEX took place in Las Palmas in Gran Canaria. One of the participants was the band Bakolo Music International. They represent the pioneers of the golden age of the Congolese rumba. Singer, guitarist and veteran Nzofu Moko Buele, called Bikunda by everyone, keeps the fire burning that &quot;Papa&quot; lit Wendolosoy, the &quot;father of the Congolese rumba&quot; in 1948 when his song &quot;Marie-Louise&quot; became an international hit.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/50/1642161_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230406050800 +0200" stop="20230406060900 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Creamfields</title>
<desc lang="fr">Creamfields - Having burst onto the ever-growing festival scene two decades ago, Creamfields has secured its spot as being one of the - if not the - biggest weekend dedicated to electronic music in the UK. Currently, the clubbing and raving pilgrimage attracts an impressive 70,000 festival-goers over the weekend. Continuously offering up the very best in EDM, house, trance, drum and bass, grime, and more, Creamfields has hosted some massive names over the past twenty years. This 2019 edition of Creamfields presents Green Velvet, MK, Carl Cox, Deadmau5, Camelphat, Nicole Moudaber, Dimitri Vegas &amp; Like Mike, and many more!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/59/1769392_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230406060900 +0200" stop="20230406074100 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Banda Magda live at BIRD Rotterdam</title>
<desc lang="fr">Banda Magda: live at BIRD Rotterdam - An irresistible live act, Banda Magda is full of humour, unflagging energy, and quirky sensibility. A tight-knit group of musicians, they turn the songs of Greek-born founder, singer, and composer Magda Giannikou into engaging gems that have taken the band to legendary venues like Carnegie Hall and, for this performance, BIRD Rotterdam. Banda Magda moves from samba to French chanson, Greek folk music to Colombian cumbia and Afro-Peruvian landó. Their songs capture the best of mid-century ballads and cinematic arrangements, drawing from the band's global background and unrestrained musicality. A joy to experience, Banda Magda makes music for a new generation that's been inspired by ones before.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230406074100 +0200" stop="20230406081300 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">The Hermes Experiment</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Hermes Experiment - The Hermes Experiment, consisting of Heloise Werner (soprano), Oliver Pashley (clarinet), Anne Denholm (harp) and Marianne Schofield (double bass) is a UK-based contemporary quartet made up of harp, clarinet, voice and double bass. Capitalising on their deliberately idiosyncratic combination of instruments, the ensemble regularly commissions new works, as well as creating their own innovative arrangements and venturing into live free improvisation. The ensemble has commissioned over 50 composers at various stages of their careers. During this showcase recorded at Classical:NEXT 2019 in Rotterdam, The Netherlands, The Hermes Experiment performs &quot;I Am Happy Living Simply'&quot;and &quot;The End of the Ending&quot; by Emily Hall, &quot;Samsara&quot; by Alex Mills, and &quot;Double Fiesta&quot; by Meredith Monk.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/13/1767495_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230406081300 +0200" stop="20230406090000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">WOMEX 2018</title>
<desc lang="fr">Mario Batkovic - WOMEX 2018 - Since 1994, World Music Expo (WOMEX) has been attracting musicians, agents, a great number of press agencies, as well as media companies from all over the world. Its main exposition event has been held in various locations throughout Europe, including Berlin, Brussels, Marseille, Stockholm, Seville, Cardiff, and Budapest. The 2018 edition of WOMEX was held in Las Palmas, Gran Canaria. One of its showcase participants, Mario Batkovic, aims to explore the sonic possibilities of the accordion, without effects or loops, rather through a mutualist symbiotic relationship between man and instrument. Challenging, hypnotic, and grandiose, Batkovic's single-handed symphonic vision is certainly unique.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/29/16/2143305_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230406090000 +0200" stop="20230406103100 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">WeARE4</title>
<desc lang="fr">Hip-hop musician Sly Johnson makes the switch to jazz, and how! At Jazz à Ramatuelle 2018 he surrounds himself with top musicians: André Ceccarelli on drums, Laurent De Wilde on keys, and Fifi Chayeb on funkbas. Together they form WeARE4. The men take on the challenge of mixing hip hop with jazz, finding the perfect level of melodic and expressive freedom. WeARE4 surprises the audience at Jazz à Ramatuelle with flawless performances full of accurate flows and well-balanced harmonies. In the intimate Théâtre de Verdure, they explore the endless possibilities that the golden bond between hip hop and jazz offers!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/35/1763357_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230406103100 +0200" stop="20230406113000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Paulo Novaes - New Year's Eve Special</title>
<desc lang="fr">Paulo Novaes - New Year's Eve Special - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the artists taking part in this series is Paulo Novaes. Coming from a family of musicians, Paulo Novaes has already lived through a lifetime of music in spite of his young age. Paulo is the cousin of singer Bruna Caram, with whom he performed in São Paulo, Madrid, Barcelona, Lisbon, and other major cities. As a singer, composer, and instrumentalist, his creativity is enjoyed in many forms.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230406113000 +0200" stop="20230406134300 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam</title>
<desc lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam - New Cool Collective is one of the foremost Dutch jazz ensembles. Pioneering new blends of music styles since 1993, NCC has performed in various formations, from small combos to larger ensembles and even big bands! The ensemble's high energy is cut out for the dance floors, as dance, Latin, salsa, afrobeat and boogaloo all meet in a jazzy mix. NCC includes saxophonist Benjamin Herman, guitarist Rory Ronde, drummer Joost Kroon, percussionists Frank van Dok and Jos de Haas, pianist Willem Friede, bassist Leslie Lopez, and trumpeter David Rockefeller.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230406134300 +0200" stop="20230406150100 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Os Capoeira</title>
<desc lang="fr">Os Capoeira - Da Pá Virada Sessions - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the bands taking part in this series is Os Capoeira. This ensemble practices the traditional Brazilian martial art from Bahia it is named after, combining elements of dance, acrobatics, and percussive music. Moreover, Os Capoeira runs a cultural center in São Paulo. Let yourself be inspired by Os Capoeira's unique take on Brazilian culture!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230406150100 +0200" stop="20230406171600 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam</title>
<desc lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam - New Cool Collective is one of the foremost Dutch jazz ensembles. Pioneering new blends of music styles since 1993, NCC has performed in various formations, from small combos to larger ensembles and even big bands! The ensemble's high energy is cut out for the dance floors, as dance, Latin, salsa, afrobeat and boogaloo all meet in a jazzy mix. NCC includes saxophonist Benjamin Herman, guitarist Rory Ronde, drummer Joost Kroon, percussionists Frank van Dok and Jos de Haas, pianist Willem Friede, bassist Leslie Lopez, and trumpeter David Rockefeller.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230406171600 +0200" stop="20230406181000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Audience Music</title>
<desc lang="fr">Enjoy ground-breaking concerts, in-depth artist interviews, and unique stories with host Ted Stryker. This concert series gives the audience an intimate view of music's most influential artists today. Shot in 4K, host Ted Stryker interviews musicians across all genres, creating one of the most unique music shows on TV today. This episode features singer/songwriter Skylar Grey, best known for her songwriting skills, as displayed in Eminem and Rihanna's &quot;Love The Way You Lie&quot; (2010). The five-time GRAMMY-nominee and Wisconsin-born pop artist takes the stage to perform some of her most popular songs, as well as some works of her forthcoming album &quot;Angel With Tattoos&quot;. Enjoy Skylar Grey's performance and interview at Audience Music 2019!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/04/2122118_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230406181000 +0200" stop="20230406191400 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Hercules Gomes</title>
<desc lang="fr">Hercules Gomes - Da Pá Virada Sessions - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the artists taking part in this series is pianist Hércules Gomes. Due to his impressive technical skill and expressive choice of repertoire he is considered one of Brazil's foremost pianists today. Hércules has performed with numerous renowned Brazilian musicians, including Arismar do Espirito Santo, Letieres Leite, Alessandro Penezzi, Wilson das Neves, and Banda Mantiqueira.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/19/1853106_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230406191400 +0200" stop="20230406203100 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">The Opera Locos</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Opera Locos - In The Opera Locos (&quot;The Opera of Crazies&quot;), a comic opera show from the Spanish theater company Yllana and theatre producer Rami Eldar, five eccentric opera singers perform some of the greatest opera arias. Classical arias from George Bizet's Carmen, W. A. Mozart's The Magic Flute, and Giuseppe Verdi's Rigoletto are combined with classics from the pop and rock repertoire. During the performance, the five characters reveal their hidden passions, personalities, and desires, leading to unpredictable, hilarious situations that audiences of all ages will appreciate. The soloists are Florian Laconi (tenor), Margaux Toqué (mezzo soprano), Michaël Koné (countertenor), Laurent Arcaro (baritone), and Diane Fourès (soprano). This performance was recorded at Théâtre Libre in Paris, France.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Evénement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/02/07/27/1763355_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230406203100 +0200" stop="20230406210000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Chopin - Ballade No. 1, Op. 23</title>
<desc lang="fr">Chopin - Ballade No. 1, Op. 23 - Roberto Giordano performs Chopin's Ballade No. 1, Op. 23. The sketches of the work date back to 1831 during Chopin's eight-month stay in Vienna. The first ballade was completed in 1835 after the composer moved to Paris. The main section of the ballade is built from two main themes which return in different keys after which a thundering chord introduces the Presto con fuoco, which eventually ends the piece in a fiery double octave scale run down the keyboard. The work gained popularity after appearing on the soundtrack to the 2002 Roman Polanski film The Pianist, where it is played by Janusz Olejniczak.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/07/13/2156410_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230406210000 +0200" stop="20230406213200 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Audience Music</title>
<desc lang="fr">X Ambassadors - Enjoy ground-breaking concerts, in-depth artist interviews, and unique stories with host Ted Stryker. This concert series gives the audience an intimate view of music's most influential artists today. Shot in 4K, host Ted Stryker interviews musicians across all genres, creating one of the most unique music shows on TV today. This episode features the alternative rock band X Ambassadors, founded in 2009. After self-releasing the debut EP &quot;Ambassadors EP&quot;, which featured &quot;Litost&quot;, a song that would later be added to the soundtrack of sci-fi blockbuster The Host, the band had its break-through when Imagine Dragons lead singer Dan Reynolds initiated their signage to a major music label.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/58/1754433_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230406213200 +0200" stop="20230406223300 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Isle of Wight 2018: Part II</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Isle of Wight Festival, held in Newport, England is a rock-pop music festival that annually serves as the first major event opening the British festival summer. The tradition of the festival first saw the light of day in 1969, opening eleven days after the closing of legendary Woodstock and was regarded as the European counterpart to the legendary &quot;counterculture&quot; festival. In 1970, its line-up was stars-studded with gigs by Jimi Hendrix, The Who, The Doors, Joni Mitchell, Supertramp, Leonard Cohen and many more, establishing the name of the festival. In 2002, the festival was revived after 30 years of silence and brought back the sounds of contemporary musical legends to the Isle of Wight.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/42/1870646_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230406223300 +0200" stop="20230406234600 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Arnaud Rebotini : Le Trabendo</title>
<desc lang="fr">Arnaud Rebotini - Trabendo Paris - Arnaud Rebotini is one of hexagonal electro's major figures and the founding father of electroclash group Black Strobe. 2017 saw the release of his soundtrack for 120 Beats Per Minute. At the end of this successful year, Rebotini put on an amazing set at Trabendo Paris. Rebotini's show is all but static - his exciting beats are supported by vocals that make the crowd go wild. This show is a feast for the eyes and ears. Enjoy Rebotini's energizing show and high-end visual effects in native 4K!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230406234600 +0200" stop="20230407005000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Jesse Cook - Follow the Road</title>
<desc lang="fr">Celebrated guitarist, composer, and music producer Jesse Cook has been delivering unforgettable concert experiences to audiences across the globe for over 25 years. As far as he has ventured, Jesse has always been fascinated with the mystique of the road that first led him out of Toronto. In his directorial debut, Cook shows us a concert from a rarely seen perspective: the musician's. Born to film director parents, guitarist Jesse Cook taps into this pedigree, and self-directed this story, his fifth Concert Special. The result is &quot;Follow the Road.&quot; Captured in 4K, during his 31-city cross-Canada tour, we follow the band down the TransCanada Highway, against a backdrop of majestic mountains and stunning natural beauty, as they traverse the scenic splendor of the second largest country in the world.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Musique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/04/2122118_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230407005000 +0200" stop="20230407015900 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Ricardo Herz Trio</title>
<desc lang="fr">Da Pá Virada sessions bring the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each sessions are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the bands that are taking part in this series are the Ricardo Herz Trio, which consists of Ricardo Herz on violin, Michi Ruzitschka on nylon string guitar, and Pedro Ito on percussions. Band leader Ricardo Herz is a classically-trained musician, who also studied jazz at the prestigious Berklee College of Music.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>