<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Voo -->
<programme start="20230404030000 +0200" stop="20230404041900 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Bad Company : Live From Red Rocks</title>
<desc lang="fr">Soundstage, an innovative and prestigious program, achieved widespread critical acclaim while featuring artists that defined the era. On May 15, 2016, at Red Rocks Amphitheater in Colorado, Soundstage captured the legendary classic rock band Bad Company delivering their biggest hits. The band consists of bassist Boz Burrell, guitarist Mick Ralphs, singer Paul Rodgers, and drummer Simon Kirke. The setlist contains their greatest songs, such as &quot;Live for the Music,&quot; &quot;Ready for Love,&quot; &quot;Can't Get Enough&quot; and &quot;Rock Steady.&quot;.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230404041900 +0200" stop="20230404050400 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Invisible World : WOMEX 2018</title>
<desc lang="fr">One of the participants was the band Invisible World, which operates at the crossroads where Eastern European and Mediterranean influences come together and break new ground. Invisible World is led by the inventive Czech bassist Tomá? Li?ka, together with the Turkish violinist Efe Turumtay, the Serbian accordionist Nikola Zari? and the Moravian drummer Kamil Slezák.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/28/13/2143305_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230404050400 +0200" stop="20230404060400 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Nubiyan Twist : Music Meeting</title>
<desc lang="fr">Nubiyan Twist - Music Meeting - Since 1985, the Dutch city of Nijmegen has been welcoming the International Music Meeting Festival every Pentecost. Ranging from jazz and improvisational music to traditional music and unique crossovers, this adventurous festival is all about musical encounters and international collaborations. In 2019, the band Nubiyan Twist performs at the International Music Meeting Festival. This London-based group operates on the intersection of soul and jazz.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230404060400 +0200" stop="20230404073800 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Antonio Faraò</title>
<desc lang="fr">Jazz à Ramatuelle: Antonio Faraò - In 1998, Antonio Faraò won the prestigious Concours Martial Solal, awarded to him by Herbie Hancock! Since then, this talented Italian jazz pianist has made his mark as a player of elegance and lyricism, which has allowed him to collaborate with the best European and American musicians. On his last album &quot;Evan&quot;, recorded in the United States, he leads an all-star band starring Joe Lovano on tenor saxophone. On a beautiful summer night at the French Jazz à Ramatuelle festival, Faraò performs at the breathtaking Theatre de Verdure in the company of saxophone legend Dave Liebman. With refined ballads, a feline groove, elegance, and lyricism, this musical meeting sparkles - if you watch closely you might even see some bright new stars lighting up in the night sky above Ramatuelle!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230404073800 +0200" stop="20230404080900 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Lifschitz &amp; Davidson</title>
<desc lang="fr">Lifschitz &amp; Davidson - Sonya Lifschitz is a pianist working across many contexts, with repertoire spanning from 15th century Faenza Codex to works written for her today. She is known for her fiercely imaginative, daring collaborations across film, animation, spoken word, visual and performance art. Robert Davidson has been making music from language since childhood. He has created music from the voices of Australia's prime ministers, from 100 years of radio broadcasts and from stories of asylum seekers and indigenous members of Australia's Stolen Generations. This performance is recorded during Classical:NEXT 2019 in Rotterdam, The Netherlands.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/49/1767496_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230404080900 +0200" stop="20230404090000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Audience Music</title>
<desc lang="fr">Urban Cone - Watch groundbreaking concerts, in-depth artist interviews, and stories with host Ted Stryker. This concert series gives the audience an intimate view of music's most influential artists today. Shot in 4K, Stryker interviews musicians across all genres, creating the most unique music show on TV today. This episode features the Swedish indie pop band Urban Cone. The band was formed in 2010 by Emil Gustafsson, Tim Formgren, Rasmus Flyckt, Jacob William Sjöberg, and Magnus Folkö. Their debut EP Our Youth came about when they were only 16 years old. The album was recorded in Flyckt's living room. The album's debut single &quot;Urban Photograph&quot; reached #2 on Hype Machine. A tour to the U.S. followed, with performances in New York City, Brooklyn, Los Angeles, and San Francisco.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/58/1754433_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230404090000 +0200" stop="20230404100400 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Nilüfer Yanya - Echoes Series: Nilufer Yanya</title>
<desc lang="fr">Echoes Series - Episode 3 - Echoes is a modern live music show hosted by Jehnny Beth (lead singer in the British band Savages). It presents leading and emerging bands and artists from the contemporary scene. The show takes place underneath the Palais de Tokyo museum in Paris, in the club of brutalist architecture, the &quot;Yoyo.&quot; The live sets are 30 minutes long and take place on a customized stage, creating closeness with the audience. Once the bands have performed, Jehnny Beth invites everyone to sit at her roundtable for a group conversation. The open discussions in every episode allow the audience to understand the rapport, artistic exchange, and intellectual debates that run through this eclectic musical universe. The intimate, immersive space lends to the atmosphere of the show.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/03/1754401_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230404100400 +0200" stop="20230404110000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Sheryl Crow</title>
<desc lang="fr">Sheryl Crow - Missouri-born country mega-star Sheryl Crow celebrates her return to the stage in an intimate performance at New York City's Iridium. Having sold over million copies of her ten studio albums worldwide over the course of her over three decade-long career, Sheryl Crow has long-established a status of one of America's most successful musicians. With a warm sound made up of elements of country, pop, rock and Americana, Crow has received nine GRAMMY-awards and over thirty nominations.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/03/1853299_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230404110000 +0200" stop="20230404123800 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Kyle Eastwood Quintet</title>
<desc lang="fr">Jazz à Ramatuelle: Kyle Eastwood Quintet - Bassist Kyle Eastwood (1968) is an explorer, equally at ease with jazz melodies as with pop songs. In the late 1970s, his father Clint took him to see his first jazz concert - a Count Basie performance. Eastwood Jr. was in awe of the drummer and wanted to play an instrument himself. It so happened he wasn't so much interested in jazz, preferring rhythm and blues, Motown and Stax records, funk groups, and North African and Indian music. Eastwood became a brilliant bassist and the composer of highly original soundtracks. His 2015 album &quot;Time Pieces&quot; is a collaboration with brilliant British musicians, such as trumpeter Quentin Collins and saxophonist Brandon Allen. In this broadcast, Eastwood and his fellow musicians revisit the hard bop legacy of Blue Note Records.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/19/1853106_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230404123800 +0200" stop="20230404132400 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Etenesh Wassie Trio : WOMEX 2018</title>
<desc lang="fr">In 2018 WOMEX took place in Las Palmas in Gran Canaria. One of the participants was the Ethiopian diva Etenesh Wassie with her trio. She mixes the contemporary energy of jazz and punk with her in-depth knowledge of the Ethiopian repertoire. The result is compelling, inspired, and truly unique.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/28/13/2143305_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230404132400 +0200" stop="20230404142500 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Mestrinho</title>
<desc lang="fr">Mestrinho - Da Pá Virada Sessions - Da Pá Virada sessions bring the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the artists taking part in this series is accordionist Mestrinho, seen in performance with Cainã Cavalcante on guitar, Alex Buck on drums, and Carlinhos Noronha on bass. They combine the subtle rhythms of Brazilian music with the leader's instrumental virtuosity.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/19/1853106_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230404142500 +0200" stop="20230404150200 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Eleanor Dubinsky - Nublu 2019</title>
<desc lang="fr">The music of vocalist, guitarist and cellist Eleanor Dubinsky lives on the narrow ledge where jazz, international music and pop meet emotionally heartfelt songwriting. The musician and her versatile band deliver dynamic compositions that explore the fragile link between human emotions and human responsibility. The core of Eleanor's artistic mission is to enter into dialogue and achieve self-realization through music.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230404150200 +0200" stop="20230404163600 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Mötley Crüe</title>
<desc lang="fr">Mötley Crüe, the American rock band formed in the 1980s, was founded by bassist Nikki Sixx and drummer Tommy Lee, who were later joined by guitarist Mick Mars, and vocalist Vince Neil. Mötley Crüe has sold more than 100 million records worldwide, including 25 million in the US. On December 31, 2015, legendary rock icons Mötley Crüe completed their 35-year touring career as a band with a spectacular final concert at Staples Center in their hometown of Los Angeles, CA, just 10 miles from the Sunset Strip where the band's infamous and decadent career first launched. The band thrilled the sold-out arena with performances of mega-hits &quot;Kickstart My Heart,&quot; &quot;Girls Girls Girls,&quot; &quot;Home Sweet Home,&quot; and &quot;Dr. Feelgood.&quot; Directed by Jeff Tremaine and Christian Lamb.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Société</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/03/1853299_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230404163600 +0200" stop="20230404173500 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Samba das Flores</title>
<desc lang="fr">Samba das Flores - Da Pá Virada Sessions - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the bands taking part in this series is the ensemble Samba das Flores, which dedicates itself to exploring the world's different rhythms, thus keeping the Brazilian heritage alive. The individual voices of the ensemble members color Samba das Flores's unique sound. Let Brazilian culture and global rhythms inspire you during this Samba das Flores performance!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230404173500 +0200" stop="20230404194800 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam</title>
<desc lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam - New Cool Collective is one of the foremost Dutch jazz ensembles. Pioneering new blends of music styles since 1993, NCC has performed in various formations, from small combos to larger ensembles and even big bands! The ensemble's high energy is cut out for the dance floors, as dance, Latin, salsa, afrobeat and boogaloo all meet in a jazzy mix. NCC includes saxophonist Benjamin Herman, guitarist Rory Ronde, drummer Joost Kroon, percussionists Frank van Dok and Jos de Haas, pianist Willem Friede, bassist Leslie Lopez, and trumpeter David Rockefeller.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230404194800 +0200" stop="20230404210000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Rooted With Wings</title>
<desc lang="fr">Rooted With Wings - Rooted with Wings is a visual dance documentary that explores the work of internationally acclaimed choreographer and dancer Tero Saarinen, granting the viewer a unique lens into this extraordinary artist's creative process. The film brings to light how Saarinen's dance works evolve from an idea or concept into a finished performance and features stunningly captured dance sequences and behind-the-scenes material from around the globe. The film follows Saarinen over five years, from 2014 to 2018, through several premieres of new works and tours in Finland, France, Korea, Kenya, and the US, while bringing to light his approach to his life as a global nomad in dance.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Documentaire</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/10/1752533_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230404210000 +0200" stop="20230404222600 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Incognito</title>
<desc lang="fr">Incognito - Sing Jazz 2018 - An acid jazz project rooted in the 1970s jazz/funk/soul world, Incognito was originally formed by Jean-Paul &quot;Bluey&quot; Maunick and Paul &quot;Tubbs&quot; Williams. Both were original members of the late 1970s disco/funk group Light of the World. They decided to take a couple of their jams into the studio and debuted with the single Parisienne Girl. Decades later, Incognito's cover of Boz Scaggs' classic Lowdown with Chaka Khan and Mario Biondi saw the band's international status grow more and more popular. At Sing Jazz 2018, Incognito takes a fresh direction on classic musical themes, giving their fans an unforgettable live show!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/28/02/2145502_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230404222600 +0200" stop="20230404232500 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Steve Vai</title>
<desc lang="fr">Steve Vai - The popular music performance series, Front and Center, which premiered nationwide on public television, in 2016, returns for Season 6. The series boasts 22, one-hour episodes and an all-star line-up. This episode features Steve Vai, the legendary guitarist who was voted the 10th Greatest Guitarist by Guitar World magazine, who treats fans to songs from his three-decade long career. As an independent guitarist he has won three Grammy Awards. Vai's solo sophomore release, Passion and Warfare, has earned gold certification in the US. At Front and Center he sits down and discusses his early interest in composing music and playing guitar as well as the many fortunes of his career.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Musique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/42/1870646_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230404232500 +0200" stop="20230405002800 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Joris Voorn</title>
<desc lang="fr">Joris Voorn - The Royal Concertgebouw is a night full of the best house and techno, hosted by one of the biggest names from the underground at one of the prettiest locations in the world. Renown as one of the most stunning sites dedicated to music, the Royal Concertgebouw has been transformed into a glorious cathedral of techno for one night only. Audio Obscura is a movement born out of love for cutting-edge underground dance music. Today, Audio Obscura has grown into one of the most sought-after destinations for leading DJs to play, and for partygoers, both young and old, to dance the night (and day) away.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/19/1849379_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230405002800 +0200" stop="20230405014700 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">HVOB</title>
<desc lang="fr">HVOB - The two musicians behind HVOB are Anna Müller and Paul Wallner. Anna Müller composes, produces, and provides the captivating, hypnotic vocals. The final production of the tracks is done in collaboration with Paul Wallner in his Vienna studio. HVOB are carving their path not just with their distinctive sound but with their live performances as well. The duo always plays live and performs with a drummer - a concept as innovative as it is successful: HVOB has just been voted number two best live act by the most influential German electronic music magazine &quot;De:bug.&quot; Enjoy their 2019 show at Trabendo Paris!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Musique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/59/1769392_A.jpg" />
</programme>