<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Voo -->
<programme start="20230325020400 +0100" stop="20230325030000 +0100" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Ed O'Brien</title>
<desc lang="fr">Echoes Series: Ed O'Brien - Echoes is a modern live music show hosted by Jehnny Beth (lead singer in the British band Savages). It presents leading and emerging bands and artists from the contemporary scene. The show takes place underneath the Palais de Tokyo museum in Paris, in the club of brutalist architecture, the &quot;Yoyo.&quot; The live sets are 30 minutes long and take place on a customized stage, creating closeness with the audience. The intimate, immersive space lends to the atmosphere of the show. The artistic direction by Antoine Carlier follows a minimalist, refined and pure aesthetic, allowing the artists' energy and emotions to take center stage. This episode features guitarist Ed O'Brien, a member of rock band Radiohead. His set includes the songs &quot;Mass,&quot; &quot;Olympik,&quot; and &quot;Brasil.&quot;.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230325030000 +0100" stop="20230325051500 +0100" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam</title>
<desc lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam - New Cool Collective is one of the foremost Dutch jazz ensembles. Pioneering new blends of music styles since 1993, NCC has performed in various formations, from small combos to larger ensembles and even big bands! The ensemble's high energy is cut out for the dance floors, as dance, Latin, salsa, afrobeat and boogaloo all meet in a jazzy mix. NCC includes saxophonist Benjamin Herman, guitarist Rory Ronde, drummer Joost Kroon, percussionists Frank van Dok and Jos de Haas, pianist Willem Friede, bassist Leslie Lopez, and trumpeter David Rockefeller.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230325051500 +0100" stop="20230325060800 +0100" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">WOMEX 2018</title>
<desc lang="fr">In 2018 WOMEX took place in Las Palmas in Gran Canaria. One of the participants was The Garifuna Collective. These young and old musicians from the Caribbean keep Andy Palacio's legacy alive.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/24/31/2143305_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230325060800 +0100" stop="20230325071100 +0100" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Liran Donin : Music Meeting</title>
<desc lang="fr">Nijmegen has been welcoming the International Music Meeting Festival, or Music Meeting for short, every spring since 1985. From jazz and improvised music to traditional music and unique crossovers: musical encounters and international collaborations are at the heart of this adventurous festival. In 2019, Tel Aviv-born bassist, producer and composer Liran Donin performed here.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230325071100 +0100" stop="20230325082800 +0100" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Chaka Khan</title>
<desc lang="fr">Chaka Khan - Chaka Khan, also known as the &quot;Queen of Funk,&quot; has sold about 70 million records worldwide in her nearly five-decade-long career. This unique singer masters many musical genres, including R&amp;B, pop, rock, gospel, country, international music, and classical music. For this concert, the 10-times Grammy Award-winning artist returns to her hometown, where she gives the performance of a lifetime to an appreciative audience. With her nine-piece band and three backing vocalists, she performs a smashing selection of her greatest hits, including &quot;I'm Every Woman,&quot; &quot;Ain't Nobody,&quot; and &quot;Tell Me Something Good.&quot; Join this world-famous superstar in this concert recorded at the Harris Theatre in Chicago, filmed in spectacular 4K.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Musique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230325082800 +0100" stop="20230325090000 +0100" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Half Moon Run</title>
<desc lang="fr">Songbook - &quot;I never heard anyone say that, and yeah, I know exactly what it means. It has to go in there, this has to be a song.&quot; Every song has its own story, and we all think it's a story we've heard before, but we haven't. Songbook finds and captures these intriguing stories by pulling you into the process of writing and composing. Known for its pristine sound, cinematic 4k video and eye for detail, Songbook live-captured episodes emphasize the paramount importance of quality. It addresses the on-the-spot elements of blending song and location at the right moment. Both the magical location and remarkable music interaction will get the attention they deserve. Simply because Songbook isn't just a live music session, it lives.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230325090000 +0100" stop="20230325094500 +0100" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Fedde le Grand @ Pacha Festival</title>
<desc lang="fr">Pacha Festival - Fedde Le Grand is considered one of the most important artists of house music, a style in constant evolution. He is known around the world for his simple &quot;Put Your Hands Up For Detroit&quot;, &quot;Rhythm Of The Night&quot;, &quot;The Creeps&quot;, and &quot;Let Me Think About It&quot;. Fedde Le Grand has received countless awards and has offered remixes of the greatest international artists such as Coldplay, Madonna, Will.i.am, Robbie Williams and, more recently, Michael Jackson (&quot;Love Never Felt So Good&quot;) and Faithless (&quot;Insomnia&quot;). His electrifying DJ set at Bali's Pacha Festival thrills the view with his breathtaking lights, fireworks, and delirious crowd!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230325094500 +0100" stop="20230325104600 +0100" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Johnny Marr - Rock en Seine</title>
<desc lang="fr">Johnny Marr at Rock en Seine 2019 - English musician, songwriter, and singer Johnny Marr has enjoyed an exemplary career since his former band The Smiths split up in 1987. His distinctive guitar sound has been part of such varied groups as The Pretenders, The Cribs, Modest Mouse, and Electronic, the group he co-founded with Bernard Sumner of New Order. Now a living legend, Johnny Marr showcases his incredible singer-songwriter talents on each new album. His recent, hit-packed release Call The Comet (2018) gave us &quot;The Tracers&quot; and &quot;Hi Hello,&quot; and his live performances - which usually include some songs from his days with The Smiths - always hit the mark. Enjoy this 2019 show recorded at Rock en Seine in Paris!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/15/2123266_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230325104600 +0100" stop="20230325115400 +0100" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">BIGYUKI : BIRD 2019</title>
<desc lang="fr">BIGYUKI - BIRD 2019 - BIGYUKI's is New York City's secret musical weapon! His unprecedented sound has attracted the attention of many, including Grammy Award-winning and nominated artists such as Q-Tip, Bilal, Talib Kweli, Harvey Mason, Marcus Strickland, Mark Giuliana, and Meshell Ndegeocello. BIGYUKI's music offers a soulful exploration into the wondrous soundscapes of his infinitely virtuosic mind. Infusing elements of jazz, classical music, hip-hop, soul, rock, dance, and electronica, BIGYUKI reaches a new and inspiring level, with support from guitarist Randy Runyon and drummer Smithsoneon. It is hard to believe that just three musicians can create a sound this massive.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/59/1769392_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230325115400 +0100" stop="20230325125600 +0100" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Nilüfer Yanya - Echoes Series: Nilufer Yanya</title>
<desc lang="fr">Echoes Series - Episode 4 - Echoes is a modern live music show hosted by Jehnny Beth (lead singer in the British band Savages). It presents leading and emerging bands and artists from the contemporary scene. The show takes place underneath the Palais de Tokyo museum in Paris, in the club of brutalist architecture, the &quot;Yoyo.&quot; The live sets are 30 minutes long and take place on a customized stage, creating closeness with the audience. Once the bands have performed, Jehnny Beth invites everyone to sit at her roundtable for a group conversation. The open discussions in every episode allow the audience to understand the rapport, artistic exchange, and intellectual debates that run through this eclectic musical universe. The intimate, immersive space lends to the atmosphere of the show.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/57/1752448_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230325125600 +0100" stop="20230325135000 +0100" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Audience Music</title>
<desc lang="fr">Enjoy ground-breaking concerts, in-depth artist interviews, and unique stories with host Ted Stryker. This concert series gives the audience an intimate view of music's most influential artists today. Shot in 4K, host Ted Stryker interviews musicians across all genres, creating one of the most unique music shows on TV today. This episode features singer/songwriter Skylar Grey, best known for her songwriting skills, as displayed in Eminem and Rihanna's &quot;Love The Way You Lie&quot; (2010). The five-time GRAMMY-nominee and Wisconsin-born pop artist takes the stage to perform some of her most popular songs, as well as some works of her forthcoming album &quot;Angel With Tattoos&quot;. Enjoy Skylar Grey's performance and interview at Audience Music 2019!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/04/2122118_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230325135000 +0100" stop="20230325150000 +0100" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Isle of Wight 2018: Part II</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Isle of Wight Festival, held in Newport, England is a rock-pop music festival that annually serves as the first major event opening the British festival summer. The tradition of the festival first saw the light of day in 1969, opening eleven days after the closing of legendary Woodstock and was regarded as the European counterpart to the legendary &quot;counterculture&quot; festival. In 1970, its line-up was stars-studded with gigs by Jimi Hendrix, The Who, The Doors, Joni Mitchell, Supertramp, Leonard Cohen and many more, establishing the name of the festival. In 2002, the festival was revived after 30 years of silence and brought back the sounds of contemporary musical legends to the Isle of Wight.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/42/1870646_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230325150000 +0100" stop="20230325163900 +0100" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Moderat at Stereolux 2016</title>
<desc lang="fr">Moderat at Stereolux 2016 - Since the German bands Modeselektor (Gernot Bronsert and Sebastian Szary) and Apparat (Sascha Ring) joined forces in 2009, they have been hugely successful as the electronic music supergroup Moderat. In 2012, the formation produced the soundtrack of Xavier Dolan's film Laurence Anyways, released as A New Error. According to Les Inrockuptibles, their album II includes &quot;the rhythmic punch of the one (Modeselektor) and atmospheric finesse of the other (Apparat) combine perfectly.&quot; In 2016, the threesome returned with an eagerly anticipated third album, III, which they present in this program, live on stage at Stereolux in Nantes, France.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230325163900 +0100" stop="20230325173400 +0100" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Altin Gün : Bird, Rotterdam</title>
<desc lang="fr">Mediterranean sounds meet western music in this performance by the band Altin Gün. Their unusual approach to traditional Turkish folk music produces an overall sound full of ethnic, funky, and even psychedelic influences. With their infinite energy, Altin Gün takes the audience on an amazing sonic roller coaster: a ride full of emotion and fun. Altin Gün consists of six talented musicians who share a great passion for Turkish music. In this live recording from BIRD Rotterdam, one of the Netherlands' most important music venues, the band presents their new album &quot;On&quot; to the enthusiastic audience.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/19/1975203_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230325173400 +0100" stop="20230325183800 +0100" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">GusGus : Live at Sónar Reykjavik</title>
<desc lang="fr">Gusgus - GusGus was founded in 1995 as a collective of film music creators. After signing a contract with the 4AD label the following year, GusGus became one of the most popular electro formations in Iceland, a status that was cemented internationally by the release of Polydistortion in 1997 Over the next two decades, GusGus explored virtually every sub-genre of electronic music, from house to trance, to techno and trip-hop. Discover GusGus at the Sónar Reykjavík 2018 festival, where founding members Biggi Veira and Daníel Ágúst present the latest album from the band, Lies Are More Flexible. With his exceptional vocal talent, fascinating electronic hacks and subtle arrangements, GusGus promises to impress you.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230325183800 +0100" stop="20230325195500 +0100" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Oumou Sangaré @ Jazz Sous Les Pommiers</title>
<desc lang="fr">Salif Keita described her as the &quot;Tina Turner of Mali.&quot; Indeed, Oumou Sangaré is one of Africa's most important female voices. While maintaining her political views as a champion of women's rights in Africa, her vocal talent has brought this singer to shine at some of the most important venues around the world. At Jazz Sous Les Pommiers 2017, Oumou Sangaré presents her latest album, Mogoya. She is accompanied by a group that combines traditional African instruments with a modern band set-up, featuring young French musicians. Recorded in spectacular 4K in a beautiful musical setting, Sangaré will surely make you sing and dance!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230325195500 +0100" stop="20230325210000 +0100" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">The Bloody Beetroots</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Bloody Beetroots - The Bloody Beetroots is the creation of Sir Bob Cornelius Rifo. Inspired by his lifelong love of punk rock and comic books, Rifo unleashed The Bloody Beetroots in late 2006 and has since crafted an intense sound that mixes his classical training, his punk rock obsession, and his passion for electronic music into an edgy rock-meets-dance hybrid sound. In 2019, The Bloody Beetroots released the Heavy EP, which sees Rifo revisiting his classic electro style and features collaborations with Ephwurd and Dr. Fresch, in addition to three new solo originals. Enjoy his show at Nameless Music Festival 2019!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230325210000 +0100" stop="20230325230900 +0100" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Carl Cox - Carl Cox</title>
<desc lang="fr">Carl Cox - It was at the age of 15 that Carl bought a set of turntables and began working as a mobile DJ. Disco was the first music that captivated him but by the early '80s, Cox had moved on to playing the same music as other young London DJs - rare groove, New York hip-hop, and electro. A musical ambassador and a veteran of acid house, a champion of techno, a dance music pioneer, label owner, King of Ibiza - you name it, Carl Cox has been there and done it, never losing sight of his passions - playing music, breaking tunes, and celebrating life. Enjoy his show at Family Piknik 2019!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/04/1754386_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230325230900 +0100" stop="20230326001100 +0100" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Nilüfer Yanya - Echoes Series: Nilufer Yanya</title>
<desc lang="fr">Echoes Series - Episode 6 - Echoes is a modern live music show hosted by Jehnny Beth (lead singer in the British band Savages). It presents leading and emerging bands and artists from the contemporary scene. The show takes place underneath the Palais de Tokyo museum in Paris, in the club of brutalist architecture, the &quot;Yoyo.&quot; The live sets are 30 minutes long and take place on a customized stage, creating closeness with the audience. Once the bands have performed, Jehnny Beth invites everyone to sit at her roundtable for a group conversation. The open discussions in every episode allow the audience to understand the rapport, artistic exchange, and intellectual debates that run through this eclectic musical universe. The intimate, immersive space lends to the atmosphere of the show.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/03/1754401_A.jpg" />
</programme>