<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Voo -->
<programme start="20230330030000 +0200" stop="20230330042000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">The Opera Locos</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Opera Locos - In The Opera Locos (&quot;The Opera of Crazies&quot;), a comic opera show from the Spanish theater company Yllana and theatre producer Rami Eldar, five eccentric opera singers perform some of the greatest opera arias. Classical arias from George Bizet's Carmen, W. A. Mozart's The Magic Flute, and Giuseppe Verdi's Rigoletto are combined with classics from the pop and rock repertoire. During the performance, the five characters reveal their hidden passions, personalities, and desires, leading to unpredictable, hilarious situations that audiences of all ages will appreciate. The soloists are Florian Laconi (tenor), Margaux Toqué (mezzo soprano), Michaël Koné (countertenor), Laurent Arcaro (baritone), and Diane Fourès (soprano). This performance was recorded at Théâtre Libre in Paris, France.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Evénement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/02/07/27/1763355_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230330042000 +0200" stop="20230330050900 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Ben Frost</title>
<desc lang="fr">Ben Frost - Australian Ben Frost produces under his Bedroom Community label albums inspired by post-classical electronic music, structured sound art and minimalism. His numerous collaborations testify to his desire to develop an artistic form combining music, texts, technology and performance. In this fascinating concert delivered at the Sónar Reykjavík 2018 festival, Frost once again displays his ingenuity as he presents the pieces of the album The Centre Cannot Hold. The award-winning visual artist MFO signs visual effects and lighting.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/59/1769392_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230330050900 +0200" stop="20230330060300 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Live From the Kennedy Center</title>
<desc lang="fr">Live From the Kennedy Center - When Nas was just 19 years old, he composed what would become one of hip-hop's defining masterpieces, Illmatic. To mark its 20th anniversary, Nas delivers a standout performance alongside the National Symphony Orchestra at Washington DC's Kennedy Center. With conductor Steven Reineke taking the orchestra through arrangements of beats by DJ Premier and Large Professor, Nas delivers impassioned renditions of tracks like &quot;N.Y. State of Mind&quot;, &quot;The World Is Yours&quot;, and &quot;Memory Lane (Sittin' in Da Park)&quot;. Between songs, the program cuts away to both archival and new interview footage to document Nas' rise from Queensbridge upstart to influential rap icon.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/58/1754433_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230330060300 +0200" stop="20230330073800 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Opera Imaginaire</title>
<desc lang="fr">Opera Imaginaire - To celebrate Le Concert Spirituel's 30th anniversary, conductor Hervé Niquet collaborated with the Baroque Music Center of Versailles to build his opéra imaginaire. For this unique project, Le Concert Spirituel presents an original performance of unpublished operas by Lully, Rameau, Charpentier, and many other French baroque composers. You will find yourself captivated by a tearful lover, intrigued by the passage to the underworld, and fascinated by the descents of the Gods. The program includes many favorite passages, such as Lully's Armide, Charpentier's Medea, and Campra's Carnaval de Venise. Experience all the magic of Louis XIV's French opera as Le Concert Spirituel transforms the Théâtre des Champs-Elysées into a true French baroque scene.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/03/1781759_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230330073800 +0200" stop="20230330081400 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Ed O'Brien</title>
<desc lang="fr">Echoes Series: Ed O'Brien - Echoes is a modern live music show hosted by Jehnny Beth (lead singer in the British band Savages). It presents leading and emerging bands and artists from the contemporary scene. The show takes place underneath the Palais de Tokyo museum in Paris, in the club of brutalist architecture, the &quot;Yoyo.&quot; The live sets are 30 minutes long and take place on a customized stage, creating closeness with the audience. The intimate, immersive space lends to the atmosphere of the show. The artistic direction by Antoine Carlier follows a minimalist, refined and pure aesthetic, allowing the artists' energy and emotions to take center stage. This episode features guitarist Ed O'Brien, a member of rock band Radiohead. His set includes the songs &quot;Mass,&quot; &quot;Olympik,&quot; and &quot;Brasil.&quot;.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230330081400 +0200" stop="20230330090000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Eleanor Dubinsky - Nublu 2019</title>
<desc lang="fr">The music of vocalist, guitarist and cellist Eleanor Dubinsky lives on the narrow ledge where jazz, international music and pop meet emotionally heartfelt songwriting. The musician and her versatile band deliver dynamic compositions that explore the fragile link between human emotions and human responsibility. The core of Eleanor's artistic mission is to enter into dialogue and achieve self-realization through music.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230330090000 +0200" stop="20230330103300 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Von Biber - Missa Salisburgensis</title>
<desc lang="fr">Von Biber - Missa Salisburgensis - In commemoration of the end of World War I, France and Czech Republic offered the Pope a concert at the Basilica of St. John Lateran in Rome on October 25, 2018. Czech musicologist Václav Luks conducts the choir and orchestra of his own Collegium 1704 in sacred vocal works by several 17th-century baroque composers. On the program are Jean-Baptiste Lully's (1632-1687) Te Deum, followed by Heinrich Ignaz Franz von Biber's (1644-1704) Missa Salisburgensis. During his lifetime, Von Biber, one of greatest composers for solo violin, was known and imitated throughout Europe. He did not limit himself to the violin and was a prolific composer of sacred vocal works as well, of which this Missa Salisburgensis is a prime example.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/02/09/04/2143760_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230330103300 +0200" stop="20230330113100 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Steve Vai</title>
<desc lang="fr">Steve Vai - The popular music performance series, Front and Center, which premiered nationwide on public television, in 2016, returns for Season 6. The series boasts 22, one-hour episodes and an all-star line-up. This episode features Steve Vai, the legendary guitarist who was voted the 10th Greatest Guitarist by Guitar World magazine, who treats fans to songs from his three-decade long career. As an independent guitarist he has won three Grammy Awards. Vai's solo sophomore release, Passion and Warfare, has earned gold certification in the US. At Front and Center he sits down and discusses his early interest in composing music and playing guitar as well as the many fortunes of his career.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Musique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/42/1870646_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230330113100 +0200" stop="20230330134400 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam</title>
<desc lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam - New Cool Collective is one of the foremost Dutch jazz ensembles. Pioneering new blends of music styles since 1993, NCC has performed in various formations, from small combos to larger ensembles and even big bands! The ensemble's high energy is cut out for the dance floors, as dance, Latin, salsa, afrobeat and boogaloo all meet in a jazzy mix. NCC includes saxophonist Benjamin Herman, guitarist Rory Ronde, drummer Joost Kroon, percussionists Frank van Dok and Jos de Haas, pianist Willem Friede, bassist Leslie Lopez, and trumpeter David Rockefeller.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230330134400 +0200" stop="20230330150300 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Tribute to Gilberto Gil</title>
<desc lang="fr">Tribute to Gilberto Gil - Da Pá Virada Sessions - The series Da Pá Virada sessions presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the bands taking part in this series is Caixa Cubo. This trio usually explores Brazil's rhythmically rich landscapes, combining them with modern Brazilian jazz trends. Yet in this singular performance, Caixa Cubo teams up with vocalist Zé Leônidas, selecting special repertoire together with Dani Gurgel from Da Pá Virada Sessions and Rokas Ku?inskas from Stingray DJAZZ.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230330150300 +0200" stop="20230330171800 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam</title>
<desc lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam - New Cool Collective is one of the foremost Dutch jazz ensembles. Pioneering new blends of music styles since 1993, NCC has performed in various formations, from small combos to larger ensembles and even big bands! The ensemble's high energy is cut out for the dance floors, as dance, Latin, salsa, afrobeat and boogaloo all meet in a jazzy mix. NCC includes saxophonist Benjamin Herman, guitarist Rory Ronde, drummer Joost Kroon, percussionists Frank van Dok and Jos de Haas, pianist Willem Friede, bassist Leslie Lopez, and trumpeter David Rockefeller.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230330171800 +0200" stop="20230330181800 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Paulo Novaes - New Year's Eve Special</title>
<desc lang="fr">Paulo Novaes - New Year's Eve Special - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the artists taking part in this series is Paulo Novaes. Coming from a family of musicians, Paulo Novaes has already lived through a lifetime of music in spite of his young age. Paulo is the cousin of singer Bruna Caram, with whom he performed in São Paulo, Madrid, Barcelona, Lisbon, and other major cities. As a singer, composer, and instrumentalist, his creativity is enjoyed in many forms.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230330181800 +0200" stop="20230330192000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Sven Väth at Family Piknik 2017</title>
<desc lang="fr">Sven Väth at Family Piknik 2017 - Active on the music scene for more than 30 years, Sven Väth is a true icon of techno. He was one of the first DJs to host a weekly event in Ibiza, and his &quot;Cocoon&quot; nights have quickly become a staple for fans of underground music in all its forms. Väth has been involved in all major developments of the techno movement, but even after three decades, this living legend is not ready to take the backstage and continues to dance crowds on five continents. Experience the unique sounds of Sven Väth with this performance recorded at the 2017 Family Piknik Festival!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230330192000 +0200" stop="20230330210000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Lalah Hathaway</title>
<desc lang="fr">Lalah Hathaway - Sing Jazz 2018 - Winner of five Grammys in four consecutive years, including the Grammy for best R&amp;B album in 2017, Lalah Hathaway is a force impossible to ignore. The American artist has shared the scene with Prince, Snoop Dogg, Stevie Wonder, Anita Baker, Mary J. Blige, Frank Ocean and many others, an irrefutable proof of her keen musical sense and enormous talent. With a 26-year career, Hathaway is still highly sought after by the biggest names in music. See her transform the 2018 Sing Jazz festival scene into a real R&amp;B club, where she flaunts her voice and stage presence out of the ordinary.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/19/1853106_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230330210000 +0200" stop="20230330213200 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">X Ambassadors</title>
<desc lang="fr">X Ambassadors - Enjoy ground-breaking concerts, in-depth artist interviews, and unique stories with host Ted Stryker. This concert series gives the audience an intimate view of music's most influential artists today. Shot in 4K, host Ted Stryker interviews musicians across all genres, creating one of the most unique music shows on TV today. This episode features the alternative rock band X Ambassadors, founded in 2009. After self-releasing the debut EP &quot;Ambassadors EP&quot;, which featured &quot;Litost&quot;, a song that would later be added to the soundtrack of sci-fi blockbuster The Host, the band had its break-through when Imagine Dragons lead singer Dan Reynolds initiated their signage to a major music label.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/58/1754433_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230330213200 +0200" stop="20230330222700 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Audience Music</title>
<desc lang="fr">Enjoy ground-breaking concerts, in-depth artist interviews, and unique stories with host Ted Stryker. This concert series gives the audience an intimate view of music's most influential artists today. Shot in 4K, host Ted Stryker interviews musicians across all genres, creating one of the most unique music shows on TV today. This episode features singer/songwriter Skylar Grey, best known for her songwriting skills, as displayed in Eminem and Rihanna's &quot;Love The Way You Lie&quot; (2010). The five-time GRAMMY-nominee and Wisconsin-born pop artist takes the stage to perform some of her most popular songs, as well as some works of her forthcoming album &quot;Angel With Tattoos&quot;. Enjoy Skylar Grey's performance and interview at Audience Music 2019!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/04/2122118_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230330222700 +0200" stop="20230330234300 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Arsenik à l'Olympia</title>
<desc lang="fr">Arsenik - Olympia, Paris - The mythical duo Arsenik is a rap group from France, made up of two brothers, Lino and Calbo. The team performs at Olympia Paris to celebrate their 20 years since their first album, Quelques gouttes suffisent... It's a unique concert: Arsenik plays the entire album with numerous special guests for the first time. The album has sold over 300,000 copies in France. Today it's being considered a classic, and it continues to be cited in the top five of the best French rap albums of all generations. Enjoy Arsenik's live show in Olympia Paris!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/04/2122118_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230330234300 +0200" stop="20230331005100 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">BIGYUKI : BIRD 2019</title>
<desc lang="fr">BIGYUKI - BIRD 2019 - BIGYUKI's is New York City's secret musical weapon! His unprecedented sound has attracted the attention of many, including Grammy Award-winning and nominated artists such as Q-Tip, Bilal, Talib Kweli, Harvey Mason, Marcus Strickland, Mark Giuliana, and Meshell Ndegeocello. BIGYUKI's music offers a soulful exploration into the wondrous soundscapes of his infinitely virtuosic mind. Infusing elements of jazz, classical music, hip-hop, soul, rock, dance, and electronica, BIGYUKI reaches a new and inspiring level, with support from guitarist Randy Runyon and drummer Smithsoneon. It is hard to believe that just three musicians can create a sound this massive.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/59/1769392_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230331005100 +0200" stop="20230331015300 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Trio Macaiba</title>
<desc lang="fr">Trio Macaiba - Da Pá Virada Sessions - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the bands taking part in this series is Trio Macaíba, consisting of Beto Corrêa (accordion), Cléber Almeida (zabumba, a type of bass drum), and Ramon Vieira (triangle). Their use of a traditional instrument combination, as well as cultural research, which all members of the group are dedicated to, contributes to the authenticity of the music and their experience as musicians.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/53/1759065_A.jpg" />
</programme>