<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Voo -->
<programme start="20230524030000 +0200" stop="20230524035000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">House of the Gipsies</title>
<desc lang="fr">House of the Gipsies - Sing Jazz 2018 - Since the Gypsy Kings made their triumphal debut on the music scene with their wild Spanish rumba four decades ago, no band has dared to follow in their footsteps ... until now! House of the Gipsies updates the raw rhythms of nomadic tribes in Rajasthan, India, collaborating with Manganiyar musicians Manjoor, Nehru and Dilawar Khan. The result is a unique sound that can be described as Indo-Gypsy fusion, which is part of the evolution of the Spanish rumba. Do not miss this eclectic performance sure to please music lovers of all generations, presented at the 2018 Sing Jazz Festival.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/03/2145502_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524035000 +0200" stop="20230524045100 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Runtown : La Machine de Moulin Rouge</title>
<desc lang="fr">Runtown - La Machine de Moulin Rouge - Enjoy Runtown's first concert in Paris, where the Nigerian superstar brings many guests to his show. One of the most talented Nigerian afrobeat scenes will make you rediscover his greatest hits. Nigeria is a very creative country when it comes to the music scene. Runtown is no exception. His first single, &quot;Party Like It's 1980,&quot; paved the way for &quot;Gallardo,&quot; which caught the entire international scene's attention. Runtown's inspiration comes from the greats, from Salif Keita and Fela Kuti to Otis Redding and Bob Marley. An exceptional event not to be missed.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524045100 +0200" stop="20230524055300 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Mariana Aydar</title>
<desc lang="fr">Mariana Aydar - Da Pá Virada Sessions - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the artists taking part in this episode is vocalist Mariana Aydar, who masters the música popular brasileira repertoire (MPB) like no other. She was born in a family of musicians, and has been dubbed the &quot;hottest singer of the moment&quot; by Veja, one of Brazil's leading newsmagazines. For her performance at Da Pá Virada Sessions, Aydar (vocals and triangle) is joined by Cosme Vieira (accordion) and Feeh Silva (zabumba).</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524055300 +0200" stop="20230524065500 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Dickey Betts: Ramblin'</title>
<desc lang="fr">Dickey Betts: Ramblin' - Surrounded by music from an early age, Dickey Betts (lead guitar) has created a distinctive sound fusion of different genres such as blues, rock, country, and jazz. This concert shows an intimate performance of the band, in which Dickey Betts is accompanied by Damon Fowler (lead/slide guitarist) and his son Duane Betts (lead guitar). The band also includes long-time band members Frankie Lombardi (drums), Steve Camilleri (drums), Pedro Arevalo (bass), and Mike Kach (keyboard). In addition, guitarist Devon Allman makes a special guest appearance on the song &quot;Midnight Rider.&quot; Other songs in this exceptional performance include &quot;Ramblin' Man,&quot; &quot;Jessica,&quot; and more.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/42/1870646_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524065500 +0200" stop="20230524074800 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Tribute to Gilberto Gil</title>
<desc lang="fr">Tribute to Gilberto Gil - Da Pá Virada Sessions - The series Da Pá Virada sessions presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the bands taking part in this series is Caixa Cubo. This trio usually explores Brazil's rhythmically rich landscapes, combining them with modern Brazilian jazz trends. Yet in this singular performance, Caixa Cubo teams up with vocalist Zé Leônidas, selecting special repertoire together with Dani Gurgel from Da Pá Virada Sessions and Rokas Ku?inskas from Stingray DJAZZ.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524074800 +0200" stop="20230524090000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Monty Alexander à La Seine Musicale</title>
<desc lang="fr">Monty Alexander - Kingston-born pianist Monty Alexander is a virtuoso with many secrets. He explores the world of jazz, swing, bebop, blues, calypso and reggae, and has created a style of his own. For him, music is a heartbeat. He plays with emotion, intelligence, humor and sensibility. During this unique performance, we are transported with his joyful swing and fizzing grooves, influenced by Afro-American jazz from Harlem, and reggae from Jamaica. This 2018 concert at the Seine Musical is exceptional. It is extremely rare for Monty Alexander to do a solo performance. We are in for an evening full of surprises.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/07/19/1995865_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524090000 +0200" stop="20230524101300 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Omer Avital Qantar - Jazz in Duketown</title>
<desc lang="fr">Jazz in Duketown is the largest free open-air jazz festival in the Netherlands. Jazz fanatics and other music lovers eagerly look forward to the performances of the many internationally renowned artists every year. In 2019 Israeli-American double bass player Omer Avital is one of them. Together with his quintet, consisting of saxophonists Asaf Yuria and Alexander Levin, drummer Ofri Nehemya and pianist Eden Ladin, he performs a strong repertoire from his album 'Qantar': vibrantly energetic, idiosyncratic jazz with oriental influences.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524101300 +0200" stop="20230524105600 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">WOMEX 2018</title>
<desc lang="fr">Norayr Kartashyan &amp; Menua - WOMEX 2018 - Since 1994, World Music Expo (WOMEX) has been attracting musicians, agents, a great number of press agencies, as well as media companies from all over the world. Its main exposition event has been held in various locations throughout Europe, including Berlin, Brussels, Marseille, Stockholm, Seville, Cardiff, and Budapest. In 2018, WOMEX was held in Las Palmas, Gran Canaria. One of its showcase participants, Norayr Kartashyan, is acclaimed as one of Armenia's finest woodwind masters and composers, an acknowledged virtuoso numerous traditional Armenian instruments. To name a few: the blul and shvi flutes, duduk, the double-reed zurna trumpet, the pku clarinet, and the parkapzuk bagpipe.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/29/16/2143305_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524105600 +0200" stop="20230524115400 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Steve Vai</title>
<desc lang="fr">Steve Vai - The popular music performance series, Front and Center, which premiered nationwide on public television, in 2016, returns for Season 6. The series boasts 22, one-hour episodes and an all-star line-up. This episode features Steve Vai, the legendary guitarist who was voted the 10th Greatest Guitarist by Guitar World magazine, who treats fans to songs from his three-decade long career. As an independent guitarist he has won three Grammy Awards. Vai's solo sophomore release, Passion and Warfare, has earned gold certification in the US. At Front and Center he sits down and discusses his early interest in composing music and playing guitar as well as the many fortunes of his career.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Musique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/42/1870646_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524115400 +0200" stop="20230524133000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Hugh Coltman</title>
<desc lang="fr">The English singer and composer Hugh Coltman started in blues rock band The Hoax, after which he moved to Paris and released two pop and folk albums. Jazz was beckoning and his next project was a tribute to singer and pianist Nat &quot;King&quot; Cole. Coltman recorded his album 'Who's Happy?' in New Orleans. With this he makes music of an important life question.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/19/1853106_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524133000 +0200" stop="20230524141000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Nilüfer Yanya - Echoes Series: Nilufer Yanya</title>
<desc lang="fr">Echoes Series: Emel Mathlouthi - Echoes is a modern live music show hosted by Jehnny Beth (lead singer in the British band Savages). It presents leading and emerging bands and artists from the contemporary scene. The show takes place underneath the Palais de Tokyo museum in Paris, in the club of brutalist architecture, the &quot;Yoyo.&quot; The live sets are 30 minutes long and take place on a customized stage, creating closeness with the audience. The intimate, immersive space lends to the atmosphere of the show. The artistic direction by Antoine Carlier follows a minimalist, refined and pure aesthetic, allowing the artists' energy and emotions to take center stage. This episode features Emel Mathlouthi. Her set includes the songs &quot;Rescuer,&quot; &quot;Something in the Way,&quot; and &quot;Holm.&quot;.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/03/1754401_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524141000 +0200" stop="20230524150100 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Echoes Series: Fontaines DC</title>
<desc lang="fr">Echoes Series: Fontaines DC - Echoes is a modern live music show hosted by Jehnny Beth (lead singer in the British band Savages). It presents leading and emerging bands and artists from the contemporary scene. The show takes place underneath the Palais de Tokyo museum in Paris, in the club of brutalist architecture, the &quot;Yoyo.&quot; The live sets are 30 minutes long and take place on a customized stage, creating closeness with the audience. The intimate, immersive space lends to the atmosphere of the show. The artistic direction by Antoine Carlier follows a minimalist, refined and pure aesthetic, allowing the artists' energy and emotions to take center stage. This episode features the band Fontaines DC. Their set includes the songs &quot;A Hero's Death,&quot; &quot;Hurricane Laughter,&quot; and &quot;I Don't Belong.&quot;.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/04/2122118_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524150100 +0200" stop="20230524160400 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Fabrizio Rat : Artemix</title>
<desc lang="fr">Fabrizio Rat - Since his teenage years, Fabrizio has worked simultaneously on both classical and electronic music productions. He's definitely not the classical music guy who has just discovered techno. Throughout his apprentice years at the musical academy in Turin, he was working as a producer in dance music studios at the same time, hiding his &quot;double life&quot; to both the professors and the DJs. Arriving in Paris in 2007, his objective starts to take shape. Fabrizio combines the acoustic sounds and weird harmonics of his prepared piano with the acid loops of the TB-303 and the beats of the TR-909. Unsurprisingly, it's in front of the dancefloor, in clubs or festivals, that Fabrizio plays his live sets. With the right hand, he plays repetitive rhythmical patterns while the left one handles the machines and manipulates the piano strings.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/43/1767478_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524160400 +0200" stop="20230524171500 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Salomao Soares Trio</title>
<desc lang="fr">Salomao Soares Trio - Da Pá Virada Sessions - Da Pá Virada sessions bring the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the bands taking part in this series is the Salomão Soares Trio, which consists of Salomão Soares on piano, Paulo Almeida on drums, and Thiago Alves on bass. Band leader Soares was a finalist of the 2017 Montreux Jazz Festival piano competition.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524171500 +0200" stop="20230524183900 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Kenny Loggins and Friends: Live on Soundstage</title>
<desc lang="fr">Kenny Loggins - Daryl Hall started Live From Daryl's House, the free monthly web show in late 2007, after having the idea of &quot;playing with my friends and putting it up on the internet.&quot; The show has since garnered acclaim from Rolling Stone, SPIN, Daily Variety, CNN, BBC, and Yahoo! Music. The influential blogger Bob Lefsetz cited Live From Daryl's House as a perfect example of a veteran artist reinventing himself in the digital age by collaborating with both established colleagues and newer performers. Kenny Loggins' remarkable four-decade-plus career has brought him from the top of the charts to the toast of the Grammys. He's had smash hits on Hollywood's favorite soundtracks, rocked worldwide stages, and found his way into people's hearts while bringing his soulful, beautiful voice to platinum albums in a wide variety of genres.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/04/1754386_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524183900 +0200" stop="20230524192200 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">WOMEX 2018</title>
<desc lang="fr">Kim So Ra - WOMEX 2018 - Since 1994, World Music Expo (WOMEX) has been attracting musicians, agents, a great number of press agencies, as well as media companies from all over the world. Its main exposition event has been held in various locations throughout Europe, including Berlin, Brussels, Marseille, Stockholm, Seville, Cardiff, and Budapest. In 2018, WOMEX was held in Las Palmas, Gran Canaria. One of its showcase participants, Korean percussionist Kim So Ra, has played the hourglass-shaped, two-headed drum known as janggu since she was a child. Quietly, she has been taking revolutionary steps to modernize perceptions within traditional Korean music.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/29/16/2143305_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524192200 +0200" stop="20230524203500 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Arnaud Rebotini : Le Trabendo</title>
<desc lang="fr">Arnaud Rebotini - Trabendo Paris - Arnaud Rebotini is one of hexagonal electro's major figures and the founding father of electroclash group Black Strobe. 2017 saw the release of his soundtrack for 120 Beats Per Minute. At the end of this successful year, Rebotini put on an amazing set at Trabendo Paris. Rebotini's show is all but static - his exciting beats are supported by vocals that make the crowd go wild. This show is a feast for the eyes and ears. Enjoy Rebotini's energizing show and high-end visual effects in native 4K!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524203500 +0200" stop="20230524210000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Wild Youth</title>
<desc lang="fr">Songbook - &quot;I never heard anyone say that, and yeah, I know exactly what it means. It has to go in there, this has to be a song.&quot; Every song has its own story, and we all think it's a story we've heard before, but we haven't. Songbook finds and captures these intriguing stories by pulling you into the process of writing and composing. Known for its pristine sound, cinematic 4k video and eye for detail, Songbook live-captured episodes emphasize the paramount importance of quality. It addresses the on-the-spot elements of blending song and location at the right moment. Both the magical location and remarkable music interaction will get the attention they deserve. Simply because Songbook isn't just a live music session, it lives. This episode of Songbook showcases the upbeat pop-rock sound of Dublin-based Wild Youth.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/04/2122118_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524210000 +0200" stop="20230524220300 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">De La Soul - Garorock</title>
<desc lang="fr">De La Soul - Garorock - There is a packed crowd for this De La Soul set at the 2019 Garorock Festival, and with good reason: they witness an unmissable concert by an incomparable group! Having released regular albums since 1989's 3 Feet High and Rising, the Long Island hip-hop stalwarts of De La Soul have been doing the rounds on a suitably named Gods of Rap tour alongside Public Enemy and the Wu-Tang Clan. With an opening that includes call and response, mic checks and arms waving in the air, the audience gets more than a touch of vintage appeal, something that has led to terms like &quot;heritage rap&quot; being associated with the group. But despite their long and influential career, the De La Soul impact has perennial relevance for much of contemporary music. They pushed boundaries back then and they continue to venture out further.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524220300 +0200" stop="20230524230600 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Tribute to Elis Regina</title>
<desc lang="fr">Tribute to Elis Regina - Da Pá Virada Sessions - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the bands taking part in this episode is a foursome that pays tribute to pioneering música popular brasileira vocalist Elis Regina: vocalist Vanessa Moreno, bassist Fi Marostica, Rhodes and keyboard player Tiago Costa, and drummer Jonatas Sansao honor the legendary Brazilian singer by performing famous pieces and hidden gems from her repertoire.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524230600 +0200" stop="20230525000600 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Filo Machado - New Year's Eve Special</title>
<desc lang="fr">Filo Machado - New Year's Eve Special - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the artists taking part in this series is Filo Machado. Born in São Paulo, this singer, composer, instrumentalist, arranger and producer has celebrated many musical successes. Filo Machado took part in saxophonist Jane Bunnett's Canadian tour with her spectacular project 'Rendez-Vous Brazil/Cuba'. He has appeared at the jazz festivals of Córsega and Uzeste and opened for the one and only Nina Simone in Cannes.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230525000600 +0200" stop="20230525013800 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Fred Hersch Trio</title>
<desc lang="fr">Since awakening from a months-long coma in 2008, Fred Hersch has experienced a spectacular physical and artistic rebirth. He filled numerous albums with his piano playing and his own compositions.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>