<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Voo -->
<programme start="20230329030000 +0200" stop="20230329035100 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Live with a Boom</title>
<desc lang="fr">Mn'JAM Experiment: Live with a Boom - Imagine that visual arts and music are no longer two separate fields; that musicians no longer focus on their instruments only, but also on the visuals of their performance. Such is the premise of Mn'JAM Experiment! Zoom in on their music and you'll find a mix between empirical and rationally constructed elements; between acoustic, electric and electronic instruments; urban rhythms and traditional melodies, vocal loops and guitar solos, turntables and acoustic drums. Zoom in on the visuals of the performance -they are analogously a product of pre-composed material and live manipulation, mostly carried out by the guy behind the turntables.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230329035100 +0200" stop="20230329045100 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Filo Machado - New Year's Eve Special</title>
<desc lang="fr">Filo Machado - New Year's Eve Special - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the artists taking part in this series is Filo Machado. Born in São Paulo, this singer, composer, instrumentalist, arranger and producer has celebrated many musical successes. Filo Machado took part in saxophonist Jane Bunnett's Canadian tour with her spectacular project 'Rendez-Vous Brazil/Cuba'. He has appeared at the jazz festivals of Córsega and Uzeste and opened for the one and only Nina Simone in Cannes.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230329045100 +0200" stop="20230329055300 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">La Fraîcheur</title>
<desc lang="fr">La Fraîcheur - For over a decade now, first in Paris, then Montreal and now in Berlin, La Fraîcheur has been brewing her blend of deep house and techno beats, making a name for herself with her signature sound of emotionally charged and acid techno sets. The queer feminist-activist is a marathon DJ who can go on for countless hours, running the gamut from classics to new songs released just hours earlier. Her craft expanded by producing music ranging from ravy epic techno to dark pumping electro, spacious open-air deep house to melancholic electronica. She wrote her critically acclaimed debut album during an artist residency with the Berlin-Detroit Connection.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/59/1769392_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230329055300 +0200" stop="20230329065500 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Nilüfer Yanya - Echoes Series: Nilufer Yanya</title>
<desc lang="fr">Echoes Series - Episode 6 - Echoes is a modern live music show hosted by Jehnny Beth (lead singer in the British band Savages). It presents leading and emerging bands and artists from the contemporary scene. The show takes place underneath the Palais de Tokyo museum in Paris, in the club of brutalist architecture, the &quot;Yoyo.&quot; The live sets are 30 minutes long and take place on a customized stage, creating closeness with the audience. Once the bands have performed, Jehnny Beth invites everyone to sit at her roundtable for a group conversation. The open discussions in every episode allow the audience to understand the rapport, artistic exchange, and intellectual debates that run through this eclectic musical universe. The intimate, immersive space lends to the atmosphere of the show.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/03/1754401_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230329065500 +0200" stop="20230329074700 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Giana Viscardi - New Year's Eve Special</title>
<desc lang="fr">Giana Viscardi - New Year's Eve Special - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the bands taking part in this series is the duo of Giana Viscardi and Gustavo Marques. After starting their career together, Giana Viscardi and Gustavo Marques released music in many places around the world. After returning to Brazil, they worked together on Giana's album &quot;ORUM&quot;, performing in Africa, Europe, and Brazil.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230329074700 +0200" stop="20230329090000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">The Bloody Beetroots</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Bloody Beetroots - The Bloody Beetroots is the creation of Sir Bob Cornelius Rifo. Inspired by his lifelong love of punk rock and comic books, Rifo unleashed The Bloody Beetroots in late 2006 and has since crafted an intense sound that mixes his classical training, his punk rock obsession, and his passion for electronic music into an edgy rock-meets-dance hybrid sound. In 2019, The Bloody Beetroots released the Heavy EP, which sees Rifo revisiting his classic electro style and features collaborations with Ephwurd and Dr. Fresch, in addition to three new solo originals. Enjoy his show at Nameless Music Festival 2019!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230329090000 +0200" stop="20230329101800 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Oumou Sangaré @ Jazz Sous Les Pommiers</title>
<desc lang="fr">Salif Keita described her as the &quot;Tina Turner of Mali.&quot; Indeed, Oumou Sangaré is one of Africa's most important female voices. While maintaining her political views as a champion of women's rights in Africa, her vocal talent has brought this singer to shine at some of the most important venues around the world. At Jazz Sous Les Pommiers 2017, Oumou Sangaré presents her latest album, Mogoya. She is accompanied by a group that combines traditional African instruments with a modern band set-up, featuring young French musicians. Recorded in spectacular 4K in a beautiful musical setting, Sangaré will surely make you sing and dance!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230329101800 +0200" stop="20230329110100 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">City Beats</title>
<desc lang="fr">City Beats - Episode 1 - London - DJ-producer Carly Foxx is on a musical journey, immersing herself in the life of five iconic European cities to find inspiration for a series of new tracks. In this episode, Carly Foxx steps outside of her comfort zone to draw inspiration for her music track from urban youths in London's grime scene. With fresh eyes, she explores what makes this city unique to the people who live there. Carly interviews people on the street and asks them about the London music scene, which is very lively and diverse. To better understand the urban music scene, Carly pays a visit to RepreZent Radio, where she interviews grime artists. She records street sounds such as a bus driving by, the ticking against a metal door, and police sirens.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Télé-Réalité</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/24/02/2134738_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230329110100 +0200" stop="20230329115500 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Rooted With Wings</title>
<desc lang="fr">Rooted With Wings - Rooted with Wings is a visual dance documentary that explores the work of internationally acclaimed choreographer and dancer Tero Saarinen, granting the viewer a unique lens into this extraordinary artist's creative process. The film brings to light how Saarinen's dance works evolve from an idea or concept into a finished performance and features stunningly captured dance sequences and behind-the-scenes material from around the globe. The film follows Saarinen over five years, from 2014 to 2018, through several premieres of new works and tours in Finland, France, Korea, Kenya, and the US, while bringing to light his approach to his life as a global nomad in dance.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Documentaire</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/10/1752533_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230329115500 +0200" stop="20230329133300 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Meute</title>
<desc lang="fr">Meute - When the bass sounds and the confetti explodes, there is no doubt that Meute is a different kind of band. The band creates a whole new genre by mixing fanfare music with hypnotic techno. Meute liberates electronic music of the classic model of the DJ console. This group breaks the codes by provoking a real interaction with the audience, who will be unable to do anything but stomp their feet. This brass and percussion ensemble revolutionizes techno music while ultimately bringing it back to its roots. The eleven musicians in their iconic red jackets have already taken over the biggest festivals in Europe! Watch them on Festival 4K with their show at Trianon Paris, 2019.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230329133300 +0200" stop="20230329141500 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Nelida Karr</title>
<desc lang="fr">One of the participants in 2018 was Nelida Karr, who not only sings and plays the guitar, but also takes care of piano, cello and percussion. Her own compositions are brimming with the many cultural influences she acquired during her childhood in Malabo.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/24/31/2143305_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230329141500 +0200" stop="20230329150300 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">WOMEX 2018</title>
<desc lang="fr">Mario Batkovic - WOMEX 2018 - Since 1994, World Music Expo (WOMEX) has been attracting musicians, agents, a great number of press agencies, as well as media companies from all over the world. Its main exposition event has been held in various locations throughout Europe, including Berlin, Brussels, Marseille, Stockholm, Seville, Cardiff, and Budapest. The 2018 edition of WOMEX was held in Las Palmas, Gran Canaria. One of its showcase participants, Mario Batkovic, aims to explore the sonic possibilities of the accordion, without effects or loops, rather through a mutualist symbiotic relationship between man and instrument. Challenging, hypnotic, and grandiose, Batkovic's single-handed symphonic vision is certainly unique.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/24/31/2143305_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230329150300 +0200" stop="20230329155700 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Karin Fernandes</title>
<desc lang="fr">Karin Fernandes - Da Pá Virada Sessions - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the artists taking part in this series is pianist Karin Fernandes. She is dedicated to the performance of 20th and 21st century piano repertoire and has premiered numerous new compositions. As a soloist, Karin Fernandes has performed with prestigious Brazilian orchestras.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230329155700 +0200" stop="20230329170000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Bloco do O</title>
<desc lang="fr">Bloco do O - Da Pá Virada Sessions - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the bands taking part in this series is Bloco do Ó, a traditional street band associated with the Brazilian carnival. A &quot;bloco&quot; is a group of people who drive through the streets in trucks, playing music and providing fun to anyone who will listen. Immerse yourself in Bloco de Ó's world of cheerful melodies and spectacular costumes!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/19/1853106_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230329170000 +0200" stop="20230329183100 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Mötley Crüe</title>
<desc lang="fr">Mötley Crüe, the American rock band formed in the 1980s, was founded by bassist Nikki Sixx and drummer Tommy Lee, who were later joined by guitarist Mick Mars, and vocalist Vince Neil. Mötley Crüe has sold more than 100 million records worldwide, including 25 million in the US. On December 31, 2015, legendary rock icons Mötley Crüe completed their 35-year touring career as a band with a spectacular final concert at Staples Center in their hometown of Los Angeles, CA, just 10 miles from the Sunset Strip where the band's infamous and decadent career first launched. The band thrilled the sold-out arena with performances of mega-hits &quot;Kickstart My Heart,&quot; &quot;Girls Girls Girls,&quot; &quot;Home Sweet Home,&quot; and &quot;Dr. Feelgood.&quot; Directed by Jeff Tremaine and Christian Lamb.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Société</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/03/1853299_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230329183100 +0200" stop="20230329191400 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">WOMEX 2018</title>
<desc lang="fr">Kim So Ra - WOMEX 2018 - Since 1994, World Music Expo (WOMEX) has been attracting musicians, agents, a great number of press agencies, as well as media companies from all over the world. Its main exposition event has been held in various locations throughout Europe, including Berlin, Brussels, Marseille, Stockholm, Seville, Cardiff, and Budapest. In 2018, WOMEX was held in Las Palmas, Gran Canaria. One of its showcase participants, Korean percussionist Kim So Ra, has played the hourglass-shaped, two-headed drum known as janggu since she was a child. Quietly, she has been taking revolutionary steps to modernize perceptions within traditional Korean music.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/24/31/2143305_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230329191400 +0200" stop="20230329202900 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">At L'Aéronef Lille 2017</title>
<desc lang="fr">At L'Aéronef Lille 2017 - Gossip fans, rejoice: Beth Ditto makes a big comeback! With her new album, the fiery singer launches into a solo career. With the boundless energy, undeniable humor, and legendary generosity that characterize her, the American phenomenon presents brand-new songs. Beth Ditto is more than a singer: she is an inescapable figure of the world's pop culture. As the lead singer of indie rock band Gossip (1999-2016), this young woman pulled off spectacular stage performances and gave hilarious interviews, greatly contributing to her sympathy capital. Her 2017 album mixes blues, pop, country, and rock, paying tribute to her native Arkansas in twelve eclectic and unifying pieces. Experience Beth Ditto as never before in this appearance at L'Aéronef Lille 2017!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Musique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/15/1838343_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230329202900 +0200" stop="20230329210000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Nana Adjoa</title>
<desc lang="fr">Songbook - Nana Adjoa - &quot;I never heard anyone say that, and yeah, I know exactly what it means. It has to go in there, this has to be a song.&quot; Every song has its own story, and we all think it's a story we've heard before, but we haven't. Songbook finds and captures these intriguing stories by pulling you into the process of writing and composing. Known for its pristine sound, cinematic 4k video, and eye for detail, Songbook live-captured episodes emphasize the paramount importance of quality. It addresses the on-the-spot elements of blending song and location at the right moment. Both the magical location and remarkable music interaction will get the attention they deserve.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/04/2122118_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230329210000 +0200" stop="20230329220300 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Jose James : Jazz à Vienne</title>
<desc lang="fr">José James - Jazz a Vienne - Since bursting onto the international scene in the late 2000s, José James and his honeyed voice are as bewitching as ever in this 2019 performance at Jazz à Vienne. Flitting between raw soul, soul-folk, hip-hop, and jazz, James is one of the few vocalists capable of keeping the crossover created by Ray Charles in the '50s alive. After sensitive and intelligent odes to Billie Holiday and John Coltrane, this time James pays tribute to a living legend of American popular music: soul man Bill Withers. James performs Bill Withers's unforgettable songs, accompanied by Marcus Machado (guitar), Aneesa Strings (bass, vocals), and Aaron Steele (drums).</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/20/48/1691820_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230329220300 +0200" stop="20230329230600 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Frederico Heliodoro</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Da Pá Virada Sessions series portrays the best musicians in Brazilian jazz today. All sessions were recorded in São Paulo and offer a unique experience, offering a fresh look at the Brazilian music scene. The artists have been selected together with the music editor of Stingray DJAZZ. Among the bands featured in this series is Caixa Cubo. Typically, this versatile trio explores the rhythmically rich Brazilian landscapes, combining them with modern Brazilian jazz trends. For this program, however, Caixa Cubo works together with vocalist Zé Leônidas, with a special repertoire that has been put together with Dani Gurgel from Da Pá Virada Sessions and Rokas Ku?inskas from Stingray DJAZZ.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/33/1626400_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230329230600 +0200" stop="20230330000500 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Roger Sanchez</title>
<desc lang="fr">Roger Sanchez - Self-made man and true legend of house music, Roger Sanchez perfectly embodies the spirit of Pacha Festival Bali. Sanchez had a humble debut in New York, but the days when he was spinning vinyls for his friends in Queens living rooms are far behind him. Today, he is the headliner of major festivals around the globe, and resident DJ of clubs in Ibiza's sights, such as the Pacha Club. With this DJ set at Pacha Festival, Sanchez brings some of the magic of Ibiza to the beaches of Bali. Expect lots of energy, breathtaking lights, and even fireworks!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230330000500 +0200" stop="20230330014300 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Kyle Eastwood Quintet</title>
<desc lang="fr">Jazz à Ramatuelle: Kyle Eastwood Quintet - Bassist Kyle Eastwood (1968) is an explorer, equally at ease with jazz melodies as with pop songs. In the late 1970s, his father Clint took him to see his first jazz concert - a Count Basie performance. Eastwood Jr. was in awe of the drummer and wanted to play an instrument himself. It so happened he wasn't so much interested in jazz, preferring rhythm and blues, Motown and Stax records, funk groups, and North African and Indian music. Eastwood became a brilliant bassist and the composer of highly original soundtracks. His 2015 album &quot;Time Pieces&quot; is a collaboration with brilliant British musicians, such as trumpeter Quentin Collins and saxophonist Brandon Allen. In this broadcast, Eastwood and his fellow musicians revisit the hard bop legacy of Blue Note Records.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/19/1853106_A.jpg" />
</programme>