<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Voo -->
<programme start="20230419030000 +0200" stop="20230419035000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">James Arthur</title>
<desc lang="fr">James Arthur - British pop singer James Arthur, best known for his power ballads &quot;Impossible&quot; (2013) and &quot;Say You Won't Let Go&quot; (2016), gives an intimate concert at New York City's Iridium. After winning the ninth season of UK's The X Factor in 2011, his powerful voice quickly helped him rise to the top of international pop charts.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230419035000 +0200" stop="20230419045000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Isle of Wight 2018: Part II</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Isle of Wight Festival, held in Newport, England is a rock-pop music festival that annually serves as the first major event opening the British festival summer. The tradition of the festival first saw the light of day in 1969, opening eleven days after the closing of legendary Woodstock and was regarded as the European counterpart to the legendary &quot;counterculture&quot; festival. In 1970, its line-up was stars-studded with gigs by Jimi Hendrix, The Who, The Doors, Joni Mitchell, Supertramp, Leonard Cohen and many more, establishing the name of the festival. In 2002, the festival was revived after 30 years of silence and brought back the sounds of contemporary musical legends to the Isle of Wight.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/42/1870646_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230419045000 +0200" stop="20230419055400 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Tribute to Elis Regina</title>
<desc lang="fr">Tribute to Elis Regina - Da Pá Virada Sessions - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the bands taking part in this episode is a foursome that pays tribute to pioneering música popular brasileira vocalist Elis Regina: vocalist Vanessa Moreno, bassist Fi Marostica, Rhodes and keyboard player Tiago Costa, and drummer Jonatas Sansao honor the legendary Brazilian singer by performing famous pieces and hidden gems from her repertoire.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230419055400 +0200" stop="20230419065900 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Martina</title>
<desc lang="fr">Martina - Da Pá Virada Sessions - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the artists taking part in this series is Martina Marana. Vocalist, instrumentalist, and composer Martina Marana uses the power of irony to show how women instrumentalists are misjudged. In her music, Martina breaks free of sexist labels, reclaiming her own power as musician and composer. A gifted lyricist, Marana makes uncompromising, unique music.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230419065900 +0200" stop="20230419075100 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Ramón Valle &amp; Reinier Baas : Music Meeting 2020</title>
<desc lang="fr">Ramón Valle &amp; Reinier Baas - Music Meeting 2020 - Since 1985, the Dutch city of Nijmegen has been welcoming the International Music Meeting Festival every Pentecost. Ranging from jazz and improvisational music to traditional music and unique crossovers, this adventurous festival is all about musical encounters and international collaborations. Disrupted by COVID-19, the festival's 2020 edition had to adapt to new challenges. It now presents this exclusive concert by pianist Ramón Valle and guitarist Reinier Baas, filmed at Concertgebouw De Vereeniging in Nijmegen.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/49/1767496_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230419075100 +0200" stop="20230419090000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Monty Alexander à La Seine Musicale</title>
<desc lang="fr">Monty Alexander - Kingston-born pianist Monty Alexander is a virtuoso with many secrets. He explores the world of jazz, swing, bebop, blues, calypso and reggae, and has created a style of his own. For him, music is a heartbeat. He plays with emotion, intelligence, humor and sensibility. During this unique performance, we are transported with his joyful swing and fizzing grooves, influenced by Afro-American jazz from Harlem, and reggae from Jamaica. This 2018 concert at the Seine Musical is exceptional. It is extremely rare for Monty Alexander to do a solo performance. We are in for an evening full of surprises.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/07/19/1995865_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230419090000 +0200" stop="20230419101800 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">At L'Aéronef Lille 2017</title>
<desc lang="fr">At L'Aéronef Lille 2017 - Gossip fans, rejoice: Beth Ditto makes a big comeback! With her new album, the fiery singer launches into a solo career. With the boundless energy, undeniable humor, and legendary generosity that characterize her, the American phenomenon presents brand-new songs. Beth Ditto is more than a singer: she is an inescapable figure of the world's pop culture. As the lead singer of indie rock band Gossip (1999-2016), this young woman pulled off spectacular stage performances and gave hilarious interviews, greatly contributing to her sympathy capital. Her 2017 album mixes blues, pop, country, and rock, paying tribute to her native Arkansas in twelve eclectic and unifying pieces. Experience Beth Ditto as never before in this appearance at L'Aéronef Lille 2017!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Musique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/15/1838343_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230419101800 +0200" stop="20230419110200 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Moonlight Benjamin : WOMEX 2018</title>
<desc lang="fr">Numerous musicians, booking agents, news agencies and media companies from all over the world have been attending the &quot;World Music Exhibition&quot; World Music Expo (WOMEX) since 1994. Over the years, this music fair has settled in several European cities, including Berlin, Brussels, Marseille, Stockholm, Seville, Cardiff and Budapest. In 2018 WOMEX took place in Las Palmas in Gran Canaria. One of the participants was the Haitian singer Moonlight Benjamin. With her band she mixes voodoo blues, Haitian rock and Creole roll into a swirling brew that is thrilling with exciting riffs and heavy grooves. Her powerful voice and fiery electric guitars do the rest.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/52/1752443_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230419110200 +0200" stop="20230419120100 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">lovelytheband</title>
<desc lang="fr">Formed in West Hollywood in 2016, lovelytheband features former Oh Honey member Mitchy Collins along with guitarist Jordan Greenwald and drummer Sam Price. The band debuted in July 2017 with the Christian Medice-produced &quot;Broken,&quot; a sprightly and infectious single that quickly racked up over three million digital streams. Signing with Another Century Records, lovelytheband released their debut EP &quot;Everything I Could&quot; in September of that year and joined Vance Joy and AWOLNATION on tour. In April 2018, &quot;Broken&quot; was still going strong and hit number one on the Billboard Alternative Songs Airplay chart. That August, lovelytheband returned with their full-length debut album, Finding It Hard to Smile.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/58/1754433_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230419120100 +0200" stop="20230419133400 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">&quot;Whatever&quot; at Jazz à Ramatuelle</title>
<desc lang="fr">China Moses: &quot;Whatever&quot; at Jazz à Ramatuelle - In 1988, Dee Dee Bridgewater was one of the first great jazz singers to perform at the Jazz Festival in Ramatuelle. In 2016, the story seems to repeat itself as her daughter China Moses took the stage at Ramatuelle. Over the years, China Moses has become a mature performer with a unique style: rocky voice, sharp sense of swing, and intense/energetic stage presence. After signing compilations dedicated to Dinah Washington and blues, Moses released in 2016 an album of his own compositions, entitled &quot;Whatever&quot;. Get ready for a most entertaining performance combining jazz, soul, and hip-hop.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230419133400 +0200" stop="20230419141100 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Tagg &amp; Petersen</title>
<desc lang="fr">Classical:NEXT 2019 - Tagg &amp; Petersen - The Kathleen Tagg / Andre Petersen piano duo brings together two of South Africa's most celebrated pianists: one eclectic-experimental classical and one jazz artist, in a unique and highly personal collaboration. Drawing inspiration from the rich sonic tapestries of classical music, nuances of South African jazz and traditional musics from sub-Saharan Africa, this duo explodes the concept of what two pianos can sound like: a bass guitar, goema drum, marimba and uhadi-plus mixing fully composed scores with improvisation in a bold, vital and highly entertaining mix with performances of original compositions and works by iconic South African jazz composers such as Abdullah Ibrahim, Bheki Mseleku and Moses Molelekwa.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/24/07/2123267_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230419141100 +0200" stop="20230419150200 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Clarinet Factory</title>
<desc lang="fr">Classical:NEXT 2019 - Clarinet Factory - Considered to be one of the most unique ensembles to feature on the Czech scene in the last 25 years, the style of the Clarinet Factory hovers between contemporary and classical music, jazz and world music. As winners of the Classic Prague Awards in 2017 for 'Best Crossover Project', the quartet combines their classic music training and clarinet art with jazz, minimalism and improvisation to create their very own music without borders, capable of communicating directly with all audiences. The Clarinet Factory also experiment with electronics, both ambient and dance-oriented, and the four musicians remain ever fascinated with the possibilities of their instrument, considering their work as a music laboratory.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/24/07/2123267_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230419150200 +0200" stop="20230419155700 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">WOMEX 2018</title>
<desc lang="fr">In 2018 WOMEX took place in Las Palmas in Gran Canaria. One of the participants was The Garifuna Collective. These young and old musicians from the Caribbean keep Andy Palacio's legacy alive.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/29/16/2143305_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230419155700 +0200" stop="20230419170200 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Dipha Barus</title>
<desc lang="fr">Dipha Barus - Dipha Barus has received several career awards, including the 2014 DJ of The Year at the Paranoia Awards and has been recognized by Rolling Stone Magazine. He has produced several popular hits in Indonesia, and recently released the amazing &quot;No One Can Stop Us&quot; with local star Kallula. Discover this Indonesian platinum star at the Pacha Festival in Bali, with a cocktail in hand, and let yourself be transported under the tropical sun.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/59/1769392_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230419170200 +0200" stop="20230419182700 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Kenny Loggins and Friends: Live on Soundstage</title>
<desc lang="fr">Kenny Loggins - Daryl Hall started Live From Daryl's House, the free monthly web show in late 2007, after having the idea of &quot;playing with my friends and putting it up on the internet.&quot; The show has since garnered acclaim from Rolling Stone, SPIN, Daily Variety, CNN, BBC, and Yahoo! Music. The influential blogger Bob Lefsetz cited Live From Daryl's House as a perfect example of a veteran artist reinventing himself in the digital age by collaborating with both established colleagues and newer performers. Kenny Loggins' remarkable four-decade-plus career has brought him from the top of the charts to the toast of the Grammys. He's had smash hits on Hollywood's favorite soundtracks, rocked worldwide stages, and found his way into people's hearts while bringing his soulful, beautiful voice to platinum albums in a wide variety of genres.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/04/1754386_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230419182700 +0200" stop="20230419191600 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Ben Frost</title>
<desc lang="fr">Ben Frost - Australian Ben Frost produces under his Bedroom Community label albums inspired by post-classical electronic music, structured sound art and minimalism. His numerous collaborations testify to his desire to develop an artistic form combining music, texts, technology and performance. In this fascinating concert delivered at the Sónar Reykjavík 2018 festival, Frost once again displays his ingenuity as he presents the pieces of the album The Centre Cannot Hold. The award-winning visual artist MFO signs visual effects and lighting.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/59/1769392_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230419191600 +0200" stop="20230419203100 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Arsenik à l'Olympia</title>
<desc lang="fr">Arsenik - Olympia, Paris - The mythical duo Arsenik is a rap group from France, made up of two brothers, Lino and Calbo. The team performs at Olympia Paris to celebrate their 20 years since their first album, Quelques gouttes suffisent... It's a unique concert: Arsenik plays the entire album with numerous special guests for the first time. The album has sold over 300,000 copies in France. Today it's being considered a classic, and it continues to be cited in the top five of the best French rap albums of all generations. Enjoy Arsenik's live show in Olympia Paris!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/04/2122118_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230419203100 +0200" stop="20230419210000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Beak</title>
<desc lang="fr">Echoes Series: Beak - Echoes is a modern live music show hosted by Jehnny Beth (lead singer in the British band Savages). It presents leading and emerging bands and artists from the contemporary scene. The show takes place underneath the Palais de Tokyo museum in Paris, in the club of brutalist architecture, the &quot;Yoyo.&quot; The live sets are 30 minutes long and take place on a customized stage, creating closeness with the audience. The intimate, immersive space lends to the atmosphere of the show. The artistic direction by Antoine Carlier follows a minimalist, refined and pure aesthetic, allowing the artists' energy and emotions to take center stage. This episode features the electronic project Beak. Their set includes the songs &quot;The Brazilian,&quot; &quot;Brean Down,&quot; and &quot;Allé Sauvage.&quot;.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/56/1752527_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230419210000 +0200" stop="20230419220200 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Fedde Le Grand Ziggo Dome</title>
<desc lang="fr">Grand - Following his sold-out shows in 2015, top DJ Fedde Le Grand decided to make a comeback in a bigger and more spectacular environment, the Ziggo Dome. The goal was simple: take down the barriers and break all codes of a traditional dance party! Grand was a spectacular show, changing the dance landscape forever and creating a full crossover between dance and theater. Ballet dancers, singers, break dancers, actors, and live musicians all play their role to the beats of Fedde Le Grand. This show is impressive, and you will be surprised again and again.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230419220200 +0200" stop="20230419230500 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Quartabe</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Da Pá Virada Sessions series portrays the best musicians in Brazilian jazz today. All sessions were recorded in São Paulo and offer a unique experience: they offer a fresh look at the Brazilian music scene. The artists have been selected together with the music editor of Stingray DJAZZ. Among the bands featured in this series is Quartabê, a unique Brazilian quartet that draws from a wide variety of influences, including São Paulo's avant-garde movement, free improvisation, pop, and electronic music. Each of these influences is reflected in Quartabê's rousing live performances! Joana Queiroz (tenor saxophone and clarinets), Maria Beraldo Bastos (clarinets), Mariá Portugal (drums), and Chicão (keys) write, arrange, improvise and sing music that is all theirs.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230419230500 +0200" stop="20230420000500 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Filo Machado - New Year's Eve Special</title>
<desc lang="fr">Filo Machado - New Year's Eve Special - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the artists taking part in this series is Filo Machado. Born in São Paulo, this singer, composer, instrumentalist, arranger and producer has celebrated many musical successes. Filo Machado took part in saxophonist Jane Bunnett's Canadian tour with her spectacular project 'Rendez-Vous Brazil/Cuba'. He has appeared at the jazz festivals of Córsega and Uzeste and opened for the one and only Nina Simone in Cannes.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230420000500 +0200" stop="20230420013600 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Banda Magda live at BIRD Rotterdam</title>
<desc lang="fr">Banda Magda: live at BIRD Rotterdam - An irresistible live act, Banda Magda is full of humour, unflagging energy, and quirky sensibility. A tight-knit group of musicians, they turn the songs of Greek-born founder, singer, and composer Magda Giannikou into engaging gems that have taken the band to legendary venues like Carnegie Hall and, for this performance, BIRD Rotterdam. Banda Magda moves from samba to French chanson, Greek folk music to Colombian cumbia and Afro-Peruvian landó. Their songs capture the best of mid-century ballads and cinematic arrangements, drawing from the band's global background and unrestrained musicality. A joy to experience, Banda Magda makes music for a new generation that's been inspired by ones before.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>