<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Voo -->
<programme start="20230409030000 +0200" stop="20230409040700 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Jungle By Night</title>
<desc lang="fr">Jungle By Night - Jazz in Duketown - Jazz in Duketown is the largest free outdoor jazz festival in the Netherlands. It's a real gathering for jazz addicts, inviting internationally renowned bands. In 2019, one of them is the Amsterdam-based Dutch instrumental collective Jungle by Night. The band plays a mix of various styles, inspired by funk, jazz, dub, rock, and others. The ensemble made its debut in 2010 and has played at numerous festivals. Their December 2010 performance with former backing musicians of Afrobeat founder Fela Kuti in Paris saw them hailed as &quot;the future of Afrobeat&quot;.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/10/1759031_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230409040700 +0200" stop="20230409050100 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Os Capoeira</title>
<desc lang="fr">Os Capoeira - Da Pá Virada Sessions - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the bands taking part in this series is Os Capoeira. This ensemble practices the traditional Brazilian martial art from Bahia it is named after, combining elements of dance, acrobatics, and percussive music. Moreover, Os Capoeira runs a cultural center in São Paulo. Let yourself be inspired by Os Capoeira's unique take on Brazilian culture!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230409050100 +0200" stop="20230409063300 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Fred Hersch Trio</title>
<desc lang="fr">Fred Hersch Trio - Jazz à Ramatuelle - At the age of 63, Fred Hersch is unquestionably one of today's key figures in jazz piano. His music touches upon millions of nuances, contains a keen sense of harmony, and displays an intrinsic knowledge of the standard repertoire. What else made him the teacher of Brad Mehldau and sideman of Stan Getz, Joe Henderson and Art Farmer? Since his recovery from a long coma in 2008, Fred Hersch has experienced a spectacular artistic renaissance. With numerous albums as composer as well as interpreter, he has managed to establish himself as a role model of jazz piano. Supported by John Hebert (double bass) and Eric McPherson (drums), Fred Hersch showcases his unparalleled technique and sensitivity at Jazz à Ramatuelle 2018.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230409063300 +0200" stop="20230409072200 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Ben Frost</title>
<desc lang="fr">Ben Frost - Australian Ben Frost produces under his Bedroom Community label albums inspired by post-classical electronic music, structured sound art and minimalism. His numerous collaborations testify to his desire to develop an artistic form combining music, texts, technology and performance. In this fascinating concert delivered at the Sónar Reykjavík 2018 festival, Frost once again displays his ingenuity as he presents the pieces of the album The Centre Cannot Hold. The award-winning visual artist MFO signs visual effects and lighting.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/59/1769392_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230409072200 +0200" stop="20230409082100 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Liam Gallagher</title>
<desc lang="fr">Liam Gallagher - After leading iconic British rock band Oasis for nearly two decades, Manchester-born singer Liam Gallagher launched his solo career in 2016. He played his first ever U.S. solo show on July 28th of 2017 at Manhattan's McKittrick Hotel in New York City. The rather small venue is known to host the immersive theater experience &quot;Sleep No More&quot;, and its limited capacities made for an intense and intimate concert experience. In a 75-minute long show featuring thirteen songs, Gallagher performed tracks of his 2017 debut album As You Were, next to a list of Oasis fan favorites. Shot in phenomenally sharp 4K, this recording offers viewers the unique opportunity to become part of the audience of this secret session.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230409082100 +0200" stop="20230409090000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Echoes Series: Fontaines DC</title>
<desc lang="fr">Echoes Series: Fontaines DC - Echoes is a modern live music show hosted by Jehnny Beth (lead singer in the British band Savages). It presents leading and emerging bands and artists from the contemporary scene. The show takes place underneath the Palais de Tokyo museum in Paris, in the club of brutalist architecture, the &quot;Yoyo.&quot; The live sets are 30 minutes long and take place on a customized stage, creating closeness with the audience. The intimate, immersive space lends to the atmosphere of the show. The artistic direction by Antoine Carlier follows a minimalist, refined and pure aesthetic, allowing the artists' energy and emotions to take center stage. This episode features the band Fontaines DC. Their set includes the songs &quot;A Hero's Death,&quot; &quot;Hurricane Laughter,&quot; and &quot;I Don't Belong.&quot;.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/04/2122118_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230409090000 +0200" stop="20230409111500 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam</title>
<desc lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam - New Cool Collective is one of the foremost Dutch jazz ensembles. Pioneering new blends of music styles since 1993, NCC has performed in various formations, from small combos to larger ensembles and even big bands! The ensemble's high energy is cut out for the dance floors, as dance, Latin, salsa, afrobeat and boogaloo all meet in a jazzy mix. NCC includes saxophonist Benjamin Herman, guitarist Rory Ronde, drummer Joost Kroon, percussionists Frank van Dok and Jos de Haas, pianist Willem Friede, bassist Leslie Lopez, and trumpeter David Rockefeller.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230409111500 +0200" stop="20230409120900 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Rooted With Wings</title>
<desc lang="fr">Rooted With Wings - Rooted with Wings is a visual dance documentary that explores the work of internationally acclaimed choreographer and dancer Tero Saarinen, granting the viewer a unique lens into this extraordinary artist's creative process. The film brings to light how Saarinen's dance works evolve from an idea or concept into a finished performance and features stunningly captured dance sequences and behind-the-scenes material from around the globe. The film follows Saarinen over five years, from 2014 to 2018, through several premieres of new works and tours in Finland, France, Korea, Kenya, and the US, while bringing to light his approach to his life as a global nomad in dance.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Documentaire</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/10/1752533_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230409120900 +0200" stop="20230409131200 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Nilüfer Yanya - Echoes Series: Nilufer Yanya</title>
<desc lang="fr">Echoes Series - Episode 1 - Echoes is a modern live music show hosted by Jehnny Beth (lead singer in the British band Savages). It presents leading and emerging bands and artists from the contemporary scene. The show takes place underneath the Palais de Tokyo museum in Paris, in the club of brutalist architecture, the &quot;Yoyo.&quot; The live sets are 30 minutes long and take place on a customized stage, creating closeness with the audience. Once the bands have performed, Jehnny Beth invites everyone to sit at her roundtable for a group conversation. The open discussions in every episode allow the audience to understand the rapport, artistic exchange, and intellectual debates that run through this eclectic musical universe. The intimate, immersive space lends to the atmosphere of the show.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/06/1752921_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230409131200 +0200" stop="20230409150100 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Alfredo Rodriguez &amp; Pedrito Martinez</title>
<desc lang="fr">Rodriguez &amp; Martinez - Jazz sous les Pommiers - Pianist Alfredo Rodriguez and percussionist Pedrito Martinez, both from Cuba, play an unforgettable Latin jazz performance at the 2019 edition of festival Jazz sous les Pommiers in Coutances, France. Although both musicians are originally from Havana, Cuba, their music careers are blooming in the USA. The duo's debut album &quot;Duologue&quot; was produced by legendary producer Quincy Jones and saw its release in 2019. Their Jazz sous les Pommiers concert features original compositions alongside Yoruba pieces in honor of the African diaspora to Cuba. Moreover, the duo plays an unexpected interpretation of the Super Mario theme during this varied performance.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/45/1769516_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230409150100 +0200" stop="20230409162400 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Rocky Mountain Way</title>
<desc lang="fr">Rocky Mountain Way - The Colorado Music Hall of Fame hosted a concert for the induction of rock 'n' roll legends Joe Walsh and the late Dan Fogelberg, along with the honoring of the famed Caribou Ranch recording studio near Nederland, Colorado, where Walsh and Fogelberg both recorded some of their best work. The concert, dubbed &quot;The Rocky Mountain Way,&quot; took place on Sunday, August 13, 2017, at Fiddler's Green. It featured performances from an all-star list of musicians including The Lumineers, Garth Brooks, Amy Grant &amp; Vince Gill, The Nitty Gritty Dirt Band, Richie Furay, Randy Owen of Alabama, Todd Park Mohr, Michael Martin Murphey, and surprise guests paying tribute to Dan Fogelberg and Caribou Ranch. Joe Walsh reunited his Caribou recording band Barnstorm for the performance.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/02/14/03/2145504_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230409162400 +0200" stop="20230409170800 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Moonlight Benjamin : WOMEX 2018</title>
<desc lang="fr">Numerous musicians, booking agents, news agencies and media companies from all over the world have been attending the &quot;World Music Exhibition&quot; World Music Expo (WOMEX) since 1994. Over the years, this music fair has settled in several European cities, including Berlin, Brussels, Marseille, Stockholm, Seville, Cardiff and Budapest. In 2018 WOMEX took place in Las Palmas in Gran Canaria. One of the participants was the Haitian singer Moonlight Benjamin. With her band she mixes voodoo blues, Haitian rock and Creole roll into a swirling brew that is thrilling with exciting riffs and heavy grooves. Her powerful voice and fiery electric guitars do the rest.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/52/1752443_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230409170800 +0200" stop="20230409180900 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Creamfields</title>
<desc lang="fr">Creamfields - Having burst onto the ever-growing festival scene two decades ago, Creamfields has secured its spot as being one of the - if not the - biggest weekend dedicated to electronic music in the UK. Currently, the clubbing and raving pilgrimage attracts an impressive 70,000 festival-goers over the weekend. Continuously offering up the very best in EDM, house, trance, drum and bass, grime, and more, Creamfields has hosted some massive names over the past twenty years. This 2019 edition of Creamfields presents Green Velvet, MK, Carl Cox, Deadmau5, Camelphat, Nicole Moudaber, Dimitri Vegas &amp; Like Mike, and many more!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/59/1769392_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230409180900 +0200" stop="20230409194000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Banda Magda live at BIRD Rotterdam</title>
<desc lang="fr">Banda Magda: live at BIRD Rotterdam - An irresistible live act, Banda Magda is full of humour, unflagging energy, and quirky sensibility. A tight-knit group of musicians, they turn the songs of Greek-born founder, singer, and composer Magda Giannikou into engaging gems that have taken the band to legendary venues like Carnegie Hall and, for this performance, BIRD Rotterdam. Banda Magda moves from samba to French chanson, Greek folk music to Colombian cumbia and Afro-Peruvian landó. Their songs capture the best of mid-century ballads and cinematic arrangements, drawing from the band's global background and unrestrained musicality. A joy to experience, Banda Magda makes music for a new generation that's been inspired by ones before.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230409194000 +0200" stop="20230409201200 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">The Hermes Experiment</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Hermes Experiment - The Hermes Experiment, consisting of Heloise Werner (soprano), Oliver Pashley (clarinet), Anne Denholm (harp) and Marianne Schofield (double bass) is a UK-based contemporary quartet made up of harp, clarinet, voice and double bass. Capitalising on their deliberately idiosyncratic combination of instruments, the ensemble regularly commissions new works, as well as creating their own innovative arrangements and venturing into live free improvisation. The ensemble has commissioned over 50 composers at various stages of their careers. During this showcase recorded at Classical:NEXT 2019 in Rotterdam, The Netherlands, The Hermes Experiment performs &quot;I Am Happy Living Simply'&quot;and &quot;The End of the Ending&quot; by Emily Hall, &quot;Samsara&quot; by Alex Mills, and &quot;Double Fiesta&quot; by Meredith Monk.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/13/1767495_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230409201200 +0200" stop="20230409210000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">?nied?</title>
<desc lang="fr">Classical:NEXT 2019 - ?nied? - ?nied? is a voice and electronics duo from Warsaw, Poland who combine extended vocal techniques with improvised, self-named &quot;glitchtronica.&quot; Singer, performer, and sound artist Aleksandra Klimczak frequently breaks boundaries between art genres through cooperating with young artists from different artistic fields. Her work has been awarded from scholarships from the Polish Ministry of Culture and the Capital City of Warsaw. Music curator Antoni Beksiak deals with contemporary crossover, ethnic, classical, jazz, and pop music in his work as an initiator, critic and creator. During this showcase recorded at Classical:NEXT 2019 in Rotterdam, The Netherlands the perform a set list of their own works.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/24/07/2123267_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230409210000 +0200" stop="20230409230900 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Above &amp; Beyond Group Therapy 300</title>
<desc lang="fr">Above &amp; Beyond Group Therapy 300 - Above and Beyond recently made their mark on ABGT300 in an epic way. Live for the 300th edition of Group Therapy Radio, the group broadcast from The Asiaworld-Expo in Hong Kong on September 29, 2018. ABGT300 also saw live performances from Andrew Bayer, Ben Böhmer, Grum, Ilan Bluestone, and Spencer Brown, with the signature set from Above and Beyond as the main event. This year, they wanted to push Group Therapy to the next level. Get ready for some magic moments and excellent music.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230409230900 +0200" stop="20230410000100 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Ramón Valle &amp; Reinier Baas : Music Meeting 2020</title>
<desc lang="fr">Ramón Valle &amp; Reinier Baas - Music Meeting 2020 - Since 1985, the Dutch city of Nijmegen has been welcoming the International Music Meeting Festival every Pentecost. Ranging from jazz and improvisational music to traditional music and unique crossovers, this adventurous festival is all about musical encounters and international collaborations. Disrupted by COVID-19, the festival's 2020 edition had to adapt to new challenges. It now presents this exclusive concert by pianist Ramón Valle and guitarist Reinier Baas, filmed at Concertgebouw De Vereeniging in Nijmegen.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/49/1767496_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230410000100 +0200" stop="20230410015900 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Tower of Power</title>
<desc lang="fr">Tower of Power - Tower of Power is an American R&amp;B-based horn section and band that has been performing since 1968. The concert shows the legendary band's return to where it all started. Recorded live over two performances at The Fox Theatre in Oakland, Tower of Power celebrates their 50th anniversary with their life-long fans, friends, and family. The lead vocalist in this performance is the electrifying, soulful and compelling Marcus Scott. The show also includes an augmented horn and string section and alumni guests, including Lenny Pickett, Bruce Conte, Chester Thompson, Ray Greene, and Francis &quot;Rocco&quot; Prestia. Celebrate the music of Tower of Power and join these memorable evenings where the band performs their full spectrum of life-affirming funk and soul hits.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>