<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Voo -->
<programme start="20230417030000 +0200" stop="20230417040700 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Amilton Godoy</title>
<desc lang="fr">Amilton Godoy - Da Pá Virada Sessions - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the artists taking part in this series is pianist Amilton Godoy. He is not only a well-known soloist in his homeland Brazil, but he is also considered one of the world's greatest pianists today, regularly guesting with international top orchestras and conductors. Godoy frequently teaches workshops throughout Brazil and abroad.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230417040700 +0200" stop="20230417050500 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Nile Rodgers</title>
<desc lang="fr">The popular music performance series Front and Center premiered nationwide on public television in 2016, and now returns for Season 6. The series boasts 22, one-hour episodes and an all-star line-up. This episode features Nile Rodgers. He started his musical career by the end of the '60s. A decade later, he scored a hit with Chic's debut single &quot;Dance Dance Dance,&quot; followed by &quot;Le Freak&quot; from the second album C'est Chic. At Front and Center, Nile Rodgers performs his most well-known songs such as &quot;Get Lucky&quot; and &quot;We Are Family.&quot; In between the songs, Nile Rodgers shares personal stories about his dreams and how they have come true. Enjoy this intimate Front and Center show!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/58/1754433_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230417050500 +0200" stop="20230417064200 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Hugh Coltman</title>
<desc lang="fr">The English singer and composer Hugh Coltman started in blues rock band The Hoax, after which he moved to Paris and released two pop and folk albums. Jazz was beckoning and his next project was a tribute to singer and pianist Nat &quot;King&quot; Cole. Coltman recorded his album 'Who's Happy?' in New Orleans. With this he makes music of an important life question.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/07/57/1642181_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230417064200 +0200" stop="20230417072700 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">BIRD</title>
<desc lang="fr">BIRD - Five promising musicians get together in Rotterdam jazz club BIRD's artists-in-residence project &quot;The Nest&quot;. In this first broadcast we get to know Lisette Ma Neza (slam poet), Peter Somuah (trumpet), Michelle Samba (drums), Huy Le (bass), and Brenn Luiten (piano). Over the course of seven sessions, they exchange ideas, work on their projects, and play music together. Following this period, during which record producer Jameszoo and music manager Jochem Tromp offer their coaching experience, BIRD and North Sea Jazz Festival's fringe festival DownTown organize a tryout performance. Enjoy this unique collaboration of upcoming musicians!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/02/18/24/2148521_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230417072700 +0200" stop="20230417082500 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Roger Sanchez</title>
<desc lang="fr">Roger Sanchez - Self-made man and true legend of house music, Roger Sanchez perfectly embodies the spirit of Pacha Festival Bali. Sanchez had a humble debut in New York, but the days when he was spinning vinyls for his friends in Queens living rooms are far behind him. Today, he is the headliner of major festivals around the globe, and resident DJ of clubs in Ibiza's sights, such as the Pacha Club. With this DJ set at Pacha Festival, Sanchez brings some of the magic of Ibiza to the beaches of Bali. Expect lots of energy, breathtaking lights, and even fireworks!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230417082500 +0200" stop="20230417090000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Close Call</title>
<desc lang="fr">Classical:NEXT 2019 - Close Call - In Close Call your smartphone is a musical instrument. And you are not just an audience member, but a musician in a crazy band with three drummers! Arthur Wagenaar is a Dutch composer and musician. He has a deep love for rock bands, theatre, opera and classical music, and his music is usually a mixture of all of this. He also loves to invent his own instruments, mechanical or electronic, such as the &quot;rampaphone,&quot; a string instrument nine meters in length, the &quot;kleurwerper,&quot; played by juggling, and of course the Close Call Live app. In this performance from Classical:NEXT! in Rotterdam, he is supported by Joep Hendrickx, Tjalling Schrik, Marijn Korff de Gidts, Boy van Ooijen, Dodó Kis, Sarah Jeffery, Lotte Pen, Matthias Konrad, and Axel Schappert.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/24/07/2123267_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230417090000 +0200" stop="20230417111500 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam</title>
<desc lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam - New Cool Collective is one of the foremost Dutch jazz ensembles. Pioneering new blends of music styles since 1993, NCC has performed in various formations, from small combos to larger ensembles and even big bands! The ensemble's high energy is cut out for the dance floors, as dance, Latin, salsa, afrobeat and boogaloo all meet in a jazzy mix. NCC includes saxophonist Benjamin Herman, guitarist Rory Ronde, drummer Joost Kroon, percussionists Frank van Dok and Jos de Haas, pianist Willem Friede, bassist Leslie Lopez, and trumpeter David Rockefeller.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230417111500 +0200" stop="20230417120800 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Tribute to Gilberto Gil</title>
<desc lang="fr">Tribute to Gilberto Gil - Da Pá Virada Sessions - The series Da Pá Virada sessions presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the bands taking part in this series is Caixa Cubo. This trio usually explores Brazil's rhythmically rich landscapes, combining them with modern Brazilian jazz trends. Yet in this singular performance, Caixa Cubo teams up with vocalist Zé Leônidas, selecting special repertoire together with Dani Gurgel from Da Pá Virada Sessions and Rokas Ku?inskas from Stingray DJAZZ.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230417120800 +0200" stop="20230417131800 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Mondriaan Jazz 2017 : FORQ</title>
<desc lang="fr">Mondriaan Jazz 2017: FORQ - Forq is an instrumental quartet with an aggressive sound and a penchant for sonic exploration. Originally founded by keyboardist Henry Hey (David Bowie, Empire of the Sun, and Jeff &quot;Tain&quot; Watts) and bassist Michael League (Grammy-winning founder of Snarky Puppy), Forq is joined by guitarist Chris McQueen and drummer Jason &quot;JT&quot; Thomas. Their group sound draws from various musical paths of its members, whether it's Jason's swampy grooves and shuffles, Chris' singular sonic approach to guitar, Henry's zeal for unique keyboard sounds and twisted ear candy, or Michael's driving world-influenced grooves. The band pushes further down the sonic rabbit hole with their stunning music. This concert was filmed during Mondriaan Jazz Festival 2017, The Hague.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/04/2122118_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230417131800 +0200" stop="20230417150300 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Christian Scott - The Centennial Trilogy</title>
<desc lang="fr">In just a few years, young trumpet player Christian Scott has become synonymous with a new jazz generation. He shakes up the conventions of jazz by taking the genre to new horizons and reaching a wider audience. No doubt, at 33 years old, Christian Scott is already forging his own path. After each record release, he seems even more determined to challenge the rules of jazz with his own avant-garde style. At his 2018 show at La Coopérative de Mai, Christian Scott celebrates 100 years of jazz with the program &quot;The Centennial Trilogy.&quot; Expect a unique performance in an intimate theatre setting, shot in native 4K!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/04/1754386_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230417150300 +0200" stop="20230417161800 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Christine &amp; the Queens</title>
<desc lang="fr">Live aux Vieilles Charrues - French singer Héloïse Létissier, aka Christine and the Queens, originates from Nantes, France. Her debut album Chaleur Humaine earned her a Victories of Music award in 2015, paving the way for future success. A versatile artist skilled in music and dance, she surrounds herself with the best. Among others, she collaborated with dancer and choreographer Marion Motin, who accompanied Madonna. In 2018, Christine and the Queens shortened her name to Chris and hit the international scene with a self-titled album. Her artistic work opens up a new perspective on femininity and masculinity, a hot topic today. In this concert, she inspires her audience at Les Vieilles Charrues in Carhaix, France, to dance all night long.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230417161800 +0200" stop="20230417170300 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Invisible World : WOMEX 2018</title>
<desc lang="fr">One of the participants was the band Invisible World, which operates at the crossroads where Eastern European and Mediterranean influences come together and break new ground. Invisible World is led by the inventive Czech bassist Tomá? Li?ka, together with the Turkish violinist Efe Turumtay, the Serbian accordionist Nikola Zari? and the Moravian drummer Kamil Slezák.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/29/16/2143305_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230417170300 +0200" stop="20230417180300 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Samba das Flores</title>
<desc lang="fr">Samba das Flores - Da Pá Virada Sessions - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the bands taking part in this series is the ensemble Samba das Flores, which dedicates itself to exploring the world's different rhythms, thus keeping the Brazilian heritage alive. The individual voices of the ensemble members color Samba das Flores's unique sound. Let Brazilian culture and global rhythms inspire you during this Samba das Flores performance!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230417180300 +0200" stop="20230417194100 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Jazz à Ramatuelle : Omar Sosa</title>
<desc lang="fr">Jazz à Ramatuelle: Omar Sosa - Experience the incredible richness of our world's music in this performance by the unparalleled Afro-Cuban pianist Omar Sosa! Whilst staying true to Cuban music traditions, Sosa shows an insatiable curiosity: tirelessly exploring music from around the world - from the Caribbean to India and from West Africa to the Arab World - nothing seems to escape his thirst for discovery. A celebration of rhythm in all its forms, this Omar Sosa concert from the French Ramatuelle Jazz Festival promises an intense mystical experience!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230417194100 +0200" stop="20230417201500 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Nilüfer Yanya - Echoes Series: Nilufer Yanya</title>
<desc lang="fr">Echoes Series: Billy Nomates - Echoes is a modern live music show hosted by Jehnny Beth (lead singer in the British band Savages). It presents leading and emerging bands and artists from the contemporary scene. The show takes place underneath the Palais de Tokyo museum in Paris, in the club of brutalist architecture, the &quot;Yoyo.&quot; The live sets are 30 minutes long and take place on a customized stage, creating closeness with the audience. The intimate, immersive space lends to the atmosphere of the show. The artistic direction by Antoine Carlier follows a minimalist, refined and pure aesthetic, allowing the artists' energy and emotions to take center stage. This episode features Billy Nomates. Her set includes the songs &quot;Happy Misery,&quot; &quot;Wild Arena,&quot; and &quot;Call in Sick.&quot;.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/03/1754401_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230417201500 +0200" stop="20230417210000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Life</title>
<desc lang="fr">Echoes Series: Life - Echoes is a modern live music show hosted by Jehnny Beth (lead singer in the British band Savages). It presents leading and emerging bands and artists from the contemporary scene. The show takes place underneath the Palais de Tokyo museum in Paris, in the club of brutalist architecture, the &quot;Yoyo.&quot; The live sets are 30 minutes long and take place on a customized stage, creating closeness with the audience. The intimate, immersive space lends to the atmosphere of the show. The artistic direction by Antoine Carlier follows a minimalist, refined and pure aesthetic, allowing the artists' energy and emotions to take center stage. This episode features the band Life. Their set includes the songs &quot;Excites Me,&quot; &quot;Hollow Thing,&quot; and &quot;Moral Fibre.&quot;.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230417210000 +0200" stop="20230417230900 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Above &amp; Beyond Group Therapy 300</title>
<desc lang="fr">Above &amp; Beyond Group Therapy 300 - Above and Beyond recently made their mark on ABGT300 in an epic way. Live for the 300th edition of Group Therapy Radio, the group broadcast from The Asiaworld-Expo in Hong Kong on September 29, 2018. ABGT300 also saw live performances from Andrew Bayer, Ben Böhmer, Grum, Ilan Bluestone, and Spencer Brown, with the signature set from Above and Beyond as the main event. This year, they wanted to push Group Therapy to the next level. Get ready for some magic moments and excellent music.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230417230900 +0200" stop="20230418000600 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">The Naked and Famous</title>
<desc lang="fr">This series features groundbreaking concerts, in-depth artist interviews and unique stories with host Ted Stryker. This concert series gives the audience an intimate view of music's most influential artists today. Shot in 4K, host Ted Stryker interviews musicians across all genres, creating the most unique music show on TV today. This episode features The Naked and Famous, a band from Auckland, New Zealand. They play a mix of electro pop and alternative rock. The group was founded in 2008 by singer Alisa Xayalith and singer/producer/guitarist Thom Powers. Soon after, they scored their first number one hit with &quot;Young Blood.&quot; Their second single &quot;Punching in a Dream&quot; also made it to the New Zealand hit lists. At the Red Studios in Hollywood, Alisa and Thom are supported by David Beadle and Luna Shadows.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/58/1754433_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230418000600 +0200" stop="20230418015100 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Leçons de ténèbres, de Michel-Richard de Lalande</title>
<desc lang="fr">Lalande - Leçons de ténèbres - Harpsichordist and organist Sébastien Daucé conducts Ensemble Correspondances and soloist Sophie Karthäuser (soprano) in a performance of Michel-Richard de Lalande's (1657-1726) sacred music piece Les Leçons des Ténèbres ('lessons of darkness'). To round off the period of Lent leading up to Easter, the congregation sings these Lamentations of Jeremiah in church. With each psalm, one of the candles is extinguished until complete darkness and silence ensues. Whatever one's faith, this tradition is a unique spiritual experience. French baroque composer Michel-Richard de Lalande, an important composer of &quot;grands&quot; motets of unprecedented length, was one of many who wrote music for this religious practice. This performance was recorded at Chapelle Corneille in Rouen, France in 2016.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/21/1756184_A.jpg" />
</programme>