<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Voo -->
<programme start="20230601030000 +0200" stop="20230601042700 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Ron Carter : Foursight</title>
<desc lang="fr">Ron Carter - Foursight - An evening with the &quot;Foursight&quot; quartet takes you on a tour of Ron Carter's discography, with two thousand five hundred albums, which is to say the consideration he has received since his debut in 1959. After accompanying Jacky Byard and Eric Dolphy, he joined Miles Davis' legendary VSOP with Herbie Hancock, Wayne Shorter, and Tony Williams, among others. Much more than an accompanist, the double bassist is above all a great soloist, as much in intimate trios as in advanced experimental formations or large orchestras. He will be remarkably surrounded here, during his &quot;Foursight&quot; show at Jazz sous les pommiers 2019.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230601042700 +0200" stop="20230601052900 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">José James - Jazz a Vienne</title>
<desc lang="fr">José James - Jazz a Vienne - Since bursting onto the international scene in the late 2000s, José James and his honeyed voice are as bewitching as ever in this 2019 performance at Jazz à Vienne. Flitting between raw soul, soul-folk, hip-hop, and jazz, James is one of the few vocalists capable of keeping the crossover created by Ray Charles in the '50s alive. After sensitive and intelligent odes to Billie Holiday and John Coltrane, this time James pays tribute to a living legend of American popular music: soul man Bill Withers. James performs Bill Withers's unforgettable songs, accompanied by Marcus Machado (guitar), Aneesa Strings (bass, vocals), and Aaron Steele (drums).</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/19/1853106_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230601052900 +0200" stop="20230601060000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Jeditah</title>
<desc lang="fr">Classical:NEXT 2019 - Jeditah - Jeditah is an experimental songwriter, producer and singer from Amsterdam. She works with Brendan Jan Walsh on cello and Jordy Pama on synths and electronics. From an early age on, Jeditah has been immersed in the world of music, travelling with her parents as a music collective. She finds inspiration in the works of acclaimed artists like Björk, James Blake, Laurie Anderson and PJ Harvey. When she began experimenting with making her own music, she first only utilized her own voice, lowering and altering it, and eventually adding electronic beats and synths. With Electric AlleyCat, Jeditah has established her position as a singer and songwriter. In between performing and recording with the band, she creates layered soundscapes from old recordings and homemade samples.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/24/07/2123267_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230601060000 +0200" stop="20230601070100 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">De La Soul - Garorock</title>
<desc lang="fr">De La Soul - Garorock - There is a packed crowd for this De La Soul set at the 2019 Garorock Festival, and with good reason: they witness an unmissable concert by an incomparable group! Having released regular albums since 1989's 3 Feet High and Rising, the Long Island hip-hop stalwarts of De La Soul have been doing the rounds on a suitably named Gods of Rap tour alongside Public Enemy and the Wu-Tang Clan. With an opening that includes call and response, mic checks and arms waving in the air, the audience gets more than a touch of vintage appeal, something that has led to terms like &quot;heritage rap&quot; being associated with the group. But despite their long and influential career, the De La Soul impact has perennial relevance for much of contemporary music. They pushed boundaries back then and they continue to venture out further.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230601070100 +0200" stop="20230601074200 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">City Beats</title>
<desc lang="fr">City Beats - Episode 5 - Amsterdam - DJ-producer Carly Foxx is on a musical journey, immersing herself in the life of five iconic European cities to find inspiration for a series of new tracks. In this episode, Carly Foxx travels to Amsterdam to influence her music track and discovers it is a lot more experimental than she imagined. After exploring the streets of Amsterdam and interviewing passersby, Carly meets up with Steim director Dick Rijken. He and his students design electronic instruments that encourage experimentation. She records various instruments and adds them to her track. Then, in the central library, Carly finds a young pianist who plays his compositions for her to record. After that, Carly travels to the North of Amsterdam to meet with DJ David Leese, who introduces her to the Amsterdam clubbing scene.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Télé-Réalité</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/20/02/2135485_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230601074200 +0200" stop="20230601090000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Jesse Cook - Follow the Road</title>
<desc lang="fr">Celebrated guitarist, composer, and music producer Jesse Cook has been delivering unforgettable concert experiences to audiences across the globe for over 25 years. As far as he has ventured, Jesse has always been fascinated with the mystique of the road that first led him out of Toronto. In his directorial debut, Cook shows us a concert from a rarely seen perspective: the musician's. Born to film director parents, guitarist Jesse Cook taps into this pedigree, and self-directed this story, his fifth Concert Special. The result is &quot;Follow the Road.&quot; Captured in 4K, during his 31-city cross-Canada tour, we follow the band down the TransCanada Highway, against a backdrop of majestic mountains and stunning natural beauty, as they traverse the scenic splendor of the second largest country in the world.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Musique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230601090000 +0200" stop="20230601103800 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Kyle Eastwood Quintet</title>
<desc lang="fr">Jazz à Ramatuelle: Kyle Eastwood Quintet - Bassist Kyle Eastwood (1968) is an explorer, equally at ease with jazz melodies as with pop songs. In the late 1970s, his father Clint took him to see his first jazz concert - a Count Basie performance. Eastwood Jr. was in awe of the drummer and wanted to play an instrument himself. It so happened he wasn't so much interested in jazz, preferring rhythm and blues, Motown and Stax records, funk groups, and North African and Indian music. Eastwood became a brilliant bassist and the composer of highly original soundtracks. His 2015 album &quot;Time Pieces&quot; is a collaboration with brilliant British musicians, such as trumpeter Quentin Collins and saxophonist Brandon Allen. In this broadcast, Eastwood and his fellow musicians revisit the hard bop legacy of Blue Note Records.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230601103800 +0200" stop="20230601113100 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Tower of Power</title>
<desc lang="fr">Tower of Power - Tower of Power is an American R&amp;B-based horn section and band that has been performing since 1968. The concert shows the legendary band's return to where it all started. Recorded live over two performances at The Fox Theatre in Oakland, Tower of Power celebrates their 50th anniversary with their life-long fans, friends, and family. The lead vocalist in this performance is the electrifying, soulful and compelling Marcus Scott. The show also includes an augmented horn and string section and alumni guests, including Lenny Pickett, Bruce Conte, Chester Thompson, Ray Greene, and Francis &quot;Rocco&quot; Prestia. Celebrate the music of Tower of Power and join these memorable evenings where the band performs their full spectrum of life-affirming funk and soul hits.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230601113100 +0200" stop="20230601120400 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Lost Heritage</title>
<desc lang="fr">Classical:NEXT 2019 - Lost Heritage - François Vasseur and Pierre Chataignon make up the French electronic and contemporary music duo Lost Heritage. Living in the region of Geneva, they are two music lovers interested in jazz, classical, urban, and electronic music. François Vasseur is an electronic composer and pianist. He has been working on electronics for many years, starting as a DJ, then as a musician and composer, while also working in the field of cultural mediation and public engagement for organisations like the Verbier Festival, the Geneva Opera and the Lyon Baroque Music Festival. Pierre Chataignon works on various projects across many musical styles, from world music to electronic, as well as in film sound production and voice-over projects that require high quality sound recording, mixing, and production.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/24/07/2123267_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230601120400 +0200" stop="20230601131000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Sgt. Pepper Tribute at Philharmonie de Paris</title>
<desc lang="fr">Sgt. Pepper Tribute at Philharmonie de Paris 2017 - Celebrated as one of the most influential albums of all times, The Beatles' 1967 Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band marked its time and inspired generations of artists. While the album was purely a recording studio product, Beatles' fans continue to be frustrated by not hearing it live. British musician and composer Ed Harcourt, author of six highly acclaimed albums and collaborator of vocalists Marianne Faithfull, Patti Smith, and trumpeter Erik Truffaz, gathered a supergroup for this occasion with top artists from the British independent rock scene. Join Ed Harcourt and members of The Libertines, Supergrass, The Coral, the Beta Band, and Primal Scream for this special tribute.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230601131000 +0200" stop="20230601134400 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Echoes Series: Black Country</title>
<desc lang="fr">Echoes Series: Black Country - Echoes is a modern live music show hosted by Jehnny Beth (lead singer in the British band Savages). It presents leading and emerging bands and artists from the contemporary scene. The show takes place underneath the Palais de Tokyo museum in Paris, in the club of brutalist architecture, the &quot;Yoyo.&quot; The live sets are 30 minutes long and take place on a customized stage, creating closeness with the audience. The intimate, immersive space lends to the atmosphere of the show. The artistic direction by Antoine Carlier follows a minimalist, refined and pure aesthetic, allowing the artists' energy and emotions to take center stage. This episode features the band Black Country. Their set includes the songs &quot;Science Fair,&quot; &quot;Sunglasses,&quot; and &quot;Opus.&quot;.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230601134400 +0200" stop="20230601150200 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Liran Donin : Music Meeting</title>
<desc lang="fr">Nijmegen has been welcoming the International Music Meeting Festival, or Music Meeting for short, every spring since 1985. From jazz and improvised music to traditional music and unique crossovers: musical encounters and international collaborations are at the heart of this adventurous festival. In 2019, Tel Aviv-born bassist, producer and composer Liran Donin performed here.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230601150200 +0200" stop="20230601162200 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Alfredo Rodriguez &amp; Pedrito Martinez</title>
<desc lang="fr">Rodriguez &amp; Martinez - Jazz sous les Pommiers - Pianist Alfredo Rodriguez and percussionist Pedrito Martinez, both from Cuba, play an unforgettable Latin jazz performance at the 2019 edition of festival Jazz sous les Pommiers in Coutances, France. Although both musicians are originally from Havana, Cuba, their music careers are blooming in the USA. The duo's debut album &quot;Duologue&quot; was produced by legendary producer Quincy Jones and saw its release in 2019. Their Jazz sous les Pommiers concert features original compositions alongside Yoruba pieces in honor of the African diaspora to Cuba. Moreover, the duo plays an unexpected interpretation of the Super Mario theme during this varied performance.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/07/06/1769516_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230601162200 +0200" stop="20230601173900 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Anna Calvi, Live at Salle Pleyel 2019</title>
<desc lang="fr">At Salle Pleyel 2019 - Strongly influenced by Hispanic culture, the English singer-songwriter Anna Calvi makes her voice and guitar vibrate with the ardor of flamenco. She gives a powerful, biting, and incredibly moving performance at the Salle Pleyel in Paris. This performance is part of a European tour to promote Anna Calvi's album Hunter, produced by Nick Launay, and recorded in London and Los Angeles. The album is raw and imbued with the primary energy with which Anna Calvi pushes the limits of her guitar and voice in ways she had never done before. Songs from the setlist include &quot;Hunter,&quot; &quot;Away,&quot; and &quot;Alpha,&quot; with an incredibly generous encore in which Anna performs &quot;Jezebel,&quot; &quot;Desire,&quot; and &quot;Ghost Rider.&quot;.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/20/14/2199079_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230601173900 +0200" stop="20230601194600 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Hardwell and the Metropole Orchestra - Symphony</title>
<desc lang="fr">Hardwell and the Metropole Orchestra - Symphony - During &quot;Symphony: The Global Revolution of Dance,&quot; the global sensation DJ Hardwell, with the world's leading pop and jazz orchestra, The Metropole Orchestra, take the audience on a musical journey through the history of dance music. The spectacular show of legendary DJ and the Metropole Orchestra is characterized by the composition of different music periods, from the '80s to the present. The show features hits from various world stars like Donna Summer, Tiësto, Carl Cox, and Daft Punk.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/21/1756184_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230601194600 +0200" stop="20230601203800 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Giana Viscardi - New Year's Eve Special</title>
<desc lang="fr">Giana Viscardi - New Year's Eve Special - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the bands taking part in this series is the duo of Giana Viscardi and Gustavo Marques. After starting their career together, Giana Viscardi and Gustavo Marques released music in many places around the world. After returning to Brazil, they worked together on Giana's album &quot;ORUM&quot;, performing in Africa, Europe, and Brazil.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/2122259_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230601203800 +0200" stop="20230601210000 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Half Moon Run</title>
<desc lang="fr">Songbook - Half Moon Run - &quot;I never heard anyone say that, and yeah, I know exactly what it means. It has to go in there, this has to be a song.&quot; Every song has its own story, and we all think it's a story we've heard before, but we haven't. Songbook finds and captures these intriguing stories by pulling you into the process of writing and composing. Known for its pristine sound, cinematic 4k video and eye for detail, Songbook live-captured episodes emphasize the paramount importance of quality. It addresses the on-the-spot elements of blending song and location at the right moment. Both the magical location and remarkable music interaction will get the attention they deserve. Simply because Songbook isn't just a live music session, it lives.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/04/1754386_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230601210000 +0200" stop="20230601223500 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Opera Imaginaire</title>
<desc lang="fr">Opera Imaginaire - To celebrate Le Concert Spirituel's 30th anniversary, conductor Hervé Niquet collaborated with the Baroque Music Center of Versailles to build his opéra imaginaire. For this unique project, Le Concert Spirituel presents an original performance of unpublished operas by Lully, Rameau, Charpentier, and many other French baroque composers. You will find yourself captivated by a tearful lover, intrigued by the passage to the underworld, and fascinated by the descents of the Gods. The program includes many favorite passages, such as Lully's Armide, Charpentier's Medea, and Campra's Carnaval de Venise. Experience all the magic of Louis XIV's French opera as Le Concert Spirituel transforms the Théâtre des Champs-Elysées into a true French baroque scene.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/03/1781759_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230601223500 +0200" stop="20230601235100 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">Beth Ditto live at L'Aéronef Lille 2017</title>
<desc lang="fr">At L'Aéronef Lille 2017 - Gossip fans, rejoice: Beth Ditto makes a big comeback! With her new album, the fiery singer launches into a solo career. With the boundless energy, undeniable humor, and legendary generosity that characterize her, the American phenomenon presents brand-new songs. Beth Ditto is more than a singer: she is an inescapable figure of the world's pop culture. As the lead singer of indie rock band Gossip (1999-2016), this young woman pulled off spectacular stage performances and gave hilarious interviews, greatly contributing to her sympathy capital. Her 2017 album mixes blues, pop, country, and rock, paying tribute to her native Arkansas in twelve eclectic and unifying pieces. Experience Beth Ditto as never before in this appearance at L'Aéronef Lille 2017!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Musique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/15/1838343_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230601235100 +0200" stop="20230602005500 +0200" channel="Festival.be">
<title lang="fr">GusGus : Live at Sónar Reykjavik</title>
<desc lang="fr">Gusgus - GusGus was founded in 1995 as a collective of film music creators. After signing a contract with the 4AD label the following year, GusGus became one of the most popular electro formations in Iceland, a status that was cemented internationally by the release of Polydistortion in 1997 Over the next two decades, GusGus explored virtually every sub-genre of electronic music, from house to trance, to techno and trip-hop. Discover GusGus at the Sónar Reykjavík 2018 festival, where founding members Biggi Veira and Daníel Ágúst present the latest album from the band, Lies Are More Flexible. With his exceptional vocal talent, fascinating electronic hacks and subtle arrangements, GusGus promises to impress you.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122119_A.jpg" />
</programme>