<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Voo -->
<programme start="20230408022500 +0200" stop="20230408025500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Dream Cars S2</title>
<desc lang="fr">They are the most spectacular convertibles in the world and the most fascinating of all automobiles: Open two-seater sports cars built for velocities exceeding 300 km/h, built for an unparalleled driving pleasure. They are the super sports cabriolets from Ferrari, Lamborghini, Porsche, Bentley and McLaren. DreamCars presents the fastest and most exclusive super sports convertibles in the world.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/50/1752909_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230408025500 +0200" stop="20230408032000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 4</title>
<desc lang="fr">Exciting sports show that follows the hottest action from the world's most unique motor sport events. Viewers will have a chance to visit some interesting competitions- from IDEMITSU 600 Super Endurance at the Chang Interna-tional Circuit in Thailand, the winter edition of the Maroc Challenge in Morocco, to the Hispania Rally, the only European rally to take place in the desert, and many more. Viewers will also find out all the news from the world of motor sports.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/40/1752403_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230408032000 +0200" stop="20230408034500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Bike World</title>
<desc lang="fr">Bike World is the magazine on MOTORVISION TV for all fans of the lifestyle on two wheels. Whether on the road, off-road or on the race track: Bike World brings the latest trends from the world of motorcycles into living rooms around the world. Watch the latest tests of new two-wheelers, exciting reports from the hottest events and thrilling insights into superbike racing.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/32/1837877_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230408034500 +0200" stop="20230408041000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Perfect Ride S6</title>
<desc lang="fr">What's hot and what's not. There are quests to be undertaken, the search for the ideal auto, for the perfect race track for the ultimate accessory gadget. What are the preferred rides of the race legends?</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/09/2153087_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230408041000 +0200" stop="20230408044000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Supercars S6</title>
<desc lang="fr">The McLaren 720S Spider is the fastest convertible in the world. Its cheeky sound is anything but a posh British accent. It's the voice of an uncompromising driving machine with a high potential for addiction. Jaguar, on the other hand, presents itself as majestic. But on the back seat of the F-Pace SVR in sports mode, the Queen would probably feel sick. We also check whether the Porsche Cayenne Coupé can justify its extra price compared to the Cayenne.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748406_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230408044000 +0200" stop="20230408052500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Spotted</title>
<desc lang="fr">Great Britain is the craziest car nation in the world: steering-wheel on the right-hand side and left-hand traffic. British cars offer anything but the average. Be it Aston Martin, Jaguar, Bentley, Morgan or McLaren: Spotted shows spectacular convertibles, coupes and supercars from the UK, shines light on crazy competitions like lawnmower racing and reveals why Britons are crazy about James Bond.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/21/07/1884377_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230408052500 +0200" stop="20230408060000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Snow &amp; Ice Drifting</title>
<desc lang="fr">Austria, at the lake Zenz, a very cool event is taking place: The snow and ice drifting, and of course here our presenter will be learning how to drift today. And he does it with the coolest rally drivers of the scene - Team Orange.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1760716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230408060000 +0200" stop="20230408062500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Go Green! S2</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Lexus RX 450h is the second revised hybrid model coming from the Toyota Group. Go Green checks out the full hybrid SUV. Plus: The young car manufactory Artega emphasizes the importance of ecologically sensitive sports cars and presents the electric Artega SE. And: Go Green takes a look at the BMW Active E, which is an electric vehicle based on the BMW 1 Series.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748432_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230408062500 +0200" stop="20230408065000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Perfect Ride S2</title>
<desc lang="fr">Today in Perfect Ride: It's all about performance. Michael Schumacher in a Formula 1 Silver Arrow on the Nordschleife. In Comparison Test: The Eternal Rally counterparts Mitsubishi Lancer EVO and Subaru WRX STI.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/19/1748438_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230408065000 +0200" stop="20230408071500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Top Ten Show S1</title>
<desc lang="fr">Day in day out, R&amp;D departments of car manufacturers ponder over about what constitutes the perfect car. It has to be extraordinary. It has to stand out and it has to be unique. This is how new concepts and models come into fruition. So today, we'll present you the ten most unusual cars of the past few years.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/50/1752909_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230408071500 +0200" stop="20230408074500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 6</title>
<desc lang="fr">Street Racers is your backstage pass to the world of Formula E. Every two weeks, the magazine takes a look behind the scenes of the most important electric car racing series and provides reviews, current news, exciting interviews and gripping background reports from the world of Formula E.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/59/1880083_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230408074500 +0200" stop="20230408083000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">GT World Challenge Europe Sprint Cup</title>
<desc lang="fr">Join Motorvision TV as it brings you all the action from the European sports car racing series.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1760716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230408083000 +0200" stop="20230408085500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Drift : Championnat de France</title>
<desc lang="fr">When it comes to national drift competitions, the French Championship is one of the most important ones. 32 drivers compete in the spectacular main event.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1760716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230408085500 +0200" stop="20230408094500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">e-Trophée Andros</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Andros Trophy is the French national ice racing championship. The idea appeared long time ago in 1985 when professional racer Max Mamers and the owner of the Andros company, Frédéric Gervoson, met as rugby fans. They spent the winter racing with friends on ice circuits. In 2003 the trophy gained an international aspect with a race at Sherbrooke in Canada. In 2020, the racing series is repositioning itself as an electric racing series.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/43/1884375_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230408094500 +0200" stop="20230408103000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Hi-Tec Drift Allstars Series Australia</title>
<desc lang="fr">The latest drifting competition on Motorvision.TV brings you the best drifters from Australia. Join us for thrilling duels, smoking wheels and non-stop drift battles for the Drift All Stars Series title.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/40/1752403_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230408103000 +0200" stop="20230408112000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">National Legend Cars</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Legends Cars National Championship brings back racing from yesteryear. The series features 5/8 scale replicas of pre-war 1930s Fords, Chevys and Dodges that are equipped with 125bhp-motorcycle engines. These cars are well known for delivering high-octane battles on race tracks around Great Britain.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1760716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230408112000 +0200" stop="20230408120000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">AWD Safari Challenge</title>
<desc lang="fr">Every year, the British All Wheel Drive Club organises the AWDC Safari Championship, which has become the largest off-road event in the UK. Modified 4x4 vehicles of all brands can participate in the competition. Those who want to score points here must complete the challenging courses of mud, slush and scree in the shortest possible time.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/25/1760728_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230408120000 +0200" stop="20230408122500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Go Green! S2</title>
<desc lang="fr">Sky Active.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748432_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230408122500 +0200" stop="20230408125000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Perfect Ride S2</title>
<desc lang="fr">Ford Focus ST (Turnier) versus Volvo V40 T5 R-Design: Two sporty all- rounders. Which of the two compact class vehicles is the better, the more beautiful, the more interesting? We make the comparison test.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/19/1748438_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230408125000 +0200" stop="20230408131500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Top Ten Show S1</title>
<desc lang="fr">Fuel prices keep going up. Oil companies are justifying this with high demands and rising oil prices. And the prices will carry-on going up. So on today's show we are showing you ten of the most fuel-efficient cars.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/50/1752909_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230408131500 +0200" stop="20230408134000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 8</title>
<desc lang="fr">Street Racers is your backstage pass to the world of Formula E. Every two weeks, the magazine takes a look behind the scenes of the most important electric car racing series and provides reviews, current news, exciting interviews and gripping background reports from the world of Formula E.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/59/1880083_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230408134000 +0200" stop="20230408142500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">GT World Challenge Europe Sprint Cup</title>
<desc lang="fr">Join Motorvision TV as it brings you all the action from the European sports car racing series.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/40/1752403_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230408142500 +0200" stop="20230408151500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Silverstone</title>
<desc lang="fr">Aucune description</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/23/1869858_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230408151500 +0200" stop="20230408154000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Rallye Monte Carlo Historique</title>
<desc lang="fr">The infamous Monte-Carlo Rally is one of the world's oldest rally events in the world. To pay tribute to its long-lasting history, the Automobile Club de Monaco organizes the Rallye Monte-Carlo Historique. The catch is: Only cars that competed in the Monte-Carlo Rally at least 40 years ago are allowed to take part in the historic edition of the Monte-Carlo Rally.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/37/1760720_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230408154000 +0200" stop="20230408160500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Hans Herrmann</title>
<desc lang="fr">Portrait of Hans Herrmann, who was famous Formula 1- and sports car driver in 1950 to 1970. He also won the 24 Hours of Le Mans.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/19/1774199_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230408160500 +0200" stop="20230408163000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Car History (Porsche Racing) S3 (n°27)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Porsche Racing»The Porsche 356, the 550 Spyder and the 917: None is faster, none is more reliable and none is more successful. They make Porsche number 1 in motorsports. In the 50s, 60s and 70s, there is hardly a race and barely a rally, that Porsche does not win. From the beginning, Porsche takes the knowledge gained from racing and uses it for series production.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/15/1740326_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230408163000 +0200" stop="20230408170000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Rallye Corsica 1997</title>
<desc lang="fr">Round six of the FIA World Rally Championship was held on the Mediterranean island of Corsica. With its narrow, twisty mountain roads. 1997 was the 41st running of the tour de course. Based in the island's capital at Ajaccio, the three day event included over two hundred kilometers of new stages.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/24/2125717_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230408170000 +0200" stop="20230408172500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Car History (The Story of Automotive Advertising, Part 3) S3 (n°34)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«The Story of Automotive Advertising, Part 3»Whether as a TV spot, as product placement in cinema film or video, or on the Internet, in no other industry are brands, models and advertising campaigns as closely linked as in the automotive industry. And nowhere else is advertising so much fun as in automotive advertising.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/15/1740326_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230408172500 +0200" stop="20230408180000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Classic Ride S4</title>
<desc lang="fr">The extraordinary story of the Chevrolet Corvair. The Chevrolet Corvair is pretty much unheard of in Europe, despite almost 1.4 million units sold. It was innovative, economical, modern, low priced and the first car which featured a turbocharger upon request. The car was nevertheless criticized, slated and later condemned.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/24/2125716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230408180000 +0200" stop="20230408182000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Go Green! S2</title>
<desc lang="fr">At first glance, the Audi A1 on this episode of Go Green seems to be an ordinary small city car, but it's actually quote special. It's driving almost without any emission. Plus: Spectacular design, unusual proportions and innovative ideas - the new Hyundai Veloster is one of the most extraordinary series cars of late. And: The Porsche Panamera S Hybrid combines driving fun with ecology.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748432_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230408182000 +0200" stop="20230408184500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Perfect Ride S1</title>
<desc lang="fr">Today's episode of Perfect Ride is all about setting off and not stopping until you've reached the peak. We will therefore be revving up to the top! The Audi A1 Quattro may seem small, but it's a tough little fighter.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/19/1748438_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230408184500 +0200" stop="20230408191000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Top Ten Show S1</title>
<desc lang="fr">The 24-hour-race at the German Nurburgring is one of the most famous and dangerous long-distance races in the world and in today's program we'll show you the cars that have won the most titles each year.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/50/1752909_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230408191000 +0200" stop="20230408193500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 7</title>
<desc lang="fr">Street Racers is your backstage pass to the world of Formula E. Every two weeks, the magazine takes a look behind the scenes of the most important electric car racing series and provides reviews, current news, exciting interviews and gripping background reports from the world of Formula E.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/59/1880083_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230408193500 +0200" stop="20230408202500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">GT World Challenge Europe Sprint Cup</title>
<desc lang="fr">Join Motorvision TV as it brings you all the action from the European sports car racing series.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/59/1763095_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230408202500 +0200" stop="20230408205000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Tour European Rally Historic</title>
<desc lang="fr">Motorvision TV brings you all the action from the independent rally series taking place around Europe.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/54/1853467_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230408205000 +0200" stop="20230408211500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Rally Terra Valle del Tevere, Italy</title>
<desc lang="fr">Amazing challenge around Europe includes 19 special stages. The top crew will become Tour European Rally champion in one of the most beautiful European rallies.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/10/1763098_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230408211500 +0200" stop="20230408214000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Championnat de Belgique des Rallyes</title>
<desc lang="fr">Motorvision TV brings you all the action from one of the most competitive national rallies in Europe.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/21/2149178_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230408214000 +0200" stop="20230408223500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Rallye : Abu Dhabi Desert Challenge</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Abu Dhabi Challenge is one of the most prestigious international cross rallies. Motorbike, quad-bike, four wheel and truck competitors battle Abu Dhabi's magnificent desert in a grueling 5-day event. In the past, international motorsports icons like Carlos Sainz, Colin McRae and Heinz Kinigadner followed the call and took on the challenging dunes of the United Arabian Emirates.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/47/1808106_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230408223500 +0200" stop="20230408230000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Dubai International Baja</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Dubai International Baja, formerly known as the Dubai International Rally, is the oldest motorsport event in the United Arab Emirates. It is part of the reformed FIA World Cup for Cross-Country Bajas and based at the famous Dubai Autodrome. It will see international drivers taking on a demanding 407-kilometer stage running through the Al Qudra desert.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/50/1776289_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230408230000 +0200" stop="20230408233000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Rally Clasico Mallorca</title>
<desc lang="fr">Motorvision.TV shows the best moments from the 2022 eMallorca Challenge.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/34/1762751_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230408233000 +0200" stop="20230409000000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Spa-Classic</title>
<desc lang="fr">Created in 2011 on one of the most iconic circuit in the world, the Spa Classic is now one of the major European events for historic racing cars. In 2019, Spa Classic celebrates its ninth staging and features events like nighttime races for touring cars and the Heritage Touring Cup, which pays tribute to the famous Spa-Francorchamps 24 Hours for Touring Cars.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/59/1763095_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230409000000 +0200" stop="20230409002500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Go Green! S2</title>
<desc lang="fr">The market for alternative drive technologies just keeps growing and the best place to present the newest cars is at the biggest car show in the world, - the IAA, in Frankfurt, Germany.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748432_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230409002500 +0200" stop="20230409005000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Perfect Ride S2</title>
<desc lang="fr">&quot;&quot;Cruising&quot;&quot;: The new &quot;&quot;300 HorsePower Hayabusa Hardcore&quot;&quot; Trike or the &quot;&quot;New Highway&quot;&quot;.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/19/1748438_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230409005000 +0200" stop="20230409011500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Top Ten Show S1</title>
<desc lang="fr">Usually, when you talk about cars, it's all about their speed and velocity. But this time we've decided to turn the tables and are going to show you the opposite end of the spectrum: the ten most sluggish cars. But don't expect to see only heavy good vehicles or big vans. We have a few surprises hidden under our sleeves!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/50/1752909_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230409011500 +0200" stop="20230409014500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 14</title>
<desc lang="fr">Street Racers is your backstage pass to the world of Formula E. Every two weeks, the magazine takes a look behind the scenes of the most important electric car racing series and provides reviews, current news, exciting interviews and gripping background reports from the world of Formula E.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/59/1880083_A.jpg" />
</programme>