<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Voo -->
<programme start="20230421022500 +0200" stop="20230421025500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">MXGP of Sardegna, Riola Sardo</title>
<desc lang="fr">Lap after lap of international motorsports action. This is coverage from the FIM (Fédération Internationale de Motocyclisme) Motocross World Championship where riders from all over the globe compete in high-octane, fast-paced motocross racing. Competitors battle it out in races lasting 35 minutes plus 2 laps per race.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/32/1907968_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230421025500 +0200" stop="20230421032000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Grand Prix of France, Nice, Palais Nikaia</title>
<desc lang="fr">FIM SuperEnduro World Championship has been held since 2007. Its circuits are built inside stadiums or arenas, recreating obstacles such as rocks, boulders and logs. The championship consists of eight Grands Prix spread around the globe on courses that are mostly off-road. These events are split into two days and two different races, after which the points towards the world championship are awarded. Each round includes a motocross test and an extreme test, in addition to the enduro test.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/22/1748447_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230421032000 +0200" stop="20230421041000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Australian Motocross Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Australian ProMX Championship is the nation's premier motocross championship. The series acts as a successful development platform for young Australian talent and is designed as a tiered system with three dedicated classes: MX3 for younger drivers, the MX2 for senior drivers and the MX1, which is the elite category in the championship.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/31/43/1763097_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230421041000 +0200" stop="20230421050500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Grand Prix of Austria, Wiener Neustadt</title>
<desc lang="fr">FIM X-Trial World Championship is the most prestigious indoor motorcycle trials tournament of the world, organised by the Fédération Internationale de Motocyclisme. The programme presents the highlights of the rounds where the participants have to take on the challenging tracks full of steep climbs and huge rocks.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/13/2162902_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230421050500 +0200" stop="20230421060000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Australian Superbike Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">Founded in 1980, the Australian Superbike Championship is one of the most important motorcycle racing competitions in Oceania. It is well respected as a springboard for riders and teams who aspire an international career in motorcycling. The 2022 season is contested in five classes: Superbike, Supersport, Supersport 300, the Yamaha R3 Cup and the Oceania Junior Cup.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1763086_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230421060000 +0200" stop="20230421062500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Go Green! S3</title>
<desc lang="fr">Quiet, efficient, ecologically-sound and still a true sports car. BMW adorns the i8 Concept with these attributes. Although not yet in series production - there is already the matching convertible.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748432_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230421062500 +0200" stop="20230421065000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Perfect Ride S3</title>
<desc lang="fr">The BMW X5 is the best selling SAV (Sports Activity Vehicle) in the world. Since the introduction of this model, which also founded its segment, the X5 was sold more than 1.2 million times. It combines dynamics with luxury and thanks to xDrive, the BMW's all-wheel drive, it always offers best traction. Perfect Ride reviews the recent third generation of the BMW X5 and reveals, where it improved.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/19/1748438_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230421065000 +0200" stop="20230421071500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Top Ten Show S1</title>
<desc lang="fr">The names car manufacturers give their models, are often somewhat uninspiring. And it can be quite difficult to learn anything about the car, from its' name. A lot of cars are therefore called by their nicknames.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/50/1752909_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230421071500 +0200" stop="20230421074000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 3</title>
<desc lang="fr">Street Racers is your backstage pass to the world of Formula E. Every two weeks, the magazine takes a look behind the scenes of the most important electric car racing series and provides reviews, current news, exciting interviews and gripping background reports from the world of Formula E.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/59/1880083_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230421074000 +0200" stop="20230421082500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">GT World Challenge America</title>
<desc lang="fr">Fanatec GT World Challenge America is the premier North American GT series. Taking place on the best US circuits form Sonoma to Indianapolis, each of the seven race weekends features 90-min double-header races.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/25/1760725_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230421082500 +0200" stop="20230421085500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">The Duels in Formula 1 - Face off for the crown</title>
<desc lang="fr">Fierce battles for championship titles, fierce duels for race victories and even disputes among teammates: Motorsports has been marked by feuds since its inception. The Formula One World Championship is full of heated rivalries, too, and fierce duels are a regular occurrence in the series. Racing Files looks back on the most exciting championship battles in the world's most important racing competition.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/49/1774755_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230421085500 +0200" stop="20230421094500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Rallye Monte Carlo Historique</title>
<desc lang="fr">The infamous Monte-Carlo Rally is one of the world's oldest rally events in the world. To pay tribute to its long-lasting history, the Automobile Club de Monaco organizes the Rallye Monte-Carlo Historique. The catch is: Only cars that competed in the Monte-Carlo Rally at least 40 years ago are allowed to take part in the historic edition of the Monte-Carlo Rally.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/50/1756288_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230421094500 +0200" stop="20230421101000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Sabine Schmitz</title>
<desc lang="fr">&quot;&quot;Queen of the Nordschleife&quot;&quot;.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/19/1774199_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230421101000 +0200" stop="20230421103500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Car History (Mercedes - Beginning of a Success Story) S4 (n°51)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Mercedes - Beginning of a Success Story»From the first three-wheel automobile to the shining star of the â??30s, from Simplex to 500K: No other brand characterizes the first 50 years of the motor better than Mercedes, no other brand represents the evolution of the automobile more than Mercedes. Car History tells the full story of this iconic brand with the three-pointed star emblem, from the invention of the automobile to a global player.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/15/1740326_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230421103500 +0200" stop="20230421110000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">BMW Motorsport 1976</title>
<desc lang="fr">In 1976, the 3-liter BMW CSL was one of the dream cars of BMW Motorsports history in the 70's. It won numerous championships. BMW was also very successful with other models in motorsport.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/24/2125717_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230421110000 +0200" stop="20230421113000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Car History (Porsche 550 Spyder) S2 (n°26)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Porsche 550 Spyder»The Porsche 550 Spyder is small, flat and fast. Even though it was built only 140 times, the 550 Spyder still made history. It laid the foundation for Porsche's success in motorsports and it was the car, in which Hollywood star James Dean was killed. This accident not only turned Dean into a legend, but they Porsche 550 as well. Car History reveals the whole story of the dream car from the 1950s.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/15/1740326_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230421113000 +0200" stop="20230421120000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Classic Ride S3</title>
<desc lang="fr">It is sexy, spectacular and comes with tremendous speed: the Audi Sport quattro S1, the most exciting rally car ever built. In part 2 of the S1 special, Classic Rides accompanies S1 pilot Michael Gerber during the second day of the Rally Legend. Plus: The whole story of the S1 told with original comments by former world champion Walter Röhrl.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/24/2125716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230421120000 +0200" stop="20230421122000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Go Green! S3</title>
<desc lang="fr">Since Spring - the most beautiful Volkswagen with Blue Motion technology can be seen on our roads: the Volkswagen CC. The addition &quot;CC&quot; stands for Comfort Coupe.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748432_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230421122000 +0200" stop="20230421125000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Perfect Ride S3</title>
<desc lang="fr">For many people, Porsche, Ferrari and Lamborghini offer unaffordable dream cars. But you don't need to spend your annual salary on these brands, if you're looking for a powerful car with high performance and a full sounding engine. For example, the Nissan 370 Z by Nismo is just half the price of a Porsche 911, rarer and with 344 HP as powerful as the German flagship sports car.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/19/1748438_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230421125000 +0200" stop="20230421131000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Top Ten Show S1</title>
<desc lang="fr">At the moment, the industry considers the SUV, Crossover or SAC to be good choices. But is it such a good idea to drive off road with a Porsche Cayenne or BMW 6X? Today, we look at the real off road monsters.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/50/1752909_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230421131000 +0200" stop="20230421134000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 23</title>
<desc lang="fr">Street Racers is your backstage pass to the world of Formula E. Every two weeks, the magazine takes a look behind the scenes of the most important electric car racing series and provides reviews, current news, exciting interviews and gripping background reports from the world of Formula E.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/59/1880083_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230421134000 +0200" stop="20230421142500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">GT World Challenge America</title>
<desc lang="fr">Fanatec GT World Challenge America is the premier North American GT series. Taking place on the best US circuits form Sonoma to Indianapolis, each of the seven race weekends features 90-min double-header races.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/59/1763095_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230421142500 +0200" stop="20230421145000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">P1 Offshore Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">The P1 Offshore Powerboat Championship promises tightly fought offshore racing with powerboats reaching top speeds of up to 100 miles per hour. Five events are schedules for the 2022 season and Motorvision.TV brings you all the thrilling action from each event!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/05/2038331_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230421145000 +0200" stop="20230421152000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">GP of Middle East</title>
<desc lang="fr">In 2022, the UIM is once again hosting its Formula 1 World Championship in Powerboat. In the 37th season, ten teams with 19 drivers from eleven countries have signed up to fight for the title of the new world champion in three Grand Prix.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/21/2061231_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230421152000 +0200" stop="20230421154500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">UIM Class 1 Powerboat Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">Want to cool down? The Class 1 Offshore Championship featuring boats with twin inboard 1100hp engines that can reach speeds in excess of 160mph. All boats, which are around 12-14 meters long and 3.5 meters wide, are limited by a minimum weight of 4,950 kilos.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/03/2034343_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230421154500 +0200" stop="20230421161500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">UIM Aquabike World Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">Caution, danger of splashing! Since 1992, the Aquabike World Championship has been the most important racing series in the sport of jet skiing and one of the fastest competitions in water sports. On specially designed race courses or on the high seas, the participants engage in thrilling races in the ski and runabout categories and fascinate with all kinds of stunts on their more than 300 hp jet skis.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/31/2029804_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230421161500 +0200" stop="20230421170000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Australian V8 Superboats Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Australian V8 Superboat Championship is one of the most important watersports series from down under. Drivers compete in three different classes: the LS Class, Group A and Unlimited, which features hardly any restrictions regarding engine sizes. In 2022, a total of seven rounds are scheduled before a new champion is crowned.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/02/22/26/1784522_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230421170000 +0200" stop="20230421180000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Daytona Beach, Florida</title>
<desc lang="fr">See all the action from the USA series of P1 AquaX, an exciting Jet Ski racing event, operated by Powerboat P1. P1 AquaX is an international motorboat racing competition organised by the Union Internationale Motornautique.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/38/1763103_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230421180000 +0200" stop="20230421182000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Go Green! S3</title>
<desc lang="fr">Forward-looking design, alternative fuels and new-use approaches: We take a look into the future of mobility and show how BMW and other European car manufacturers are working on the sports cars of tomorrow. Plus: Fewer and fewer people own cars. Instead car sharing becomes increasingly popular. We explain, why people rather share than buy their own car.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748432_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230421182000 +0200" stop="20230421185000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Perfect Ride S3</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Tesla Model S is the car of the 21st century. It teaches the major automobile companies, what is possible when you believe in your own idea. It is one of the most exceptional cars one can buy. It offers an electric range of up to 500 kilometers and accelerates from zero to 100 km/h in 4 seconds. In addition to that, Tesla promises that every buyer can charge its car for free forever.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/19/1748438_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230421185000 +0200" stop="20230421191500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Top Ten Show S1</title>
<desc lang="fr">When car manufacturers decide to name their cars after animals, they're obviously suggesting that their car reflects certain characteristics of the animals that they're naming the cars after.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/50/1752909_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230421191500 +0200" stop="20230421194000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 9</title>
<desc lang="fr">Street Racers is your backstage pass to the world of Formula E. Every two weeks, the magazine takes a look behind the scenes of the most important electric car racing series and provides reviews, current news, exciting interviews and gripping background reports from the world of Formula E.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/59/1880083_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230421194000 +0200" stop="20230421202500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">GT World Challenge America</title>
<desc lang="fr">Fanatec GT World Challenge America is the premier North American GT series. Taking place on the best US circuits form Sonoma to Indianapolis, each of the seven race weekends features 90-min double-header races.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/50/1756288_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230421202500 +0200" stop="20230421205000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Drift : Championnat de France</title>
<desc lang="fr">When it comes to national drift competitions, the French Championship is one of the most important ones. 32 drivers compete in the spectacular main event.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/59/1763095_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230421205000 +0200" stop="20230421214000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">e-Trophée Andros</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Andros Trophy is the French national ice racing championship. The idea appeared long time ago in 1985 when professional racer Max Mamers and the owner of the Andros company, Frédéric Gervoson, met as rugby fans. They spent the winter racing with friends on ice circuits. In 2003 the trophy gained an international aspect with a race at Sherbrooke in Canada. In 2020, the racing series is repositioning itself as an electric racing series.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/43/1884375_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230421214000 +0200" stop="20230421223000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Hi-Tec Drift Allstars Series Australia</title>
<desc lang="fr">The latest drifting competition on Motorvision.TV brings you the best drifters from Australia. Join us for thrilling duels, smoking wheels and non-stop drift battles for the Drift All Stars Series title.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/25/1760725_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230421223000 +0200" stop="20230421232000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">National Legend Cars</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Legends Cars National Championship brings back racing from yesteryear. The series features 5/8 scale replicas of pre-war 1930s Fords, Chevys and Dodges that are equipped with 125bhp-motorcycle engines. These cars are well known for delivering high-octane battles on race tracks around Great Britain.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/59/1763095_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230421232000 +0200" stop="20230422000000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">AWD Safari Challenge</title>
<desc lang="fr">Every year, the British All Wheel Drive Club organises the AWDC Safari Championship, which has become the largest off-road event in the UK. Modified 4x4 vehicles of all brands can participate in the competition. Those who want to score points here must complete the challenging courses of mud, slush and scree in the shortest possible time.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/40/1975310_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230422000000 +0200" stop="20230422002500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Go Green! S3</title>
<desc lang="fr">2007 saw the launch of a successor to the Fiat Cinquecento. The Fiat Twin-Air is greener version of the Fiat 500 and comes with a two-cylinder turbo engine. The sound of its high-torque engine alone makes this car fun and seductive. Plus: Bloggers from around the world get the chance to put the Volvo C30 E to the extreme test in the ice and snow of Northern Sweden.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748432_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230422002500 +0200" stop="20230422005000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Perfect Ride S3</title>
<desc lang="fr">The 2012 Mercedes A-Class managed to shake off its image as a vehicle for retired people. But AMG tops it all and presents the hottest A-Class ever. Its impressive 360-hp engine is the most powerful production four-cylinder in the world. Plus: Musketier Tuning turns the Citroen DS 3 into a defening driving machine. Perfect Ride discusses the differences between the tuned and the production model.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/19/1748438_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230422005000 +0200" stop="20230422011500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Top Ten Show S1</title>
<desc lang="fr">There are cars-- or let's say vehicles, which turn every head on the street. And that's not necessarily because they're beautiful, but because there are exceptionally weird. Some of these drivable oddballs are unique customizations, while others are simply classics. We'll show you the ten strangest vehicles ever built.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/39/1752442_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230422011500 +0200" stop="20230422014000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 10</title>
<desc lang="fr">Street Racers is your backstage pass to the world of Formula E. Every two weeks, the magazine takes a look behind the scenes of the most important electric car racing series and provides reviews, current news, exciting interviews and gripping background reports from the world of Formula E.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/59/1880083_A.jpg" />
</programme>