<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Voo -->
<programme start="20230527023500 +0200" stop="20230527030000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Bike World</title>
<desc lang="fr">Bike World revolves around the speedway and the racers swishing by on their two wheelers. Find out the latest news and reports regarding two-wheel competitions in the world of speed. This is the content to enjoy for all motorcycle enthusiasts across the world. Explore the best motorbikes, top locations, and iconic racers who have a lot of fun doing it.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/32/1837877_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230527030000 +0200" stop="20230527032500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 3</title>
<desc lang="fr">Exciting sports show that follows the hottest action from the world's most unique motor sport events. Viewers will have a chance to visit some interesting competitions- from IDEMITSU 600 Super Endurance at the Chang Interna-tional Circuit in Thailand, the winter edition of the Maroc Challenge in Morocco, to the Hispania Rally, the only European rally to take place in the desert, and many more. Viewers will also find out all the news from the world of motor sports.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/40/1752403_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230527032500 +0200" stop="20230527035000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Perfect Ride S6</title>
<desc lang="fr">What's hot and what's not. There are quests to be undertaken, the search for the ideal auto, for the perfect race track for the ultimate accessory gadget. What are the preferred rides of the race legends?</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/20/01/2153087_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230527035000 +0200" stop="20230527041500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Supercars</title>
<desc lang="fr">A synergy of high-octane power, speed, luxury and prestige. Supercars features some of the most desirable automobiles in the world, whether it be an agile sports car to a comfortable limousine. It features the likes of prestige brands filled with rich heritage and motorsport pedigree; such as Bentley, BMW M, Mercedes AMG, Aston Martin, Maserati, Porsche and Ferrari to niche-market, lightweight Lotuses, KTMs and Caterhams. Supercars has everything a petrolhead needs to get up to speed on the latest and greatest of high-performance road machines.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748406_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230527041500 +0200" stop="20230527044500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Go Green!</title>
<desc lang="fr">Energy saving is becoming a more and more important goal for the world's leading car manufacturers. Motorvision TV explores the environment-friendly solutions emerging in the car industry. presenting the latest ideas from research and development teams. Find out what are the best ways to go green when it comes to your vehicle.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748432_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230527044500 +0200" stop="20230527052500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Spotted</title>
<desc lang="fr">When car spotters find rare cars it's like winning the lottery. One of the most exclusive cars in the world is the Paguani Huayra, which was built just 20 times. Its counterpart: the Rimac Concept One, which writes history as the world's fastest electric car with a top speed of 355 kmph. Lamborghini Huracan O.CT and Arden Jaguar F-Type promise brutal tuning power beyond good and evil.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/20/59/1884377_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230527052500 +0200" stop="20230527060000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Trackmasters</title>
<desc lang="fr">Patrick makes André sweat! Also on the show tourists from all over the world have made their way down to the Green Hell including many Germans, Austrians and 5 crazy Englishmen in a taxi!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/25/59/1986723_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230527060000 +0200" stop="20230527062500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Stunt Heroes (Action Special) S3 (n°33)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Action Special»&quot;Stunt Heroes&quot; of MotorvisionTV is giving answers to those questions. The stuntteam of &quot;&quot;action concept&quot;&quot;, one of the biggest film- and stunt productions in Europe is given a spectacular insight to their daily business. Things that are never seen in the movies. Often enough they are working several days or weeks for a five-second-stunt! A tough job! The action-special shows all stunts of the second season of the show, explains differences between the different kinds of tools they got in their arsenal. &quot;Stunt Heroes&quot;.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/15/35/1790601_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230527062500 +0200" stop="20230527065000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Supercars S5</title>
<desc lang="fr">Most people associate Aston Martin with James Bond, luxury, style and elegance or real men. The Vantage N430 is a sports car that makes you feel the heritage of British racecars. It is elegant, fast, comes with a marvelous sound and a design which reminds you of Aston Martin's racing successes from the past. Also on this episode: Supercars checks out the Bentley GTC Speed.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748406_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230527065000 +0200" stop="20230527071500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Classic Ride S2</title>
<desc lang="fr">It looks like a Ferrari but it comes from Bavaria, Germany: The Glas GT, one of the rarest oldtimers in the world!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/24/2125716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230527071500 +0200" stop="20230527074000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Formula E - Specials</title>
<desc lang="fr">In less than six years the ABB FIA Formula E Championship has grown from ambitious start-up to one of the most innovative sports entertainment properties in the world, attracting a host of the globe's biggest automotive manufacturers. The Story Of Formula E plots the extraordinary rise of the all-electric championship with some of the key players including Lucas Di Grassi, Jean Eric Vergne, Sebastien Buemi, Sam Bird and founder Alejandro Agag.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/10/08/2194935_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230527074000 +0200" stop="20230527083500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Grand Prix of Andorra, Andorra La Vella</title>
<desc lang="fr">X-Trial is a young and dynamic sport. The events take place in arenas and the spectators are up close during the entire period. Spectacular setups with challenging obstacles combined with the skill of the best riders in the world promise great entertainment. Motorvision.TV shows highlights from all six events of the 2022 season.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/13/2162902_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230527083500 +0200" stop="20230527090000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">AWD Safari Challenge</title>
<desc lang="fr">Watch the exciting Safari Championship organized by the British All Wheel Drive Club, in which modified 4x4 vehicles of all brands can participate.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/25/1760728_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230527090000 +0200" stop="20230527095000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Hi-Tec Drift Allstars Series Australia</title>
<desc lang="fr">The latest drifting competition on Motorvision.TV brings you the best drifters from Australia. Join us for thrilling duels, smoking wheels and non-stop drift battles for the Drift All Stars Series title.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/50/1756288_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230527095000 +0200" stop="20230527101500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Arlington</title>
<desc lang="fr">Aucune description</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/40/1752403_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230527101500 +0200" stop="20230527111000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Top Fuel Australia Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">Aucune description</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/40/1752403_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230527111000 +0200" stop="20230527120000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">National Legend Cars</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Legends Cars National Championship brings back racing from yesteryear. The series features 5/8 scale replicas of pre-war 1930s Fords, Chevys and Dodges that are equipped with 125bhp-motorcycle engines. These cars are well known for delivering high-octane battles on race tracks around Great Britain.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/59/1763095_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230527120000 +0200" stop="20230527122500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Stunt Heroes (The Stunt Movies) S3 (n°32)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«The Stunt Movies»To every stunt belongs a little movie. The Stunt Heroes always kept it like that! In the second season the stuntteam created again 13 action-film sequences - sometimes funny, sometimes brutal, sometimes evil - but always spectacular. This special shows all 13 stunt movies of the new season of MotorvisonTVs favourite stunt show.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/15/35/1790601_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230527122500 +0200" stop="20230527125000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Supercars S5</title>
<desc lang="fr">What birngs more fun, than the perfect street? And what is even better than to conquer the street with lightweighted roadsters? Not to much! The &quot;&quot;&quot;Slivretta Hochalpenstrasse&quot;&quot;&quot; in Austria is the ideal palyground for the Lotus Elise and the Roding Roadster. And a very classic car opens it's roff again: the Porsche 911 Targa 4S.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748406_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230527125000 +0200" stop="20230527131500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Classic Ride S2</title>
<desc lang="fr">&quot;Investigate the Porsche cult.&quot; Which ride is more enjoyable, the Porsche tractor or Porsche Targa? Porsche is cult. For over 5 decades the fans have been addicted to these cars out of Zuffenhausen. But when was the big bang of the Porsche brand and when was the first Porsche created?</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/24/2125716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230527131500 +0200" stop="20230527134500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Formula E - Specials</title>
<desc lang="fr">ABB FIA Formula E the Number 1s, a look back over all the races to find the most amazing moments in Formula E's history. We pick the Number 1 moment in ten categories looking at amazing action from overtakes, close shaves, starts, and incidents, through the best driver reactions, FanBoosts and Attack Modes, to innovations and insights, and finally we pick out the best race so far.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/12/06/2195752_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230527134500 +0200" stop="20230527143500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Grand Prix of Spain, Barcelona</title>
<desc lang="fr">X-Trial is a young and dynamic sport. The events take place in arenas and the spectators are up close during the entire period. Spectacular setups with challenging obstacles combined with the skill of the best riders in the world promise great entertainment. Motorvision.TV shows highlights from all six events of the 2022 season.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/13/2162902_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230527143500 +0200" stop="20230527150000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">The Rallye World Championship 1982</title>
<desc lang="fr">The African continent is always a difficult terrain for rally drivers. That wasn't any different for the 1982 World Rally Championship, when heat, dust, mud and hardly passable routes posed major challenges for drivers, co-drivers and engines.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/20/04/2125717_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230527150000 +0200" stop="20230527153000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Legendary Tracks - Brooklands, Monthlery, Avus</title>
<desc lang="fr">Mountain races, rallies and city races: In the early days of motorsport, races were held on existing roads and off-roads. After a series of serious accidents, organizers began to build their own circuits for their events. Today tracks like the Silverstone Circuit, Monza or the Indianapolis Motor Speedway are a Mecca for all racing enthusiasts. MOTORVISION TV looks into the racing files of the world's most legendary racetracks and tells their story.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/49/1774755_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230527153000 +0200" stop="20230527155500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Rallye Monte Carlo Historique</title>
<desc lang="fr">The infamous Monte-Carlo Rally is one of the world's oldest rally events in the world. To pay tribute to its long-lasting history, the Automobile Club de Monaco organizes the Rallye Monte-Carlo Historique. The catch is: Only cars that competed in the Monte-Carlo Rally at least 40 years ago are allowed to take part in the historic edition of the Monte-Carlo Rally.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/59/1763095_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230527155500 +0200" stop="20230527162000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Classic Ride S3</title>
<desc lang="fr">It is one of the most spectacular cars of the last 30 years: the Delorean DMC-12. But after 9000 built cars, the production came to an end in 1982.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/24/2125716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230527162000 +0200" stop="20230527165000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Rally Clasico Mallorca</title>
<desc lang="fr">Motorvision.TV shows the best moments from the 2022 eMallorca Challenge.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/38/1758023_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230527165000 +0200" stop="20230527174500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Chateau Impney Hill Climb</title>
<desc lang="fr">Motorsports has been taken place at the Château Impney near Droitwich Spa in Worcestershire, England since the 1950s. But no event was as big and successful as the Chateau Impney Hill Climb. Every year, the event attracts a wide array of vintage cars and more modern supercars. However, 2019 sees the last edition of the iconic Chateau Impney Hill Climb.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1760716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230527174500 +0200" stop="20230527180000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 6</title>
<desc lang="fr">When their ambitions exceed their driving skills, when well-secured racing professionals are thrown out of corners, we always have a camera at hand. Breathtaking stunts by professional drivers and slapstick-action in highly-tuned tin can rockets. Spectacular scenes where nobody gets hurt.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/31/00/1748416_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230527180000 +0200" stop="20230527182500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Stunt Heroes (The Remote Control) S1 (n°3)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«The Remote Control»The Stunt Heroes from Action Concept try out another new stunt: Stuntman Tobi, aka Heidi, operates an Artega GT at full speed with a remote control. This is, however, just a warm-up before the big stunt, in which he drives a car up a steep ramp at 68 mph. The Question is: How high can remote control cars fly? It's an action-packed flying spectacle!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/15/35/1790601_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230527182500 +0200" stop="20230527185000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Supercars S2</title>
<desc lang="fr">The evolutionary history of the Infinity FX50, Sebastian Vettel Edition. 1.370 Kg and 620 horsepower - this is the Porsche GT2 RS. This car is the most expensive and fastest serial 911 Porsche all times.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748406_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230527185000 +0200" stop="20230527192000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Classic Ride S3</title>
<desc lang="fr">It is sexy, spectacular and comes with tremendous speed: the Audi Sport quattro S1, the most exciting rally car ever built. In part 2 of the S1 special, Classic Rides accompanies S1 pilot Michael Gerber during the second day of the Rally Legend. Plus: The whole story of the S1 told with original comments by former world champion Walter Röhrl.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/24/2125716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230527192000 +0200" stop="20230527194500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Formula E - Specials</title>
<desc lang="fr">In less than six years the ABB FIA Formula E Championship has grown from ambitious start-up to one of the most innovative sports entertainment properties in the world, attracting a host of the globe's biggest automotive manufacturers. The Story Of Formula E plots the extraordinary rise of the all-electric championship with some of the key players including Lucas Di Grassi, Jean Eric Vergne, Sebastien Buemi, Sam Bird and founder Alejandro Agag.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/12/06/2195752_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230527194500 +0200" stop="20230527203500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">WeatherTech SportsCar Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">The IMSA Weathertech Sportscar Championship is back on MOTORVISION TV. Twelve races are again scheduled for the 2022 season, including four endurance classics. Motorvision TV provides live and extensive highlights coverage of all events.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/37/1760720_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230527203500 +0200" stop="20230527210000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Championnat de Belgique des Rallyes</title>
<desc lang="fr">BRC.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/20/02/2149178_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230527210000 +0200" stop="20230527212500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Rally Regione Piemonte, Italy</title>
<desc lang="fr">Amazing challenge around Europe includes 19 special stages. The top crew will become Tour European Rally champion in one of the most beautiful European rallies.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/24/1760723_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230527212500 +0200" stop="20230527215000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Morocco Desert Challenge</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Morocco Desert Challenge has been the fastest growing rallies in the Sahara since its creation in 2008. Until May 2016 the event was called &quot;the Libya Rally&quot; because its origins were in Libya. As a result of the war in 2011 the Khadafi regime came to an end but it is still impossible to host a large international sports event in Libya. In 2013 the rally was moved to Morocco, and thanks to a huge variety of landscapes and tracks it was a success.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/06/11/2193719_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230527215000 +0200" stop="20230527221500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Morocco Desert Challenge</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Morocco Desert Challenge has been the fastest growing rallies in the Sahara since its creation in 2008. Until May 2016 the event was called &quot;the Libya Rally&quot; because its origins were in Libya. As a result of the war in 2011 the Khadafi regime came to an end but it is still impossible to host a large international sports event in Libya. In 2013 the rally was moved to Morocco, and thanks to a huge variety of landscapes and tracks it was a success.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/06/11/2193719_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230527221500 +0200" stop="20230527224000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 2</title>
<desc lang="fr">Aucune description</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/10/1763098_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230527224000 +0200" stop="20230527233000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">BTRDA Rallycross Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">Aucune description</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/40/1752403_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230527233000 +0200" stop="20230528000000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Kaiafas Battle 2022</title>
<desc lang="fr">Aucune description</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/03/2034343_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230528000000 +0200" stop="20230528002500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Stunt Heroes (Stunt Highlights) S3 (n°31)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Stunt Highlights»Explosions - accidents - pain - stunt coordinator Domi and his team give everything for spectacular stunts - in each episodes they are pushing the limits.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/15/35/1790601_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230528002500 +0200" stop="20230528005000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Supercars S5</title>
<desc lang="fr">Luxury does not necesseraly mean to waste time. Hybrid is one of the techniques wich promises less fuel consumption with a still powerful engine. Lexus ist the pioneer in electrification of cars. Supercars drives the new LS 600h, The BMW Actiev Hybrid 7 and teh Porsche Panamera S E-Hybrid.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748406_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230528005000 +0200" stop="20230528011500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Classic Ride S4</title>
<desc lang="fr">One of the most popular racing series of the world - the Formula Vee. The 'Vee', or simply 'V', stands for Volkswagen, as the small formula cars were equipped with the technology of the legendary Beetle. This historical Formula Vee racing series took place around 15 years ago.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/24/2125716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230528011500 +0200" stop="20230528014000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Formula E - Specials</title>
<desc lang="fr">ABB FIA Formula E the Number 1s, a look back over all the races to find the most amazing moments in Formula E's history. We pick the Number 1 moment in ten categories looking at amazing action from overtakes, close shaves, starts, and incidents, through the best driver reactions, FanBoosts and Attack Modes, to innovations and insights, and finally we pick out the best race so far.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/12/06/2195752_A.jpg" />
</programme>