<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Voo -->
<programme start="20230504020000 +0200" stop="20230504024500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Southern Races Part 2</title>
<desc lang="fr">King of the Roads.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/20/50/2186513_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230504024500 +0200" stop="20230504033500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Asian Le Mans Series</title>
<desc lang="fr">Asian sports car racing endurance series created by the Automobile Club de l'Ouest and based in Asia aims to attract teams and drivers from Asian countries. The Asian Le Mans Series is the symbol of the Spirit of Le Mans, and holds the same passion for creating world class endurance racing.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/20/00/2125604_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230504033500 +0200" stop="20230504043000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Circuit de Barcelona-Catalunya, Spain</title>
<desc lang="fr">European Le Mans Series believes in the team spirit during long distance performance. The duty of the ELMS is to offer its competitors a full season to race their cars on some of the best tracks in Europe, while keeping tight control of the costs associated with running in a top European wide series. The champions are offered a place on the grid of the 24 Heures du Mans, which gives an extra, important dimension to the title race across the three categories.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/08/39/2182076_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230504043000 +0200" stop="20230504051500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Autodromo Nazionale</title>
<desc lang="fr">See all the action and best parts from the GT World Challenge Europe, a sports car racing series divided into two separate championships - the GT World Challenge Europe Sprint Cup, and the GT World Challenge Europe Endurance Cup.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/50/1756288_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230504051500 +0200" stop="20230504060000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">WeatherTech SportsCar Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">The IMSA WeatherTech SportsCar Championhip is an endurance racing championship in North America where up to five different classes compete in eleven events.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/25/1760725_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230504060000 +0200" stop="20230504063000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Stunt Heroes (The Remote Control) S1 (n°3)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«The Remote Control»The Stunt Heroes from Action Concept try out another new stunt: Stuntman Tobi, aka Heidi, operates an Artega GT at full speed with a remote control. This is, however, just a warm-up before the big stunt, in which he drives a car up a steep ramp at 68 mph. The Question is: How high can remote control cars fly? It's an action-packed flying spectacle!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/15/35/1790601_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230504063000 +0200" stop="20230504065000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Supercars S3</title>
<desc lang="fr">They are sleek, they are exclusive and most of all: they are extremely fast - supercars! See the first Arabian supercar and many other brand new luxury sport cars from the Qatar Motor Show.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748406_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230504065000 +0200" stop="20230504071500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Classic Ride S5</title>
<desc lang="fr">For more than 50 years the Porsche 911 has been driving on the roads and race tracks of the world. Each generation set standards in the sports car segment. We look back at the beginnings of this success story. But it is not the only legend from the class of 1963. At the same time Corvette Stingray celebrates its premier and becomes the American sports car dream par excellence.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/24/2125716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230504071500 +0200" stop="20230504074000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 24</title>
<desc lang="fr">Street Racers is your backstage pass to the world of Formula E. Every two weeks, the magazine takes a look behind the scenes of the most important electric car racing series and provides reviews, current news, exciting interviews and gripping background reports from the world of Formula E.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/59/1880083_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230504074000 +0200" stop="20230504083500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Hungaroring, Hungary</title>
<desc lang="fr">The European Le Mans Series, a series open to Le Mans Prototypes and grand tourer-style racing cars, is back with another action-filled season. This year's calendar features six 4-hour races around Europe including the return of the 4 Hours of Imola.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/08/39/2182076_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230504083500 +0200" stop="20230504092500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Jet Ski World Series</title>
<desc lang="fr">Aucune description</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/37/1763088_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230504092500 +0200" stop="20230504095000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">GP of Indonesia, Kopiko</title>
<desc lang="fr">Follow all the exciting action from the adrenaline-filled Formula 1 Powerboat World Championship, an international motorboat racing competition for powerboats, organised by the Union Internationale Motonautique.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/21/2061231_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230504095000 +0200" stop="20230504104000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Australian V8 Superboats Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Australian V8 Superboat Championship is one of the most important watersports series from down under. Drivers compete in three different classes: the LS Class, Group A and Unlimited, which features hardly any restrictions regarding engine sizes. In 2022, a total of seven rounds are scheduled before a new champion is crowned.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/02/22/26/1784522_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230504104000 +0200" stop="20230504110500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Powerboat: P1 USA AquaX Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">See all the action from the USA series of P1 AquaX, an exciting Jet Ski racing event, operated by Powerboat P1. P1 AquaX is an international motorboat racing competition organised by the Union Internationale Motornautique.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/38/1763103_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230504110500 +0200" stop="20230504113500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">UIM Class 1 Powerboat Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">Want to cool down? The Class 1 Offshore Championship featuring boats with twin inboard 1100hp engines that can reach speeds in excess of 160mph. All boats, which are around 12-14 meters long and 3.5 meters wide, are limited by a minimum weight of 4,950 kilos.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/54/1804798_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230504113500 +0200" stop="20230504120000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">P1 Offshore Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">The P1 Offshore Powerboat Championship promises tightly fought offshore racing with powerboats reaching top speeds of up to 100 miles per hour. Five events are schedules for the 2022 season and Motorvision.TV brings you all the thrilling action from each event!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/05/2038331_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230504120000 +0200" stop="20230504122500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Stunt Heroes (Salto mortale) S1 (n°2)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Salto mortale»The Stunt Heroes from Action Concept face a new mission: performing a front-flip through the air with a stuntman on board of an estate wagon. It's a new task for coordinator and adrenaline junkie Christoph &quot;Domi&quot; Domanski. Stuntmen Daniel and Lars display a brilliant fighting choreography in some spectacular driving scenes. Adrenaline-pumped stunts with lots of crashing are guaranteed!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/15/35/1790601_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230504122500 +0200" stop="20230504125000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Supercars S6</title>
<desc lang="fr">BMW M3 and Mercedes C63 AMG. The top models battle it out forever. While the C63 has better performance values on paper, the M3 has always been delivering the better performance. It's a never ending back and forth. But they are not alone in their battle for the crown. An exotic creature from Japan lies in wait: the Lexus RC-F. It's eight cylinders and 477 hp push the Japanese extrovert over asphalt. It's top speed: 270 km/h. Is he a threat to its German competitors?</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748406_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230504125000 +0200" stop="20230504132000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Classic Ride S5</title>
<desc lang="fr">Aston Martin usually triggers thoughts of James Bond and wickedly expensive and racy sports cars. But there's more to Aston Martin than that. The British luxury brand also offers sedans like the 1976 Aston Martin Lagonda Shooting Brake. But a solvent Aston fan wanted more so he turned its V8 sedan into to a station wagon. Classic Ride showcases the station wagon and further cars.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/24/2125716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230504132000 +0200" stop="20230504134500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 23</title>
<desc lang="fr">Street Racers is your backstage pass to the world of Formula E. Every two weeks, the magazine takes a look behind the scenes of the most important electric car racing series and provides reviews, current news, exciting interviews and gripping background reports from the world of Formula E.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/59/1880083_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230504134500 +0200" stop="20230504144000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Autodromo di Imola, Italy</title>
<desc lang="fr">The European Le Mans Series, a series open to Le Mans Prototypes and grand tourer-style racing cars, is back with another action-filled season. This year's calendar features six 4-hour races around Europe including the return of the 4 Hours of Imola.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/08/39/2182076_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230504144000 +0200" stop="20230504150500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Bike World</title>
<desc lang="fr">Bike World revolves around the speedway and the racers swishing by on their two wheelers. Find out the latest news and reports regarding two-wheel competitions in the world of speed. This is the content to enjoy for all motorcycle enthusiasts across the world. Explore the best motorbikes, top locations, and iconic racers who have a lot of fun doing it.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/32/1837877_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230504150500 +0200" stop="20230504153000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 4</title>
<desc lang="fr">Exciting sports show that follows the hottest action from the world's most unique motor sport events. Viewers will have a chance to visit some interesting competitions- from IDEMITSU 600 Super Endurance at the Chang Interna-tional Circuit in Thailand, the winter edition of the Maroc Challenge in Morocco, to the Hispania Rally, the only European rally to take place in the desert, and many more. Viewers will also find out all the news from the world of motor sports.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1760716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230504153000 +0200" stop="20230504160000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Perfect Ride S6</title>
<desc lang="fr">What's hot and what's not. There are quests to be undertaken, the search for the ideal auto, for the perfect race track for the ultimate accessory gadget. What are the preferred rides of the race legends?</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/09/2153087_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230504160000 +0200" stop="20230504163000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Supercars S6</title>
<desc lang="fr">There are details which set super cars apart from normal cars and these details are essential. Super cars are the biggest, loudest and most expensive cars on the highway; they're four-wheeled works of arts.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748406_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230504163000 +0200" stop="20230504170000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Electric Pickups</title>
<desc lang="fr">Pickups are the epitome of the american way of drive! High displacement V8 engines combined with plenty of space. Seldom seen in Europe, they are the cashcows of many automakers in the US market. In the future traditional manufacturers will hardly be able to avoid an electric versoin of their trucks. And the competition is getting bigger and bigger. Ever since Elon Musk presented the Tesla Cybertruck bothe the established brands and new startups had been on the advance to conquer the market with vehicles that have the equivalent of over 1000 hp. Ford F-150 Ligtning, Bollinger B2 or Hummer EV - Go Green shows what we can expect in the next few years.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1760716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230504170000 +0200" stop="20230504174500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Spotted</title>
<desc lang="fr">With its Model S, American carmaker Tesla wants to establish electric engines in the full size class. For the very first time it is possible to attain driving ranges over 400 kilometers. Its tremendous acceleration becomes an image boost for the brand. Porsche stands for lots of speed and horsepower, too. With its Panamera Sport Turismo, the sports car manufacturer taps into a new market.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/21/07/1884377_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230504174500 +0200" stop="20230504180000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Red Gold Dream</title>
<desc lang="fr">This years motto of the Conti Tuning Day is 'power sedans' and Tuning host Lucy examines the bolides carefully. Plus: The McLaren SLR is the masterpiece of Mercedes, a super sports car among all sports cars. Only 3.500 units have been produced. Tunings showcases the most expensive SLR in the world, which outshines all other SLR models.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1760716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230504180000 +0200" stop="20230504182500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Stunt Heroes (The Examination) S1 (n°4)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«The Examination»This is what it looks like when the Stunt Heroes from Action Concept perform a long jump: A vehicle jumps at full speed over four cars, which explode one after the other. It's a matter of precision and timing. Up-and-coming stuntwoman Tina has to prove, what she can do. It's a spectacular, action-packed stunt with guaranteed bruising!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/15/35/1790601_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230504182500 +0200" stop="20230504185000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Supercars S4</title>
<desc lang="fr">Jaguar is back in the world of sports cars. With the F-Type, the British manufacturer presents its first roadster since the E-Type. And it is not just good looking, but also displays an extraordinary performance. Supercars compares the F-Type with the BMW Z4. In addition to that, two further competitors of the Jaguar battle it out. It's Porsche Boxster S vs. Nissan 370 Z.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748406_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230504185000 +0200" stop="20230504191000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Classic Ride S3</title>
<desc lang="fr">The 1952 Cadillac Fleetwood is also known as the American Rolls-Royce, because it's the car of celebrities, presidents, millionaires and mafia bosses. Only around 16,000 units were built, so it's a treasured collector's piece. One owner of the 52 Cadillac is German-American actor and entertainer Ron Williams, who has a special relationship with the car.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/24/2125716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230504191000 +0200" stop="20230504194000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 25</title>
<desc lang="fr">Street Racers is your backstage pass to the world of Formula E. Every two weeks, the magazine takes a look behind the scenes of the most important electric car racing series and provides reviews, current news, exciting interviews and gripping background reports from the world of Formula E.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/59/1880083_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230504194000 +0200" stop="20230504203000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Circuit de Barcelona-Catalunya, Spain</title>
<desc lang="fr">The European Le Mans Series, a series open to Le Mans Prototypes and grand tourer-style racing cars, is back with another action-filled season. This year's calendar features six 4-hour races around Europe including the return of the 4 Hours of Imola.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/08/39/2182076_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230504203000 +0200" stop="20230504205500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">German Touring Championship 1995</title>
<desc lang="fr">Exciting, brutal and thrilling. The 1995 German Touring Car Championships. And with powerful races - also successful on the international stage. Mercedes driver Bernd Schneider dominated and won the title.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/24/2125717_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230504205500 +0200" stop="20230504212000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Jim Clark - The Flying Scotsman</title>
<desc lang="fr">Flying Scotsman.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/49/1774755_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230504212000 +0200" stop="20230504221500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Le Mans Classic</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Le Mans Classic is a vintage sports car event that took place for the first time in 2002 on the site of the 24-hour race of Le Mans. All participating drivers are at a top level as far as driving is concerned.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/20/2162901_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230504221500 +0200" stop="20230504224000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Classic Ride S3</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Mercedes 300SL might be the most exciting sports car of the post-war era. A panel of judges even named it the sports car of the century. Hans Kleissl from Polling near Munich owns one of the world's leading repair and restoration shops for SL models. Classic Ride accompanies him and his 300SL, originally owned by playboy Porfiro Rubirosa, to the Classic Days at Schloss Dyck.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/24/2125716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230504224000 +0200" stop="20230504233000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Chateau Impney Hill Climb</title>
<desc lang="fr">Motorsports has been taken place at the Château Impney near Droitwich Spa in Worcestershire, England since the 1950s. But no event was as big and successful as the Chateau Impney Hill Climb. Every year, the event attracts a wide array of vintage cars and more modern supercars. However, 2019 sees the last edition of the iconic Chateau Impney Hill Climb.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/25/1760725_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230504233000 +0200" stop="20230505000000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Manthey Racing</title>
<desc lang="fr">Racing in the Green Hell.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/40/1752403_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230505000000 +0200" stop="20230505003000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Stunt Heroes (Drift, fly &amp; fire) S1 (n°1)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Drift, fly &amp; fire»The Stunt Heroes from the German company â?oeAction Conceptâ? really let it rip. In the past they produced several award-winning stunts, but are always on the hunt for new spectacular scenes. This time stuntman Paul slides under an exploding vehicle. At the same time gangster bride Anna flies through the air.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/15/35/1790601_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230505003000 +0200" stop="20230505005500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Supercars S6</title>
<desc lang="fr">More than 10 years ago the 1,000 hp Bugatti Veyron started a new era of super sports cars. By now almost all renowned manufacturers offer their own supercar. Frequently, today's strongest and fastest cars rely on hybrid technology or even drive in pure electric mode. Supercars takes a look at the sports car of the future and gives an insight into the latest technology and driving systems of the future.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748406_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230505005500 +0200" stop="20230505011500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Classic Ride S1</title>
<desc lang="fr">Once a year Russian vintage fans meet at a spots stadium in Moscow Sports for the Retro Style, a vintage rally through Moscow. Classic Ride takes advantage of the opportunity to celebrate the passion for old cars with Russan drivers. Once ahead of its time, the Citroen SM is now a rare collector's item. Classic Rides takes a look at the French diva with an Italian heart.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/24/2125716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230505011500 +0200" stop="20230505014500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 22</title>
<desc lang="fr">Street Racers is your backstage pass to the world of Formula E. Every two weeks, the magazine takes a look behind the scenes of the most important electric car racing series and provides reviews, current news, exciting interviews and gripping background reports from the world of Formula E.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/59/1880083_A.jpg" />
</programme>