<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Voo -->
<programme start="20230425023000 +0200" stop="20230425025500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Drift : Championnat de France</title>
<desc lang="fr">When it comes to national drift competitions, the French Championship is one of the most important ones. 32 drivers compete in the spectacular main event.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1760716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230425025500 +0200" stop="20230425034000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">e-Trophée Andros</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Andros Trophy is the French national ice racing championship. The idea appeared long time ago in 1985 when professional racer Max Mamers and the owner of the Andros company, Frédéric Gervoson, met as rugby fans. They spent the winter racing with friends on ice circuits. In 2003 the trophy gained an international aspect with a race at Sherbrooke in Canada. In 2020, the racing series is repositioning itself as an electric racing series.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/43/1884375_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230425034000 +0200" stop="20230425043000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Hi-Tec Drift Allstars Series Australia</title>
<desc lang="fr">The latest drifting competition on Motorvision.TV brings you the best drifters from Australia. Join us for thrilling duels, smoking wheels and non-stop drift battles for the Drift All Stars Series title.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/59/1763095_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230425043000 +0200" stop="20230425052000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">National Legend Cars</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Legends Cars National Championship brings back racing from yesteryear. The series features 5/8 scale replicas of pre-war 1930s Fords, Chevys and Dodges that are equipped with 125bhp-motorcycle engines. These cars are well known for delivering high-octane battles on race tracks around Great Britain.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/59/1763095_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230425052000 +0200" stop="20230425060000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">AWD Safari Challenge</title>
<desc lang="fr">Every year, the British All Wheel Drive Club organises the AWDC Safari Championship, which has become the largest off-road event in the UK. Modified 4x4 vehicles of all brands can participate in the competition. Those who want to score points here must complete the challenging courses of mud, slush and scree in the shortest possible time.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/24/1760723_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230425060000 +0200" stop="20230425062500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Go Green! S3</title>
<desc lang="fr">The IAA in Frankfurt is the biggest motor show in the entire world. Every second year the automobile manufacturers display their newest models and reveal the innovations that they have been working on over the last couple of month. Environmental protection and alternative drive systems are two issues that become more and more important. Go Green presents the latest trends from the IAA.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748432_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230425062500 +0200" stop="20230425065000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Perfect Ride S6</title>
<desc lang="fr">Looking to find the balance between price and performance, Kia delivers good cars at fair prices. We'll be testing the Kia Stinger's for its everyday use in Munich's city center. Seat's sports sub-brand &quot;Cupra&quot; has brought the Ateca to the market, the cheapest performance SUV currently available. And a crossover-look for the city: the Fiat 500X is available for less than 18,000 Euros.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/09/2153087_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230425065000 +0200" stop="20230425071500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Top Ten Show S1</title>
<desc lang="fr">Which were the most expensive cars in days gone by? Which cars were the most ridiculous? And which vehicles are the most sporty? Nadira Tudor knows the answers!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/40/1752467_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230425071500 +0200" stop="20230425074000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 17</title>
<desc lang="fr">Street Racers is your backstage pass to the world of Formula E. Every two weeks, the magazine takes a look behind the scenes of the most important electric car racing series and provides reviews, current news, exciting interviews and gripping background reports from the world of Formula E.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/59/1880083_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230425074000 +0200" stop="20230425082500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">GT World Challenge America</title>
<desc lang="fr">Fanatec GT World Challenge America is the premier North American GT series. Taking place on the best US circuits form Sonoma to Indianapolis, each of the seven race weekends features 90-min double-header races.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/25/1760725_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230425082500 +0200" stop="20230425085500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">MXGP of Sardegna, Riola Sardo</title>
<desc lang="fr">Lap after lap of international motorsports action. This is coverage from the FIM (Fédération Internationale de Motocyclisme) Motocross World Championship where riders from all over the globe compete in high-octane, fast-paced motocross racing. Competitors battle it out in races lasting 35 minutes plus 2 laps per race.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/32/1907968_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230425085500 +0200" stop="20230425092000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Grand Prix of France, Nice, Palais Nikaia</title>
<desc lang="fr">FIM SuperEnduro World Championship has been held since 2007. Its circuits are built inside stadiums or arenas, recreating obstacles such as rocks, boulders and logs. The championship consists of eight Grands Prix spread around the globe on courses that are mostly off-road. These events are split into two days and two different races, after which the points towards the world championship are awarded. Each round includes a motocross test and an extreme test, in addition to the enduro test.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/22/1748447_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230425092000 +0200" stop="20230425101000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Australian Motocross Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Australian ProMX Championship is the nation's premier motocross championship. The series acts as a successful development platform for young Australian talent and is designed as a tiered system with three dedicated classes: MX3 for younger drivers, the MX2 for senior drivers and the MX1, which is the elite category in the championship.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1765320_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230425101000 +0200" stop="20230425110000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Grand Prix of Austria, Wiener Neustadt</title>
<desc lang="fr">FIM X-Trial World Championship is the most prestigious indoor motorcycle trials tournament of the world, organised by the Fédération Internationale de Motocyclisme. The programme presents the highlights of the rounds where the participants have to take on the challenging tracks full of steep climbs and huge rocks.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/13/2162902_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230425110000 +0200" stop="20230425120000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Australian Superbike Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">Founded in 1980, the Australian Superbike Championship is one of the most important motorcycle racing competitions in Oceania. It is well respected as a springboard for riders and teams who aspire an international career in motorcycling. The 2022 season is contested in five classes: Superbike, Supersport, Supersport 300, the Yamaha R3 Cup and the Oceania Junior Cup.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/48/1853102_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230425120000 +0200" stop="20230425125000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">BTRDA Rallycross Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">Being a mixture of circuit racing and rallying, rallycross is often considered to be the wildchild of motor sports. One of the most exciting competitions in this genre is the BTRDA Rallycross Championship. Motorvision.TV brings you the highlights from each of their events.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/25/1760725_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230425125000 +0200" stop="20230425134000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Ferrari Challenge Europe</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Ferrari Challenge Europe is back for another season on Motorvision.TV. The longest-running single-make series championship in the history of the Prancing Horse-company promises high performance and talented drivers on challenging tracks around Europe. Seven events are scheduled for the 2022 season including the Finali Mondiali, which brings together the final stages of all Ferrari Challenge divisions around the world.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/25/55/2162175_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230425134000 +0200" stop="20230425142000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">GP Belgium, Circuit Zolder</title>
<desc lang="fr">NASCAR, America's most popular racing series, is now well established in Europe and there is no better proof than its European division: the NASCAR Whelen Euro Series. This year, 17 teams from nine different countries with a total of 39 cars prove once again that the NWES with its pure racing character is one of the best touring car series on the old continent. Motorvision.TV shows highlights from every race weekend.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748423_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230425142000 +0200" stop="20230425151500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Asian Le Mans Series</title>
<desc lang="fr">Asian sports car racing endurance series created by the Automobile Club de l'Ouest and based in Asia aims to attract teams and drivers from Asian countries. The Asian Le Mans Series is the symbol of the Spirit of Le Mans, and holds the same passion for creating world class endurance racing.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/20/00/2125604_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230425151500 +0200" stop="20230425160000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">WeatherTech SportsCar Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">Catch the action from the sports car racing series organized by the International Motor Sports Association. It is America's premier sports car racing series where almost all premium manufacturers are represented. This includes companies such as Acura, Aston Martin, Audi, BMW, Cadillac, Chevrolet, Ferrari, Honda, Lamborghini, Lexus, Mazda, Mercedes-AMG and Porsche.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/40/1752403_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230425160000 +0200" stop="20230425164500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Southern Races Part 1</title>
<desc lang="fr">King of the Roads.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1763086_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230425164500 +0200" stop="20230425173500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Silverstone</title>
<desc lang="fr">Aucune description</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/23/1869858_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230425173500 +0200" stop="20230425180000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">CM.com Circuit Zandvoort, Netherlands</title>
<desc lang="fr">League of super sports cars.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/59/1884373_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230425180000 +0200" stop="20230425182500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Go Green! S3</title>
<desc lang="fr">Electric cars of the future don't need to be charged for hours. Instead they tank up &quot;&quot;&quot;&quot;liquid power&quot;&quot;&quot;&quot; at the gas pump - or more precisely: they tank up electrolytes. And this takes only a few minutes. So-called flow cell batteries might be the most important improvement in the field of electric vehicles. Also on this episode of Go Green: How the cars of the future can drive without a driver.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748432_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230425182500 +0200" stop="20230425185000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Perfect Ride S6</title>
<desc lang="fr">Station wagons on a Formula 1 racetrack: Porsche has packed a ton of power into their Panamera with the turbocharged four liter V8 engine. We're taking the Sport Turismo out onto the F1 track in Bahrain. BMW has redesigned its 530i Touring. Can you get a hallelujah moment driving the new four-cylinder? And: We're heading on an expedition to Cologne with the Volvo V60.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/09/2153087_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230425185000 +0200" stop="20230425191500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Top Ten Show S1</title>
<desc lang="fr">Imagine yiou are on the motorway and suddenly, without warning, another car swerves into your lane and you have to slam on the brakes. Usually, stepping on the brakes will avoid a collision. But with the cars on this episode of our Top Ten Show, you might not be so lucky. We'll present you the ten cars with the longest braking distance.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/50/1752909_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230425191500 +0200" stop="20230425194000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 13</title>
<desc lang="fr">Street Racers is your backstage pass to the world of Formula E. Every two weeks, the magazine takes a look behind the scenes of the most important electric car racing series and provides reviews, current news, exciting interviews and gripping background reports from the world of Formula E.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/59/1880083_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230425194000 +0200" stop="20230425202500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">GT World Challenge America</title>
<desc lang="fr">Fanatec GT World Challenge America is the premier North American GT series. Taking place on the best US circuits form Sonoma to Indianapolis, each of the seven race weekends features 90-min double-header races.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1760716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230425202500 +0200" stop="20230425205500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Dream Cars S2</title>
<desc lang="fr">They are wild, they are busrting with power and they are cult, the American Muscle Cars. Whether it is the Ford Mustang, the Chevrolet Camaro or the Corvette, Muscle Cars are coveted all over the world because of their rebellious design, impeteous horsepower and their stunning speed. Dream Cars presents the most spectacular and fastest US-Sport- and Musclecars.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/50/1752909_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230425205500 +0200" stop="20230425212000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 5</title>
<desc lang="fr">Exciting sports show that follows the hottest action from the world's most unique motor sport events. Viewers will have a chance to visit some interesting competitions- from IDEMITSU 600 Super Endurance at the Chang Interna-tional Circuit in Thailand, the winter edition of the Maroc Challenge in Morocco, to the Hispania Rally, the only European rally to take place in the desert, and many more. Viewers will also find out all the news from the world of motor sports.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1760716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230425212000 +0200" stop="20230425214500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Bike World</title>
<desc lang="fr">Bike World is the magazine on MOTORVISION TV for all fans of the lifestyle on two wheels. Whether on the road, off-road or on the race track: Bike World brings the latest trends from the world of motorcycles into living rooms around the world. Watch the latest tests of new two-wheelers, exciting reports from the hottest events and thrilling insights into superbike racing.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/32/1837877_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230425214500 +0200" stop="20230425221000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Perfect Ride S6</title>
<desc lang="fr">What's hot and what's not. There are quests to be undertaken, the search for the ideal auto, for the perfect race track for the ultimate accessory gadget. What are the preferred rides of the race legends?</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/09/2153087_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230425221000 +0200" stop="20230425223500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Supercars</title>
<desc lang="fr">A synergy of high-octane power, speed, luxury and prestige. Supercars features some of the most desirable automobiles in the world, whether it be an agile sports car to a comfortable limousine. It features the likes of prestige brands filled with rich heritage and motorsport pedigree; such as Bentley, BMW M, Mercedes AMG, Aston Martin, Maserati, Porsche and Ferrari to niche-market, lightweight Lotuses, KTMs and Caterhams. Supercars has everything a petrolhead needs to get up to speed on the latest and greatest of high-performance road machines.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748406_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230425223500 +0200" stop="20230425231500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Spotted</title>
<desc lang="fr">They are extremely loud, extremely fast and extremely honed: the compact cars Mercedes A45 AMG Performmaster and MTM Audi RS3 R. Ferrari and Rolls-Royce, two of the world's most famous car brands, don't need any tuning. MOTORVISION TV - #SPOTTED explains the myth of Ferrari and takes a look behind the scenes of the Rolls Royce Bespoke production.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/21/07/1884377_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230425231500 +0200" stop="20230425234500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Offroad Legends</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Land Rover Defender makes the hearts of offraod fans leap since over 70 years. Can the modern Landy follow in the footsteps of the old icon? And: How does offroad driving work exactly? We let an offroad beginner onto rough grounds.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/00/2125714_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230425234500 +0200" stop="20230426000000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 4</title>
<desc lang="fr">When their ambitions exceed their driving skills, when well-secured racing professionals are thrown out of corners, we always have a camera at hand. Breathtaking stunts by professional drivers and slapstick-action in highly-tuned tin can rockets. Spectacular scenes where nobody gets hurt.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/31/00/1748416_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230426000000 +0200" stop="20230426002500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Go Green! S3</title>
<desc lang="fr">Flowing lines, unusual proportions and movements inspired by natural forms: Japanese car manufacturers give their vehicles a striking design and innovative technology. We take a look at the Nissan Resonance and concept cars from Infiniti. Plus: The Toyota i-Road and the IMA Colibri are two absolutely extraordinary cars that might revolutionize mobility in cities.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748432_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230426002500 +0200" stop="20230426005500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Perfect Ride S1</title>
<desc lang="fr">Today's Perfect Ride episode is all about power and torque: Perfect, faster, further - racer Dennis Rostek drives it to the top. With Mathilda Racing on the Nurburgring Nordschleife.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/19/1748438_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230426005500 +0200" stop="20230426011500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Top Ten Show S1</title>
<desc lang="fr">These days everyone talks is how we can make cars more fuel efficient and more environmentally friendly. Electro- cars, hybrid cars, 1 litre-engine cars and 3 cylinder cars, all seem to be the craze at the moment. But we are going to turn all of this on its head and have a look at ten cars that suffer from dreadful fuel consumption.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/40/1752467_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230426011500 +0200" stop="20230426014000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 2</title>
<desc lang="fr">Street Racers is your backstage pass to the world of Formula E. Every two weeks, the magazine takes a look behind the scenes of the most important electric car racing series and provides reviews, current news, exciting interviews and gripping background reports from the world of Formula E.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/59/1880083_A.jpg" />
</programme>