<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Voo -->
<programme start="20230529023500 +0200" stop="20230529030000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">The Rallye World Championship 1982</title>
<desc lang="fr">The African continent is always a difficult terrain for rally drivers. That wasn't any different for the 1982 World Rally Championship, when heat, dust, mud and hardly passable routes posed major challenges for drivers, co-drivers and engines.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/20/04/2125717_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230529030000 +0200" stop="20230529033000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Legendary Tracks - Brooklands, Monthlery, Avus</title>
<desc lang="fr">Mountain races, rallies and city races: In the early days of motorsport, races were held on existing roads and off-roads. After a series of serious accidents, organizers began to build their own circuits for their events. Today tracks like the Silverstone Circuit, Monza or the Indianapolis Motor Speedway are a Mecca for all racing enthusiasts. MOTORVISION TV looks into the racing files of the world's most legendary racetracks and tells their story.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/49/1774755_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230529033000 +0200" stop="20230529035500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Rallye Monte Carlo Historique</title>
<desc lang="fr">The infamous Monte-Carlo Rally is one of the world's oldest rally events in the world. To pay tribute to its long-lasting history, the Automobile Club de Monaco organizes the Rallye Monte-Carlo Historique. The catch is: Only cars that competed in the Monte-Carlo Rally at least 40 years ago are allowed to take part in the historic edition of the Monte-Carlo Rally.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/37/1760720_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230529035500 +0200" stop="20230529042000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Classic Ride S3</title>
<desc lang="fr">It is one of the most spectacular cars of the last 30 years: the Delorean DMC-12. But after 9000 built cars, the production came to an end in 1982.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/24/2125716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230529042000 +0200" stop="20230529045500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Rally Clasico Mallorca</title>
<desc lang="fr">Motorvision.TV shows the best moments from the 2022 eMallorca Challenge.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/34/1762751_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230529045500 +0200" stop="20230529054500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Chateau Impney Hill Climb</title>
<desc lang="fr">Motorsports has been taken place at the Château Impney near Droitwich Spa in Worcestershire, England since the 1950s. But no event was as big and successful as the Chateau Impney Hill Climb. Every year, the event attracts a wide array of vintage cars and more modern supercars. However, 2019 sees the last edition of the iconic Chateau Impney Hill Climb.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/40/1752403_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230529054500 +0200" stop="20230529060000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 6</title>
<desc lang="fr">When their ambitions exceed their driving skills, when well-secured racing professionals are thrown out of corners, we always have a camera at hand. Breathtaking stunts by professional drivers and slapstick-action in highly-tuned tin can rockets. Spectacular scenes where nobody gets hurt.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/31/00/1748416_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230529060000 +0200" stop="20230529065000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">British Truck Racing</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Brisith Truck Racing Championship features some of the heaviest racing machines you'll ever see. Each truck weighs more than five tonnes and produces in excess of 1000bhp. The 2022 season features a total of 7 events that are contested around the United Kingdom.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/25/1760725_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230529065000 +0200" stop="20230529074500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">DTM</title>
<desc lang="fr">The DTM - Deutsche Tourenwagen Masters - is the premier German touring car championship. In 2022, the competition is in its 23rd season and features 16 races across 8 weekends. Motorvision.TV shows the best bits from each event.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/25/2125719_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230529074500 +0200" stop="20230529083500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Ferrari Challenge Europe</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Ferrari Challenge is a single-marque motorsport championship that was created in 1993 and is now the longest-running single-make series championship. The European series is a two-class championship and by far the largest series. It contains 7 races, held on challenging and most prestigious European circuits.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/25/55/2162175_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230529083500 +0200" stop="20230529092000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">GT World Challenge Europe Sprint Cup</title>
<desc lang="fr">Join Motorvision TV as it brings you all the action from the European sports car racing series.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/25/1760725_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230529092000 +0200" stop="20230529101000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">WeatherTech SportsCar Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">The IMSA WeatherTech SportsCar Championhip is an endurance racing championship in North America where up to five different classes compete in eleven events.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1760716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230529101000 +0200" stop="20230529105500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">GT World Challenge America</title>
<desc lang="fr">It's America's most challenging and scenic circuits. GT World Challenge America offers exclusive GT3 racing in an exciting way with the two-driver, 90-minute SprintX style format with full-service pit stops that provide great racing and high competition. Each event features two races per weekend in a friendly atmosphere. Many manufacturers including Acura, BMW, Bentley, Ferrari, Lamborghini, Mercedes-AMG, Nissan, and Porsche campaign entries in the category.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/59/1763095_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230529105500 +0200" stop="20230529114000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">GT World Challenge Europe Brands Hatch</title>
<desc lang="fr">GT World Challenge Europe arrives at Brands Hatch, showcasing cars from the biggest manufacturers, the likes of Audi, Porsche, Ferrari, and more. View the latest action, updates, and stats from the event!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/40/1752403_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230529114000 +0200" stop="20230529120000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Championnat d'Europe de courses de camions</title>
<desc lang="fr">The FIA European Truck Racing Championship is the biggest, most imposing racing series in the world. The racing trucks are equipped with 1200 hp engines doing up to 100 miles per hour. On a grid with 26 big rigs the 5.5-ton machines doing battle there's guaranteed action-packed lights-to-flag racing galore.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/25/00/1748421_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230529120000 +0200" stop="20230529122500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Stunt Heroes (The Remote Control) S1 (n°3)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«The Remote Control»The Stunt Heroes from Action Concept try out another new stunt: Stuntman Tobi, aka Heidi, operates an Artega GT at full speed with a remote control. This is, however, just a warm-up before the big stunt, in which he drives a car up a steep ramp at 68 mph. The Question is: How high can remote control cars fly? It's an action-packed flying spectacle!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Découverte</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/15/35/1790601_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230529122500 +0200" stop="20230529125500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Supercars S2</title>
<desc lang="fr">The evolutionary history of the Infinity FX50, Sebastian Vettel Edition. 1.370 Kg and 620 horsepower - this is the Porsche GT2 RS. This car is the most expensive and fastest serial 911 Porsche all times.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748406_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230529125500 +0200" stop="20230529132000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Classic Ride S3</title>
<desc lang="fr">It is sexy, spectacular and comes with tremendous speed: the Audi Sport quattro S1, the most exciting rally car ever built. In part 2 of the S1 special, Classic Rides accompanies S1 pilot Michael Gerber during the second day of the Rally Legend. Plus: The whole story of the S1 told with original comments by former world champion Walter Röhrl.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/24/2125716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230529132000 +0200" stop="20230529134500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Formula E - Specials</title>
<desc lang="fr">In less than six years the ABB FIA Formula E Championship has grown from ambitious start-up to one of the most innovative sports entertainment properties in the world, attracting a host of the globe's biggest automotive manufacturers. The Story Of Formula E plots the extraordinary rise of the all-electric championship with some of the key players including Lucas Di Grassi, Jean Eric Vergne, Sebastien Buemi, Sam Bird and founder Alejandro Agag.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/12/06/2195752_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230529134500 +0200" stop="20230529143500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">WeatherTech SportsCar Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">The IMSA Weathertech Sportscar Championship is back on MOTORVISION TV. Twelve races are again scheduled for the 2022 season, including four endurance classics. Motorvision TV provides live and extensive highlights coverage of all events.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/59/1763095_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230529143500 +0200" stop="20230529150000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Championnat de Belgique des Rallyes</title>
<desc lang="fr">BRC.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/20/02/2149178_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230529150000 +0200" stop="20230529152500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Rally Regione Piemonte, Italy</title>
<desc lang="fr">Amazing challenge around Europe includes 19 special stages. The top crew will become Tour European Rally champion in one of the most beautiful European rallies.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/24/1760723_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230529152500 +0200" stop="20230529155000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Morocco Desert Challenge</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Morocco Desert Challenge has been the fastest growing rallies in the Sahara since its creation in 2008. Until May 2016 the event was called &quot;the Libya Rally&quot; because its origins were in Libya. As a result of the war in 2011 the Khadafi regime came to an end but it is still impossible to host a large international sports event in Libya. In 2013 the rally was moved to Morocco, and thanks to a huge variety of landscapes and tracks it was a success.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/06/11/2193719_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230529155000 +0200" stop="20230529161500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Morocco Desert Challenge</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Morocco Desert Challenge has been the fastest growing rallies in the Sahara since its creation in 2008. Until May 2016 the event was called &quot;the Libya Rally&quot; because its origins were in Libya. As a result of the war in 2011 the Khadafi regime came to an end but it is still impossible to host a large international sports event in Libya. In 2013 the rally was moved to Morocco, and thanks to a huge variety of landscapes and tracks it was a success.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/06/11/2193719_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230529161500 +0200" stop="20230529164000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 2</title>
<desc lang="fr">Aucune description</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/48/2123747_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230529164000 +0200" stop="20230529173000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">BTRDA Rallycross Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">Aucune description</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/40/1752403_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230529173000 +0200" stop="20230529180000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Kaiafas Battle 2022</title>
<desc lang="fr">Aucune description</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/03/2034343_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230529180000 +0200" stop="20230529182500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Stunt Heroes (Body Stunt Highlights) S2 (n°14)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Body Stunt Highlights»Today it's Action Concepts most popular and most spectacular body stunts: Jumping from rooftops, falling of a driving car, tumbling down stairs. Despite inevitable wounds, the legendary stunt crew enjoys the job.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Découverte</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/15/35/1790601_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230529182500 +0200" stop="20230529184500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Supercars S2</title>
<desc lang="fr">What a car! It looks like it's been made in a futuristic factory. From a world beyond our recognition. It's fast and extremely powerful. It's unique!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748406_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230529184500 +0200" stop="20230529191500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Classic Ride S6</title>
<desc lang="fr">In 2013 the great Henry Ford would have turned 150 years old. The successful entrepreneur from the United States is best known for introducing the assembly line and mass production of automobiles. Classic Ride pays tribute to Henry Ford and three models that can be considered an important part of his sporting heritage: Ford Thunderbird (1955), Ford Mustang (1964) and Ford Capri (1968).</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/24/2125716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230529191500 +0200" stop="20230529194000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Formula E - Specials</title>
<desc lang="fr">In less than six years the ABB FIA Formula E Championship has grown from ambitious start-up to one of the most innovative sports entertainment properties in the world, attracting a host of the globe's biggest automotive manufacturers. The Story Of Formula E plots the extraordinary rise of the all-electric championship with some of the key players including Lucas Di Grassi, Jean Eric Vergne, Sebastien Buemi, Sam Bird and founder Alejandro Agag.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/12/06/2195752_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230529194000 +0200" stop="20230529203000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">WeatherTech SportsCar Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">The IMSA Weathertech Sportscar Championship is back on MOTORVISION TV. Twelve races are again scheduled for the 2022 season, including four endurance classics. Motorvision TV provides live and extensive highlights coverage of all events.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1760716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230529203000 +0200" stop="20230529205500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">MXGP of Portugal, Agueda</title>
<desc lang="fr">Lap after lap of international motorsports action. This is coverage from the FIM (Fédération Internationale de Motocyclisme) Motocross World Championship where riders from all over the globe compete in high-octane, fast-paced motocross racing. Competitors battle it out in races lasting 35 minutes plus 2 laps per race.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/20/00/1907968_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230529205500 +0200" stop="20230529212000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Grand Prix of Poland, Krakow, Tauron Arena</title>
<desc lang="fr">FIM SuperEnduro World Championship has been held since 2007. Its circuits are built inside stadiums or arenas, recreating obstacles such as rocks, boulders and logs. The championship consists of eight Grands Prix spread around the globe on courses that are mostly off-road. These events are split into two days and two different races, after which the points towards the world championship are awarded. Each round includes a motocross test and an extreme test, in addition to the enduro test.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/22/1748447_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230529212000 +0200" stop="20230529221000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Australian Motocross Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Australian ProMX Championship is the nation's premier motocross championship. The series acts as a successful development platform for young Australian talent and is designed as a tiered system with three dedicated classes: MX3 for younger drivers, the MX2 for senior drivers and the MX1, which is the elite category in the championship.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/31/43/1763097_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230529221000 +0200" stop="20230529230500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Grand Prix of Andorra</title>
<desc lang="fr">FIM X-Trial World Championship is the most prestigious indoor motorcycle trials tournament of the world, organised by the Fédération Internationale de Motocyclisme. The programme presents the highlights of the rounds where the participants have to take on the challenging tracks full of steep climbs and huge rocks.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/13/2162902_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230529230500 +0200" stop="20230530000000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Australian Superbike Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">Welcome to the national motorcycle racing championship in Australia, organised by Motorcycling Australia. Get all the action and cutting edge stories, reports and results.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1763086_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230530000000 +0200" stop="20230530002500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Stunt Heroes (Action Special) S3 (n°33)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Action Special»&quot;Stunt Heroes&quot; of MotorvisionTV is giving answers to those questions. The stuntteam of &quot;&quot;action concept&quot;&quot;, one of the biggest film- and stunt productions in Europe is given a spectacular insight to their daily business. Things that are never seen in the movies. Often enough they are working several days or weeks for a five-second-stunt! A tough job! The action-special shows all stunts of the second season of the show, explains differences between the different kinds of tools they got in their arsenal. &quot;Stunt Heroes&quot;.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Découverte</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/15/35/1790601_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230530002500 +0200" stop="20230530005000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Supercars S5</title>
<desc lang="fr">Most people associate Aston Martin with James Bond, luxury, style and elegance or real men. The Vantage N430 is a sports car that makes you feel the heritage of British racecars. It is elegant, fast, comes with a marvelous sound and a design which reminds you of Aston Martin's racing successes from the past. Also on this episode: Supercars checks out the Bentley GTC Speed.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748406_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230530005000 +0200" stop="20230530011500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Classic Ride S2</title>
<desc lang="fr">It looks like a Ferrari but it comes from Bavaria, Germany: The Glas GT, one of the rarest oldtimers in the world!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/24/2125716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230530011500 +0200" stop="20230530014000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Formula E - Specials</title>
<desc lang="fr">In less than six years the ABB FIA Formula E Championship has grown from ambitious start-up to one of the most innovative sports entertainment properties in the world, attracting a host of the globe's biggest automotive manufacturers. The Story Of Formula E plots the extraordinary rise of the all-electric championship with some of the key players including Lucas Di Grassi, Jean Eric Vergne, Sebastien Buemi, Sam Bird and founder Alejandro Agag.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/10/08/2194935_A.jpg" />
</programme>