<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Voo -->
<programme start="20230524023500 +0200" stop="20230524030000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Championnat de Belgique des Rallyes</title>
<desc lang="fr">BRC.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/21/2149178_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524030000 +0200" stop="20230524032500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Rally Regione Piemonte, Italy</title>
<desc lang="fr">Amazing challenge around Europe includes 19 special stages. The top crew will become Tour European Rally champion in one of the most beautiful European rallies.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/48/2123747_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524032500 +0200" stop="20230524035500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Morocco Desert Challenge</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Morocco Desert Challenge has been the fastest growing rallies in the Sahara since its creation in 2008. Until May 2016 the event was called &quot;the Libya Rally&quot; because its origins were in Libya. As a result of the war in 2011 the Khadafi regime came to an end but it is still impossible to host a large international sports event in Libya. In 2013 the rally was moved to Morocco, and thanks to a huge variety of landscapes and tracks it was a success.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/06/11/2193719_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524035500 +0200" stop="20230524044500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Middle East Bajas World Cup</title>
<desc lang="fr">Aucune description</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/50/1756288_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524044500 +0200" stop="20230524053500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">BTRDA Rallycross Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">Aucune description</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1760716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524053500 +0200" stop="20230524060000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 2</title>
<desc lang="fr">Aucune description</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/24/1760723_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524060000 +0200" stop="20230524062500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Stunt Heroes (Revenge) S3 (n°30)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Revenge»The Stunt Heroes are testing for a big movie. They are filming a car crash and the idea is that it should look like if the main character of the movie, the actor is really driving the car. They are using filmtricks and a self constructed airbag to reach their goal. The documentary shows how the stunt people create that kind of stunt.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Découverte</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/15/35/1790601_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524062500 +0200" stop="20230524065000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Supercars S5</title>
<desc lang="fr">He is one of the most exciting sportscars in the world: the Ferrari 458 Speciale. A screaming racecar for the street, a car that puts your nervs on permanent fire. To drive this rolling thunder is unforgetable. Also in this show. The Mc Laren 650S, a car as fast as the Ferrari but quiet more on the technical than on the emotional side.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748406_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524065000 +0200" stop="20230524071500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Classic Ride S5</title>
<desc lang="fr">Classic Ride takes a trip around the world to visit some of the most fascinating vintage cars ever built. In Thailand a gull-winged Mercedes 190 SL and other souped-up classic cars take part in the Bangkok Classic Car Ride. Plus: An Oldsmobile convertible travels on Venezuela's most beautiful island, while oldies from the US like a 1952 Chevrolet Styleline become a tourist attraction in Cuba.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/24/2125716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524071500 +0200" stop="20230524074000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Formula E - Specials</title>
<desc lang="fr">ABB FIA Formula E the Number 1s, a look back over all the races to find the most amazing moments in Formula E's history. We pick the Number 1 moment in ten categories looking at amazing action from overtakes, close shaves, starts, and incidents, through the best driver reactions, FanBoosts and Attack Modes, to innovations and insights, and finally we pick out the best race so far.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/10/08/2194935_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524074000 +0200" stop="20230524083500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Grand Prix of France, Chalon Sur Saone</title>
<desc lang="fr">X-Trial is a young and dynamic sport. The events take place in arenas and the spectators are up close during the entire period. Spectacular setups with challenging obstacles combined with the skill of the best riders in the world promise great entertainment. Motorvision.TV shows highlights from all six events of the 2022 season.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/13/2162902_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524083500 +0200" stop="20230524090000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Bike World</title>
<desc lang="fr">Bike World revolves around the speedway and the racers swishing by on their two wheelers. Find out the latest news and reports regarding two-wheel competitions in the world of speed. This is the content to enjoy for all motorcycle enthusiasts across the world. Explore the best motorbikes, top locations, and iconic racers who have a lot of fun doing it.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/32/1837877_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524090000 +0200" stop="20230524092500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 3</title>
<desc lang="fr">Exciting sports show that follows the hottest action from the world's most unique motor sport events. Viewers will have a chance to visit some interesting competitions- from IDEMITSU 600 Super Endurance at the Chang Interna-tional Circuit in Thailand, the winter edition of the Maroc Challenge in Morocco, to the Hispania Rally, the only European rally to take place in the desert, and many more. Viewers will also find out all the news from the world of motor sports.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/40/1752403_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524092500 +0200" stop="20230524095500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Perfect Ride S6</title>
<desc lang="fr">What's hot and what's not. There are quests to be undertaken, the search for the ideal auto, for the perfect race track for the ultimate accessory gadget. What are the preferred rides of the race legends?</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/09/2153087_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524095500 +0200" stop="20230524102000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Supercars</title>
<desc lang="fr">A synergy of high-octane power, speed, luxury and prestige. Supercars features some of the most desirable automobiles in the world, whether it be an agile sports car to a comfortable limousine. It features the likes of prestige brands filled with rich heritage and motorsport pedigree; such as Bentley, BMW M, Mercedes AMG, Aston Martin, Maserati, Porsche and Ferrari to niche-market, lightweight Lotuses, KTMs and Caterhams. Supercars has everything a petrolhead needs to get up to speed on the latest and greatest of high-performance road machines.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748406_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524102000 +0200" stop="20230524104500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Go Green!</title>
<desc lang="fr">Energy saving is becoming a more and more important goal for the world's leading car manufacturers. Motorvision TV explores the environment-friendly solutions emerging in the car industry. presenting the latest ideas from research and development teams. Find out what are the best ways to go green when it comes to your vehicle.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748432_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524104500 +0200" stop="20230524113000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Spotted</title>
<desc lang="fr">When car spotters find rare cars it's like winning the lottery. One of the most exclusive cars in the world is the Paguani Huayra, which was built just 20 times. Its counterpart: the Rimac Concept One, which writes history as the world's fastest electric car with a top speed of 355 kmph. Lamborghini Huracan O.CT and Arden Jaguar F-Type promise brutal tuning power beyond good and evil.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/21/07/1884377_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524113000 +0200" stop="20230524120000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Trackmasters</title>
<desc lang="fr">Patrick makes André sweat! Also on the show tourists from all over the world have made their way down to the Green Hell including many Germans, Austrians and 5 crazy Englishmen in a taxi!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/25/59/1986723_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524120000 +0200" stop="20230524122500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Stunt Heroes (Motorbike Launch) S3 (n°29)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Motorbike Launch»A new test by the stunt people of Action Concept. They have to show a spectacular flight with a motobike, which is crashing afterwards. But that would be too dangerous for a stuntman. Stunt coordinator Ramazan Bulut hast to be creative. The guys develop a cannon for the motorbike. Will it have enough pressure to shoot the bike? The result is very impressive. Even the hard headed stunt guys are surprised!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Découverte</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/15/35/1790601_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524122500 +0200" stop="20230524125000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Supercars S5</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Porsche Panamera Turbo S is the most dynamic sedan in the world. No other car finds the perfect balance between calm gliding on the one hand and extreme performance on the other hand. 570 hp, 3,8 seconds from zero to 100 km/h and a top speed of 310 km/h are impressive performance data for this big car. Plus: the Jaguar XJR with a 550 hp V8 engine and the Mercedes CLS 500.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748406_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524125000 +0200" stop="20230524131000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Classic Ride S3</title>
<desc lang="fr">In the early 70s it was the fastest and most sportive production sports car in Germany: The Porsche Carrera RS. Today the RS is a classic Porsche with the highest acclaim.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/24/2125716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524131000 +0200" stop="20230524134000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Formula E - Specials</title>
<desc lang="fr">ABB FIA Formula E the Number 1s, a look back over all the races to find the most amazing moments in Formula E's history. We pick the Number 1 moment in ten categories looking at amazing action from overtakes, close shaves, starts, and incidents, through the best driver reactions, FanBoosts and Attack Modes, to innovations and insights, and finally we pick out the best race so far.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/09/40/1997864_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524134000 +0200" stop="20230524143500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Grand Prix of France, Nice</title>
<desc lang="fr">X-Trial is a young and dynamic sport. The events take place in arenas and the spectators are up close during the entire period. Spectacular setups with challenging obstacles combined with the skill of the best riders in the world promise great entertainment. Motorvision.TV shows highlights from all six events of the 2022 season.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/13/2162902_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524143500 +0200" stop="20230524150000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">MXGP of Trentino, Pietramurata</title>
<desc lang="fr">Lap after lap of international motorsports action. This is coverage from the FIM (Fédération Internationale de Motocyclisme) Motocross World Championship where riders from all over the globe compete in high-octane, fast-paced motocross racing. Competitors battle it out in races lasting 35 minutes plus 2 laps per race.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/32/1907968_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524150000 +0200" stop="20230524152500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Grand Prix of Poland, Gliwice</title>
<desc lang="fr">FIM SuperEnduro World Championship has been held since 2007. Its circuits are built inside stadiums or arenas, recreating obstacles such as rocks, boulders and logs. The championship consists of eight Grands Prix spread around the globe on courses that are mostly off-road. These events are split into two days and two different races, after which the points towards the world championship are awarded. Each round includes a motocross test and an extreme test, in addition to the enduro test.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/22/1748447_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524152500 +0200" stop="20230524161500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Australian Motocross Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Australian ProMX Championship is the nation's premier motocross championship. The series acts as a successful development platform for young Australian talent and is designed as a tiered system with three dedicated classes: MX3 for younger drivers, the MX2 for senior drivers and the MX1, which is the elite category in the championship.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/07/2125726_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524161500 +0200" stop="20230524171000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Grand Prix of France, Bordeaux</title>
<desc lang="fr">FIM X-Trial World Championship is the most prestigious indoor motorcycle trials tournament of the world, organised by the Fédération Internationale de Motocyclisme. The programme presents the highlights of the rounds where the participants have to take on the challenging tracks full of steep climbs and huge rocks.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/13/2162902_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524171000 +0200" stop="20230524180000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Victoria</title>
<desc lang="fr">Aucune description</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/15/12/2185021_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524180000 +0200" stop="20230524182000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Stunt Heroes (Stunt Highlights) S3 (n°31)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Stunt Highlights»Explosions - accidents - pain - stunt coordinator Domi and his team give everything for spectacular stunts - in each episodes they are pushing the limits.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Découverte</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/15/35/1790601_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524182000 +0200" stop="20230524184500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Supercars S5</title>
<desc lang="fr">Luxury does not necesseraly mean to waste time. Hybrid is one of the techniques wich promises less fuel consumption with a still powerful engine. Lexus ist the pioneer in electrification of cars. Supercars drives the new LS 600h, The BMW Actiev Hybrid 7 and teh Porsche Panamera S E-Hybrid.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748406_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524184500 +0200" stop="20230524191000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Classic Ride S3</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Amphicar 770 is a rare classic. Its special attraction is that you drive motorboat on the road. It may not be the fastest car on the street, but it's ready to be used on the water as well. Thus careful maintenance and continuous checks are a must. If something leaks, the Amphicar will sink like a stone. Classic Ride meets Richard Orthuber who owns an Amphicar 770.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/24/2125716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524191000 +0200" stop="20230524193500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Formula E - Specials</title>
<desc lang="fr">ABB FIA Formula E the Number 1s, a look back over all the races to find the most amazing moments in Formula E's history. We pick the Number 1 moment in ten categories looking at amazing action from overtakes, close shaves, starts, and incidents, through the best driver reactions, FanBoosts and Attack Modes, to innovations and insights, and finally we pick out the best race so far.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/12/06/2195752_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524193500 +0200" stop="20230524203000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Grand Prix of Spain, Madrid</title>
<desc lang="fr">X-Trial is a young and dynamic sport. The events take place in arenas and the spectators are up close during the entire period. Spectacular setups with challenging obstacles combined with the skill of the best riders in the world promise great entertainment. Motorvision.TV shows highlights from all six events of the 2022 season.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/13/2162902_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524203000 +0200" stop="20230524212000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Jet Ski World Series</title>
<desc lang="fr">The &quot;&quot;WGP#1 World Series&quot;&quot; is a jet-ski championship with events in Europe, the US and Asia.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/37/1763088_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524212000 +0200" stop="20230524215000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">GP of Italy, Regione Sardegna, Qualifying</title>
<desc lang="fr">In 2022, the UIM is once again hosting its Formula 1 World Championship in Powerboat. In the 37th season, ten teams with 19 drivers from eleven countries have signed up to fight for the title of the new world champion in three Grand Prix.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/21/2061231_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524215000 +0200" stop="20230524223500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Australian V8 Superboats Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Australian V8 Superboat Championship is one of the most important watersports series from down under. Drivers compete in three different classes: the LS Class, Group A and Unlimited, which features hardly any restrictions regarding engine sizes. In 2022, a total of seven rounds are scheduled before a new champion is crowned.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/02/22/26/1784522_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524223500 +0200" stop="20230524230500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Powerboat: P1 USA AquaX Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">See all the action from the USA series of P1 AquaX, an exciting Jet Ski racing event, operated by Powerboat P1. P1 AquaX is an international motorboat racing competition organised by the Union Internationale Motornautique.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/37/1763088_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524230500 +0200" stop="20230524233000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">UIM Class 1 Powerboat Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">Want to cool down? The Class 1 Offshore Championship featuring boats with twin inboard 1100hp engines that can reach speeds in excess of 160mph. All boats, which are around 12-14 meters long and 3.5 meters wide, are limited by a minimum weight of 4,950 kilos.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/54/1804798_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524233000 +0200" stop="20230525000000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">P1 Offshore Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">The P1 Offshore Powerboat Championship promises tightly fought offshore racing with powerboats reaching top speeds of up to 100 miles per hour. Five events are schedules for the 2022 season and Motorvision.TV brings you all the thrilling action from each event!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/03/2034343_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230525000000 +0200" stop="20230525005000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">British Truck Racing</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Brisith Truck Racing Championship features some of the heaviest racing machines you'll ever see. Each truck weighs more than five tonnes and produces in excess of 1000bhp. The 2022 season features a total of 7 events that are contested around the United Kingdom.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1760716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230525005000 +0200" stop="20230525014000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">DTM</title>
<desc lang="fr">The DTM - Deutsche Tourenwagen Masters - is the premier German touring car championship. In 2022, the competition is in its 23rd season and features 16 races across 8 weekends. Motorvision.TV shows the best bits from each event.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/25/2125719_A.jpg" />
</programme>