<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Voo -->
<programme start="20230412022500 +0200" stop="20230412025000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Tour European Rally Historic</title>
<desc lang="fr">Motorvision TV brings you all the action from the independent rally series taking place around Europe.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/24/1760723_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230412025000 +0200" stop="20230412031500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Rally Terra Valle del Tevere, Italy</title>
<desc lang="fr">Amazing challenge around Europe includes 19 special stages. The top crew will become Tour European Rally champion in one of the most beautiful European rallies.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/10/1763098_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230412031500 +0200" stop="20230412034000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Championnat de Belgique des Rallyes</title>
<desc lang="fr">Motorvision TV brings you all the action from one of the most competitive national rallies in Europe.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/21/2149178_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230412034000 +0200" stop="20230412043500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Rallye : Abu Dhabi Desert Challenge</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Abu Dhabi Challenge is one of the most prestigious international cross rallies. Motorbike, quad-bike, four wheel and truck competitors battle Abu Dhabi's magnificent desert in a grueling 5-day event. In the past, international motorsports icons like Carlos Sainz, Colin McRae and Heinz Kinigadner followed the call and took on the challenging dunes of the United Arabian Emirates.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/47/1808106_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230412043500 +0200" stop="20230412050500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Dubai International Baja</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Dubai International Baja, formerly known as the Dubai International Rally, is the oldest motorsport event in the United Arab Emirates. It is part of the reformed FIA World Cup for Cross-Country Bajas and based at the famous Dubai Autodrome. It will see international drivers taking on a demanding 407-kilometer stage running through the Al Qudra desert.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/50/1776289_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230412050500 +0200" stop="20230412053000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Rally Clasico Mallorca</title>
<desc lang="fr">Motorvision.TV shows the best moments from the 2022 eMallorca Challenge.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/48/1758021_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230412053000 +0200" stop="20230412060000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Spa-Classic</title>
<desc lang="fr">Created in 2011 on one of the most iconic circuit in the world, the Spa Classic is now one of the major European events for historic racing cars. In 2019, Spa Classic celebrates its ninth staging and features events like nighttime races for touring cars and the Heritage Touring Cup, which pays tribute to the famous Spa-Francorchamps 24 Hours for Touring Cars.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/37/1760720_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230412060000 +0200" stop="20230412062500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Go Green! S2</title>
<desc lang="fr">It takes place once a year: Essen has become the scene of action, exceptional attractions and a lot of cars. The Essen Motor Show is T H E event for the automotive and motor sports enthusiasts.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748432_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230412062500 +0200" stop="20230412065500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Perfect Ride S5</title>
<desc lang="fr">It is said to be the first of a new generation. The BMW i8 is truly a miracle of technology and the world's first eco-friendly sports car. The combination of lightweight construction, electrical engine and 3-cylinder combustion engine promises economical driving pleasure. Plus: Perfect Ride reviews the impressive and superlight sports cars Lotus Elise and Roding Roadster in Austria.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/19/1748438_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230412065500 +0200" stop="20230412071500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Top Ten Show S1</title>
<desc lang="fr">It's time to get nostalgic: Who do you think is the most important pioneer of the automotive world? We do a little time travel and trace back the trail of the modern car. While we won't go back to antiquity and the first steam or sail wagons, we'll travel to the beginning of the 20th century and present you the ten oldest car manufacturers.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/50/1752909_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230412071500 +0200" stop="20230412074500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 4</title>
<desc lang="fr">Street Racers is your backstage pass to the world of Formula E. Every two weeks, the magazine takes a look behind the scenes of the most important electric car racing series and provides reviews, current news, exciting interviews and gripping background reports from the world of Formula E.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/59/1880083_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230412074500 +0200" stop="20230412083000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">GT World Challenge Europe Sprint Cup</title>
<desc lang="fr">Join Motorvision TV as it brings you all the action from the European sports car racing series.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/59/1763095_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230412083000 +0200" stop="20230412085500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Dream Cars S2</title>
<desc lang="fr">They are wild, they are busrting with power and they are cult, the American Muscle Cars. Whether it is the Ford Mustang, the Chevrolet Camaro or the Corvette, Muscle Cars are coveted all over the world because of their rebellious design, impeteous horsepower and their stunning speed. Dream Cars presents the most spectacular and fastest US-Sport- and Musclecars.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/50/1752909_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230412085500 +0200" stop="20230412092500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 4</title>
<desc lang="fr">Exciting sports show that follows the hottest action from the world's most unique motor sport events. Viewers will have a chance to visit some interesting competitions- from IDEMITSU 600 Super Endurance at the Chang Interna-tional Circuit in Thailand, the winter edition of the Maroc Challenge in Morocco, to the Hispania Rally, the only European rally to take place in the desert, and many more. Viewers will also find out all the news from the world of motor sports.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/40/1752403_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230412092500 +0200" stop="20230412095000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Bike World</title>
<desc lang="fr">Bike World is the magazine on MOTORVISION TV for all fans of the lifestyle on two wheels. Whether on the road, off-road or on the race track: Bike World brings the latest trends from the world of motorcycles into living rooms around the world. Watch the latest tests of new two-wheelers, exciting reports from the hottest events and thrilling insights into superbike racing.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/32/1837877_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230412095000 +0200" stop="20230412101500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Perfect Ride S6</title>
<desc lang="fr">What's hot and what's not. There are quests to be undertaken, the search for the ideal auto, for the perfect race track for the ultimate accessory gadget. What are the preferred rides of the race legends?</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/09/2153087_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230412101500 +0200" stop="20230412103500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Supercars S6</title>
<desc lang="fr">There are details which set super cars apart from normal cars and these details are essential. Super cars are the biggest, loudest and most expensive cars on the highway; they're four-wheeled works of arts.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748406_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230412103500 +0200" stop="20230412112500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Spotted</title>
<desc lang="fr">Audi or BMW, all-wheel or rear-wheel drive? It's a question of faith and #Spotted pitches the RS 5 and M4 CS against each other. Both performance-driven sports coupes come together for the very first time. While the Clubsport version of the BMW M4 comes with an output of 460 HP, the Abt modified Audi RS 5 offers an output of 510 PS. Who will win the battle? Plus: Rare tuning vehicles from Japan.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/21/07/1884377_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230412112500 +0200" stop="20230412120000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Snow Mobiles</title>
<desc lang="fr">At the grand Winter-opening of the Alps, no expense or effort is spared to turn the Austrian town into a snow-covered track for the 5th time. Professionals and celebrities provide a snow battle like no other.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1760716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230412120000 +0200" stop="20230412122500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Go Green! S2</title>
<desc lang="fr">After the Tsunami and Fukushima - This years Tokyo Motor Show will promote both optimism and fun. The highlights: Mercedes brought the study of the hydrogen-powered F125 to the 'Land of the Rising Sun'.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748432_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230412122500 +0200" stop="20230412125000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Perfect Ride S5</title>
<desc lang="fr">In 1989 Audi introduced the first turbocharged diesel engine. Since then turbochargers became standard and result into smooth running of engines and increased driving pleasure. Perfect Ride reviews the latest TDI engines and previews the Audi RS5 TDI Concept, which shows how sporty diesel engines could be used in future production cars.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/19/1748438_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230412125000 +0200" stop="20230412131000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Top Ten Show S1</title>
<desc lang="fr">In today's show we are going to show you the most affordable hybrid models. The trail-blazers are definitely the Japanese, who have a whole bunch of cars to offer.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/50/1752909_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230412131000 +0200" stop="20230412134000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 3</title>
<desc lang="fr">Street Racers is your backstage pass to the world of Formula E. Every two weeks, the magazine takes a look behind the scenes of the most important electric car racing series and provides reviews, current news, exciting interviews and gripping background reports from the world of Formula E.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/59/1880083_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230412134000 +0200" stop="20230412142500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">GT World Challenge Europe Sprint Cup</title>
<desc lang="fr">Join Motorvision TV as it brings you all the action from the European sports car racing series.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/59/1763095_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230412142500 +0200" stop="20230412145000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">MXGP of Patagonia, Vilal La Angostura</title>
<desc lang="fr">Lap after lap of international motorsports action. This is coverage from the FIM (Fédération Internationale de Motocyclisme) Motocross World Championship where riders from all over the globe compete in high-octane, fast-paced motocross racing. Competitors battle it out in races lasting 35 minutes plus 2 laps per race.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/32/1907968_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230412145000 +0200" stop="20230412152000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Grand Prix of Hungary, Budapest, Papp Laszlo SportAre</title>
<desc lang="fr">FIM SuperEnduro World Championship has been held since 2007. Its circuits are built inside stadiums or arenas, recreating obstacles such as rocks, boulders and logs. The championship consists of eight Grands Prix spread around the globe on courses that are mostly off-road. These events are split into two days and two different races, after which the points towards the world championship are awarded. Each round includes a motocross test and an extreme test, in addition to the enduro test.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/22/1748447_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230412152000 +0200" stop="20230412161000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Australian Motocross Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Australian ProMX Championship is the nation's premier motocross championship. The series acts as a successful development platform for young Australian talent and is designed as a tiered system with three dedicated classes: MX3 for younger drivers, the MX2 for senior drivers and the MX1, which is the elite category in the championship.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/07/2125726_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230412161000 +0200" stop="20230412170000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Grand Prix of Spain, Barcelona</title>
<desc lang="fr">FIM X-Trial World Championship is the most prestigious indoor motorcycle trials tournament of the world, organised by the Fédération Internationale de Motocyclisme. The programme presents the highlights of the rounds where the participants have to take on the challenging tracks full of steep climbs and huge rocks.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/13/2162902_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230412170000 +0200" stop="20230412180000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Australian Superbike Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">Founded in 1980, the Australian Superbike Championship is one of the most important motorcycle racing competitions in Oceania. It is well respected as a springboard for riders and teams who aspire an international career in motorcycling. The 2022 season is contested in five classes: Superbike, Supersport, Supersport 300, the Yamaha R3 Cup and the Oceania Junior Cup.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/48/1853102_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230412180000 +0200" stop="20230412182000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Go Green! S2</title>
<desc lang="fr">No fuel consumption, no noise disturbance and no emissions while driving: That'ts what the Citroen C Zero from France promises. Go Green reviews the egg shaped vehicle. Plus: Daimler wants to prove that hydrogen powered electric vehicles are suitable for daily use and sends three B-Class F-Cell emission free around the world. And: Go Green previews the new Volvo V60 Plug-in-Hybrid.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748432_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230412182000 +0200" stop="20230412184500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Perfect Ride S5</title>
<desc lang="fr">Individuality and a wide array of equipment options are the keys to reaching lots of buyers. At least that's what car manufacturers think when it comes to small cars. Perfect Ride answers the question, if they offer too much lifestyle and reviews three trendy small cars: the Mini 5 door, the Opel Adam Rocks (also known as the Vauxhall Adam Rocks) and the Kia Soul EV.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/19/1748438_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230412184500 +0200" stop="20230412191000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Top Ten Show S1</title>
<desc lang="fr">Some cars are not just a means of transport, but influenced entire generations and became legends on their own. That's why we won't talk about expensive, fast or successful cars on this episode. Instead we show you ten cars that managed to achieve cult status and have numerous fan clubs that are still paying homage to them.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/50/1752909_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230412191000 +0200" stop="20230412194000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 9</title>
<desc lang="fr">Street Racers is your backstage pass to the world of Formula E. Every two weeks, the magazine takes a look behind the scenes of the most important electric car racing series and provides reviews, current news, exciting interviews and gripping background reports from the world of Formula E.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/59/1880083_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230412194000 +0200" stop="20230412202500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">GT World Challenge Asia</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Fanatec GT World Challenge Asia is back for another season with five scheduled events for the 2022 season. Unlike its European and North American counterparts, GT World Challenge Asia also features GT4 entries.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/30/2013488_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230412202500 +0200" stop="20230412205000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">P1 Offshore Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">The P1 Offshore Powerboat Championship promises tightly fought offshore racing with powerboats reaching top speeds of up to 100 miles per hour. Five events are schedules for the 2022 season and Motorvision.TV brings you all the thrilling action from each event!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/05/2038331_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230412205000 +0200" stop="20230412212000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">GP of Sharjah, UAE</title>
<desc lang="fr">In 2022, the UIM is once again hosting its Formula 1 World Championship in Powerboat. In the 37th season, ten teams with 19 drivers from eleven countries have signed up to fight for the title of the new world champion in three Grand Prix.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/21/2061231_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230412212000 +0200" stop="20230412214500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">UIM Class 1 Powerboat Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">Want to cool down? The Class 1 Offshore Championship featuring boats with twin inboard 1100hp engines that can reach speeds in excess of 160mph. All boats, which are around 12-14 meters long and 3.5 meters wide, are limited by a minimum weight of 4,950 kilos.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/03/2034343_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230412214500 +0200" stop="20230412221500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">UIM Aquabike World Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">Caution, danger of splashing! Since 1992, the Aquabike World Championship has been the most important racing series in the sport of jet skiing and one of the fastest competitions in water sports. On specially designed race courses or on the high seas, the participants engage in thrilling races in the ski and runabout categories and fascinate with all kinds of stunts on their more than 300 hp jet skis.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/31/2029804_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230412221500 +0200" stop="20230412230000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Australian V8 Superboats Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Australian V8 Superboat Championship is one of the most important watersports series from down under. Drivers compete in three different classes: the LS Class, Group A and Unlimited, which features hardly any restrictions regarding engine sizes. In 2022, a total of seven rounds are scheduled before a new champion is crowned.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/02/22/26/1784522_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230412230000 +0200" stop="20230413000000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">St Pete Downtown, Florida</title>
<desc lang="fr">See all the action from the USA series of P1 AquaX, an exciting Jet Ski racing event, operated by Powerboat P1. P1 AquaX is an international motorboat racing competition organised by the Union Internationale Motornautique.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/37/1763088_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230413000000 +0200" stop="20230413005000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">BTRDA Rallycross Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">Being a mixture of circuit racing and rallying, rallycross is often considered to be the wildchild of motor sports. One of the most exciting competitions in this genre is the BTRDA Rallycross Championship. Motorvision.TV brings you the highlights from each of their events.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/25/1760725_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230413005000 +0200" stop="20230413014000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Ferrari Challenge Europe</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Ferrari Challenge Europe is back for another season on Motorvision.TV. The longest-running single-make series championship in the history of the Prancing Horse-company promises high performance and talented drivers on challenging tracks around Europe. Seven events are scheduled for the 2022 season including the Finali Mondiali, which brings together the final stages of all Ferrari Challenge divisions around the world.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/25/55/2162175_A.jpg" />
</programme>