<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Voo -->
<programme start="20230502023500 +0200" stop="20230502030000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Drift : Championnat de France</title>
<desc lang="fr">The French Drift Championship is one of the most important national championships in the European drift sport and attracts the interest of around 300 pilots every year. However, only the 32 best drivers can compete in the main event. To survive in the 1-on-1-battles, they must impress the judges with speed, precision and spectacular drift maneuvers.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/25/1760725_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230502030000 +0200" stop="20230502035000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">e-Trophée Andros</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Andros Trophy is the French national ice racing championship. The idea appeared long time ago in 1985 when professional racer Max Mamers and the owner of the Andros company, Frédéric Gervoson, met as rugby fans. They spent the winter racing with friends on ice circuits. In 2003 the trophy gained an international aspect with a race at Sherbrooke in Canada. In 2020, the racing series is repositioning itself as an electric racing series.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/43/1884375_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230502035000 +0200" stop="20230502044500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Hi-Tec Drift Allstars Series Australia</title>
<desc lang="fr">The latest drifting competition on Motorvision.TV brings you the best drifters from Australia. Join us for thrilling duels, smoking wheels and non-stop drift battles for the Drift All Stars Series title.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/37/1760720_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230502044500 +0200" stop="20230502053500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">National Legend Cars</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Legends Cars National Championship brings back racing from yesteryear. The series features 5/8 scale replicas of pre-war 1930s Fords, Chevys and Dodges that are equipped with 125bhp-motorcycle engines. These cars are well known for delivering high-octane battles on race tracks around Great Britain.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/50/1756288_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230502053500 +0200" stop="20230502060000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">G Series Andorra</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Andorra-Pas de la Casa Circuit offers an excellent quality on the ice surface thanks to their geographical location. A thousand meters long and ten wide route that combines a wide straight line with curves of all kinds, completely covered with ice and snow.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/54/1853464_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230502060000 +0200" stop="20230502063000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Stunt Heroes (Drift, fly &amp; fire) S1 (n°1)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Drift, fly &amp; fire»The Stunt Heroes from the German company â?oeAction Conceptâ? really let it rip. In the past they produced several award-winning stunts, but are always on the hunt for new spectacular scenes. This time stuntman Paul slides under an exploding vehicle. At the same time gangster bride Anna flies through the air.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/15/35/1790601_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230502063000 +0200" stop="20230502065500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Supercars S6</title>
<desc lang="fr">More than 10 years ago the 1,000 hp Bugatti Veyron started a new era of super sports cars. By now almost all renowned manufacturers offer their own supercar. Frequently, today's strongest and fastest cars rely on hybrid technology or even drive in pure electric mode. Supercars takes a look at the sports car of the future and gives an insight into the latest technology and driving systems of the future.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748406_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230502065500 +0200" stop="20230502072000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Classic Ride S1</title>
<desc lang="fr">Once a year Russian vintage fans meet at a spots stadium in Moscow Sports for the Retro Style, a vintage rally through Moscow. Classic Ride takes advantage of the opportunity to celebrate the passion for old cars with Russan drivers. Once ahead of its time, the Citroen SM is now a rare collector's item. Classic Rides takes a look at the French diva with an Italian heart.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/24/2125716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230502072000 +0200" stop="20230502074500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 22</title>
<desc lang="fr">Street Racers is your backstage pass to the world of Formula E. Every two weeks, the magazine takes a look behind the scenes of the most important electric car racing series and provides reviews, current news, exciting interviews and gripping background reports from the world of Formula E.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/59/1880083_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230502074500 +0200" stop="20230502084000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Circuit Paul Ricard, Le Castellet, France</title>
<desc lang="fr">The European Le Mans Series, a series open to Le Mans Prototypes and grand tourer-style racing cars, is back with another action-filled season. This year's calendar features six 4-hour races around Europe including the return of the 4 Hours of Imola.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/08/39/2182076_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230502084000 +0200" stop="20230502090500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">MXGP of Switzerland, Frauenfeld</title>
<desc lang="fr">Lap after lap of international motorsports action. This is coverage from the FIM (Fédération Internationale de Motocyclisme) Motocross World Championship where riders from all over the globe compete in high-octane, fast-paced motocross racing. Competitors battle it out in races lasting 35 minutes plus 2 laps per race.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/32/1907968_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230502090500 +0200" stop="20230502093000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Grand Prix of Israel, Jerusalem, Pais Arena</title>
<desc lang="fr">FIM SuperEnduro World Championship has been held since 2007. Its circuits are built inside stadiums or arenas, recreating obstacles such as rocks, boulders and logs. The championship consists of eight Grands Prix spread around the globe on courses that are mostly off-road. These events are split into two days and two different races, after which the points towards the world championship are awarded. Each round includes a motocross test and an extreme test, in addition to the enduro test.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/22/1748447_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230502093000 +0200" stop="20230502102000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Australian Motocross Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Australian ProMX Championship is the nation's premier motocross championship. The series acts as a successful development platform for young Australian talent and is designed as a tiered system with three dedicated classes: MX3 for younger drivers, the MX2 for senior drivers and the MX1, which is the elite category in the championship.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/31/43/1763097_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230502102000 +0200" stop="20230502111500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Grand Prix of Spain, Pamplona</title>
<desc lang="fr">FIM X-Trial World Championship is the most prestigious indoor motorcycle trials tournament of the world, organised by the Fédération Internationale de Motocyclisme. The programme presents the highlights of the rounds where the participants have to take on the challenging tracks full of steep climbs and huge rocks.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/13/2162902_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230502111500 +0200" stop="20230502120000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Victoria</title>
<desc lang="fr">Aucune description</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/15/12/2185021_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230502120000 +0200" stop="20230502122500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Hockenheimring, Germany</title>
<desc lang="fr">League of super sports cars.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/59/1884373_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230502122500 +0200" stop="20230502130500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">GP Croatia, Automotodrom Grobnik</title>
<desc lang="fr">NASCAR, America's most popular racing series, is now well established in Europe and there is no better proof than its European division: the NASCAR Whelen Euro Series. This year, 17 teams from nine different countries with a total of 39 cars prove once again that the NWES with its pure racing character is one of the best touring car series on the old continent. Motorvision.TV shows highlights from every race weekend.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748423_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230502130500 +0200" stop="20230502140000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Goodwood Members Meeting</title>
<desc lang="fr">Goodwood is a british motor racing event where fans get to witness modern and historic racecars in action.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/37/1760720_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230502140000 +0200" stop="20230502144500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Southern Races Part 2</title>
<desc lang="fr">King of the Roads.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/20/26/2186521_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230502144500 +0200" stop="20230502153500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Asian Le Mans Series</title>
<desc lang="fr">Asian sports car racing endurance series created by the Automobile Club de l'Ouest and based in Asia aims to attract teams and drivers from Asian countries. The Asian Le Mans Series is the symbol of the Spirit of Le Mans, and holds the same passion for creating world class endurance racing.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/20/00/2125604_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230502153500 +0200" stop="20230502163000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Circuit de Barcelona-Catalunya, Spain</title>
<desc lang="fr">European Le Mans Series believes in the team spirit during long distance performance. The duty of the ELMS is to offer its competitors a full season to race their cars on some of the best tracks in Europe, while keeping tight control of the costs associated with running in a top European wide series. The champions are offered a place on the grid of the 24 Heures du Mans, which gives an extra, important dimension to the title race across the three categories.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/08/39/2182076_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230502163000 +0200" stop="20230502171000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Autodromo Nazionale</title>
<desc lang="fr">See all the action and best parts from the GT World Challenge Europe, a sports car racing series divided into two separate championships - the GT World Challenge Europe Sprint Cup, and the GT World Challenge Europe Endurance Cup.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/25/1760725_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230502171000 +0200" stop="20230502180000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">WeatherTech SportsCar Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">The IMSA WeatherTech SportsCar Championhip is an endurance racing championship in North America where up to five different classes compete in eleven events.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1760716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230502180000 +0200" stop="20230502182500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Stunt Heroes (Salto mortale) S1 (n°2)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Salto mortale»The Stunt Heroes from Action Concept face a new mission: performing a front-flip through the air with a stuntman on board of an estate wagon. It's a new task for coordinator and adrenaline junkie Christoph &quot;Domi&quot; Domanski. Stuntmen Daniel and Lars display a brilliant fighting choreography in some spectacular driving scenes. Adrenaline-pumped stunts with lots of crashing are guaranteed!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/15/35/1790601_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230502182500 +0200" stop="20230502185000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Supercars S6</title>
<desc lang="fr">BMW M3 and Mercedes C63 AMG. The top models battle it out forever. While the C63 has better performance values on paper, the M3 has always been delivering the better performance. It's a never ending back and forth. But they are not alone in their battle for the crown. An exotic creature from Japan lies in wait: the Lexus RC-F. It's eight cylinders and 477 hp push the Japanese extrovert over asphalt. It's top speed: 270 km/h. Is he a threat to its German competitors?</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748406_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230502185000 +0200" stop="20230502191000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Classic Ride S3</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Amphicar 770 is a rare classic. Its special attraction is that you drive motorboat on the road. It may not be the fastest car on the street, but it's ready to be used on the water as well. Thus careful maintenance and continuous checks are a must. If something leaks, the Amphicar will sink like a stone. Classic Ride meets Richard Orthuber who owns an Amphicar 770.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/24/2125716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230502191000 +0200" stop="20230502194000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 23</title>
<desc lang="fr">Street Racers is your backstage pass to the world of Formula E. Every two weeks, the magazine takes a look behind the scenes of the most important electric car racing series and provides reviews, current news, exciting interviews and gripping background reports from the world of Formula E.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/59/1880083_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230502194000 +0200" stop="20230502203000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Circuit Paul Ricard, Le Castellet, France</title>
<desc lang="fr">The European Le Mans Series, a series open to Le Mans Prototypes and grand tourer-style racing cars, is back with another action-filled season. This year's calendar features six 4-hour races around Europe including the return of the 4 Hours of Imola.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/08/39/2182076_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230502203000 +0200" stop="20230502205500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Bike World</title>
<desc lang="fr">Bike World revolves around the speedway and the racers swishing by on their two wheelers. Find out the latest news and reports regarding two-wheel competitions in the world of speed. This is the content to enjoy for all motorcycle enthusiasts across the world. Explore the best motorbikes, top locations, and iconic racers who have a lot of fun doing it.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/32/1837877_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230502205500 +0200" stop="20230502212000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 4</title>
<desc lang="fr">Exciting sports show that follows the hottest action from the world's most unique motor sport events. Viewers will have a chance to visit some interesting competitions- from IDEMITSU 600 Super Endurance at the Chang Interna-tional Circuit in Thailand, the winter edition of the Maroc Challenge in Morocco, to the Hispania Rally, the only European rally to take place in the desert, and many more. Viewers will also find out all the news from the world of motor sports.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/40/1752403_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230502212000 +0200" stop="20230502215000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Perfect Ride S6</title>
<desc lang="fr">What's hot and what's not. There are quests to be undertaken, the search for the ideal auto, for the perfect race track for the ultimate accessory gadget. What are the preferred rides of the race legends?</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/09/2153087_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230502215000 +0200" stop="20230502222500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Supercars S6</title>
<desc lang="fr">There are details which set super cars apart from normal cars and these details are essential. Super cars are the biggest, loudest and most expensive cars on the highway; they're four-wheeled works of arts.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748406_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230502222500 +0200" stop="20230502225000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Electric Pickups</title>
<desc lang="fr">Pickups are the epitome of the american way of drive! High displacement V8 engines combined with plenty of space. Seldom seen in Europe, they are the cashcows of many automakers in the US market. In the future traditional manufacturers will hardly be able to avoid an electric versoin of their trucks. And the competition is getting bigger and bigger. Ever since Elon Musk presented the Tesla Cybertruck bothe the established brands and new startups had been on the advance to conquer the market with vehicles that have the equivalent of over 1000 hp. Ford F-150 Ligtning, Bollinger B2 or Hummer EV - Go Green shows what we can expect in the next few years.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1760716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230502225000 +0200" stop="20230502234000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Spotted</title>
<desc lang="fr">With its Model S, American carmaker Tesla wants to establish electric engines in the full size class. For the very first time it is possible to attain driving ranges over 400 kilometers. Its tremendous acceleration becomes an image boost for the brand. Porsche stands for lots of speed and horsepower, too. With its Panamera Sport Turismo, the sports car manufacturer taps into a new market.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/21/07/1884377_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230502234000 +0200" stop="20230503000000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Red Gold Dream</title>
<desc lang="fr">This years motto of the Conti Tuning Day is 'power sedans' and Tuning host Lucy examines the bolides carefully. Plus: The McLaren SLR is the masterpiece of Mercedes, a super sports car among all sports cars. Only 3.500 units have been produced. Tunings showcases the most expensive SLR in the world, which outshines all other SLR models.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1760716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230503000000 +0200" stop="20230503002500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Go Green! S3</title>
<desc lang="fr">Neither e-cars nor hydrogen compulsion can guarantee clean mobility on their own. Sustainable mobility only works if there is more than just replacing one drive concept with another one. The key to the mobility of the future is connectivity. A positive side effect is that cities can be freed from long lines of parking cars. Part 3 of Sustainable Mobility shows how that can work.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748432_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230503002500 +0200" stop="20230503005000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Perfect Ride S2</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Porsche 911. Modern design, advanced technology, everything is new but still: For 50 years, still unmistakable. And we also test the world's first series-produced plug-in hybrid with diesel engine: the Volvo V60!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/19/1748438_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230503005000 +0200" stop="20230503011500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Top Ten Show S1</title>
<desc lang="fr">Today we'll be taking a look at some extreme cars from around the world: Supercars! We're going to be showing you the top ten most beautiful supercars of recent times.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/50/1752909_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230503011500 +0200" stop="20230503014500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 21</title>
<desc lang="fr">Street Racers is your backstage pass to the world of Formula E. Every two weeks, the magazine takes a look behind the scenes of the most important electric car racing series and provides reviews, current news, exciting interviews and gripping background reports from the world of Formula E.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/59/1880083_A.jpg" />
</programme>