<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Voo -->
<programme start="20230501021000 +0200" stop="20230501024000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 24</title>
<desc lang="fr">Street Racers is your backstage pass to the world of Formula E. Every two weeks, the magazine takes a look behind the scenes of the most important electric car racing series and provides reviews, current news, exciting interviews and gripping background reports from the world of Formula E.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/59/1880083_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230501024000 +0200" stop="20230501030500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">The Genius of Colin Chapman</title>
<desc lang="fr">Designer, engineer, and team boss, Colin Chapman was one of the driving forces behind Formula One throughout the 1960s and '70s. A man whose name became synonymous with motorsport innovation, Chapman's racing career began with an unimpressive start behind the wheel before the Briton came to realize that his real talents lay elsewhere.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/49/1774755_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230501030500 +0200" stop="20230501035500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Rallye Monte Carlo Historique</title>
<desc lang="fr">The infamous Monte-Carlo Rally is one of the world's oldest rally events in the world. To pay tribute to its long-lasting history, the Automobile Club de Monaco organizes the Rallye Monte-Carlo Historique. The catch is: Only cars that competed in the Monte-Carlo Rally at least 40 years ago are allowed to take part in the historic edition of the Monte-Carlo Rally.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/59/1763095_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230501035500 +0200" stop="20230501042000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Ferry Porsche</title>
<desc lang="fr">Portrait of Ferdinand &quot;Ferry&quot; Porsche, the father of the Porsche 911. He started his automobile legacy when he built the Porsche 935 after World War II.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/19/1774199_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230501042000 +0200" stop="20230501044500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Car History (Lancia) S2 (n°15)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Lancia»Lancia - Legendary racing successes, technological innovations and exclusive vehicles, made this brand world famous. But Lancia hasn't just enjoyed success in its history. The Italian car manufacturer had to endure severe misfortunes and economic mismanagement as well. Nonetheless, the legend lives on to this day. Car History looks back on the ups and downs in the history of Lancia.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/15/1740326_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230501044500 +0200" stop="20230501051000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">The Rallye World Championship 1982</title>
<desc lang="fr">The African continent is always a difficult terrain for rally drivers. That wasn't any different for the 1982 World Rally Championship, when heat, dust, mud and hardly passable routes posed major challenges for drivers, co-drivers and engines.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/24/2125717_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230501051000 +0200" stop="20230501053500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Car History (Volvo) S2 (n°19)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Volvo»Volvo Classic Cars are always solid, always safe, but not always beautiful. Since 1927 the Swedish car company produces cars, which are a little bit different. But no matter if their individual models are curvy or boxy; a Volvo is always an individual car. Get ready for a ride through the history of Volvo on this episode of Car History.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/15/1740326_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230501053500 +0200" stop="20230501060000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Classic Ride S2</title>
<desc lang="fr">One real eye catcher is the very rare AMC Pacer from the movie 'Waynes World'. This car has caught the attention of famous German Music-Manager Andreas Laesker.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/24/2125716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230501060000 +0200" stop="20230501062500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Hockenheimring, Germany</title>
<desc lang="fr">League of super sports cars.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/59/1884373_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230501062500 +0200" stop="20230501071000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">GP Croatia, Automotodrom Grobnik</title>
<desc lang="fr">NASCAR, America's most popular racing series, is now well established in Europe and there is no better proof than its European division: the NASCAR Whelen Euro Series. This year, 17 teams from nine different countries with a total of 39 cars prove once again that the NWES with its pure racing character is one of the best touring car series on the old continent. Motorvision.TV shows highlights from every race weekend.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748423_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230501071000 +0200" stop="20230501080000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Goodwood Members Meeting</title>
<desc lang="fr">Goodwood is a british motor racing event where fans get to witness modern and historic racecars in action.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/25/1760725_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230501080000 +0200" stop="20230501084500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Southern Races Part 2</title>
<desc lang="fr">King of the Roads.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/20/50/2186513_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230501084500 +0200" stop="20230501094000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Asian Le Mans Series</title>
<desc lang="fr">Asian sports car racing endurance series created by the Automobile Club de l'Ouest and based in Asia aims to attract teams and drivers from Asian countries. The Asian Le Mans Series is the symbol of the Spirit of Le Mans, and holds the same passion for creating world class endurance racing.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/20/00/2125604_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230501094000 +0200" stop="20230501103000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Circuit de Barcelona-Catalunya, Spain</title>
<desc lang="fr">European Le Mans Series believes in the team spirit during long distance performance. The duty of the ELMS is to offer its competitors a full season to race their cars on some of the best tracks in Europe, while keeping tight control of the costs associated with running in a top European wide series. The champions are offered a place on the grid of the 24 Heures du Mans, which gives an extra, important dimension to the title race across the three categories.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/08/39/2182076_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230501103000 +0200" stop="20230501111500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Autodromo Nazionale</title>
<desc lang="fr">See all the action and best parts from the GT World Challenge Europe, a sports car racing series divided into two separate championships - the GT World Challenge Europe Sprint Cup, and the GT World Challenge Europe Endurance Cup.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1760716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230501111500 +0200" stop="20230501120000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">WeatherTech SportsCar Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">The IMSA WeatherTech SportsCar Championhip is an endurance racing championship in North America where up to five different classes compete in eleven events.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/40/1752403_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230501120000 +0200" stop="20230501122500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Go Green! S3</title>
<desc lang="fr">Neither e-cars nor hydrogen compulsion can guarantee clean mobility on their own. Sustainable mobility only works if there is more than just replacing one drive concept with another one. The key to the mobility of the future is connectivity. A positive side effect is that cities can be freed from long lines of parking cars. Part 3 of Sustainable Mobility shows how that can work.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748432_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230501122500 +0200" stop="20230501125000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Perfect Ride S2</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Porsche 911. Modern design, advanced technology, everything is new but still: For 50 years, still unmistakable. And we also test the world's first series-produced plug-in hybrid with diesel engine: the Volvo V60!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/19/1748438_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230501125000 +0200" stop="20230501131500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Top Ten Show S1</title>
<desc lang="fr">Today we'll be taking a look at some extreme cars from around the world: Supercars! We're going to be showing you the top ten most beautiful supercars of recent times.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/50/1752909_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230501131500 +0200" stop="20230501134500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 21</title>
<desc lang="fr">Street Racers is your backstage pass to the world of Formula E. Every two weeks, the magazine takes a look behind the scenes of the most important electric car racing series and provides reviews, current news, exciting interviews and gripping background reports from the world of Formula E.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/59/1880083_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230501134500 +0200" stop="20230501143500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Race 3, Kangerlussuaq, Greenland</title>
<desc lang="fr">Extreme E is a racing series for SUVs with electric motors that has been held worldwide since 2021. In the race, all teams compete with the same vehicles, which are powered by two electric motors and are allowed to produce a maximum of 500kW (680HP).</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/20/33/1951083_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230501143500 +0200" stop="20230501150000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Tour European Rally Historic</title>
<desc lang="fr">Motorvision TV brings you all the action from the independent rally series taking place around Europe.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/28/1760738_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230501150000 +0200" stop="20230501152000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Rallye Sierra Morena, Spain</title>
<desc lang="fr">Amazing challenge around Europe includes 19 special stages. The top crew will become Tour European Rally champion in one of the most beautiful European rallies.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/48/2123747_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230501152000 +0200" stop="20230501155000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Championnat de Belgique des Rallyes</title>
<desc lang="fr">BRC.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/21/2149178_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230501155000 +0200" stop="20230501161500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Dubai International Baja</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Dubai International Baja, formerly known as the Dubai International Rally, is the oldest motorsport event in the United Arab Emirates. It is part of the reformed FIA World Cup for Cross-Country Bajas and based at the famous Dubai Autodrome. It will see international drivers taking on a demanding 407-kilometer stage running through the Al Qudra desert.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/50/1776289_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230501161500 +0200" stop="20230501164000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Arctic Lapland Rally - A Tour European Rally Promo Event</title>
<desc lang="fr">Organised as a promo event by the TER, the Artic Lapland Rally is the coldest rally competition in the world. Despite temperatures dropping to -35°C, the rally attracts more than 200,000 spectators to Rovaniemi, the capital of Finnish Lappland. It's hated, but also loved among the 150 drivers taking part every year. MOTORVISION TV shows you the highlights from the 2020 Arctic Lapland Rally.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/28/1760738_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230501164000 +0200" stop="20230501173500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Baja Hail Toyota Rally</title>
<desc lang="fr">In 2020, Saudi Arabia hosta the Baja Hail Rally for the 16th time. This year, two rounds of the event take place in the kingdom. Not only do they serve as preparation for the 2021 Dakar Rally, but they also represent the last two rounds of the official FIA World Championship for Cross Country Bajas. MOTORVISION TV shows the highlights from both events.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/33/1786567_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230501173500 +0200" stop="20230501180000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Rallye Classique de Majorque</title>
<desc lang="fr">Aucune description</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/48/2123747_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230501180000 +0200" stop="20230501182000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Stunt Heroes (The Gravel Pit) S2 (n°19)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«The Gravel Pit»Heavy equipment comes into use - as a car has to crash at full speed into a pile of gravel...</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/15/35/1790601_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230501182000 +0200" stop="20230501184500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Supercars S3</title>
<desc lang="fr">They are sleek, they are exclusive and most of all: they are extremely fast - supercars! See the first Arabian supercar and many other brand new luxury sport cars from the Qatar Motor Show.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748406_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230501184500 +0200" stop="20230501190500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Classic Ride S1</title>
<desc lang="fr">Once a year Russian vintage fans meet at a spots stadium in Moscow Sports for the Retro Style, a vintage rally through Moscow. Classic Ride takes advantage of the opportunity to celebrate the passion for old cars with Russan drivers. Once ahead of its time, the Citroen SM is now a rare collector's item. Classic Rides takes a look at the French diva with an Italian heart.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/24/2125716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230501190500 +0200" stop="20230501193000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 22</title>
<desc lang="fr">Street Racers is your backstage pass to the world of Formula E. Every two weeks, the magazine takes a look behind the scenes of the most important electric car racing series and provides reviews, current news, exciting interviews and gripping background reports from the world of Formula E.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/59/1880083_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230501193000 +0200" stop="20230501202500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Circuit Paul Ricard, Le Castellet, France</title>
<desc lang="fr">The European Le Mans Series, a series open to Le Mans Prototypes and grand tourer-style racing cars, is back with another action-filled season. This year's calendar features six 4-hour races around Europe including the return of the 4 Hours of Imola.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/08/39/2182076_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230501202500 +0200" stop="20230501205000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">MXGP of Switzerland, Frauenfeld</title>
<desc lang="fr">Lap after lap of international motorsports action. This is coverage from the FIM (Fédération Internationale de Motocyclisme) Motocross World Championship where riders from all over the globe compete in high-octane, fast-paced motocross racing. Competitors battle it out in races lasting 35 minutes plus 2 laps per race.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/32/1907968_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230501205000 +0200" stop="20230501212000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Grand Prix of Israel, Jerusalem, Pais Arena</title>
<desc lang="fr">FIM SuperEnduro World Championship has been held since 2007. Its circuits are built inside stadiums or arenas, recreating obstacles such as rocks, boulders and logs. The championship consists of eight Grands Prix spread around the globe on courses that are mostly off-road. These events are split into two days and two different races, after which the points towards the world championship are awarded. Each round includes a motocross test and an extreme test, in addition to the enduro test.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/22/1748447_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230501212000 +0200" stop="20230501221500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Australian Motocross Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Australian ProMX Championship is the nation's premier motocross championship. The series acts as a successful development platform for young Australian talent and is designed as a tiered system with three dedicated classes: MX3 for younger drivers, the MX2 for senior drivers and the MX1, which is the elite category in the championship.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/24/2125721_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230501221500 +0200" stop="20230501230500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Grand Prix of Spain, Pamplona</title>
<desc lang="fr">FIM X-Trial World Championship is the most prestigious indoor motorcycle trials tournament of the world, organised by the Fédération Internationale de Motocyclisme. The programme presents the highlights of the rounds where the participants have to take on the challenging tracks full of steep climbs and huge rocks.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/13/2162902_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230501230500 +0200" stop="20230502000000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Victoria</title>
<desc lang="fr">Aucune description</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/15/12/2185021_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230502000000 +0200" stop="20230502002500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Go Green! S3</title>
<desc lang="fr">Electric engines fight fossil fuel and the resulting pollution of the environment. They promise a quiet and clean urban environment and have huge potential in densely populated parts of the world. A newly developed production approach for e-cars leads to 50% less noise, too. That spares the worker's ears and the environment. But many people still don't seem to be positive about e-mobility.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748432_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230502002500 +0200" stop="20230502005000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Perfect Ride S6</title>
<desc lang="fr">N-Line.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/09/2153087_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230502005000 +0200" stop="20230502012000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Top Ten Show S1</title>
<desc lang="fr">Today is all about 'Coupés'. It's all about beautiful shapes and sporty elegance. We'll show you pioneering Coupés in terms of design. And to make this competition more exciting, we're going to set horsepower limit of 400.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/40/1752467_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230502012000 +0200" stop="20230502014500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 1</title>
<desc lang="fr">Street Racers is your backstage pass to the world of Formula E. Every two weeks, the magazine takes a look behind the scenes of the most important electric car racing series and provides reviews, current news, exciting interviews and gripping background reports from the world of Formula E.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/59/1880083_A.jpg" />
</programme>