<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Voo -->
<programme start="20230331023000 +0200" stop="20230331030000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">BitCiMXGP of Turkey, Afyonkarahisar</title>
<desc lang="fr">The FIM Motocross World Championship - also known as the MXGP - is the premier championship of motocross racing. In 2022, the championship and will be contested over 18 rounds in Europe, the Middle East, Asia and South America. Motorvision.TV takes viewers behind the scenes of every single event, presents interviews with all drivers and shows the most exciting moments from every weekend.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/32/1907968_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230331030000 +0200" stop="20230331032500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Grand Prix of Andorra, Sant Julia</title>
<desc lang="fr">It's time for the third and penultimate round of the 2020 FIM Trial World Championship. Contenders for the Trial GP title travel to Sant Julia de Loria in Andorra, where they try to beat one of the toughest courses of the season.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/37/1763099_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230331032500 +0200" stop="20230331035000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Grand Prix of Germany, Riesa, SachsenArena</title>
<desc lang="fr">FIM SuperEnduro World Championship has been held since 2007. Its circuits are built inside stadiums or arenas, recreating obstacles such as rocks, boulders and logs. The championship consists of eight Grands Prix spread around the globe on courses that are mostly off-road. These events are split into two days and two different races, after which the points towards the world championship are awarded. Each round includes a motocross test and an extreme test, in addition to the enduro test.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/22/1748447_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230331035000 +0200" stop="20230331044000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Australian Motocross Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Australian ProMX Championship is the nation's premier motocross championship. The series acts as a successful development platform for young Australian talent and is designed as a tiered system with three dedicated classes: MX3 for younger drivers, the MX2 for senior drivers and the MX1, which is the elite category in the championship.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1765320_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230331044000 +0200" stop="20230331053000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Australian Superbike Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">Founded in 1980, the Australian Superbike Championship is one of the most important motorcycle racing competitions in Oceania. It is well respected as a springboard for riders and teams who aspire an international career in motorcycling. The 2022 season is contested in five classes: Superbike, Supersport, Supersport 300, the Yamaha R3 Cup and the Oceania Junior Cup.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/46/1762227_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230331053000 +0200" stop="20230331060000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Enduro - Red Bull Romaniacs</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Red Bull Romaniacs is known for being the hardest Enduro Rally in the world. If you make it here you count yourself amongst the world's toughest enduro drivers. In 2019, the event acts as the fifth stop of the World Enduro Super Series and provides brilliant off-road action in the wilderness of Romania. MOTORVISION TV shows the best moments in this highlight recap.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/48/1853102_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230331060000 +0200" stop="20230331062500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Car History (Lancia) S2 (n°15)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Lancia»Lancia - Legendary racing successes, technological innovations and exclusive vehicles, made this brand world famous. But Lancia hasn't just enjoyed success in its history. The Italian car manufacturer had to endure severe misfortunes and economic mismanagement as well. Nonetheless, the legend lives on to this day. Car History looks back on the ups and downs in the history of Lancia.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/15/1740326_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230331062500 +0200" stop="20230331064500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Car People (Driving Instructor Danny Pfeil) S1 (n°4)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Driving Instructor Danny Pfeil»The Thomathal at the Katschberg Pass in Austria - there is still a morning early calm. As soon as Danny Pfeil's European Speed Club begins to train for winter racing, the silence is over.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/02/18/36/2149177_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230331064500 +0200" stop="20230331071500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Eco-Tuning</title>
<desc lang="fr">Tuning doesn't always have to be a sin. For its i8, BMW combines the electric future with fuel saving qualities into a spacey future tech mix. But can this concept amaze experienced petrolheads? Plus: Saving fuel by increasing the power. What first appears to be a contradiction, has to proof itself in a practical test. The &quot;Race Chip&quot; is tested on a 3000 kilometers track. Furthermore: What use does the switchable performance increase from DTE Systems have? Patrick Simon is looking for the additional power in Norway.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1760716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230331071500 +0200" stop="20230331074000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">WeatherTech SportsCar Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Road to Racing.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/59/1763095_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230331074000 +0200" stop="20230331082500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">NW200 Races Part 2</title>
<desc lang="fr">King of the Roads.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/46/1762227_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230331082500 +0200" stop="20230331091500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Grand Prix de Monaco historique</title>
<desc lang="fr">Do you miss the thrilling motorsports from yesteryear? Take a trip with Motorvision.TV to the French Riviera, when the Grand Prix de Monaco Historique turns back the wheel of time and brings back legendary racing cars for one more adrenaline-filled race featuring high speeds, risky maneuvers and head-to-head fights that we all love in motorsports.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/54/2007077_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230331091500 +0200" stop="20230331094000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Car History (Ferrari) S1 (n°8)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Ferrari»Ferrari - the name alone gets your heart racing. Wherever the iconic fire red legend from Maranello is, the car with the jumping horse on its emblem is always at the center of attention. Car History recounts the story of Ferrari, from the very first sports car up to the Ferrari FF, and shows historical footage from the Formula One and interviews with seven times world champion Michael Schumacher.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/15/1740326_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230331094000 +0200" stop="20230331100500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Legendary Races: Targa Florio and Mille Miglia</title>
<desc lang="fr">Italy was home to two of the most famous road races of the 20th century: the Targa Florio and the Mille Miglia. From their very inception, these city to city road races were linked with both glamour and mortality, as racers lost their lives in pursuit of pace. The Targa, for example, was set on the mountain roads of Sicily and featured hairpin bends and dramatic changes of elevation. The Mille Miglia, on the other hand, made legends of marques like Alfa Romeo, Maserati, Mercedes-Benz, and Porsche.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/24/05/1774755_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230331100500 +0200" stop="20230331103500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Car History (Citroen) S2 (n°22)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Citroen»Always ahead of the time, always different from the others: For Citroen, the joy of the extravagance has always been the engine for automotive revolution. But for some time, Citroen mutated from exceptional to mass produced cars. Car History recalls the evolution of Citroen and reveals the secret behind three of its cult cars: the Gooddess, the Gangers' limousine and the Duck.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/15/1740326_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230331103500 +0200" stop="20230331110000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Classic Ride S7</title>
<desc lang="fr">With the M3, BMW brings race car technology to the road! 120 years Mercedes motorsport history. In celebration, Motorvision TV starts at the Nürburgring in Germany, with DTM legends Bernd Schneider and Ellen Lohr! Turbo-Power in the DTM. The Ford Sierra RS Cosworth teaches the racing competition the meaning of fear.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/24/2125716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230331110000 +0200" stop="20230331112500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Sabine Schmitz</title>
<desc lang="fr">&quot;&quot;Queen of the Nordschleife&quot;&quot;.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/19/1774199_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230331112500 +0200" stop="20230331120000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Rallye Sport 1984</title>
<desc lang="fr">1984. The rally professionals and Drift-artists, Hannu Mikkola, Walter Röhrl, Björn Waldegaard, Marku Alen and the rally- Amazon, Michele Mouton, fighting fiercly in Europe and Africa for the World Championship title.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/24/2125717_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230331120000 +0200" stop="20230331122500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Car History (AMG) S2 (n°14)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«AMG»AMG - three letters that quicken your pulse. From the very beginning, AMG has been specialized in improving performance for Mercedes cars. It is the embodiment of automotive performance, exclusivity and dynamic driving pleasure. Car History details AMG's growth from its humble beginnings as an independent engineering firm to being a world renowned company owned by Mercedes-Benz.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/15/1740326_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230331122500 +0200" stop="20230331125000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Car People (The Towing Company) S1 (n°3)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«The Towing Company»Cars which stop driving, are their business. It doesn't matter if it was an accident or a parking offence: Non-moving cars have to be disposed of. It's a case for the breakdown service as they tidy up on the road.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/02/18/36/2149177_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230331125000 +0200" stop="20230331131500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Porsche Is a Religion</title>
<desc lang="fr">Porsche is a religion. The persuasions are: punk, tech and race. Porsche punk, collector and tuner Magnus Walker is the face of this movement. He preaches individualism for historic cars. Tech is personified by Alois RUF since 1983. As an manifestation of the tech movement, the RUF RT 35, which is based on the Porsche Turbo, puts an additional 70 hp to the streets. And Porsche itself has the ultimate track tool for the racers amongst the believers. GT3 RS is the codeword in order to be allowed entry to the motorsports paradise once and for all.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1760716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230331131500 +0200" stop="20230331134500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">WeatherTech SportsCar Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Road to Racing.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/50/1756288_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230331134500 +0200" stop="20230331143500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">NW200 Races Part 1</title>
<desc lang="fr">King of the Roads.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/48/1853102_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230331143500 +0200" stop="20230331152500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Australian V8 Superboats Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Australian V8 Superboat Championship is one of the most important watersports series from down under. Drivers compete in three different classes: the LS Class, Group A and Unlimited, which features hardly any restrictions regarding engine sizes. In 2022, a total of seven rounds are scheduled before a new champion is crowned.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/02/22/26/1784522_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230331152500 +0200" stop="20230331155000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Powerboat: P1 USA AquaX Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">See all the action from the USA series of P1 AquaX, an exciting Jet Ski racing event, operated by Powerboat P1. P1 AquaX is an international motorboat racing competition organised by the Union Internationale Motornautique.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/37/1763088_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230331155000 +0200" stop="20230331162000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">P1 Offshore Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">The P1 Offshore Powerboat Championship promises tightly fought offshore racing with powerboats reaching top speeds of up to 100 miles per hour. Five events are schedules for the 2022 season and Motorvision.TV brings you all the thrilling action from each event!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/05/2038331_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230331162000 +0200" stop="20230331164500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Motonautisme : Championnat du monde de Formule 1</title>
<desc lang="fr">In 2022, the UIM is once again hosting its Formula 1 World Championship in Powerboat. In the 37th season, ten teams with 19 drivers from eleven countries have signed up to fight for the title of the new world champion in three Grand Prix.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/21/2061231_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230331164500 +0200" stop="20230331171500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">UIM Aquabike World Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">Caution, danger of splashing! Since 1992, the Aquabike World Championship has been the most important racing series in the sport of jet skiing and one of the fastest competitions in water sports. On specially designed race courses or on the high seas, the participants engage in thrilling races in the ski and runabout categories and fascinate with all kinds of stunts on their more than 300 hp jet skis.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/31/2029804_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230331171500 +0200" stop="20230331180000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Whanganui, Shelterview, Neuseeland</title>
<desc lang="fr">The New Zealand Jetsprint Championship is the most important sprint boat competition from New Zealand, the country where the sport was founded in 1981. Jetsprinting is comparable to rally sports, but there is only one boat on the track at any given time and boats drive at very high speeds. The up to 500 HP strong jet sprint boats therefore try to achieve the best time on the tracks.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/32/1774197_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230331180000 +0200" stop="20230331182500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Car History (BMW M) S2 (n°16)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«BMW M»The Motorsport division of BMW has been a success story since its inception, but they are not just celebrating success on the race tracks. The road cars with the letter M on the rear fascinate car drivers from around the world and quickly gained a large cult following. Car History looks back on BMW M which was founded in 1972 as BMW Motorsport GmbH.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/15/1740326_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230331182500 +0200" stop="20230331184500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Car People (Race Queen Sabine Schmitz) S1 (n°5)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Race Queen Sabine Schmitz»Sabine Schmitz is the queen of the Nordschleife. In 1996 she won The 24 Hours Nuerburgring in a BMW M3 as the first woman. In the next year she repeated her triumph right again. The Nordschleife has influenced her life.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/02/18/36/2149177_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230331184500 +0200" stop="20230331191000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">All-American Heroes</title>
<desc lang="fr">They are the automotive icons from America: Chevy, Ford Mustang and Corvette. They are extremely popular with the members of the tuning and refining community. They guarantee their owners finest V8 sound a true feeling of freedom. Fans of historic racing cars and rockabilly pay homage to their heroes at the Race 61. Plus: Tuning fathoms the history of the Ford Mustang from the very first to the latest model. It's a wild herd of Mustangs that just waits to be unleashed on the streets. And when all horses are captured again, Tuning releases the Corvette Z06 with the collective power of 659 horses.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1760716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230331191000 +0200" stop="20230331193500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">WeatherTech SportsCar Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Road to Racing.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/40/1752403_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230331193500 +0200" stop="20230331202000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Southern Races Part 1</title>
<desc lang="fr">King of the Roads.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/27/1760732_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230331202000 +0200" stop="20230331204500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Drift : Championnat de France</title>
<desc lang="fr">When it comes to national drift competitions, the French Championship is one of the most important ones. 32 drivers compete in the spectacular main event.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/40/1752403_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230331204500 +0200" stop="20230331213500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">e-Trophée Andros</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Andros Trophy is the French national ice racing championship. The idea appeared long time ago in 1985 when professional racer Max Mamers and the owner of the Andros company, Frédéric Gervoson, met as rugby fans. They spent the winter racing with friends on ice circuits. In 2003 the trophy gained an international aspect with a race at Sherbrooke in Canada. In 2020, the racing series is repositioning itself as an electric racing series.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/43/1884375_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230331213500 +0200" stop="20230331223000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Hi-Tec Drift Allstars Series Australia</title>
<desc lang="fr">The latest drifting competition on Motorvision.TV brings you the best drifters from Australia. Join us for thrilling duels, smoking wheels and non-stop drift battles for the Drift All Stars Series title.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/50/1756288_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230331223000 +0200" stop="20230331232000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">National Legend Cars</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Legends Cars National Championship brings back racing from yesteryear. The series features 5/8 scale replicas of pre-war 1930s Fords, Chevys and Dodges that are equipped with 125bhp-motorcycle engines. These cars are well known for delivering high-octane battles on race tracks around Great Britain.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/37/1760720_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230331232000 +0200" stop="20230331235500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Icelandic Formula Offroad</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Icelandic Formula Off-Road is one of the most extreme racing series in the world and demands everything from the teams and their specially built vehicles. Nearly vertical cliffs have to be climbed, demanding time challenges have to be solved or spectacular aquaplaning stunts have to be performed.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1760716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230331235500 +0200" stop="20230401002000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Car History (BMW) S1 (n°13)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«BMW»If there is a typical BMW, then it is the BMW 3 Series. It is fast, it is a cult, and it is the epitome of the sports sedan. Since its debut in 1975 the BMW 3 Series is the undisputed leader in the premium segment and the right car for every need: It is a family-limousine, sports car, tuning and racing car. Car History recounts all the models and reveals the whole story of the BMW 3 Series.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/15/1740326_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230401002000 +0200" stop="20230401004500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Car People (Pirelli Tuning Award) S1 (n°2)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Pirelli Tuning Award»Extreme lacquering, chrome-plated wheel rims and lots of monitors. Annually the elite of the screwing scene attends the Pirelli Tuning Award.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/02/18/36/2149177_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230401004500 +0200" stop="20230401011000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Monster Tuning</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Monza Rally Show is a true classic amongst drifting shows. Since 1978 motorsport stars meet on the legendary Formula One course in the Italian city of Monza and hold onto the fly-off lever. Patron and MOTOGP star Valentino Rossi and his guests offer the fans an unforgettable show. Also on this episode: The Mercedes G-Class becomes a special off-road vehicle 'ORC Bull'. No part of this ultimate hunting vessel for the toughest terrain remains untouched. Plus: A Mini gets turned into a racing car for the Rally Dakar. Rally pro StephanÃ© Peterhansel explains the basics of race tuning, when he shows his Mini Rally-Countryman.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1760716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230401011000 +0200" stop="20230401014000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">WeatherTech SportsCar Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Road to Racing.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/40/1752403_A.jpg" />
</programme>