<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Voo -->
<programme start="20230402023500 +0200" stop="20230402032000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Australian V8 Superboats Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Australian V8 Superboat Championship is one of the most important watersports series from down under. Drivers compete in three different classes: the LS Class, Group A and Unlimited, which features hardly any restrictions regarding engine sizes. In 2022, a total of seven rounds are scheduled before a new champion is crowned.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/02/22/26/1784522_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230402032000 +0200" stop="20230402035000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Powerboat: P1 USA AquaX Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">See all the action from the USA series of P1 AquaX, an exciting Jet Ski racing event, operated by Powerboat P1. P1 AquaX is an international motorboat racing competition organised by the Union Internationale Motornautique.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/38/1763103_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230402035000 +0200" stop="20230402041500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">P1 Offshore Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">The P1 Offshore Powerboat Championship promises tightly fought offshore racing with powerboats reaching top speeds of up to 100 miles per hour. Five events are schedules for the 2022 season and Motorvision.TV brings you all the thrilling action from each event!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/31/2029804_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230402041500 +0200" stop="20230402044500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Season Review</title>
<desc lang="fr">In 2022, the UIM is once again hosting its Formula 1 World Championship in Powerboat. In the 37th season, ten teams with 19 drivers from eleven countries have signed up to fight for the title of the new world champion in three Grand Prix.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/21/2061231_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230402044500 +0200" stop="20230402051000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">UIM Aquabike World Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">Caution, danger of splashing! Since 1992, the Aquabike World Championship has been the most important racing series in the sport of jet skiing and one of the fastest competitions in water sports. On specially designed race courses or on the high seas, the participants engage in thrilling races in the ski and runabout categories and fascinate with all kinds of stunts on their more than 300 hp jet skis.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/03/2034343_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230402051000 +0200" stop="20230402060000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Whanganui, Shelterview, Neuseeland</title>
<desc lang="fr">The New Zealand Jetsprint Championship is the most important sprint boat competition from New Zealand, the country where the sport was founded in 1981. Jetsprinting is comparable to rally sports, but there is only one boat on the track at any given time and boats drive at very high speeds. The up to 500 HP strong jet sprint boats therefore try to achieve the best time on the tracks.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/18/1774193_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230402060000 +0200" stop="20230402062500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Car History (VW Golf) S2 (n°23)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«VW Golf»The Volkswagen Golf is a reasonable car. it's not really exiting, but a bestseller! With more than 30 million units sold, the Golf is one of the most successful cars in automotive history. The models of the first generation have been cult objects for years, especially the Golf GTI and the Golf Cabriolet. Car History tells the story of the Volkswagen Golf and reveals its secret to success.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/15/1740326_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230402062500 +0200" stop="20230402064500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Car People (Vintage Car Assessor Thomas Eschenbach) S3 (n°27)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Vintage Car Assessor Thomas Eschenbach»Laim, Munich, where Thomas Eschenbach's office is located. For 17 years he has been working as a surveyor for car damages and appraisals. His specialty: surveying and appraising classic cars.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/02/18/36/2149177_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230402064500 +0200" stop="20230402071500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Touareg JE Design</title>
<desc lang="fr">Phoenix Racing takes part in motorsports since the end of the 1990s and can look back at an impressive Wall of Fame. Tuning visits the team at the Nuerburgring. Plus: Tuning checks out the VW Touareg after it got the JE Design treatment and takes a look at the Oldtimer Grand Prix at the Nuerburgring, where thousands of fans of vintage old motorsports cars get together.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1760716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230402071500 +0200" stop="20230402080000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Southern Races Part 2</title>
<desc lang="fr">King of the Roads.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/48/1853102_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230402080000 +0200" stop="20230402082500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Tour European Rally Historic</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Tour European Rally Historic is a brand new independent rally series that made its debut in 2019. It offers an exciting mix of great rallies and outstanding venues.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/10/1763098_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230402082500 +0200" stop="20230402085000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Rali Bae Ceredigion</title>
<desc lang="fr">Tour European Rally is an up-and-coming rally series that combines some of Europe's most breathtaking and challenging rally events into one pan-European rally series. Each season consists of 5-6 individual events, plus annual TER promo events.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/48/2123747_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230402085000 +0200" stop="20230402091500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Championnat de Belgique des Rallyes</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Belgian Rally Championship is one of the most fiercely contested rally championships at a national level. It also attracts prominent guest entrants such as Thierry Neuville, Craig Breen and Stéphane Lefebvre.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/27/24/2149178_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230402091500 +0200" stop="20230402094000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Arctic Lapland Rally - A Tour European Rally Promo Event</title>
<desc lang="fr">Organised as a promo event by the TER, the Artic Lapland Rally is the coldest rally competition in the world. Despite temperatures dropping to -35°C, the rally attracts more than 200,000 spectators to Rovaniemi, the capital of Finnish Lappland. It's hated, but also loved among the 150 drivers taking part every year. MOTORVISION TV shows you the highlights from the 2020 Arctic Lapland Rally.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/55/1999411_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230402094000 +0200" stop="20230402101000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Rallye : Rallye Dakar</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Dakar Rally coverage which is an annual rally raid organised by the Amaury Sport Organisation.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/36/2118143_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230402101000 +0200" stop="20230402110000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Dubai International Baja</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Dubai International Baja, formerly known as the Dubai International Rally, is the oldest motorsport event in the United Arab Emirates. It is part of the reformed FIA World Cup for Cross-Country Bajas and based at the famous Dubai Autodrome. It will see international drivers taking on a demanding 407-kilometer stage running through the Al Qudra desert.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/27/08/1776289_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230402110000 +0200" stop="20230402120000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Australian Offroad Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">Founded in 2007, the Australian Off-Road Championship is the official Enduro championship of Motorcycling Australia. It provides a platform for all Australians that enjoy tight bush trails and fast open tracks. But its goal is not just to produce the nation's biggest off-road event, but also to produce top level off-road competitors who then move on to represent Australia in international Enduro competitions.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/46/1762227_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230402120000 +0200" stop="20230402122500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Car History (BMW M) S2 (n°16)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«BMW M»The Motorsport division of BMW has been a success story since its inception, but they are not just celebrating success on the race tracks. The road cars with the letter M on the rear fascinate car drivers from around the world and quickly gained a large cult following. Car History looks back on BMW M which was founded in 1972 as BMW Motorsport GmbH.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/15/1740326_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230402122500 +0200" stop="20230402124500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Car People (Race Queen Sabine Schmitz) S1 (n°5)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Race Queen Sabine Schmitz»Sabine Schmitz is the queen of the Nordschleife. In 1996 she won The 24 Hours Nuerburgring in a BMW M3 as the first woman. In the next year she repeated her triumph right again. The Nordschleife has influenced her life.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/02/18/36/2149177_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230402124500 +0200" stop="20230402131000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">All-American Heroes</title>
<desc lang="fr">They are the automotive icons from America: Chevy, Ford Mustang and Corvette. They are extremely popular with the members of the tuning and refining community. They guarantee their owners finest V8 sound a true feeling of freedom. Fans of historic racing cars and rockabilly pay homage to their heroes at the Race 61. Plus: Tuning fathoms the history of the Ford Mustang from the very first to the latest model. It's a wild herd of Mustangs that just waits to be unleashed on the streets. And when all horses are captured again, Tuning releases the Corvette Z06 with the collective power of 659 horses.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1760716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230402131000 +0200" stop="20230402134000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">WeatherTech SportsCar Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Road to Racing.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/25/1760725_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230402134000 +0200" stop="20230402142500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Southern Races Part 1</title>
<desc lang="fr">King of the Roads.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/46/1762227_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230402142500 +0200" stop="20230402145000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Drift : Championnat de France</title>
<desc lang="fr">When it comes to national drift competitions, the French Championship is one of the most important ones. 32 drivers compete in the spectacular main event.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/37/1760720_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230402145000 +0200" stop="20230402154000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">e-Trophée Andros</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Andros Trophy is the French national ice racing championship. The idea appeared long time ago in 1985 when professional racer Max Mamers and the owner of the Andros company, Frédéric Gervoson, met as rugby fans. They spent the winter racing with friends on ice circuits. In 2003 the trophy gained an international aspect with a race at Sherbrooke in Canada. In 2020, the racing series is repositioning itself as an electric racing series.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/43/1884375_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230402154000 +0200" stop="20230402163500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Hi-Tec Drift Allstars Series Australia</title>
<desc lang="fr">The latest drifting competition on Motorvision.TV brings you the best drifters from Australia. Join us for thrilling duels, smoking wheels and non-stop drift battles for the Drift All Stars Series title.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1760716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230402163500 +0200" stop="20230402172000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">National Legend Cars</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Legends Cars National Championship brings back racing from yesteryear. The series features 5/8 scale replicas of pre-war 1930s Fords, Chevys and Dodges that are equipped with 125bhp-motorcycle engines. These cars are well known for delivering high-octane battles on race tracks around Great Britain.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/50/1756288_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230402172000 +0200" stop="20230402180000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Icelandic Formula Offroad</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Icelandic Formula Off-Road is one of the most extreme racing series in the world and demands everything from the teams and their specially built vehicles. Nearly vertical cliffs have to be climbed, demanding time challenges have to be solved or spectacular aquaplaning stunts have to be performed.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/40/1752403_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230402180000 +0200" stop="20230402185500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">British Truck Racing</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Brisith Truck Racing Championship features some of the heaviest racing machines you'll ever see. Each truck weighs more than five tonnes and produces in excess of 1000bhp. The 2022 season features a total of 7 events that are contested around the United Kingdom.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1760716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230402185500 +0200" stop="20230402211500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">GT World Challenge America</title>
<desc lang="fr">It's America's most challenging and scenic circuits. GT World Challenge America offers exclusive GT3 racing in an exciting way with the two-driver, 90-minute SprintX style format with full-service pit stops that provide great racing and high competition. Each event features two races per weekend in a friendly atmosphere. Many manufacturers including Acura, BMW, Bentley, Ferrari, Lamborghini, Mercedes-AMG, Nissan, and Porsche campaign entries in the category.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/59/1763095_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230402211500 +0200" stop="20230402225500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">GT World Challenge Europe Sprint Cup</title>
<desc lang="fr">Join Motorvision TV as it brings you all the action from the European sports car racing series.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/50/1756288_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230402225500 +0200" stop="20230403000000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">DTM</title>
<desc lang="fr">The DTM - Deutsche Tourenwagen Masters - is the premier German touring car championship. In 2022, the competition is in its 23rd season and features 16 races across 8 weekends. Motorvision.TV shows the best bits from each event.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/25/2125719_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230403000000 +0200" stop="20230403002500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Car History (Lancia) S2 (n°15)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Lancia»Lancia - Legendary racing successes, technological innovations and exclusive vehicles, made this brand world famous. But Lancia hasn't just enjoyed success in its history. The Italian car manufacturer had to endure severe misfortunes and economic mismanagement as well. Nonetheless, the legend lives on to this day. Car History looks back on the ups and downs in the history of Lancia.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/15/1740326_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230403002500 +0200" stop="20230403004500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Car People (Driving Instructor Danny Pfeil) S1 (n°4)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Driving Instructor Danny Pfeil»The Thomathal at the Katschberg Pass in Austria - there is still a morning early calm. As soon as Danny Pfeil's European Speed Club begins to train for winter racing, the silence is over.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/02/18/36/2149177_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230403004500 +0200" stop="20230403011500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Eco-Tuning</title>
<desc lang="fr">Tuning doesn't always have to be a sin. For its i8, BMW combines the electric future with fuel saving qualities into a spacey future tech mix. But can this concept amaze experienced petrolheads? Plus: Saving fuel by increasing the power. What first appears to be a contradiction, has to proof itself in a practical test. The &quot;Race Chip&quot; is tested on a 3000 kilometers track. Furthermore: What use does the switchable performance increase from DTE Systems have? Patrick Simon is looking for the additional power in Norway.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1760716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230403011500 +0200" stop="20230403014000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">WeatherTech SportsCar Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Road to Racing.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/59/1763095_A.jpg" />
</programme>