<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Voo -->
<programme start="20230416022500 +0200" stop="20230416025500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">P1 Offshore Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">The P1 Offshore Powerboat Championship promises tightly fought offshore racing with powerboats reaching top speeds of up to 100 miles per hour. Five events are schedules for the 2022 season and Motorvision.TV brings you all the thrilling action from each event!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/00/1806160_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230416025500 +0200" stop="20230416032000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">GP of Sharjah, UAE</title>
<desc lang="fr">In 2022, the UIM is once again hosting its Formula 1 World Championship in Powerboat. In the 37th season, ten teams with 19 drivers from eleven countries have signed up to fight for the title of the new world champion in three Grand Prix.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/21/2061231_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230416032000 +0200" stop="20230416035000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">UIM Class 1 Powerboat Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">Want to cool down? The Class 1 Offshore Championship featuring boats with twin inboard 1100hp engines that can reach speeds in excess of 160mph. All boats, which are around 12-14 meters long and 3.5 meters wide, are limited by a minimum weight of 4,950 kilos.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/05/2038331_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230416035000 +0200" stop="20230416041500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">UIM Aquabike World Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">Caution, danger of splashing! Since 1992, the Aquabike World Championship has been the most important racing series in the sport of jet skiing and one of the fastest competitions in water sports. On specially designed race courses or on the high seas, the participants engage in thrilling races in the ski and runabout categories and fascinate with all kinds of stunts on their more than 300 hp jet skis.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/03/2034343_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230416041500 +0200" stop="20230416050500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Australian V8 Superboats Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Australian V8 Superboat Championship is one of the most important watersports series from down under. Drivers compete in three different classes: the LS Class, Group A and Unlimited, which features hardly any restrictions regarding engine sizes. In 2022, a total of seven rounds are scheduled before a new champion is crowned.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/02/22/26/1784522_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230416050500 +0200" stop="20230416060000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">St Pete Downtown, Florida</title>
<desc lang="fr">See all the action from the USA series of P1 AquaX, an exciting Jet Ski racing event, operated by Powerboat P1. P1 AquaX is an international motorboat racing competition organised by the Union Internationale Motornautique.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/37/1763088_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230416060000 +0200" stop="20230416062500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Go Green! S2</title>
<desc lang="fr">For many years, the BMW 3 Series has been on top of its competition. But that might be about to change, because Mercedes launches its all-new C-Class Coupe. Go Green takes a look at the Mercedes-Benz C 350 Blue Efficiency. Plus: The third generation of the Toyota Prius received a face lift. If you don't want to spend money on the new model, you could also buy a used one from the second generation.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748432_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230416062500 +0200" stop="20230416064500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Perfect Ride S2</title>
<desc lang="fr">The duel of the city runabouts. The Audi A1 Quattro versus its significantly cheaper competitor, the Renault Clio RS. Pressing the Gas pedal stylishly! One of the most radical roadsters in the world, the Morgan Plus 8.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/19/1748438_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230416064500 +0200" stop="20230416071000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Top Ten Show S1</title>
<desc lang="fr">Most manufacturers sell their models in other countries. The production figures, therefore, easily rise into the hundreds of thousands. But time and time again, the manufacturers create very special works of art which are limited, exclusive and therefore rather expensive. On this episode of our Top Ten Show we'll show you the rarest series of cars.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/50/1752909_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230416071000 +0200" stop="20230416074000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 13</title>
<desc lang="fr">Street Racers is your backstage pass to the world of Formula E. Every two weeks, the magazine takes a look behind the scenes of the most important electric car racing series and provides reviews, current news, exciting interviews and gripping background reports from the world of Formula E.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/59/1880083_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230416074000 +0200" stop="20230416082500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">GT World Challenge Asia</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Fanatec GT World Challenge Asia is back for another season with five scheduled events for the 2022 season. Unlike its European and North American counterparts, GT World Challenge Asia also features GT4 entries.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/30/2013488_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230416082500 +0200" stop="20230416085000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Tour European Rally Historic</title>
<desc lang="fr">Motorvision TV brings you all the action from the independent rally series taking place around Europe.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/24/1760723_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230416085000 +0200" stop="20230416091500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Rally Terra Valle del Tevere, Italy</title>
<desc lang="fr">Amazing challenge around Europe includes 19 special stages. The top crew will become Tour European Rally champion in one of the most beautiful European rallies.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/24/1760723_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230416091500 +0200" stop="20230416094000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Championnat de Belgique des Rallyes</title>
<desc lang="fr">Motorvision TV brings you all the action from one of the most competitive national rallies in Europe.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/21/2149178_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230416094000 +0200" stop="20230416103500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Rallye : Championnat du monde</title>
<desc lang="fr">Aucune description</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/56/1851758_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230416103500 +0200" stop="20230416113000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">BTRDA Rallycross Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">Being a mixture of circuit racing and rallying, rallycross is often considered to be the wildchild of motor sports. One of the most exciting competitions in this genre is the BTRDA Rallycross Championship. Motorvision.TV brings you the highlights from each of their events.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1760716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230416113000 +0200" stop="20230416120000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Rallye de la Route de la Soie</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Silk Road Rally is repositioning itself for the 2019 season. For the first time ever, the transcontinental off-road race will take its participants across mountains, deserts and endless steppes. The teams will also pass the deepest lake in the world, Lake Baikal. Start of the Silk Roadf Rally is in Irkutsk in the south of Russia, further stages take participants to Mongolia and China. MOTORVISION TV shows the highlights of the 2019 Silk Road Rally.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/48/2123747_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230416120000 +0200" stop="20230416122000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Go Green! S2</title>
<desc lang="fr">A new hybrid at Le Mans: On the track at Le Castellet Japanese car manufacturer Toyota presents its new LMP1 prototype for the 24 Hours of Le Mans. With the Toyota TS 030 hybrid, the Japanese want to challenge Audi, which has dominated the most famous race in the world for years. Plus: AC Schnitzer developed the 99d with Continental, a concept car that puts the focus on the tires.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748432_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230416122000 +0200" stop="20230416124500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Perfect Ride S5</title>
<desc lang="fr">There is hardly any car that's more German than the Volkswagen Passat. It is convenient, solidly constructed and offers enough space for the average German family. But even its eighth generation is quite conservative. It's neither edgy nor does it evoke any emotions. Instead, it's neutrally designed and functional. Perfect Ride reviews the Volkswagen Golf and hunts for more typical German cars.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/19/1748438_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230416124500 +0200" stop="20230416131000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Top Ten Show S1</title>
<desc lang="fr">Today we are going for Lux. It has been said that beauty is in the eye of the beholder. So we promise to maintain some objectivity. Desirable cars are what we want, and what we shall get.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/50/1752909_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230416131000 +0200" stop="20230416133500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 12</title>
<desc lang="fr">Street Racers is your backstage pass to the world of Formula E. Every two weeks, the magazine takes a look behind the scenes of the most important electric car racing series and provides reviews, current news, exciting interviews and gripping background reports from the world of Formula E.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/59/1880083_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230416133500 +0200" stop="20230416142500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">GT World Challenge Asia</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Fanatec GT World Challenge Asia is back for another season with five scheduled events for the 2022 season. Unlike its European and North American counterparts, GT World Challenge Asia also features GT4 entries.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/30/2013488_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230416142500 +0200" stop="20230416145500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Drift : Championnat de France</title>
<desc lang="fr">When it comes to national drift competitions, the French Championship is one of the most important ones. 32 drivers compete in the spectacular main event.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/59/1763095_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230416145500 +0200" stop="20230416211500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Goodwood Members Meeting</title>
<desc lang="fr">Bringing you live coverage of the Goodwood Members' Meeting. Join us for a weekend filled with world-class races and a plenty of other entertaining activities on and off the track. For all motorsport fans, definitely an event you don't want to miss!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1760716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230416211500 +0200" stop="20230416220500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">WeatherTech SportsCar Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">Catch the action from the sports car racing series organized by the International Motor Sports Association. It is America's premier sports car racing series where almost all premium manufacturers are represented. This includes companies such as Acura, Aston Martin, Audi, BMW, Cadillac, Chevrolet, Ferrari, Honda, Lamborghini, Lexus, Mazda, Mercedes-AMG and Porsche.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/25/1760725_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230416220500 +0200" stop="20230416225000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">NW200 Races Part 2</title>
<desc lang="fr">King of the Roads.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/37/1760719_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230416225000 +0200" stop="20230416231500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Autódromo Internacional do Algarve, Portugal</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Michelin Le Mans Cup is an International sports car racing endurance series inspired by the 24 Hours of Le Mans race and run by the Automobile Club de l'Ouest.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/01/06/2177304_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230416231500 +0200" stop="20230416234000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Season Review</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Michelin Le Mans Cup is an International sports car racing endurance series inspired by the 24 Hours of Le Mans race and run by the Automobile Club de l'Ouest.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/01/06/2177304_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230416234000 +0200" stop="20230417000000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 7</title>
<desc lang="fr">When their ambitions exceed their driving skills, when well-secured racing professionals are thrown out of corners, we always have a camera at hand. Breathtaking stunts by professional drivers and slapstick-action in highly-tuned tin can rockets. Spectacular scenes where nobody gets hurt.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/31/00/1748416_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230417000000 +0200" stop="20230417002500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Go Green! S2</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Detroit Motor Show is the biggest auto show in the US. Manufacturers like Ford and GM use the NAIAS to present their eco-friendly products. But German car makers BMW and VW are present as well. Plus: After its debut in the Audi Q5, the hybrid engine finds its way into sedans. Go Green reviews the Audi A6 Hybrid. Its boost the electric engine can briefly be switched to the gasoline engine.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748432_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230417002500 +0200" stop="20230417005500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Perfect Ride S5</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Nuerburgring Nordschleife is unique, world famous and known as the toughest speedway in the world. Despite countless hazards, it's has an exceptional appeal with racing fans. Together with legendary racing driver Hans-Joachim Stuck, Perfect Ride explores the myth Nordschleife and tries to find out, what it takes to be 'King of the Ring'.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/19/1748438_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230417005500 +0200" stop="20230417011500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Top Ten Show S1</title>
<desc lang="fr">The car-manufacturers' design departments are constantly tinkering around, in a quest to invent the perfect car. And more often than not, very elegantly-shaped cars are the result. But sometimes you really have to call into question the designer's taste. We're going to have a look at ten of the ugliest cars.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/40/1752467_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230417011500 +0200" stop="20230417014500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 5</title>
<desc lang="fr">Street Racers is your backstage pass to the world of Formula E. Every two weeks, the magazine takes a look behind the scenes of the most important electric car racing series and provides reviews, current news, exciting interviews and gripping background reports from the world of Formula E.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/59/1880083_A.jpg" />
</programme>