<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Voo -->
<programme start="20230511023000 +0200" stop="20230511032500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Ferrari Challenge Europe</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Ferrari Challenge is a single-marque motorsport championship that was created in 1993 and is now the longest-running single-make series championship. The European series is a two-class championship and by far the largest series. It contains 7 races, held on challenging and most prestigious European circuits.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/25/55/2162175_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230511032500 +0200" stop="20230511041000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">GT World Challenge Asia</title>
<desc lang="fr">Aucune description</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/30/2013488_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230511041000 +0200" stop="20230511045500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">GT World Challenge America</title>
<desc lang="fr">It's America's most challenging and scenic circuits. GT World Challenge America offers exclusive GT3 racing in an exciting way with the two-driver, 90-minute SprintX style format with full-service pit stops that provide great racing and high competition. Each event features two races per weekend in a friendly atmosphere. Many manufacturers including Acura, BMW, Bentley, Ferrari, Lamborghini, Mercedes-AMG, Nissan, and Porsche campaign entries in the category.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/50/1756288_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230511045500 +0200" stop="20230511060000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Autodromo Nazionale Monza, Italy</title>
<desc lang="fr">See all the action and best parts from the GT World Challenge Europe, a sports car racing series divided into two separate championships - the GT World Challenge Europe Sprint Cup, and the GT World Challenge Europe Endurance Cup.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/40/1752403_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230511060000 +0200" stop="20230511063000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Stunt Heroes (The White Army) S1 (n°12)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«The White Army»The Stunt Heroes from Action Concept leave their headquarters behind and travel to a ski resort. Between the trees of a nearby forest they simulate the attack of an army of white-dressed soldiers. As part of this spectacular stunt they want to make a car explode and fly through the air.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/15/35/1790601_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230511063000 +0200" stop="20230511065000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Supercars S6</title>
<desc lang="fr">If we should build our dream garage ther would be a Rolly Royce Phantom, an Aston Martin DBS Superleggera as well as the Audi RS4! A car for every occasion.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748406_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230511065000 +0200" stop="20230511071500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Classic Ride S6</title>
<desc lang="fr">Revisiting the past to portray the classic and veteran cars of decades gone by, meeting the personalities who wrote automotive history, sending very old cars running round very fast circuits.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/24/2125716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230511071500 +0200" stop="20230511074500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 5</title>
<desc lang="fr">Street Racers is your backstage pass to the world of Formula E. Every two weeks, the magazine takes a look behind the scenes of the most important electric car racing series and provides reviews, current news, exciting interviews and gripping background reports from the world of Formula E.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/59/1880083_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230511074500 +0200" stop="20230511083500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Ferrari Challenge Europe</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Ferrari Challenge Europe is back for another season on Motorvision.TV. The longest-running single-make series championship in the history of the Prancing Horse-company promises high performance and talented drivers on challenging tracks around Europe. Seven events are scheduled for the 2022 season including the Finali Mondiali, which brings together the final stages of all Ferrari Challenge divisions around the world.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/25/55/2162175_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230511083500 +0200" stop="20230511092500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Jet Ski World Series</title>
<desc lang="fr">Aucune description</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/37/1763088_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230511092500 +0200" stop="20230511095500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Season Review</title>
<desc lang="fr">In 2022, the UIM is once again hosting its Formula 1 World Championship in Powerboat. In the 37th season, ten teams with 19 drivers from eleven countries have signed up to fight for the title of the new world champion in three Grand Prix.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/21/2061231_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230511095500 +0200" stop="20230511104000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Australian V8 Superboats Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Australian V8 Superboat Championship is one of the most important watersports series from down under. Drivers compete in three different classes: the LS Class, Group A and Unlimited, which features hardly any restrictions regarding engine sizes. In 2022, a total of seven rounds are scheduled before a new champion is crowned.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/02/22/26/1784522_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230511104000 +0200" stop="20230511111000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Powerboat: P1 USA AquaX Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">See all the action from the USA series of P1 AquaX, an exciting Jet Ski racing event, operated by Powerboat P1. P1 AquaX is an international motorboat racing competition organised by the Union Internationale Motornautique.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/37/1763088_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230511111000 +0200" stop="20230511113500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">UIM Class 1 Powerboat Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">Want to cool down? The Class 1 Offshore Championship featuring boats with twin inboard 1100hp engines that can reach speeds in excess of 160mph. All boats, which are around 12-14 meters long and 3.5 meters wide, are limited by a minimum weight of 4,950 kilos.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/05/2038331_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230511113500 +0200" stop="20230511120000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">P1 Offshore Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">The P1 Offshore Powerboat Championship promises tightly fought offshore racing with powerboats reaching top speeds of up to 100 miles per hour. Five events are schedules for the 2022 season and Motorvision.TV brings you all the thrilling action from each event!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/54/1804798_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230511120000 +0200" stop="20230511122500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Stunt Heroes (The Pile-Up) S1 (n°11)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«The Pile-Up»Fog, darkness and a pileup involving multiple cars: It's a scene that you can often see on highways and it's a scene that the Stunt Heroes from Action Concept want to recreate as part of a stunt with burning people, a late arriving fireman and a car that flies through the air. It's a matter of manpower, courage, trust â?&quot; and perfect timing.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/15/35/1790601_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230511122500 +0200" stop="20230511125000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Supercars S6</title>
<desc lang="fr">See the Audi R8 Quattro Performance and the Huracan Evo getting an powerfull update along with the faceliftof the Porsche Macan S with ist ne V6 Engine.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748406_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230511125000 +0200" stop="20230511131500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Classic Ride S6</title>
<desc lang="fr">Luxurious coupes with 12 cylinders! The Jaguar XJC V12 purrs like a kitten and growls like a wild cat. BMW 850. The high-tech luxury coupe from Bavaria tried to snatch the clientele from Mercedes-Benz. A luxury Ferrari on the track. This 250 GTE writes in the sixties racing history.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/24/2125716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230511131500 +0200" stop="20230511134000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 4</title>
<desc lang="fr">Street Racers is your backstage pass to the world of Formula E. Every two weeks, the magazine takes a look behind the scenes of the most important electric car racing series and provides reviews, current news, exciting interviews and gripping background reports from the world of Formula E.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/59/1880083_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230511134000 +0200" stop="20230511143000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Ferrari Challenge Europe</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Ferrari Challenge Europe is back for another season on Motorvision.TV. The longest-running single-make series championship in the history of the Prancing Horse-company promises high performance and talented drivers on challenging tracks around Europe. Seven events are scheduled for the 2022 season including the Finali Mondiali, which brings together the final stages of all Ferrari Challenge divisions around the world.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/25/55/2162175_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230511143000 +0200" stop="20230511145500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Bike World</title>
<desc lang="fr">Bike World revolves around the speedway and the racers swishing by on their two wheelers. Find out the latest news and reports regarding two-wheel competitions in the world of speed. This is the content to enjoy for all motorcycle enthusiasts across the world. Explore the best motorbikes, top locations, and iconic racers who have a lot of fun doing it.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/32/1837877_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230511145500 +0200" stop="20230511152500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 1</title>
<desc lang="fr">Exciting sports show that follows the hottest action from the world's most unique motor sport events. Viewers will have a chance to visit some interesting competitions- from IDEMITSU 600 Super Endurance at the Chang Interna-tional Circuit in Thailand, the winter edition of the Maroc Challenge in Morocco, to the Hispania Rally, the only European rally to take place in the desert, and many more. Viewers will also find out all the news from the world of motor sports.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/40/1752403_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230511152500 +0200" stop="20230511155500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Perfect Ride S6</title>
<desc lang="fr">What's hot and what's not. There are quests to be undertaken, the search for the ideal auto, for the perfect race track for the ultimate accessory gadget. What are the preferred rides of the race legends?</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/09/2153087_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230511155500 +0200" stop="20230511161500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Supercars S6</title>
<desc lang="fr">There are details which set super cars apart from normal cars and these details are essential. Super cars are the biggest, loudest and most expensive cars on the highway; they're four-wheeled works of arts.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748406_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230511161500 +0200" stop="20230511164500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Electric Pickups</title>
<desc lang="fr">Pickups are the epitome of the american way of drive! High displacement V8 engines combined with plenty of space. Seldom seen in Europe, they are the cashcows of many automakers in the US market. In the future traditional manufacturers will hardly be able to avoid an electric versoin of their trucks. And the competition is getting bigger and bigger. Ever since Elon Musk presented the Tesla Cybertruck bothe the established brands and new startups had been on the advance to conquer the market with vehicles that have the equivalent of over 1000 hp. Ford F-150 Ligtning, Bollinger B2 or Hummer EV - Go Green shows what we can expect in the next few years.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1760716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230511164500 +0200" stop="20230511173000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Spotted</title>
<desc lang="fr">Every year, the unique flair of the biker scene in California is a matchless inspiration for Ola Stenegard, Head of Vehicle Design at BMW Motorrad. In Los Angeles he meets world-famous customizers like Michael &quot;Wooley&quot; Woolaway und Alan Stulberg. Plus: MOTORVISION TV - #SPOTTED presents the craziest &quot;homemade supercars&quot; such as the Fahrradi Farfalla FFX, the slowest sports car in the world.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/21/07/1884377_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230511173000 +0200" stop="20230511180000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Trackmasters</title>
<desc lang="fr">On today's show we will be showing you the history of a racing legend who has won the 24-hour race four times in a row: Olaf Manthey. Stick around and perhaps you'll find out the secret of his success.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/25/59/1986723_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230511180000 +0200" stop="20230511182500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Stunt Heroes (The Canonball) S1 (n°13)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«The Canonball»The Stunt Heroes from Action Concept are still at their ski resort and party hard. This time they prepared a spectacular stunt involving a station wagon. It is thrown 50 meters into the air with a cannon and if everything goes according to plan, the high-flying car crashes into a second car on the field.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/15/35/1790601_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230511182500 +0200" stop="20230511184500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Supercars S6</title>
<desc lang="fr">Almost every car manufacturer has their own tuning company, where models improve in performance and get a sportier look. However, for many customers this is not enough. Individuality is the key. Those customers are the target group of smaller tuning companies like Performmaster. Their version of the C63 AMG S features 612 hp instead of 510 hp and a maximum torque of 840 Nm instead of 700 Nm.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748406_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230511184500 +0200" stop="20230511191500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Classic Ride S7</title>
<desc lang="fr">Cruising like in &quot;Miss Marple&quot; times. The 1947 Triumph 1800 Roadster has space for 5 fresh air fans. Le Jog - the toughest classic car rally in Europe. A German women's team takes on the challenge in the VW Iltis. In addition, charming small Cabriolet from the brass age. The 1919 Wolseley Stellite.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/24/2125716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230511191500 +0200" stop="20230511194000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 6</title>
<desc lang="fr">Street Racers is your backstage pass to the world of Formula E. Every two weeks, the magazine takes a look behind the scenes of the most important electric car racing series and provides reviews, current news, exciting interviews and gripping background reports from the world of Formula E.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/59/1880083_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230511194000 +0200" stop="20230511203000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Ferrari Challenge Europe</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Ferrari Challenge Europe is back for another season on Motorvision.TV. The longest-running single-make series championship in the history of the Prancing Horse-company promises high performance and talented drivers on challenging tracks around Europe. Seven events are scheduled for the 2022 season including the Finali Mondiali, which brings together the final stages of all Ferrari Challenge divisions around the world.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/25/55/2162175_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230511203000 +0200" stop="20230511205500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Quattro the New Dimension 1985</title>
<desc lang="fr">With the introduction of the Group D-Monsters in the World Rally Championships, the fight for the title got harder and harder. Thats why Audi brought a strong trump onto the road in 1985 - The Sport Quattro. And with it began a new dimension.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/24/2125717_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230511205500 +0200" stop="20230511212500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">The Duels in Formula 1 - Face off for the crown</title>
<desc lang="fr">Fierce battles for championship titles, fierce duels for race victories and even disputes among teammates: Motorsports has been marked by feuds since its inception. The Formula One World Championship is full of heated rivalries, too, and fierce duels are a regular occurrence in the series. Racing Files looks back on the most exciting championship battles in the world's most important racing competition.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/49/1774755_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230511212500 +0200" stop="20230511221500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Automobilisme : Grand Prix de Monaco historique</title>
<desc lang="fr">Do you miss the thrilling motorsports from yesteryear? Take a trip with Motorvision.TV to the French Riviera, when the Grand Prix de Monaco Historique turns back the wheel of time and brings back legendary racing cars for one more adrenaline-filled race featuring high speeds, risky maneuvers and head-to-head fights that we all love in motorsports.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/54/2007077_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230511221500 +0200" stop="20230511224000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Classic Ride S1</title>
<desc lang="fr">In 1960 the English sports car marque Aston Martin engaged the services of the Italian bodywork craftsmen at Zagato to give the DB4 GT a unique look. An overall weight of 1,250 kilograms and six-cylinder engine with an output of 314hp give this DB4 a power-to-weight ratio comparable with today's Porsche Turbo. With only 23 units built, the DB4 is even more exclusive than any Ferrari GTO.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/24/2125716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230511224000 +0200" stop="20230511233000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Chateau Impney Hill Climb</title>
<desc lang="fr">Motorsports has been taken place at the Château Impney near Droitwich Spa in Worcestershire, England since the 1950s. But no event was as big and successful as the Chateau Impney Hill Climb. Every year, the event attracts a wide array of vintage cars and more modern supercars. However, 2019 sees the last edition of the iconic Chateau Impney Hill Climb.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/37/1760720_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230511233000 +0200" stop="20230512000000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">The Present</title>
<desc lang="fr">Green Hell&quot;. &quot;Gone to Hell.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1760716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230512000000 +0200" stop="20230512002500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Stunt Heroes (The Matrix) S1 (n°10)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«The Matrix»Martial arts specialist Ramazan creates a choreography for a fight. It involves four stuntmen who need to disguise as secret agents and bash on him. Will Ramazan be able to free himself from this uncomfortable position and who will spectacularly take off with a car? Find out on this episode of Stunt Heroes.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/15/35/1790601_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230512002500 +0200" stop="20230512005000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Supercars S6</title>
<desc lang="fr">If we should build our dream garage ther would be a Rolly Royce Phantom, an Aston Martin DBS Superleggera as well as the Audi RS4! A car for every occasion.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748406_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230512005000 +0200" stop="20230512011500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Classic Ride S5</title>
<desc lang="fr">Once a year the noblest and rarest classic cars are gathered at one location: the Concorso d' Eleganza Villa d'Este at Lake Como about 50 kilometers north of Arese. Proud owners present their vintage vehicles from long forgotten decades. Plus: Classic Ride visits French Art Deco beauties at the Retro Classics and the Alfa Museum in Milan, where they show the Alfa Romeo Spider Duetto.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/24/2125716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230512011500 +0200" stop="20230512014500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 3</title>
<desc lang="fr">Street Racers is your backstage pass to the world of Formula E. Every two weeks, the magazine takes a look behind the scenes of the most important electric car racing series and provides reviews, current news, exciting interviews and gripping background reports from the world of Formula E.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/59/1880083_A.jpg" />
</programme>