<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Voo -->
<programme start="20230526023500 +0200" stop="20230526030000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">MXGP of Trentino, Pietramurata</title>
<desc lang="fr">Lap after lap of international motorsports action. This is coverage from the FIM (Fédération Internationale de Motocyclisme) Motocross World Championship where riders from all over the globe compete in high-octane, fast-paced motocross racing. Competitors battle it out in races lasting 35 minutes plus 2 laps per race.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/20/00/1907968_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230526030000 +0200" stop="20230526033000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Grand Prix of Poland, Gliwice</title>
<desc lang="fr">FIM SuperEnduro World Championship has been held since 2007. Its circuits are built inside stadiums or arenas, recreating obstacles such as rocks, boulders and logs. The championship consists of eight Grands Prix spread around the globe on courses that are mostly off-road. These events are split into two days and two different races, after which the points towards the world championship are awarded. Each round includes a motocross test and an extreme test, in addition to the enduro test.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/22/1748447_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230526033000 +0200" stop="20230526041500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Australian Motocross Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Australian ProMX Championship is the nation's premier motocross championship. The series acts as a successful development platform for young Australian talent and is designed as a tiered system with three dedicated classes: MX3 for younger drivers, the MX2 for senior drivers and the MX1, which is the elite category in the championship.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/31/43/1763097_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230526041500 +0200" stop="20230526051000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Grand Prix of France, Bordeaux</title>
<desc lang="fr">FIM X-Trial World Championship is the most prestigious indoor motorcycle trials tournament of the world, organised by the Fédération Internationale de Motocyclisme. The programme presents the highlights of the rounds where the participants have to take on the challenging tracks full of steep climbs and huge rocks.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/13/2162902_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230526051000 +0200" stop="20230526060000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Victoria</title>
<desc lang="fr">Aucune description</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/15/12/2185021_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230526060000 +0200" stop="20230526062500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Stunt Heroes (The Stunt Movies) S3 (n°32)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«The Stunt Movies»To every stunt belongs a little movie. The Stunt Heroes always kept it like that! In the second season the stuntteam created again 13 action-film sequences - sometimes funny, sometimes brutal, sometimes evil - but always spectacular. This special shows all 13 stunt movies of the new season of MotorvisonTVs favourite stunt show.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/15/35/1790601_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230526062500 +0200" stop="20230526065000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Supercars S5</title>
<desc lang="fr">What birngs more fun, than the perfect street? And what is even better than to conquer the street with lightweighted roadsters? Not to much! The &quot;&quot;&quot;Slivretta Hochalpenstrasse&quot;&quot;&quot; in Austria is the ideal palyground for the Lotus Elise and the Roding Roadster. And a very classic car opens it's roff again: the Porsche 911 Targa 4S.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748406_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230526065000 +0200" stop="20230526072000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Classic Ride S2</title>
<desc lang="fr">&quot;Investigate the Porsche cult.&quot; Which ride is more enjoyable, the Porsche tractor or Porsche Targa? Porsche is cult. For over 5 decades the fans have been addicted to these cars out of Zuffenhausen. But when was the big bang of the Porsche brand and when was the first Porsche created?</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/24/2125716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230526072000 +0200" stop="20230526074500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Formula E - Specials</title>
<desc lang="fr">ABB FIA Formula E the Number 1s, a look back over all the races to find the most amazing moments in Formula E's history. We pick the Number 1 moment in ten categories looking at amazing action from overtakes, close shaves, starts, and incidents, through the best driver reactions, FanBoosts and Attack Modes, to innovations and insights, and finally we pick out the best race so far.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/12/06/2195752_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230526074500 +0200" stop="20230526084000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Grand Prix of Spain, Barcelona</title>
<desc lang="fr">X-Trial is a young and dynamic sport. The events take place in arenas and the spectators are up close during the entire period. Spectacular setups with challenging obstacles combined with the skill of the best riders in the world promise great entertainment. Motorvision.TV shows highlights from all six events of the 2022 season.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/13/2162902_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230526084000 +0200" stop="20230526090500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">The Rallye World Championship 1982</title>
<desc lang="fr">The African continent is always a difficult terrain for rally drivers. That wasn't any different for the 1982 World Rally Championship, when heat, dust, mud and hardly passable routes posed major challenges for drivers, co-drivers and engines.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/20/04/2125717_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230526090500 +0200" stop="20230526093000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Legendary Tracks - Brooklands, Monthlery, Avus</title>
<desc lang="fr">Mountain races, rallies and city races: In the early days of motorsport, races were held on existing roads and off-roads. After a series of serious accidents, organizers began to build their own circuits for their events. Today tracks like the Silverstone Circuit, Monza or the Indianapolis Motor Speedway are a Mecca for all racing enthusiasts. MOTORVISION TV looks into the racing files of the world's most legendary racetracks and tells their story.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/49/1774755_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230526093000 +0200" stop="20230526095500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Rallye Monte Carlo Historique</title>
<desc lang="fr">The infamous Monte-Carlo Rally is one of the world's oldest rally events in the world. To pay tribute to its long-lasting history, the Automobile Club de Monaco organizes the Rallye Monte-Carlo Historique. The catch is: Only cars that competed in the Monte-Carlo Rally at least 40 years ago are allowed to take part in the historic edition of the Monte-Carlo Rally.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1760716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230526095500 +0200" stop="20230526102000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Classic Ride S3</title>
<desc lang="fr">It is one of the most spectacular cars of the last 30 years: the Delorean DMC-12. But after 9000 built cars, the production came to an end in 1982.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/24/2125716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230526102000 +0200" stop="20230526105500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Rally Clasico Mallorca</title>
<desc lang="fr">Motorvision.TV shows the best moments from the 2022 eMallorca Challenge.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/51/1752441_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230526105500 +0200" stop="20230526114000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Chateau Impney Hill Climb</title>
<desc lang="fr">Motorsports has been taken place at the Château Impney near Droitwich Spa in Worcestershire, England since the 1950s. But no event was as big and successful as the Chateau Impney Hill Climb. Every year, the event attracts a wide array of vintage cars and more modern supercars. However, 2019 sees the last edition of the iconic Chateau Impney Hill Climb.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/40/1752403_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230526114000 +0200" stop="20230526120000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 6</title>
<desc lang="fr">When their ambitions exceed their driving skills, when well-secured racing professionals are thrown out of corners, we always have a camera at hand. Breathtaking stunts by professional drivers and slapstick-action in highly-tuned tin can rockets. Spectacular scenes where nobody gets hurt.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/31/00/1748416_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230526120000 +0200" stop="20230526122500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Stunt Heroes (Stunt Highlights) S3 (n°31)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Stunt Highlights»Explosions - accidents - pain - stunt coordinator Domi and his team give everything for spectacular stunts - in each episodes they are pushing the limits.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/15/35/1790601_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230526122500 +0200" stop="20230526124500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Supercars S5</title>
<desc lang="fr">Luxury does not necesseraly mean to waste time. Hybrid is one of the techniques wich promises less fuel consumption with a still powerful engine. Lexus ist the pioneer in electrification of cars. Supercars drives the new LS 600h, The BMW Actiev Hybrid 7 and teh Porsche Panamera S E-Hybrid.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748406_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230526124500 +0200" stop="20230526131500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Classic Ride S4</title>
<desc lang="fr">One of the most popular racing series of the world - the Formula Vee. The 'Vee', or simply 'V', stands for Volkswagen, as the small formula cars were equipped with the technology of the legendary Beetle. This historical Formula Vee racing series took place around 15 years ago.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/24/2125716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230526131500 +0200" stop="20230526134000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Formula E - Specials</title>
<desc lang="fr">ABB FIA Formula E the Number 1s, a look back over all the races to find the most amazing moments in Formula E's history. We pick the Number 1 moment in ten categories looking at amazing action from overtakes, close shaves, starts, and incidents, through the best driver reactions, FanBoosts and Attack Modes, to innovations and insights, and finally we pick out the best race so far.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/12/06/2195752_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230526134000 +0200" stop="20230526143500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Grand Prix of Spain, Madrid</title>
<desc lang="fr">X-Trial is a young and dynamic sport. The events take place in arenas and the spectators are up close during the entire period. Spectacular setups with challenging obstacles combined with the skill of the best riders in the world promise great entertainment. Motorvision.TV shows highlights from all six events of the 2022 season.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/13/2162902_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230526143500 +0200" stop="20230526152500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Jet Ski World Series</title>
<desc lang="fr">The &quot;&quot;WGP#1 World Series&quot;&quot; is a jet-ski championship with events in Europe, the US and Asia.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/38/1763103_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230526152500 +0200" stop="20230526155500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">GP of Italy, Regione Sardegna, Qualifying</title>
<desc lang="fr">In 2022, the UIM is once again hosting its Formula 1 World Championship in Powerboat. In the 37th season, ten teams with 19 drivers from eleven countries have signed up to fight for the title of the new world champion in three Grand Prix.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/20/08/2061231_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230526155500 +0200" stop="20230526164500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Australian V8 Superboats Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Australian V8 Superboat Championship is one of the most important watersports series from down under. Drivers compete in three different classes: the LS Class, Group A and Unlimited, which features hardly any restrictions regarding engine sizes. In 2022, a total of seven rounds are scheduled before a new champion is crowned.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/02/22/26/1784522_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230526164500 +0200" stop="20230526171000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Powerboat: P1 USA AquaX Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">See all the action from the USA series of P1 AquaX, an exciting Jet Ski racing event, operated by Powerboat P1. P1 AquaX is an international motorboat racing competition organised by the Union Internationale Motornautique.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/37/1763088_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230526171000 +0200" stop="20230526173500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">UIM Class 1 Powerboat Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">Want to cool down? The Class 1 Offshore Championship featuring boats with twin inboard 1100hp engines that can reach speeds in excess of 160mph. All boats, which are around 12-14 meters long and 3.5 meters wide, are limited by a minimum weight of 4,950 kilos.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/54/1804798_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230526173500 +0200" stop="20230526180000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">P1 Offshore Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">The P1 Offshore Powerboat Championship promises tightly fought offshore racing with powerboats reaching top speeds of up to 100 miles per hour. Five events are schedules for the 2022 season and Motorvision.TV brings you all the thrilling action from each event!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/54/1804798_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230526180000 +0200" stop="20230526182500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Stunt Heroes (Action Special) S3 (n°33)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Action Special»&quot;Stunt Heroes&quot; of MotorvisionTV is giving answers to those questions. The stuntteam of &quot;&quot;action concept&quot;&quot;, one of the biggest film- and stunt productions in Europe is given a spectacular insight to their daily business. Things that are never seen in the movies. Often enough they are working several days or weeks for a five-second-stunt! A tough job! The action-special shows all stunts of the second season of the show, explains differences between the different kinds of tools they got in their arsenal. &quot;Stunt Heroes&quot;.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/15/35/1790601_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230526182500 +0200" stop="20230526184500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Supercars S5</title>
<desc lang="fr">Most people associate Aston Martin with James Bond, luxury, style and elegance or real men. The Vantage N430 is a sports car that makes you feel the heritage of British racecars. It is elegant, fast, comes with a marvelous sound and a design which reminds you of Aston Martin's racing successes from the past. Also on this episode: Supercars checks out the Bentley GTC Speed.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748406_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230526184500 +0200" stop="20230526191000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Classic Ride S2</title>
<desc lang="fr">It looks like a Ferrari but it comes from Bavaria, Germany: The Glas GT, one of the rarest oldtimers in the world!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/24/2125716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230526191000 +0200" stop="20230526194000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Formula E - Specials</title>
<desc lang="fr">In less than six years the ABB FIA Formula E Championship has grown from ambitious start-up to one of the most innovative sports entertainment properties in the world, attracting a host of the globe's biggest automotive manufacturers. The Story Of Formula E plots the extraordinary rise of the all-electric championship with some of the key players including Lucas Di Grassi, Jean Eric Vergne, Sebastien Buemi, Sam Bird and founder Alejandro Agag.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/10/08/2194935_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230526194000 +0200" stop="20230526203000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Grand Prix of Andorra, Andorra La Vella</title>
<desc lang="fr">X-Trial is a young and dynamic sport. The events take place in arenas and the spectators are up close during the entire period. Spectacular setups with challenging obstacles combined with the skill of the best riders in the world promise great entertainment. Motorvision.TV shows highlights from all six events of the 2022 season.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/13/2162902_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230526203000 +0200" stop="20230526205500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">AWD Safari Challenge</title>
<desc lang="fr">Watch the exciting Safari Championship organized by the British All Wheel Drive Club, in which modified 4x4 vehicles of all brands can participate.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/40/1975310_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230526205500 +0200" stop="20230526214500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Hi-Tec Drift Allstars Series Australia</title>
<desc lang="fr">The latest drifting competition on Motorvision.TV brings you the best drifters from Australia. Join us for thrilling duels, smoking wheels and non-stop drift battles for the Drift All Stars Series title.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1760716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230526214500 +0200" stop="20230526221000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Arlington</title>
<desc lang="fr">Aucune description</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1760716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230526221000 +0200" stop="20230526225500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Top Fuel Australia Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">Aucune description</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/50/1756288_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230526225500 +0200" stop="20230527000000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">National Legend Cars</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Legends Cars National Championship brings back racing from yesteryear. The series features 5/8 scale replicas of pre-war 1930s Fords, Chevys and Dodges that are equipped with 125bhp-motorcycle engines. These cars are well known for delivering high-octane battles on race tracks around Great Britain.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/25/1760725_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230527000000 +0200" stop="20230527002500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Stunt Heroes (Revenge) S3 (n°30)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Revenge»The Stunt Heroes are testing for a big movie. They are filming a car crash and the idea is that it should look like if the main character of the movie, the actor is really driving the car. They are using filmtricks and a self constructed airbag to reach their goal. The documentary shows how the stunt people create that kind of stunt.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/15/35/1790601_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230527002500 +0200" stop="20230527005000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Supercars S5</title>
<desc lang="fr">He is one of the most exciting sportscars in the world: the Ferrari 458 Speciale. A screaming racecar for the street, a car that puts your nervs on permanent fire. To drive this rolling thunder is unforgetable. Also in this show. The Mc Laren 650S, a car as fast as the Ferrari but quiet more on the technical than on the emotional side.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748406_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230527005000 +0200" stop="20230527011500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Classic Ride S5</title>
<desc lang="fr">Classic Ride takes a trip around the world to visit some of the most fascinating vintage cars ever built. In Thailand a gull-winged Mercedes 190 SL and other souped-up classic cars take part in the Bangkok Classic Car Ride. Plus: An Oldsmobile convertible travels on Venezuela's most beautiful island, while oldies from the US like a 1952 Chevrolet Styleline become a tourist attraction in Cuba.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/24/2125716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230527011500 +0200" stop="20230527014000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Formula E - Specials</title>
<desc lang="fr">ABB FIA Formula E the Number 1s, a look back over all the races to find the most amazing moments in Formula E's history. We pick the Number 1 moment in ten categories looking at amazing action from overtakes, close shaves, starts, and incidents, through the best driver reactions, FanBoosts and Attack Modes, to innovations and insights, and finally we pick out the best race so far.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/10/08/2194935_A.jpg" />
</programme>