<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Voo -->
<programme start="20230419022500 +0200" stop="20230419025000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Tour European Rally Historic</title>
<desc lang="fr">Motorvision TV brings you all the action from the independent rally series taking place around Europe.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/28/1760738_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230419025000 +0200" stop="20230419031500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Rally Terra Valle del Tevere, Italy</title>
<desc lang="fr">Amazing challenge around Europe includes 19 special stages. The top crew will become Tour European Rally champion in one of the most beautiful European rallies.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/10/1763098_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230419031500 +0200" stop="20230419034000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Championnat de Belgique des Rallyes</title>
<desc lang="fr">Motorvision TV brings you all the action from one of the most competitive national rallies in Europe.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/21/2149178_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230419034000 +0200" stop="20230419043500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Rallye : Championnat du monde</title>
<desc lang="fr">Aucune description</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/56/1851758_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230419043500 +0200" stop="20230419053000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">BTRDA Rallycross Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">Being a mixture of circuit racing and rallying, rallycross is often considered to be the wildchild of motor sports. One of the most exciting competitions in this genre is the BTRDA Rallycross Championship. Motorvision.TV brings you the highlights from each of their events.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/25/1760725_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230419053000 +0200" stop="20230419060000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Rallye de la Route de la Soie</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Silk Road Rally is repositioning itself for the 2019 season. For the first time ever, the transcontinental off-road race will take its participants across mountains, deserts and endless steppes. The teams will also pass the deepest lake in the world, Lake Baikal. Start of the Silk Roadf Rally is in Irkutsk in the south of Russia, further stages take participants to Mongolia and China. MOTORVISION TV shows the highlights of the 2019 Silk Road Rally.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/48/2123747_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230419060000 +0200" stop="20230419062500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Go Green! S3</title>
<desc lang="fr">2007 saw the launch of a successor to the Fiat Cinquecento. The Fiat Twin-Air is greener version of the Fiat 500 and comes with a two-cylinder turbo engine. The sound of its high-torque engine alone makes this car fun and seductive. Plus: Bloggers from around the world get the chance to put the Volvo C30 E to the extreme test in the ice and snow of Northern Sweden.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748432_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230419062500 +0200" stop="20230419065000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Perfect Ride S3</title>
<desc lang="fr">The 2012 Mercedes A-Class managed to shake off its image as a vehicle for retired people. But AMG tops it all and presents the hottest A-Class ever. Its impressive 360-hp engine is the most powerful production four-cylinder in the world. Plus: Musketier Tuning turns the Citroen DS 3 into a defening driving machine. Perfect Ride discusses the differences between the tuned and the production model.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/19/1748438_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230419065000 +0200" stop="20230419071500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Top Ten Show S1</title>
<desc lang="fr">There are cars-- or let's say vehicles, which turn every head on the street. And that's not necessarily because they're beautiful, but because there are exceptionally weird. Some of these drivable oddballs are unique customizations, while others are simply classics. We'll show you the ten strangest vehicles ever built.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/39/1752442_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230419071500 +0200" stop="20230419074000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 10</title>
<desc lang="fr">Street Racers is your backstage pass to the world of Formula E. Every two weeks, the magazine takes a look behind the scenes of the most important electric car racing series and provides reviews, current news, exciting interviews and gripping background reports from the world of Formula E.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/59/1880083_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230419074000 +0200" stop="20230419082500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">GT World Challenge Asia</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Fanatec GT World Challenge Asia is back for another season with five scheduled events for the 2022 season. Unlike its European and North American counterparts, GT World Challenge Asia also features GT4 entries.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/30/2013488_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230419082500 +0200" stop="20230419085500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Dream Cars S2</title>
<desc lang="fr">DreamCars presents the most expensive, most luxurious and fastest dream cars from Germany. Whether it's the Porsche 918 Spyder, Mercedes S-Class, BMW M6 or Audi A8: the premium cars from Germany define the benchmark for comfort, status, dynamics and driving pleasure.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/50/1752909_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230419085500 +0200" stop="20230419092000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 5</title>
<desc lang="fr">Exciting sports show that follows the hottest action from the world's most unique motor sport events. Viewers will have a chance to visit some interesting competitions- from IDEMITSU 600 Super Endurance at the Chang Interna-tional Circuit in Thailand, the winter edition of the Maroc Challenge in Morocco, to the Hispania Rally, the only European rally to take place in the desert, and many more. Viewers will also find out all the news from the world of motor sports.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1760716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230419092000 +0200" stop="20230419095000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Bike World</title>
<desc lang="fr">Bike World is the magazine on MOTORVISION TV for all fans of the lifestyle on two wheels. Whether on the road, off-road or on the race track: Bike World brings the latest trends from the world of motorcycles into living rooms around the world. Watch the latest tests of new two-wheelers, exciting reports from the hottest events and thrilling insights into superbike racing.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/32/1837877_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230419095000 +0200" stop="20230419101500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Perfect Ride S6</title>
<desc lang="fr">What's hot and what's not. There are quests to be undertaken, the search for the ideal auto, for the perfect race track for the ultimate accessory gadget. What are the preferred rides of the race legends?</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/09/2153087_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230419101500 +0200" stop="20230419104000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Supercars S6</title>
<desc lang="fr">There are details which set super cars apart from normal cars and these details are essential. Super cars are the biggest, loudest and most expensive cars on the highway; they're four-wheeled works of arts.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748406_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230419104000 +0200" stop="20230419112500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Spotted</title>
<desc lang="fr">Frank Slopianka is highly ambitious and committed to the drag racing event 'Race@Airport'. The US car dealer from Berlin takes about eleven seconds to finish the quarter mile with his 700-hp Camaro. Tuning company Mansory promises additional acceleration and horse power for Lamborghini cars. A good example is the Mansory Carbonado, a rebuilt Aventador Convertible.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/21/07/1884377_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230419112500 +0200" stop="20230419120000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">BMW M1 Meeting</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Austrian racing scene is now richer by one attraction, having added the Histo Cup Austria. 10.000 motor racing fans make their way to the Salzburgring in Austria to admire over 200 historical race cars in action.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1760716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230419120000 +0200" stop="20230419122500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Go Green! S2</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Geneva Motor Show - the first major European motor show of the year. More than almost any other event, the car show on Lake Geneva represents a variety of studies, exotic and super sports cars.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748432_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230419122500 +0200" stop="20230419125000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Perfect Ride S3</title>
<desc lang="fr">Audi A3, BMW 5 Series and Mercedes CLS have been bestsellers for years. In order to attract even more buyers and close the niches between the different vehicle classes, manufacturers extend their model series every so often: Proven technology under the bonnet, but a redesigned body. The results are cars between two worlds such as A3 Sedan, 5 Series Gran Turismo and CLS Shooting Brake.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/19/1748438_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230419125000 +0200" stop="20230419131500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Top Ten Show S1</title>
<desc lang="fr">Almost every compact car is now available in a sporty version. And funnily enough the little racers usually have more power under the bonnet than you might think.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/40/1752467_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230419131500 +0200" stop="20230419134000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 2</title>
<desc lang="fr">Street Racers is your backstage pass to the world of Formula E. Every two weeks, the magazine takes a look behind the scenes of the most important electric car racing series and provides reviews, current news, exciting interviews and gripping background reports from the world of Formula E.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/59/1880083_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230419134000 +0200" stop="20230419142500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">GT World Challenge Asia</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Fanatec GT World Challenge Asia is back for another season with five scheduled events for the 2022 season. Unlike its European and North American counterparts, GT World Challenge Asia also features GT4 entries.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/30/2013488_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230419142500 +0200" stop="20230419145500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">MXGP of Sardegna, Riola Sardo</title>
<desc lang="fr">Lap after lap of international motorsports action. This is coverage from the FIM (Fédération Internationale de Motocyclisme) Motocross World Championship where riders from all over the globe compete in high-octane, fast-paced motocross racing. Competitors battle it out in races lasting 35 minutes plus 2 laps per race.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/32/1907968_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230419145500 +0200" stop="20230419152000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Grand Prix of France, Nice, Palais Nikaia</title>
<desc lang="fr">FIM SuperEnduro World Championship has been held since 2007. Its circuits are built inside stadiums or arenas, recreating obstacles such as rocks, boulders and logs. The championship consists of eight Grands Prix spread around the globe on courses that are mostly off-road. These events are split into two days and two different races, after which the points towards the world championship are awarded. Each round includes a motocross test and an extreme test, in addition to the enduro test.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/22/1748447_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230419152000 +0200" stop="20230419161000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Australian Motocross Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Australian ProMX Championship is the nation's premier motocross championship. The series acts as a successful development platform for young Australian talent and is designed as a tiered system with three dedicated classes: MX3 for younger drivers, the MX2 for senior drivers and the MX1, which is the elite category in the championship.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/25/1760729_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230419161000 +0200" stop="20230419170500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Grand Prix of Austria, Wiener Neustadt</title>
<desc lang="fr">FIM X-Trial World Championship is the most prestigious indoor motorcycle trials tournament of the world, organised by the Fédération Internationale de Motocyclisme. The programme presents the highlights of the rounds where the participants have to take on the challenging tracks full of steep climbs and huge rocks.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/13/2162902_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230419170500 +0200" stop="20230419180000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Australian Superbike Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">Founded in 1980, the Australian Superbike Championship is one of the most important motorcycle racing competitions in Oceania. It is well respected as a springboard for riders and teams who aspire an international career in motorcycling. The 2022 season is contested in five classes: Superbike, Supersport, Supersport 300, the Yamaha R3 Cup and the Oceania Junior Cup.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/38/1760724_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230419180000 +0200" stop="20230419182000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Go Green! S3</title>
<desc lang="fr">Since Spring - the most beautiful Volkswagen with Blue Motion technology can be seen on our roads: the Volkswagen CC. The addition &quot;CC&quot; stands for Comfort Coupe.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748432_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230419182000 +0200" stop="20230419184500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Perfect Ride S3</title>
<desc lang="fr">For many people, Porsche, Ferrari and Lamborghini offer unaffordable dream cars. But you don't need to spend your annual salary on these brands, if you're looking for a powerful car with high performance and a full sounding engine. For example, the Nissan 370 Z by Nismo is just half the price of a Porsche 911, rarer and with 344 HP as powerful as the German flagship sports car.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/19/1748438_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230419184500 +0200" stop="20230419191000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Top Ten Show S1</title>
<desc lang="fr">At the moment, the industry considers the SUV, Crossover or SAC to be good choices. But is it such a good idea to drive off road with a Porsche Cayenne or BMW 6X? Today, we look at the real off road monsters.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/50/1752909_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230419191000 +0200" stop="20230419194000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 23</title>
<desc lang="fr">Street Racers is your backstage pass to the world of Formula E. Every two weeks, the magazine takes a look behind the scenes of the most important electric car racing series and provides reviews, current news, exciting interviews and gripping background reports from the world of Formula E.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/59/1880083_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230419194000 +0200" stop="20230419202500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">GT World Challenge America</title>
<desc lang="fr">Fanatec GT World Challenge America is the premier North American GT series. Taking place on the best US circuits form Sonoma to Indianapolis, each of the seven race weekends features 90-min double-header races.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/40/1752403_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230419202500 +0200" stop="20230419205000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">P1 Offshore Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">The P1 Offshore Powerboat Championship promises tightly fought offshore racing with powerboats reaching top speeds of up to 100 miles per hour. Five events are schedules for the 2022 season and Motorvision.TV brings you all the thrilling action from each event!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/03/2034343_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230419205000 +0200" stop="20230419212000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">GP of Middle East</title>
<desc lang="fr">In 2022, the UIM is once again hosting its Formula 1 World Championship in Powerboat. In the 37th season, ten teams with 19 drivers from eleven countries have signed up to fight for the title of the new world champion in three Grand Prix.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/21/2061231_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230419212000 +0200" stop="20230419214500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">UIM Class 1 Powerboat Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">Want to cool down? The Class 1 Offshore Championship featuring boats with twin inboard 1100hp engines that can reach speeds in excess of 160mph. All boats, which are around 12-14 meters long and 3.5 meters wide, are limited by a minimum weight of 4,950 kilos.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/31/2029804_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230419214500 +0200" stop="20230419221000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">UIM Aquabike World Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">Caution, danger of splashing! Since 1992, the Aquabike World Championship has been the most important racing series in the sport of jet skiing and one of the fastest competitions in water sports. On specially designed race courses or on the high seas, the participants engage in thrilling races in the ski and runabout categories and fascinate with all kinds of stunts on their more than 300 hp jet skis.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/03/2034343_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230419221000 +0200" stop="20230419230000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Australian V8 Superboats Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Australian V8 Superboat Championship is one of the most important watersports series from down under. Drivers compete in three different classes: the LS Class, Group A and Unlimited, which features hardly any restrictions regarding engine sizes. In 2022, a total of seven rounds are scheduled before a new champion is crowned.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/02/22/26/1784522_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230419230000 +0200" stop="20230420000000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Daytona Beach, Florida</title>
<desc lang="fr">See all the action from the USA series of P1 AquaX, an exciting Jet Ski racing event, operated by Powerboat P1. P1 AquaX is an international motorboat racing competition organised by the Union Internationale Motornautique.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/37/1763088_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230420000000 +0200" stop="20230420005000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Ferrari Challenge Europe</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Ferrari Challenge Europe is back for another season on Motorvision.TV. The longest-running single-make series championship in the history of the Prancing Horse-company promises high performance and talented drivers on challenging tracks around Europe. Seven events are scheduled for the 2022 season including the Finali Mondiali, which brings together the final stages of all Ferrari Challenge divisions around the world.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/25/55/2162175_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230420005000 +0200" stop="20230420011500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Championnat d'Europe de courses de camions</title>
<desc lang="fr">The FIA European Truck Racing Championship is the biggest, most imposing racing series in the world. The racing trucks are equipped with 1200 hp engines doing up to 100 miles per hour. On a grid with 26 big rigs the 5.5-ton machines doing battle there's guaranteed action-packed lights-to-flag racing galore.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/25/00/1748421_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230420011500 +0200" stop="20230420014500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Championnat d'Europe de courses de camions</title>
<desc lang="fr">The FIA European Truck Racing Championship is the biggest, most imposing racing series in the world. The racing trucks are equipped with 1200 hp engines doing up to 100 miles per hour. On a grid with 26 big rigs the 5.5-ton machines doing battle there's guaranteed action-packed lights-to-flag racing galore.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/25/00/1748421_A.jpg" />
</programme>