<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Voo -->
<programme start="20230522023500 +0200" stop="20230522030000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Rallye Munich - Marrakesh 1990</title>
<desc lang="fr">Difficult conditions over 5.000 kilometres. Extreme heat and treacherous water hazards, require everything from the amateur rally drivers.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/24/2125717_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230522030000 +0200" stop="20230522032500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">The Knight from Scotland, Sir Jackie Stewart</title>
<desc lang="fr">One of Britain's best known racing drivers, Sir Jackie Stewart is as respected for his work to improve driver safety standards as he is for his three world championships. Stewart's career encompassed some of the most dangerous years in the history of Formula One, and the Scottish driver's 27 impressive F1 wins pale into insignificance when compared with the number of lives he has helped to save.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/49/1774755_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230522032500 +0200" stop="20230522041000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Silverstone</title>
<desc lang="fr">Aucune description</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/2130215_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230522041000 +0200" stop="20230522044000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Classic Ride S4</title>
<desc lang="fr">A small group of car enthusiastic ladies offers resistance in the otherwise man dominated oldtimer world . One of them is Johanna. The 24-year-old loves her 69s Corvette more than everything. And she would never let a man sit behind the steering wheel of her V8.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/24/2125716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230522044000 +0200" stop="20230522053000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Chateau Impney Hill Climb</title>
<desc lang="fr">Motorsports has been taken place at the Château Impney near Droitwich Spa in Worcestershire, England since the 1950s. But no event was as big and successful as the Chateau Impney Hill Climb. Every year, the event attracts a wide array of vintage cars and more modern supercars. However, 2019 sees the last edition of the iconic Chateau Impney Hill Climb.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/37/1760720_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230522053000 +0200" stop="20230522060000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Schall Motorsport</title>
<desc lang="fr">Since its opening in 1927, the Nürburgring has made a name for itself worldwide as the most demanding racetrack in the world. Nevertheless, or precisely because of this, numerous professional and amateur pilots dare to take on the Nordschleife adventure. Among them are Ralf and Andreas Schall, who have been participating in the races on the Nordschleife with their own racing team for 30 years.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1760716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230522060000 +0200" stop="20230522065000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">British Truck Racing</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Brisith Truck Racing Championship features some of the heaviest racing machines you'll ever see. Each truck weighs more than five tonnes and produces in excess of 1000bhp. The 2022 season features a total of 7 events that are contested around the United Kingdom.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/25/1760725_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230522065000 +0200" stop="20230522074500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">DTM</title>
<desc lang="fr">The DTM - Deutsche Tourenwagen Masters - is the premier German touring car championship. In 2022, the competition is in its 23rd season and features 16 races across 8 weekends. Motorvision.TV shows the best bits from each event.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/25/2125719_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230522074500 +0200" stop="20230522083500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Ferrari Challenge Europe</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Ferrari Challenge is a single-marque motorsport championship that was created in 1993 and is now the longest-running single-make series championship. The European series is a two-class championship and by far the largest series. It contains 7 races, held on challenging and most prestigious European circuits.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/25/55/2162175_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230522083500 +0200" stop="20230522090000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Lausitzring, Germany</title>
<desc lang="fr">League of super sports cars.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/59/1763095_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230522090000 +0200" stop="20230522095000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">WeatherTech SportsCar Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">The IMSA WeatherTech SportsCar Championhip is an endurance racing championship in North America where up to five different classes compete in eleven events.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/59/1763095_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230522095000 +0200" stop="20230522103500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">GT World Challenge Europe Brands Hatch</title>
<desc lang="fr">GT World Challenge Europe arrives at Brands Hatch, showcasing cars from the biggest manufacturers, the likes of Audi, Porsche, Ferrari, and more. View the latest action, updates, and stats from the event!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/37/1760720_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230522103500 +0200" stop="20230522112000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">GT World Challenge America</title>
<desc lang="fr">It's America's most challenging and scenic circuits. GT World Challenge America offers exclusive GT3 racing in an exciting way with the two-driver, 90-minute SprintX style format with full-service pit stops that provide great racing and high competition. Each event features two races per weekend in a friendly atmosphere. Many manufacturers including Acura, BMW, Bentley, Ferrari, Lamborghini, Mercedes-AMG, Nissan, and Porsche campaign entries in the category.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/25/1760725_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230522112000 +0200" stop="20230522115000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Championnat d'Europe de courses de camions</title>
<desc lang="fr">The FIA European Truck Racing Championship is the biggest, most imposing racing series in the world. The racing trucks are equipped with 1200 hp engines doing up to 100 miles per hour. On a grid with 26 big rigs the 5.5-ton machines doing battle there's guaranteed action-packed lights-to-flag racing galore.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/25/00/1748421_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230522115000 +0200" stop="20230522120000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 6</title>
<desc lang="fr">When their ambitions exceed their driving skills, when well-secured racing professionals are thrown out of corners, we always have a camera at hand. Breathtaking stunts by professional drivers and slapstick-action in highly-tuned tin can rockets. Spectacular scenes where nobody gets hurt.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/31/00/1748416_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230522120000 +0200" stop="20230522122500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Stunt Heroes (The Matrix) S1 (n°10)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«The Matrix»Martial arts specialist Ramazan creates a choreography for a fight. It involves four stuntmen who need to disguise as secret agents and bash on him. Will Ramazan be able to free himself from this uncomfortable position and who will spectacularly take off with a car? Find out on this episode of Stunt Heroes.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Découverte</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/15/35/1790601_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230522122500 +0200" stop="20230522125000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Supercars S2</title>
<desc lang="fr">It's showtime! The BMW ACS5 Sport S Limousine is on the track. Last year at the International Motor Show it's 'smoother' brother was introduced and after the 'beauty' now the 'beast' is released.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748406_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230522125000 +0200" stop="20230522131500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Classic Ride S2</title>
<desc lang="fr">There is a crazy new thing from Volkswagen. A car that can dress up after you get it, to look anyway you want it. A car that can be anything, can do anything, is a car that only can be called The Thing by Volkswagen.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/24/2125716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230522131500 +0200" stop="20230522134000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 14</title>
<desc lang="fr">Street Racers is your backstage pass to the world of Formula E. Every two weeks, the magazine takes a look behind the scenes of the most important electric car racing series and provides reviews, current news, exciting interviews and gripping background reports from the world of Formula E.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/59/1880083_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230522134000 +0200" stop="20230522143500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Grand Prix of Spain, Bilbao</title>
<desc lang="fr">Teams and drivers of the 2020 FIM X-Trial World Championship travel to Spain for the fifth round of the season. The round takes place at the Bizkaia Arena, which is the largest mixed-use venue in Spain. What the drivers didn't know at that time: The round in Bilbao became the final round of the 2020 season, because the finale in Andorra got cancelled due to the coronavirus pandemic.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/13/2162902_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230522143500 +0200" stop="20230522150000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Championnat de Belgique des Rallyes</title>
<desc lang="fr">BRC.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/21/2149178_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230522150000 +0200" stop="20230522152500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Rally Regione Piemonte, Italy</title>
<desc lang="fr">Amazing challenge around Europe includes 19 special stages. The top crew will become Tour European Rally champion in one of the most beautiful European rallies.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/48/2123747_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230522152500 +0200" stop="20230522155000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Morocco Desert Challenge</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Morocco Desert Challenge has been the fastest growing rallies in the Sahara since its creation in 2008. Until May 2016 the event was called &quot;the Libya Rally&quot; because its origins were in Libya. As a result of the war in 2011 the Khadafi regime came to an end but it is still impossible to host a large international sports event in Libya. In 2013 the rally was moved to Morocco, and thanks to a huge variety of landscapes and tracks it was a success.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/06/11/2193719_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230522155000 +0200" stop="20230522164500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Middle East Bajas World Cup</title>
<desc lang="fr">Aucune description</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/59/1763095_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230522164500 +0200" stop="20230522173500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">BTRDA Rallycross Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">Aucune description</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/59/1763095_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230522173500 +0200" stop="20230522180000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 2</title>
<desc lang="fr">Aucune description</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/28/1760738_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230522180000 +0200" stop="20230522182500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Stunt Heroes (Motorbike Launch) S3 (n°29)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Motorbike Launch»A new test by the stunt people of Action Concept. They have to show a spectacular flight with a motobike, which is crashing afterwards. But that would be too dangerous for a stuntman. Stunt coordinator Ramazan Bulut hast to be creative. The guys develop a cannon for the motorbike. Will it have enough pressure to shoot the bike? The result is very impressive. Even the hard headed stunt guys are surprised!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Découverte</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/15/35/1790601_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230522182500 +0200" stop="20230522184500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Supercars S5</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Porsche Panamera Turbo S is the most dynamic sedan in the world. No other car finds the perfect balance between calm gliding on the one hand and extreme performance on the other hand. 570 hp, 3,8 seconds from zero to 100 km/h and a top speed of 310 km/h are impressive performance data for this big car. Plus: the Jaguar XJR with a 550 hp V8 engine and the Mercedes CLS 500.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748406_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230522184500 +0200" stop="20230522191000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Classic Ride S1</title>
<desc lang="fr">In its original form the Karmann Ghia promised solid Volkswagen mass produced technology paired with an elegant Italian silhouette. But on this episode a Karmann is put to the test that is very different. Its engine comes from a 10-year-old Porsche. Plus: Classic Ride visits the Mexican Bettle scene which appreciates the Volkswagen Beetle as an collector's item and a means of transport.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/24/2125716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230522191000 +0200" stop="20230522193500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Formula E - Specials</title>
<desc lang="fr">ABB FIA Formula E the Number 1s, a look back over all the races to find the most amazing moments in Formula E's history. We pick the Number 1 moment in ten categories looking at amazing action from overtakes, close shaves, starts, and incidents, through the best driver reactions, FanBoosts and Attack Modes, to innovations and insights, and finally we pick out the best race so far.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/09/40/1997864_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230522193500 +0200" stop="20230522203000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Grand Prix of France, Nice</title>
<desc lang="fr">X-Trial is a young and dynamic sport. The events take place in arenas and the spectators are up close during the entire period. Spectacular setups with challenging obstacles combined with the skill of the best riders in the world promise great entertainment. Motorvision.TV shows highlights from all six events of the 2022 season.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/13/2162902_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230522203000 +0200" stop="20230522205500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">MXGP of Trentino, Pietramurata</title>
<desc lang="fr">Lap after lap of international motorsports action. This is coverage from the FIM (Fédération Internationale de Motocyclisme) Motocross World Championship where riders from all over the globe compete in high-octane, fast-paced motocross racing. Competitors battle it out in races lasting 35 minutes plus 2 laps per race.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/32/1907968_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230522205500 +0200" stop="20230522212500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Grand Prix of Poland, Gliwice</title>
<desc lang="fr">FIM SuperEnduro World Championship has been held since 2007. Its circuits are built inside stadiums or arenas, recreating obstacles such as rocks, boulders and logs. The championship consists of eight Grands Prix spread around the globe on courses that are mostly off-road. These events are split into two days and two different races, after which the points towards the world championship are awarded. Each round includes a motocross test and an extreme test, in addition to the enduro test.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/22/1748447_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230522212500 +0200" stop="20230522221000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Australian Motocross Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Australian ProMX Championship is the nation's premier motocross championship. The series acts as a successful development platform for young Australian talent and is designed as a tiered system with three dedicated classes: MX3 for younger drivers, the MX2 for senior drivers and the MX1, which is the elite category in the championship.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/06/1799367_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230522221000 +0200" stop="20230522230500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Grand Prix of France, Bordeaux</title>
<desc lang="fr">FIM X-Trial World Championship is the most prestigious indoor motorcycle trials tournament of the world, organised by the Fédération Internationale de Motocyclisme. The programme presents the highlights of the rounds where the participants have to take on the challenging tracks full of steep climbs and huge rocks.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/13/2162902_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230522230500 +0200" stop="20230523000000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Victoria</title>
<desc lang="fr">Aucune description</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/15/12/2185021_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230523000000 +0200" stop="20230523002500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Stunt Heroes (The Cannon) S3 (n°27)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«The Cannon»The Stunt Heroes have a new car-canon in their arsenal. The canon accelerates a car in one second from zero to 70 km/h. The Stunt Heroes had something like that before. But the new canon doesn't produce any smoke. That is a very important feature for the filmmakers - now they don't have to digitally remove the smoke out of the stunt. In this episode the guys test the canon after shooting a wild car chase between three cops and a gangster on the autobahn.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Découverte</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/15/35/1790601_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230523002500 +0200" stop="20230523005000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Supercars S5</title>
<desc lang="fr">He is one of the most exciting sportscars in the world: the Ferrari 458 Speciale. A screaming racecar for the street, a car that puts your nervs on permanent fire. To drive this rolling thunder is unforgetable. Also in this show. The Mc Laren 650S, a car as fast as the Ferrari but quiet more on the technical than on the emotional side.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748406_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230523005000 +0200" stop="20230523011500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Classic Ride S2</title>
<desc lang="fr">Prince Leopold of Bavaria owns two cars, which can't be as oppositional: the BMW isetta and the BMW Z8. The BMW Isetta is one oft he most unusual and most successful smal cars of the 50ties. Designed like an egg on wheels, with a 250ccm motobike-engine and 12 hp. The BMW Z8 ist still a dreamcar, with a timeless design, 5-Liter engine and 400hp. Classic Rides follows Leopold of Bavaria, as he gets both cars ready fort he summer.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/24/2125716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230523011500 +0200" stop="20230523014000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 13</title>
<desc lang="fr">Street Racers is your backstage pass to the world of Formula E. Every two weeks, the magazine takes a look behind the scenes of the most important electric car racing series and provides reviews, current news, exciting interviews and gripping background reports from the world of Formula E.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/59/1880083_A.jpg" />
</programme>