<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Voo -->
<programme start="20230503023500 +0200" stop="20230503030000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Tour European Rally Historic</title>
<desc lang="fr">Motorvision TV brings you all the action from the independent rally series taking place around Europe.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/24/1760723_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230503030000 +0200" stop="20230503032500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Rallye Sierra Morena, Spain</title>
<desc lang="fr">Amazing challenge around Europe includes 19 special stages. The top crew will become Tour European Rally champion in one of the most beautiful European rallies.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/28/1760738_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230503032500 +0200" stop="20230503035000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Championnat de Belgique des Rallyes</title>
<desc lang="fr">BRC.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/21/2149178_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230503035000 +0200" stop="20230503041500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Dubai International Baja</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Dubai International Baja, formerly known as the Dubai International Rally, is the oldest motorsport event in the United Arab Emirates. It is part of the reformed FIA World Cup for Cross-Country Bajas and based at the famous Dubai Autodrome. It will see international drivers taking on a demanding 407-kilometer stage running through the Al Qudra desert.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/50/1776289_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230503041500 +0200" stop="20230503044000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Arctic Lapland Rally - A Tour European Rally Promo Event</title>
<desc lang="fr">Organised as a promo event by the TER, the Artic Lapland Rally is the coldest rally competition in the world. Despite temperatures dropping to -35°C, the rally attracts more than 200,000 spectators to Rovaniemi, the capital of Finnish Lappland. It's hated, but also loved among the 150 drivers taking part every year. MOTORVISION TV shows you the highlights from the 2020 Arctic Lapland Rally.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/28/1760738_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230503044000 +0200" stop="20230503053000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Baja Hail Toyota Rally</title>
<desc lang="fr">In 2020, Saudi Arabia hosta the Baja Hail Rally for the 16th time. This year, two rounds of the event take place in the kingdom. Not only do they serve as preparation for the 2021 Dakar Rally, but they also represent the last two rounds of the official FIA World Championship for Cross Country Bajas. MOTORVISION TV shows the highlights from both events.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/33/1786567_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230503053000 +0200" stop="20230503060000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Rallye Classique de Majorque</title>
<desc lang="fr">Aucune description</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/48/2123747_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230503060000 +0200" stop="20230503063000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Stunt Heroes (Salto mortale) S1 (n°2)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Salto mortale»The Stunt Heroes from Action Concept face a new mission: performing a front-flip through the air with a stuntman on board of an estate wagon. It's a new task for coordinator and adrenaline junkie Christoph &quot;Domi&quot; Domanski. Stuntmen Daniel and Lars display a brilliant fighting choreography in some spectacular driving scenes. Adrenaline-pumped stunts with lots of crashing are guaranteed!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/15/35/1790601_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230503063000 +0200" stop="20230503065000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Supercars S6</title>
<desc lang="fr">BMW M3 and Mercedes C63 AMG. The top models battle it out forever. While the C63 has better performance values on paper, the M3 has always been delivering the better performance. It's a never ending back and forth. But they are not alone in their battle for the crown. An exotic creature from Japan lies in wait: the Lexus RC-F. It's eight cylinders and 477 hp push the Japanese extrovert over asphalt. It's top speed: 270 km/h. Is he a threat to its German competitors?</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748406_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230503065000 +0200" stop="20230503072000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Classic Ride S5</title>
<desc lang="fr">Aston Martin usually triggers thoughts of James Bond and wickedly expensive and racy sports cars. But there's more to Aston Martin than that. The British luxury brand also offers sedans like the 1976 Aston Martin Lagonda Shooting Brake. But a solvent Aston fan wanted more so he turned its V8 sedan into to a station wagon. Classic Ride showcases the station wagon and further cars.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/24/2125716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230503072000 +0200" stop="20230503074500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 23</title>
<desc lang="fr">Street Racers is your backstage pass to the world of Formula E. Every two weeks, the magazine takes a look behind the scenes of the most important electric car racing series and provides reviews, current news, exciting interviews and gripping background reports from the world of Formula E.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/59/1880083_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230503074500 +0200" stop="20230503084000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Circuit Paul Ricard, Le Castellet, France</title>
<desc lang="fr">The European Le Mans Series, a series open to Le Mans Prototypes and grand tourer-style racing cars, is back with another action-filled season. This year's calendar features six 4-hour races around Europe including the return of the 4 Hours of Imola.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/08/39/2182076_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230503084000 +0200" stop="20230503090500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Bike World</title>
<desc lang="fr">Bike World revolves around the speedway and the racers swishing by on their two wheelers. Find out the latest news and reports regarding two-wheel competitions in the world of speed. This is the content to enjoy for all motorcycle enthusiasts across the world. Explore the best motorbikes, top locations, and iconic racers who have a lot of fun doing it.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/32/1837877_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230503090500 +0200" stop="20230503093000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 4</title>
<desc lang="fr">Exciting sports show that follows the hottest action from the world's most unique motor sport events. Viewers will have a chance to visit some interesting competitions- from IDEMITSU 600 Super Endurance at the Chang Interna-tional Circuit in Thailand, the winter edition of the Maroc Challenge in Morocco, to the Hispania Rally, the only European rally to take place in the desert, and many more. Viewers will also find out all the news from the world of motor sports.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1760716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230503093000 +0200" stop="20230503100000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Perfect Ride S6</title>
<desc lang="fr">What's hot and what's not. There are quests to be undertaken, the search for the ideal auto, for the perfect race track for the ultimate accessory gadget. What are the preferred rides of the race legends?</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/09/2153087_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230503100000 +0200" stop="20230503103500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Supercars S6</title>
<desc lang="fr">There are details which set super cars apart from normal cars and these details are essential. Super cars are the biggest, loudest and most expensive cars on the highway; they're four-wheeled works of arts.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748406_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230503103500 +0200" stop="20230503110000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Electric Pickups</title>
<desc lang="fr">Pickups are the epitome of the american way of drive! High displacement V8 engines combined with plenty of space. Seldom seen in Europe, they are the cashcows of many automakers in the US market. In the future traditional manufacturers will hardly be able to avoid an electric versoin of their trucks. And the competition is getting bigger and bigger. Ever since Elon Musk presented the Tesla Cybertruck bothe the established brands and new startups had been on the advance to conquer the market with vehicles that have the equivalent of over 1000 hp. Ford F-150 Ligtning, Bollinger B2 or Hummer EV - Go Green shows what we can expect in the next few years.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1760716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230503110000 +0200" stop="20230503114500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Spotted</title>
<desc lang="fr">With its Model S, American carmaker Tesla wants to establish electric engines in the full size class. For the very first time it is possible to attain driving ranges over 400 kilometers. Its tremendous acceleration becomes an image boost for the brand. Porsche stands for lots of speed and horsepower, too. With its Panamera Sport Turismo, the sports car manufacturer taps into a new market.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/21/07/1884377_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230503114500 +0200" stop="20230503120000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Red Gold Dream</title>
<desc lang="fr">This years motto of the Conti Tuning Day is 'power sedans' and Tuning host Lucy examines the bolides carefully. Plus: The McLaren SLR is the masterpiece of Mercedes, a super sports car among all sports cars. Only 3.500 units have been produced. Tunings showcases the most expensive SLR in the world, which outshines all other SLR models.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1760716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230503120000 +0200" stop="20230503122500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Stunt Heroes (Drift, fly &amp; fire) S1 (n°1)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Drift, fly &amp; fire»The Stunt Heroes from the German company â?oeAction Conceptâ? really let it rip. In the past they produced several award-winning stunts, but are always on the hunt for new spectacular scenes. This time stuntman Paul slides under an exploding vehicle. At the same time gangster bride Anna flies through the air.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/15/35/1790601_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230503122500 +0200" stop="20230503125500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Supercars S6</title>
<desc lang="fr">More than 10 years ago the 1,000 hp Bugatti Veyron started a new era of super sports cars. By now almost all renowned manufacturers offer their own supercar. Frequently, today's strongest and fastest cars rely on hybrid technology or even drive in pure electric mode. Supercars takes a look at the sports car of the future and gives an insight into the latest technology and driving systems of the future.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748406_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230503125500 +0200" stop="20230503131500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Classic Ride S1</title>
<desc lang="fr">Once a year Russian vintage fans meet at a spots stadium in Moscow Sports for the Retro Style, a vintage rally through Moscow. Classic Ride takes advantage of the opportunity to celebrate the passion for old cars with Russan drivers. Once ahead of its time, the Citroen SM is now a rare collector's item. Classic Rides takes a look at the French diva with an Italian heart.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/24/2125716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230503131500 +0200" stop="20230503134500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 22</title>
<desc lang="fr">Street Racers is your backstage pass to the world of Formula E. Every two weeks, the magazine takes a look behind the scenes of the most important electric car racing series and provides reviews, current news, exciting interviews and gripping background reports from the world of Formula E.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/59/1880083_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230503134500 +0200" stop="20230503143500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Circuit Paul Ricard, Le Castellet, France</title>
<desc lang="fr">The European Le Mans Series, a series open to Le Mans Prototypes and grand tourer-style racing cars, is back with another action-filled season. This year's calendar features six 4-hour races around Europe including the return of the 4 Hours of Imola.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/08/39/2182076_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230503143500 +0200" stop="20230503150500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">MXGP of Switzerland, Frauenfeld</title>
<desc lang="fr">Lap after lap of international motorsports action. This is coverage from the FIM (Fédération Internationale de Motocyclisme) Motocross World Championship where riders from all over the globe compete in high-octane, fast-paced motocross racing. Competitors battle it out in races lasting 35 minutes plus 2 laps per race.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/32/1907968_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230503150500 +0200" stop="20230503153000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Grand Prix of Israel, Jerusalem, Pais Arena</title>
<desc lang="fr">FIM SuperEnduro World Championship has been held since 2007. Its circuits are built inside stadiums or arenas, recreating obstacles such as rocks, boulders and logs. The championship consists of eight Grands Prix spread around the globe on courses that are mostly off-road. These events are split into two days and two different races, after which the points towards the world championship are awarded. Each round includes a motocross test and an extreme test, in addition to the enduro test.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/22/1748447_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230503153000 +0200" stop="20230503162000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Australian Motocross Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Australian ProMX Championship is the nation's premier motocross championship. The series acts as a successful development platform for young Australian talent and is designed as a tiered system with three dedicated classes: MX3 for younger drivers, the MX2 for senior drivers and the MX1, which is the elite category in the championship.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/25/1760729_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230503162000 +0200" stop="20230503171000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Grand Prix of Spain, Pamplona</title>
<desc lang="fr">FIM X-Trial World Championship is the most prestigious indoor motorcycle trials tournament of the world, organised by the Fédération Internationale de Motocyclisme. The programme presents the highlights of the rounds where the participants have to take on the challenging tracks full of steep climbs and huge rocks.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/13/2162902_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230503171000 +0200" stop="20230503180000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Victoria</title>
<desc lang="fr">Aucune description</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/15/12/2185021_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230503180000 +0200" stop="20230503182500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Stunt Heroes (The Remote Control) S1 (n°3)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«The Remote Control»The Stunt Heroes from Action Concept try out another new stunt: Stuntman Tobi, aka Heidi, operates an Artega GT at full speed with a remote control. This is, however, just a warm-up before the big stunt, in which he drives a car up a steep ramp at 68 mph. The Question is: How high can remote control cars fly? It's an action-packed flying spectacle!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/15/35/1790601_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230503182500 +0200" stop="20230503184500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Supercars S3</title>
<desc lang="fr">They are sleek, they are exclusive and most of all: they are extremely fast - supercars! See the first Arabian supercar and many other brand new luxury sport cars from the Qatar Motor Show.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748406_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230503184500 +0200" stop="20230503191000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Classic Ride S5</title>
<desc lang="fr">For more than 50 years the Porsche 911 has been driving on the roads and race tracks of the world. Each generation set standards in the sports car segment. We look back at the beginnings of this success story. But it is not the only legend from the class of 1963. At the same time Corvette Stingray celebrates its premier and becomes the American sports car dream par excellence.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/24/2125716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230503191000 +0200" stop="20230503194000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 24</title>
<desc lang="fr">Street Racers is your backstage pass to the world of Formula E. Every two weeks, the magazine takes a look behind the scenes of the most important electric car racing series and provides reviews, current news, exciting interviews and gripping background reports from the world of Formula E.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/59/1880083_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230503194000 +0200" stop="20230503203000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Circuit Paul Ricard, Le Castellet, France</title>
<desc lang="fr">The European Le Mans Series, a series open to Le Mans Prototypes and grand tourer-style racing cars, is back with another action-filled season. This year's calendar features six 4-hour races around Europe including the return of the 4 Hours of Imola.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/08/39/2182076_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230503203000 +0200" stop="20230503212500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Jet Ski World Series</title>
<desc lang="fr">Aucune description</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/37/1763088_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230503212500 +0200" stop="20230503215000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">GP of Indonesia, Kopiko</title>
<desc lang="fr">Follow all the exciting action from the adrenaline-filled Formula 1 Powerboat World Championship, an international motorboat racing competition for powerboats, organised by the Union Internationale Motonautique.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/21/2061231_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230503215000 +0200" stop="20230503224000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Australian V8 Superboats Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Australian V8 Superboat Championship is one of the most important watersports series from down under. Drivers compete in three different classes: the LS Class, Group A and Unlimited, which features hardly any restrictions regarding engine sizes. In 2022, a total of seven rounds are scheduled before a new champion is crowned.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/02/22/26/1784522_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230503224000 +0200" stop="20230503231000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Powerboat: P1 USA AquaX Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">See all the action from the USA series of P1 AquaX, an exciting Jet Ski racing event, operated by Powerboat P1. P1 AquaX is an international motorboat racing competition organised by the Union Internationale Motornautique.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/38/1763103_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230503231000 +0200" stop="20230503233500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">UIM Class 1 Powerboat Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">Want to cool down? The Class 1 Offshore Championship featuring boats with twin inboard 1100hp engines that can reach speeds in excess of 160mph. All boats, which are around 12-14 meters long and 3.5 meters wide, are limited by a minimum weight of 4,950 kilos.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/00/1806160_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230503233500 +0200" stop="20230504000000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Meremere Auckland, Neuseeland, Superboat</title>
<desc lang="fr">The New Zealand Jetsprint Championship is the most important sprint boat competition from New Zealand, the country where the sport was founded in 1981. Jetsprinting is comparable to rally sports, but there is only one boat on the track at any given time and boats drive at very high speeds. The up to 500 HP strong jet sprint boats therefore try to achieve the best time on the tracks.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/18/1774193_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230504000000 +0200" stop="20230504002500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Hockenheimring, Germany</title>
<desc lang="fr">League of super sports cars.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/59/1884373_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230504002500 +0200" stop="20230504010500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">GP Croatia, Automotodrom Grobnik</title>
<desc lang="fr">NASCAR, America's most popular racing series, is now well established in Europe and there is no better proof than its European division: the NASCAR Whelen Euro Series. This year, 17 teams from nine different countries with a total of 39 cars prove once again that the NWES with its pure racing character is one of the best touring car series on the old continent. Motorvision.TV shows highlights from every race weekend.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748423_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230504010500 +0200" stop="20230504020000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Goodwood Members Meeting</title>
<desc lang="fr">Goodwood is a british motor racing event where fans get to witness modern and historic racecars in action.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/50/1756288_A.jpg" />
</programme>