<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Voo -->
<programme start="20230325013000 +0100" stop="20230325020000 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Dream Cars S2</title>
<desc lang="fr">They guarantee an exclusive appearance and, More than any other car, stand for status, prestige and perfection: international limousines from Rolls Royce, Bentley, Mercedes, BMW and Jaguar. They are the highlight of the worldwide automotive works and are the defining scale when it comes to magnificent luxury and elegant comfort. DreamCars shows the most expensive, most luxurious and most exclusive limousines in the world.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/50/1752909_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230325020000 +0100" stop="20230325022500 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 2</title>
<desc lang="fr">Exciting sports show that follows the hottest action from the world's most unique motor sport events. Viewers will have a chance to visit some interesting competitions- from IDEMITSU 600 Super Endurance at the Chang Interna-tional Circuit in Thailand, the winter edition of the Maroc Challenge in Morocco, to the Hispania Rally, the only European rally to take place in the desert, and many more. Viewers will also find out all the news from the world of motor sports.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/40/1752403_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230325022500 +0100" stop="20230325025500 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Go Green! S3</title>
<desc lang="fr">From concept to reality - these are important steps for car manufacturers - especially when it comes to environmentally friendly technologies. Go Green! checks out the ecological developments in the motor industry.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748432_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230325025500 +0100" stop="20230325032000 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Bike World</title>
<desc lang="fr">Bike World is the magazine on MOTORVISION TV for all fans of the lifestyle on two wheels. Whether on the road, off-road or on the race track: Bike World brings the latest trends from the world of motorcycles into living rooms around the world. Watch the latest tests of new two-wheelers, exciting reports from the hottest events and thrilling insights into superbike racing.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/32/1837877_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230325032000 +0100" stop="20230325034500 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Perfect Ride S3</title>
<desc lang="fr">1964 saw the introduction of the Ford Mustang, which is considered to be the ancestor of all pony cars. In the first year Ford sold more than 680,000 units of this car. It's a record that no other vehicle was able to break. To this day, people around the world value it for its strength, superior V8 and reasonable price. Perfect Ride reviews the Mustang and its relatives, the Challenger and Camaro.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/09/2153087_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230325034500 +0100" stop="20230325041000 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">MotorStories (L.A. Road Trip - BMW i8) (n°5)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«L.A. Road Trip - BMW i8»Petrolheads in California can only think about horsepower and engine sizes. The hybrid sports car BMW i8 combines these classic values with green thinking and sets new environmental trends. But how do conservative petrolheads respond to such a futuristic and clean car? On the Road Trip through LA some octane junkies who usually drive a Porsche 911, Chevy Corvette or tuned bikes test the BMW i8.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Documentaire</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748434_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230325041000 +0100" stop="20230325043500 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Made In... S2</title>
<desc lang="fr">Kempten in Allgau. The ABT Sportsline company with ? 115 year tradition resides at the foot of the Alps. ABT Sportsline is the largest Volkswagen group-tuning company in the world and works closely with Audi.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/24/02/1748419_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230325043500 +0100" stop="20230325050000 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Manthey Racing</title>
<desc lang="fr">Racing in the Green Hell.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/40/1752403_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230325050000 +0100" stop="20230325052500 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Car History (Ford - The Beginning of the Modern Era) S3 (n°37)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Ford - The Beginning of the Modern Era»At a time when horses and carriages characterized traffic, visionaries like Henry Ford were working on the mobility of tomorrow. His ideas and approaches have a major share of the individual mobilization in the world. The mass production of the Ford models is clearly one of the milestones in automotive history and Fords work has changed the world of cars forever. CAR HISTORY tells the whole story.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/15/1740326_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230325052500 +0100" stop="20230325055000 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Car People (The Red Baron) S2 (n°25)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«The Red Baron»Peter Goldstern- He's the Pilot who flies the King of Tonga around. He takes the Majesty of Tonga all around the South Pacific in the governments very own bright red aircraft. It would take 24 hours to get to Tonga from Germany.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/02/18/36/2149177_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230325055000 +0100" stop="20230325061500 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">GTs</title>
<desc lang="fr">GT used to stand for 'Gran Turisme', high performance racing cars for long-distance races. Today, FIA passes regulations for several GT classes. Car makers offer GT models as &quot;the icing on the cake&quot; of their model ranges, too. Mercedes even names a model GT and tops it all off with the GT S. Porsche knows to excite with a GTS as well, while J-Sport turns the Subaru GT 86 into a power machine.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1760716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230325061500 +0100" stop="20230325064000 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">WeatherTech SportsCar Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Road to Racing.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1760716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230325064000 +0100" stop="20230325073500 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Cookstown Road Races Part 1</title>
<desc lang="fr">King of the Roads.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/27/1760732_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230325073500 +0100" stop="20230325080000 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Drift : Championnat de France</title>
<desc lang="fr">When it comes to national drift competitions, the French Championship is one of the most important ones. 32 drivers compete in the spectacular main event.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/50/1756288_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230325080000 +0100" stop="20230325084500 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">e-Trophée Andros</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Andros Trophy is the French national ice racing championship. The idea appeared long time ago in 1985 when professional racer Max Mamers and the owner of the Andros company, Frédéric Gervoson, met as rugby fans. They spent the winter racing with friends on ice circuits. In 2003 the trophy gained an international aspect with a race at Sherbrooke in Canada. In 2020, the racing series is repositioning itself as an electric racing series.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/43/1884375_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230325084500 +0100" stop="20230325094000 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Hi-Tec Drift Allstars Series Australia</title>
<desc lang="fr">The latest drifting competition on Motorvision.TV brings you the best drifters from Australia. Join us for thrilling duels, smoking wheels and non-stop drift battles for the Drift All Stars Series title.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/37/1760720_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230325094000 +0100" stop="20230325103000 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">National Legend Cars</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Legends Cars National Championship brings back racing from yesteryear. The series features 5/8 scale replicas of pre-war 1930s Fords, Chevys and Dodges that are equipped with 125bhp-motorcycle engines. These cars are well known for delivering high-octane battles on race tracks around Great Britain.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/50/1756288_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230325103000 +0100" stop="20230325110000 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Icelandic Formula Offroad</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Icelandic Formula Off-Road is one of the most extreme racing series in the world and demands everything from the teams and their specially built vehicles. Nearly vertical cliffs have to be climbed, demanding time challenges have to be solved or spectacular aquaplaning stunts have to be performed.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/37/1760720_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230325110000 +0100" stop="20230325112500 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Car History (Auto Union) S3 (n°36)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Auto Union»The Auto Union is the incredible story of the 'Fantastic Four': Horch, Audi, DKW and Wanderer. With the sign of the four rings, they are the second-largest automotive group in Germany behind Opel in the 1930s. The four brands of Auto Union are automobile pacemakers, build technical milestones and the fastest car in the world. Today, the name is long gone, but the brand lives on.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/15/1740326_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230325112500 +0100" stop="20230325115000 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Car People (Vehicle Inspector Thomas Eschenbach) S2 (n°24)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Vehicle Inspector Thomas Eschenbach»Small incident but a big impact. After accidents, a damage appraisal should give a bit of clarity to the situation. The man to do this: Vehicle inspector Thomas Eschenbach.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/02/18/36/2149177_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230325115000 +0100" stop="20230325121500 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Stars of AMG</title>
<desc lang="fr">Mercedes' tuning company AMG starts its own battle of the stars - at least when it comes to horsepower. The C63 AMG, E 63 S AMG and S 63 AMG outdo each other with their performance data. AMG stands for Aufrecht, Melcher and Grossasbach - the founders' names and the founding site. But you could also read it as absolute motoring geniuses, because all stars of AMG offer ultimate driving pleasure.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1760716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230325121500 +0100" stop="20230325124500 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">WeatherTech SportsCar Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Road to Racing.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1760716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230325124500 +0100" stop="20230325133500 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Macau Bike Grand Prix</title>
<desc lang="fr">King of the Roads.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/38/1760724_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230325133500 +0100" stop="20230325142500 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Rolex Monterey Motorsports Reunion</title>
<desc lang="fr">Rolex Monterey Motorsports Reunion was established in 1974 under Monterey Historic Automobile Races moniker by Steve Earle. Today, it is an annual event held at Laguna Seca, California with over 500 historic racecars participating.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/25/1760725_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230325142500 +0100" stop="20230325145000 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Car History (Porsche Racing) S3 (n°27)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Porsche Racing»The Porsche 356, the 550 Spyder and the 917: None is faster, none is more reliable and none is more successful. They make Porsche number 1 in motorsports. In the 50s, 60s and 70s, there is hardly a race and barely a rally, that Porsche does not win. From the beginning, Porsche takes the knowledge gained from racing and uses it for series production.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/15/1740326_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230325145000 +0100" stop="20230325152000 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Classic Ride S7</title>
<desc lang="fr">Whoever believes in the socialist era of the East there was only oil smelly two-stroke Trabant and Wartburg or license production cars á la Lada, is wrong. Companies like Tatra from Czechoslovakia introduced in the fifties advanced, even pioneering automobiles. Unfortunately, the clientele was exclusive, and in the west countries the streamlined cars are big rarities. Today, these cars are cult and interesting collectibles. Classic Ride presents a lover and his extraordinary Tatra T87 of 1937.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/24/2125716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230325152000 +0100" stop="20230325154000 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Car History (SAAB) S2 (n°17)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«SAAB»Saab, the iconic brand from Sweden, is a rolling manifesto of &quot;otherness&quot;. A Saab is the perfect car for all non-conformists who have a sense of aesthetics, quality and comfort. They cars are considered to be individual and innovative. But in the end, Saab is insolvent as well. The fans remain though and keep the brand alive. Car History documents the rise and fall of this unique company.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/15/1740326_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230325154000 +0100" stop="20230325160500 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Hans-Joachim Stuck</title>
<desc lang="fr">Portrait of Hans-Joachim Stuck, one of the best race drivers in Germany. He stopped racing after participating in the 2011 24 Hours of Nürburgring.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/19/1774199_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230325160500 +0100" stop="20230325170000 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Le Mans Classic</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Le Mans Classic is a vintage sports car event that took place for the first time in 2002 on the site of the 24-hour race of Le Mans. All participating drivers are at a top level as far as driving is concerned.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/20/2162901_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230325170000 +0100" stop="20230325172500 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Car History (VW Beetle) S1 (n°7)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«VW Beetle»The People's Car.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/15/1740326_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230325172500 +0100" stop="20230325174500 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Car People (Vintage Car Assessor Thomas Eschenbach) S3 (n°27)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Vintage Car Assessor Thomas Eschenbach»Laim, Munich, where Thomas Eschenbach's office is located. For 17 years he has been working as a surveyor for car damages and appraisals. His specialty: surveying and appraising classic cars.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/02/18/36/2149177_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230325174500 +0100" stop="20230325181500 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Tuner Grand Prix</title>
<desc lang="fr">Today we are at a special event at the Hockenheim Ring in Germany. Because, for over 20 years, the best tuners and drifters in Europe have come here to take part in the 'Tuner Grand Prix'. Enjoy!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1760716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230325181500 +0100" stop="20230325184000 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">WeatherTech SportsCar Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Road to Racing.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1760716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230325184000 +0100" stop="20230325193000 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Cookstown Road Races Part 2</title>
<desc lang="fr">King of the Roads.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/27/1760732_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230325193000 +0100" stop="20230325195500 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Tour European Rally Historic</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Tour European Rally Historic is a brand new independent rally series that made its debut in 2019. It offers an exciting mix of great rallies and outstanding venues.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/27/1760734_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230325195500 +0100" stop="20230325202000 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Rally Montre, Japan</title>
<desc lang="fr">Tour European Rally is an up-and-coming rally series that combines some of Europe's most breathtaking and challenging rally events into one pan-European rally series. Each season consists of 5-6 individual events, plus annual TER promo events.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/28/1760738_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230325202000 +0100" stop="20230325211500 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Rallye : Championnat du monde</title>
<desc lang="fr">Aucune description</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/24/10/1851758_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230325211500 +0100" stop="20230325214000 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Kaiafas Battle</title>
<desc lang="fr">Aucune description</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/31/2029804_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230325214000 +0100" stop="20230325220500 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Rallye de la Route de la Soie</title>
<desc lang="fr">Silk Way Rally is an annual rally raid type of off-road race. The first Silk Way Rally was raced in 2009 from Kazan, Russia to Ashgabat, Turkmenistan. The rally has three categories - moto, cars and trucks. It is one of the biggest rally-raid competitions in the world, and it is traditionally held in mid-summer. In less than two weeks the rally route crosses the territory of several different countries.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/24/1760723_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230325220500 +0100" stop="20230325223000 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Championnat de Belgique des Rallyes</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Belgian Rally Championship is one of the most fiercely contested rally championships at a national level. It also attracts prominent guest entrants such as Thierry Neuville, Craig Breen and Stéphane Lefebvre.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/24/20/2149178_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230325223000 +0100" stop="20230325225500 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Arctic Lapland Rally - A Tour European Rally Promo Event</title>
<desc lang="fr">Organised as a promo event by the TER, the Artic Lapland Rally is the coldest rally competition in the world. Despite temperatures dropping to -35°C, the rally attracts more than 200,000 spectators to Rovaniemi, the capital of Finnish Lappland. It's hated, but also loved among the 150 drivers taking part every year. MOTORVISION TV shows you the highlights from the 2020 Arctic Lapland Rally.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/55/1999411_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230325225500 +0100" stop="20230325232500 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Car History (The Audi Story) S3 (n°35)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«The Audi Story»Selling more than a million cars per year, Audi is now one of the most successful car manufacturers in the world. The brand with the four rings does stand for innovation, superior technology and outstanding design. In the '80s Audi revolutionized the automotive world with the Audi Quattro, which not only changes the world of rally sports but also brings the all-wheel drive to everyday cars.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/15/1740326_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230325232500 +0100" stop="20230325235000 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Car People (Alex Renner Motors Dubai) S2 (n°23)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Alex Renner Motors Dubai»On the outskirts of Dubai, where the desert still prevails, a young man from Germany is working hard to make his dream come true: Alex Renner wants to run the most luxurious garage in the Arabian Golf.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/02/18/36/2149177_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230325235000 +0100" stop="20230326001500 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Magic NumberThree</title>
<desc lang="fr">Want an everyday car with extra power under the bonnet? The BMW 3-Series, Nissan 370 Z or Citroen CS DS3 are rather average cars. But as M-version, Nismo or Musketier, they get wild and become really powerful. While the Bavarian competitor comes with an output of431 hp, the Nismo from Japan offers an output of 344 PS. The Citroen musketeer on the other hand is as strong as 222 French horses.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1760716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230326001500 +0100" stop="20230326004000 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">WeatherTech SportsCar Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Road to Racing.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/25/1760725_A.jpg" />
</programme>