<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Voo -->
<programme start="20230414022500 +0200" stop="20230414025500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">MXGP of Patagonia, Vilal La Angostura</title>
<desc lang="fr">Lap after lap of international motorsports action. This is coverage from the FIM (Fédération Internationale de Motocyclisme) Motocross World Championship where riders from all over the globe compete in high-octane, fast-paced motocross racing. Competitors battle it out in races lasting 35 minutes plus 2 laps per race.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/32/1907968_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230414025500 +0200" stop="20230414032000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Grand Prix of Hungary, Budapest, Papp Laszlo SportAre</title>
<desc lang="fr">FIM SuperEnduro World Championship has been held since 2007. Its circuits are built inside stadiums or arenas, recreating obstacles such as rocks, boulders and logs. The championship consists of eight Grands Prix spread around the globe on courses that are mostly off-road. These events are split into two days and two different races, after which the points towards the world championship are awarded. Each round includes a motocross test and an extreme test, in addition to the enduro test.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/22/1748447_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230414032000 +0200" stop="20230414041000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Australian Motocross Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Australian ProMX Championship is the nation's premier motocross championship. The series acts as a successful development platform for young Australian talent and is designed as a tiered system with three dedicated classes: MX3 for younger drivers, the MX2 for senior drivers and the MX1, which is the elite category in the championship.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/25/1760729_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230414041000 +0200" stop="20230414050000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Grand Prix of Spain, Barcelona</title>
<desc lang="fr">FIM X-Trial World Championship is the most prestigious indoor motorcycle trials tournament of the world, organised by the Fédération Internationale de Motocyclisme. The programme presents the highlights of the rounds where the participants have to take on the challenging tracks full of steep climbs and huge rocks.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/13/2162902_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230414050000 +0200" stop="20230414060000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Australian Superbike Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">Founded in 1980, the Australian Superbike Championship is one of the most important motorcycle racing competitions in Oceania. It is well respected as a springboard for riders and teams who aspire an international career in motorcycling. The 2022 season is contested in five classes: Superbike, Supersport, Supersport 300, the Yamaha R3 Cup and the Oceania Junior Cup.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/38/1760724_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230414060000 +0200" stop="20230414062500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Go Green! S2</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Detroit Motor Show is the biggest auto show in the US. Manufacturers like Ford and GM use the NAIAS to present their eco-friendly products. But German car makers BMW and VW are present as well. Plus: After its debut in the Audi Q5, the hybrid engine finds its way into sedans. Go Green reviews the Audi A6 Hybrid. Its boost the electric engine can briefly be switched to the gasoline engine.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748432_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230414062500 +0200" stop="20230414065500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Perfect Ride S5</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Nuerburgring Nordschleife is unique, world famous and known as the toughest speedway in the world. Despite countless hazards, it's has an exceptional appeal with racing fans. Together with legendary racing driver Hans-Joachim Stuck, Perfect Ride explores the myth Nordschleife and tries to find out, what it takes to be 'King of the Ring'.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/09/2153087_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230414065500 +0200" stop="20230414071500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Top Ten Show S1</title>
<desc lang="fr">The car-manufacturers' design departments are constantly tinkering around, in a quest to invent the perfect car. And more often than not, very elegantly-shaped cars are the result. But sometimes you really have to call into question the designer's taste. We're going to have a look at ten of the ugliest cars.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/40/1752467_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230414071500 +0200" stop="20230414074500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 5</title>
<desc lang="fr">Street Racers is your backstage pass to the world of Formula E. Every two weeks, the magazine takes a look behind the scenes of the most important electric car racing series and provides reviews, current news, exciting interviews and gripping background reports from the world of Formula E.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/59/1880083_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230414074500 +0200" stop="20230414083500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">GT World Challenge Asia</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Fanatec GT World Challenge Asia is back for another season with five scheduled events for the 2022 season. Unlike its European and North American counterparts, GT World Challenge Asia also features GT4 entries.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/30/2013488_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230414083500 +0200" stop="20230414093000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Automobilisme : Grand Prix de Monaco historique</title>
<desc lang="fr">Do you miss the thrilling motorsports from yesteryear? Take a trip with Motorvision.TV to the French Riviera, when the Grand Prix de Monaco Historique turns back the wheel of time and brings back legendary racing cars for one more adrenaline-filled race featuring high speeds, risky maneuvers and head-to-head fights that we all love in motorsports.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/54/2007077_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230414093000 +0200" stop="20230414095500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Rallye Monte Carlo Historique</title>
<desc lang="fr">The infamous Monte-Carlo Rally is one of the world's oldest rally events in the world. To pay tribute to its long-lasting history, the Automobile Club de Monaco organizes the Rallye Monte-Carlo Historique. The catch is: Only cars that competed in the Monte-Carlo Rally at least 40 years ago are allowed to take part in the historic edition of the Monte-Carlo Rally.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/37/1760720_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230414095500 +0200" stop="20230414101500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Stephane Peterhansel</title>
<desc lang="fr">Portrait of Stephane Peterhansel, who is a famous rally driver from France and nine-time winner of the Dakar Rallye.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/19/1774199_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230414101500 +0200" stop="20230414104500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Car History (Volkswagen History (1re partie)) S4 (n°42)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Volkswagen History (1re partie)»The Volkswagen Group is the second biggest car company in the world. It all starts in 1936 with one car: the Volkswagen Beetle. It is supposed to make people's dream of owning a car come true, but turns to be even more: a object of the propaganda in the Third Reich, a developtment worker after WW II, a million seller, a film star and a sports car. The Beetle makes Volkswagen world-famous.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/15/1740326_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230414104500 +0200" stop="20230414111000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Rallye Sport 1984</title>
<desc lang="fr">1984. The rally professionals and Drift-artists, Hannu Mikkola, Walter Röhrl, Björn Waldegaard, Marku Alen and the rally- Amazon, Michele Mouton, fighting fiercly in Europe and Africa for the World Championship title.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/24/2125717_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230414111000 +0200" stop="20230414113500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Car History (Mercedes Motorsports: Rallye Years) S4 (n°48)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Mercedes Motorsports: Rallye Years»Whether it is the Monte Carlo Rally, the European Rally Championship or the Street Grand Prix of Argentina: There was a time when Mercedes dominated the international rally scene with cars like the sluggish 180D or the heavy touring saloons 220 or 300SE. After retiring from Formula 1 and Le Mans, Mercedes used rally sport as a testing ground as the use of close-to-production cars was mandatory. Car History commemorates the entire Mercedes rally history.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/15/1740326_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230414113500 +0200" stop="20230414120000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Classic Ride S3</title>
<desc lang="fr">In the early 70s it was the fastest and most sportive production sports car in Germany: The Porsche Carrera RS. Today the RS is a classic Porsche with the highest acclaim.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/24/2125716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230414120000 +0200" stop="20230414122500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Go Green! S2</title>
<desc lang="fr">No fuel consumption, no noise disturbance and no emissions while driving: That'ts what the Citroen C Zero from France promises. Go Green reviews the egg shaped vehicle. Plus: Daimler wants to prove that hydrogen powered electric vehicles are suitable for daily use and sends three B-Class F-Cell emission free around the world. And: Go Green previews the new Volvo V60 Plug-in-Hybrid.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748432_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230414122500 +0200" stop="20230414125000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Perfect Ride S5</title>
<desc lang="fr">Individuality and a wide array of equipment options are the keys to reaching lots of buyers. At least that's what car manufacturers think when it comes to small cars. Perfect Ride answers the question, if they offer too much lifestyle and reviews three trendy small cars: the Mini 5 door, the Opel Adam Rocks (also known as the Vauxhall Adam Rocks) and the Kia Soul EV.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/19/1748438_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230414125000 +0200" stop="20230414131500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Top Ten Show S1</title>
<desc lang="fr">Some cars are not just a means of transport, but influenced entire generations and became legends on their own. That's why we won't talk about expensive, fast or successful cars on this episode. Instead we show you ten cars that managed to achieve cult status and have numerous fan clubs that are still paying homage to them.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/50/1752909_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230414131500 +0200" stop="20230414134000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 9</title>
<desc lang="fr">Street Racers is your backstage pass to the world of Formula E. Every two weeks, the magazine takes a look behind the scenes of the most important electric car racing series and provides reviews, current news, exciting interviews and gripping background reports from the world of Formula E.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/59/1880083_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230414134000 +0200" stop="20230414142500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">GT World Challenge Asia</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Fanatec GT World Challenge Asia is back for another season with five scheduled events for the 2022 season. Unlike its European and North American counterparts, GT World Challenge Asia also features GT4 entries.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/30/2013488_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230414142500 +0200" stop="20230414145500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">P1 Offshore Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">The P1 Offshore Powerboat Championship promises tightly fought offshore racing with powerboats reaching top speeds of up to 100 miles per hour. Five events are schedules for the 2022 season and Motorvision.TV brings you all the thrilling action from each event!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/05/2038331_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230414145500 +0200" stop="20230414152000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">GP of Sharjah, UAE</title>
<desc lang="fr">In 2022, the UIM is once again hosting its Formula 1 World Championship in Powerboat. In the 37th season, ten teams with 19 drivers from eleven countries have signed up to fight for the title of the new world champion in three Grand Prix.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/21/2061231_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230414152000 +0200" stop="20230414154500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">UIM Class 1 Powerboat Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">Want to cool down? The Class 1 Offshore Championship featuring boats with twin inboard 1100hp engines that can reach speeds in excess of 160mph. All boats, which are around 12-14 meters long and 3.5 meters wide, are limited by a minimum weight of 4,950 kilos.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/03/2034343_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230414154500 +0200" stop="20230414161500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">UIM Aquabike World Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">Caution, danger of splashing! Since 1992, the Aquabike World Championship has been the most important racing series in the sport of jet skiing and one of the fastest competitions in water sports. On specially designed race courses or on the high seas, the participants engage in thrilling races in the ski and runabout categories and fascinate with all kinds of stunts on their more than 300 hp jet skis.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/03/2034343_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230414161500 +0200" stop="20230414170500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Australian V8 Superboats Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Australian V8 Superboat Championship is one of the most important watersports series from down under. Drivers compete in three different classes: the LS Class, Group A and Unlimited, which features hardly any restrictions regarding engine sizes. In 2022, a total of seven rounds are scheduled before a new champion is crowned.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/02/22/26/1784522_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230414170500 +0200" stop="20230414180000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">St Pete Downtown, Florida</title>
<desc lang="fr">See all the action from the USA series of P1 AquaX, an exciting Jet Ski racing event, operated by Powerboat P1. P1 AquaX is an international motorboat racing competition organised by the Union Internationale Motornautique.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/38/1763103_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230414180000 +0200" stop="20230414181500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Go Green! S2</title>
<desc lang="fr">A new hybrid at Le Mans: On the track at Le Castellet Japanese car manufacturer Toyota presents its new LMP1 prototype for the 24 Hours of Le Mans. With the Toyota TS 030 hybrid, the Japanese want to challenge Audi, which has dominated the most famous race in the world for years. Plus: AC Schnitzer developed the 99d with Continental, a concept car that puts the focus on the tires.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748432_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230414181500 +0200" stop="20230414184500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Perfect Ride S5</title>
<desc lang="fr">There is hardly any car that's more German than the Volkswagen Passat. It is convenient, solidly constructed and offers enough space for the average German family. But even its eighth generation is quite conservative. It's neither edgy nor does it evoke any emotions. Instead, it's neutrally designed and functional. Perfect Ride reviews the Volkswagen Golf and hunts for more typical German cars.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/19/1748438_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230414184500 +0200" stop="20230414191000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Top Ten Show S1</title>
<desc lang="fr">Today we are going for Lux. It has been said that beauty is in the eye of the beholder. So we promise to maintain some objectivity. Desirable cars are what we want, and what we shall get.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/50/1752909_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230414191000 +0200" stop="20230414193500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 12</title>
<desc lang="fr">Street Racers is your backstage pass to the world of Formula E. Every two weeks, the magazine takes a look behind the scenes of the most important electric car racing series and provides reviews, current news, exciting interviews and gripping background reports from the world of Formula E.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/59/1880083_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230414193500 +0200" stop="20230414202000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">GT World Challenge Asia</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Fanatec GT World Challenge Asia is back for another season with five scheduled events for the 2022 season. Unlike its European and North American counterparts, GT World Challenge Asia also features GT4 entries.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/30/2013488_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230414202000 +0200" stop="20230414204500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Drift : Championnat de France</title>
<desc lang="fr">When it comes to national drift competitions, the French Championship is one of the most important ones. 32 drivers compete in the spectacular main event.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/59/1763095_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230414204500 +0200" stop="20230414213500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">e-Trophée Andros</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Andros Trophy is the French national ice racing championship. The idea appeared long time ago in 1985 when professional racer Max Mamers and the owner of the Andros company, Frédéric Gervoson, met as rugby fans. They spent the winter racing with friends on ice circuits. In 2003 the trophy gained an international aspect with a race at Sherbrooke in Canada. In 2020, the racing series is repositioning itself as an electric racing series.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/43/1884375_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230414213500 +0200" stop="20230414222500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Hi-Tec Drift Allstars Series Australia</title>
<desc lang="fr">The latest drifting competition on Motorvision.TV brings you the best drifters from Australia. Join us for thrilling duels, smoking wheels and non-stop drift battles for the Drift All Stars Series title.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/40/1752403_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230414222500 +0200" stop="20230414231500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">National Legend Cars</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Legends Cars National Championship brings back racing from yesteryear. The series features 5/8 scale replicas of pre-war 1930s Fords, Chevys and Dodges that are equipped with 125bhp-motorcycle engines. These cars are well known for delivering high-octane battles on race tracks around Great Britain.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/40/1752403_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230414231500 +0200" stop="20230414234500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">AWD Safari Challenge</title>
<desc lang="fr">Every year, the British All Wheel Drive Club organises the AWDC Safari Championship, which has become the largest off-road event in the UK. Modified 4x4 vehicles of all brands can participate in the competition. Those who want to score points here must complete the challenging courses of mud, slush and scree in the shortest possible time.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/24/1760723_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230414234500 +0200" stop="20230415000000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 8</title>
<desc lang="fr">When their ambitions exceed their driving skills, when well-secured racing professionals are thrown out of corners, we always have a camera at hand. Breathtaking stunts by professional drivers and slapstick-action in highly-tuned tin can rockets. Spectacular scenes where nobody gets hurt.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/31/00/1748416_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230415000000 +0200" stop="20230415002500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Go Green! S2</title>
<desc lang="fr">It takes place once a year: Essen has become the scene of action, exceptional attractions and a lot of cars. The Essen Motor Show is T H E event for the automotive and motor sports enthusiasts.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748432_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230415002500 +0200" stop="20230415005500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Perfect Ride S5</title>
<desc lang="fr">It is said to be the first of a new generation. The BMW i8 is truly a miracle of technology and the world's first eco-friendly sports car. The combination of lightweight construction, electrical engine and 3-cylinder combustion engine promises economical driving pleasure. Plus: Perfect Ride reviews the impressive and superlight sports cars Lotus Elise and Roding Roadster in Austria.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/19/1748438_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230415005500 +0200" stop="20230415011500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Top Ten Show S1</title>
<desc lang="fr">It's time to get nostalgic: Who do you think is the most important pioneer of the automotive world? We do a little time travel and trace back the trail of the modern car. While we won't go back to antiquity and the first steam or sail wagons, we'll travel to the beginning of the 20th century and present you the ten oldest car manufacturers.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/50/1752909_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230415011500 +0200" stop="20230415014500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 4</title>
<desc lang="fr">Street Racers is your backstage pass to the world of Formula E. Every two weeks, the magazine takes a look behind the scenes of the most important electric car racing series and provides reviews, current news, exciting interviews and gripping background reports from the world of Formula E.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/59/1880083_A.jpg" />
</programme>