<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Voo -->
<programme start="20230422022500 +0200" stop="20230422025500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Dream Cars S2</title>
<desc lang="fr">DreamCars presents the most expensive, most luxurious and fastest dream cars from Germany. Whether it's the Porsche 918 Spyder, Mercedes S-Class, BMW M6 or Audi A8: the premium cars from Germany define the benchmark for comfort, status, dynamics and driving pleasure.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/50/1752909_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230422025500 +0200" stop="20230422032000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 5</title>
<desc lang="fr">Exciting sports show that follows the hottest action from the world's most unique motor sport events. Viewers will have a chance to visit some interesting competitions- from IDEMITSU 600 Super Endurance at the Chang Interna-tional Circuit in Thailand, the winter edition of the Maroc Challenge in Morocco, to the Hispania Rally, the only European rally to take place in the desert, and many more. Viewers will also find out all the news from the world of motor sports.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/40/1752403_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230422032000 +0200" stop="20230422034500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Bike World</title>
<desc lang="fr">Bike World is the magazine on MOTORVISION TV for all fans of the lifestyle on two wheels. Whether on the road, off-road or on the race track: Bike World brings the latest trends from the world of motorcycles into living rooms around the world. Watch the latest tests of new two-wheelers, exciting reports from the hottest events and thrilling insights into superbike racing.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/32/1837877_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230422034500 +0200" stop="20230422041500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Perfect Ride S6</title>
<desc lang="fr">What's hot and what's not. There are quests to be undertaken, the search for the ideal auto, for the perfect race track for the ultimate accessory gadget. What are the preferred rides of the race legends?</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/09/2153087_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230422041500 +0200" stop="20230422043500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Supercars S6</title>
<desc lang="fr">There are details which set super cars apart from normal cars and these details are essential. Super cars are the biggest, loudest and most expensive cars on the highway; they're four-wheeled works of arts.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748406_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230422043500 +0200" stop="20230422052500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Spotted</title>
<desc lang="fr">Frank Slopianka is highly ambitious and committed to the drag racing event 'Race@Airport'. The US car dealer from Berlin takes about eleven seconds to finish the quarter mile with his 700-hp Camaro. Tuning company Mansory promises additional acceleration and horse power for Lamborghini cars. A good example is the Mansory Carbonado, a rebuilt Aventador Convertible.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/21/07/1884377_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230422052500 +0200" stop="20230422060000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">BMW M1 Meeting</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Austrian racing scene is now richer by one attraction, having added the Histo Cup Austria. 10.000 motor racing fans make their way to the Salzburgring in Austria to admire over 200 historical race cars in action.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1760716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230422060000 +0200" stop="20230422062500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Go Green! S3</title>
<desc lang="fr">Forward-looking design, alternative fuels and new-use approaches: We take a look into the future of mobility and show how BMW and other European car manufacturers are working on the sports cars of tomorrow. Plus: Fewer and fewer people own cars. Instead car sharing becomes increasingly popular. We explain, why people rather share than buy their own car.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748432_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230422062500 +0200" stop="20230422065500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Perfect Ride S3</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Tesla Model S is the car of the 21st century. It teaches the major automobile companies, what is possible when you believe in your own idea. It is one of the most exceptional cars one can buy. It offers an electric range of up to 500 kilometers and accelerates from zero to 100 km/h in 4 seconds. In addition to that, Tesla promises that every buyer can charge its car for free forever.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/19/1748438_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230422065500 +0200" stop="20230422071500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Top Ten Show S1</title>
<desc lang="fr">When car manufacturers decide to name their cars after animals, they're obviously suggesting that their car reflects certain characteristics of the animals that they're naming the cars after.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/50/1752909_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230422071500 +0200" stop="20230422074500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 9</title>
<desc lang="fr">Street Racers is your backstage pass to the world of Formula E. Every two weeks, the magazine takes a look behind the scenes of the most important electric car racing series and provides reviews, current news, exciting interviews and gripping background reports from the world of Formula E.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/59/1880083_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230422074500 +0200" stop="20230422083000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">GT World Challenge America</title>
<desc lang="fr">Fanatec GT World Challenge America is the premier North American GT series. Taking place on the best US circuits form Sonoma to Indianapolis, each of the seven race weekends features 90-min double-header races.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1760716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230422083000 +0200" stop="20230422085500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Drift : Championnat de France</title>
<desc lang="fr">When it comes to national drift competitions, the French Championship is one of the most important ones. 32 drivers compete in the spectacular main event.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/40/1752403_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230422085500 +0200" stop="20230422094500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">e-Trophée Andros</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Andros Trophy is the French national ice racing championship. The idea appeared long time ago in 1985 when professional racer Max Mamers and the owner of the Andros company, Frédéric Gervoson, met as rugby fans. They spent the winter racing with friends on ice circuits. In 2003 the trophy gained an international aspect with a race at Sherbrooke in Canada. In 2020, the racing series is repositioning itself as an electric racing series.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/43/1884375_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230422094500 +0200" stop="20230422103000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Hi-Tec Drift Allstars Series Australia</title>
<desc lang="fr">The latest drifting competition on Motorvision.TV brings you the best drifters from Australia. Join us for thrilling duels, smoking wheels and non-stop drift battles for the Drift All Stars Series title.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/50/1756288_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230422103000 +0200" stop="20230422112000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">National Legend Cars</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Legends Cars National Championship brings back racing from yesteryear. The series features 5/8 scale replicas of pre-war 1930s Fords, Chevys and Dodges that are equipped with 125bhp-motorcycle engines. These cars are well known for delivering high-octane battles on race tracks around Great Britain.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/25/1760725_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230422112000 +0200" stop="20230422120000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">AWD Safari Challenge</title>
<desc lang="fr">Every year, the British All Wheel Drive Club organises the AWDC Safari Championship, which has become the largest off-road event in the UK. Modified 4x4 vehicles of all brands can participate in the competition. Those who want to score points here must complete the challenging courses of mud, slush and scree in the shortest possible time.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/40/1975310_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230422120000 +0200" stop="20230422122000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Go Green! S3</title>
<desc lang="fr">Quiet, efficient, ecologically-sound and still a true sports car. BMW adorns the i8 Concept with these attributes. Although not yet in series production - there is already the matching convertible.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748432_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230422122000 +0200" stop="20230422124500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Perfect Ride S3</title>
<desc lang="fr">The BMW X5 is the best selling SAV (Sports Activity Vehicle) in the world. Since the introduction of this model, which also founded its segment, the X5 was sold more than 1.2 million times. It combines dynamics with luxury and thanks to xDrive, the BMW's all-wheel drive, it always offers best traction. Perfect Ride reviews the recent third generation of the BMW X5 and reveals, where it improved.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/19/1748438_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230422124500 +0200" stop="20230422131000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Top Ten Show S1</title>
<desc lang="fr">The names car manufacturers give their models, are often somewhat uninspiring. And it can be quite difficult to learn anything about the car, from its' name. A lot of cars are therefore called by their nicknames.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/50/1752909_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230422131000 +0200" stop="20230422134000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 3</title>
<desc lang="fr">Street Racers is your backstage pass to the world of Formula E. Every two weeks, the magazine takes a look behind the scenes of the most important electric car racing series and provides reviews, current news, exciting interviews and gripping background reports from the world of Formula E.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/59/1880083_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230422134000 +0200" stop="20230422142500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">GT World Challenge America</title>
<desc lang="fr">Fanatec GT World Challenge America is the premier North American GT series. Taking place on the best US circuits form Sonoma to Indianapolis, each of the seven race weekends features 90-min double-header races.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1760716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230422142500 +0200" stop="20230422145000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">The Duels in Formula 1 - Face off for the crown</title>
<desc lang="fr">Fierce battles for championship titles, fierce duels for race victories and even disputes among teammates: Motorsports has been marked by feuds since its inception. The Formula One World Championship is full of heated rivalries, too, and fierce duels are a regular occurrence in the series. Racing Files looks back on the most exciting championship battles in the world's most important racing competition.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/49/1774755_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230422145000 +0200" stop="20230422154500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Rallye Monte Carlo Historique</title>
<desc lang="fr">The infamous Monte-Carlo Rally is one of the world's oldest rally events in the world. To pay tribute to its long-lasting history, the Automobile Club de Monaco organizes the Rallye Monte-Carlo Historique. The catch is: Only cars that competed in the Monte-Carlo Rally at least 40 years ago are allowed to take part in the historic edition of the Monte-Carlo Rally.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/25/1760725_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230422154500 +0200" stop="20230422161000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Sabine Schmitz</title>
<desc lang="fr">&quot;&quot;Queen of the Nordschleife&quot;&quot;.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/19/1774199_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230422161000 +0200" stop="20230422163500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Car History (Mercedes - Beginning of a Success Story) S4 (n°51)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Mercedes - Beginning of a Success Story»From the first three-wheel automobile to the shining star of the â??30s, from Simplex to 500K: No other brand characterizes the first 50 years of the motor better than Mercedes, no other brand represents the evolution of the automobile more than Mercedes. Car History tells the full story of this iconic brand with the three-pointed star emblem, from the invention of the automobile to a global player.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/15/1740326_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230422163500 +0200" stop="20230422170000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">BMW Motorsport 1976</title>
<desc lang="fr">In 1976, the 3-liter BMW CSL was one of the dream cars of BMW Motorsports history in the 70's. It won numerous championships. BMW was also very successful with other models in motorsport.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/24/2125717_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230422170000 +0200" stop="20230422172500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Car History (Porsche 550 Spyder) S2 (n°26)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Porsche 550 Spyder»The Porsche 550 Spyder is small, flat and fast. Even though it was built only 140 times, the 550 Spyder still made history. It laid the foundation for Porsche's success in motorsports and it was the car, in which Hollywood star James Dean was killed. This accident not only turned Dean into a legend, but they Porsche 550 as well. Car History reveals the whole story of the dream car from the 1950s.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/15/1740326_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230422172500 +0200" stop="20230422180000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Classic Ride S3</title>
<desc lang="fr">It is sexy, spectacular and comes with tremendous speed: the Audi Sport quattro S1, the most exciting rally car ever built. In part 2 of the S1 special, Classic Rides accompanies S1 pilot Michael Gerber during the second day of the Rally Legend. Plus: The whole story of the S1 told with original comments by former world champion Walter Röhrl.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/24/2125716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230422180000 +0200" stop="20230422182500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Go Green! S3</title>
<desc lang="fr">Flowing lines, unusual proportions and movements inspired by natural forms: Japanese car manufacturers give their vehicles a striking design and innovative technology. We take a look at the Nissan Resonance and concept cars from Infiniti. Plus: The Toyota i-Road and the IMA Colibri are two absolutely extraordinary cars that might revolutionize mobility in cities.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748432_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230422182500 +0200" stop="20230422185000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Perfect Ride S1</title>
<desc lang="fr">Today's Perfect Ride episode is all about power and torque: Perfect, faster, further - racer Dennis Rostek drives it to the top. With Mathilda Racing on the Nurburgring Nordschleife.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/19/1748438_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230422185000 +0200" stop="20230422191500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Top Ten Show S1</title>
<desc lang="fr">These days everyone talks is how we can make cars more fuel efficient and more environmentally friendly. Electro- cars, hybrid cars, 1 litre-engine cars and 3 cylinder cars, all seem to be the craze at the moment. But we are going to turn all of this on its head and have a look at ten cars that suffer from dreadful fuel consumption.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/40/1752467_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230422191500 +0200" stop="20230422194000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 2</title>
<desc lang="fr">Street Racers is your backstage pass to the world of Formula E. Every two weeks, the magazine takes a look behind the scenes of the most important electric car racing series and provides reviews, current news, exciting interviews and gripping background reports from the world of Formula E.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/59/1880083_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230422194000 +0200" stop="20230422202500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">GT World Challenge America</title>
<desc lang="fr">Fanatec GT World Challenge America is the premier North American GT series. Taking place on the best US circuits form Sonoma to Indianapolis, each of the seven race weekends features 90-min double-header races.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/59/1763095_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230422202500 +0200" stop="20230422205000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Tour European Rally Historic</title>
<desc lang="fr">Motorvision TV brings you all the action from the independent rally series taking place around Europe.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/54/1853467_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230422205000 +0200" stop="20230422211500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Rallye Sierra Morena, Spain</title>
<desc lang="fr">Amazing challenge around Europe includes 19 special stages. The top crew will become Tour European Rally champion in one of the most beautiful European rallies.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/27/1760734_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230422211500 +0200" stop="20230422214500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Championnat de Belgique des Rallyes</title>
<desc lang="fr">Motorvision TV brings you all the action from one of the most competitive national rallies in Europe.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/21/2149178_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230422214500 +0200" stop="20230422221000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Spa-Classic</title>
<desc lang="fr">Created in 2011 on one of the most iconic circuit in the world, the Spa Classic is now one of the major European events for historic racing cars. In 2019, Spa Classic celebrates its ninth staging and features events like nighttime races for touring cars and the Heritage Touring Cup, which pays tribute to the famous Spa-Francorchamps 24 Hours for Touring Cars.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/50/1756288_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230422221000 +0200" stop="20230422230500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Baja Hail Toyota Rally</title>
<desc lang="fr">In 2020, Saudi Arabia hosta the Baja Hail Rally for the 16th time. This year, two rounds of the event take place in the kingdom. Not only do they serve as preparation for the 2021 Dakar Rally, but they also represent the last two rounds of the official FIA World Championship for Cross Country Bajas. MOTORVISION TV shows the highlights from both events.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/33/1786567_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230422230500 +0200" stop="20230422233000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Rallye : Rallye d'Andalousie</title>
<desc lang="fr">Aucune description</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/08/53/1823540_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230422233000 +0200" stop="20230423000000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Rallye de la Route de la Soie</title>
<desc lang="fr">Silk Way Rally is an annual rally raid type of off-road race. The first Silk Way Rally was raced in 2009 from Kazan, Russia to Ashgabat, Turkmenistan. The rally has three categories - moto, cars and trucks. It is one of the biggest rally-raid competitions in the world, and it is traditionally held in mid-summer. In less than two weeks the rally route crosses the territory of several different countries.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/28/1760738_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230423000000 +0200" stop="20230423002000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Go Green! S3</title>
<desc lang="fr">Since Spring - the most beautiful Volkswagen with Blue Motion technology can be seen on our roads: the Volkswagen CC. The addition &quot;CC&quot; stands for Comfort Coupe.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748432_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230423002000 +0200" stop="20230423005000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Perfect Ride S3</title>
<desc lang="fr">For many people, Porsche, Ferrari and Lamborghini offer unaffordable dream cars. But you don't need to spend your annual salary on these brands, if you're looking for a powerful car with high performance and a full sounding engine. For example, the Nissan 370 Z by Nismo is just half the price of a Porsche 911, rarer and with 344 HP as powerful as the German flagship sports car.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/19/1748438_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230423005000 +0200" stop="20230423011500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Top Ten Show S1</title>
<desc lang="fr">At the moment, the industry considers the SUV, Crossover or SAC to be good choices. But is it such a good idea to drive off road with a Porsche Cayenne or BMW 6X? Today, we look at the real off road monsters.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/50/1752909_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230423011500 +0200" stop="20230423014000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 23</title>
<desc lang="fr">Street Racers is your backstage pass to the world of Formula E. Every two weeks, the magazine takes a look behind the scenes of the most important electric car racing series and provides reviews, current news, exciting interviews and gripping background reports from the world of Formula E.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/59/1880083_A.jpg" />
</programme>