<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Voo -->
<programme start="20230323012000 +0100" stop="20230323020500 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">British Truck Racing</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Brisith Truck Racing Championship features some of the heaviest racing machines you'll ever see. Each truck weighs more than five tonnes and produces in excess of 1000bhp. The 2022 season features a total of 7 events that are contested around the United Kingdom.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/37/1760720_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230323020500 +0100" stop="20230323025000 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">GT World Challenge America</title>
<desc lang="fr">Fanatec GT World Challenge America is the premier North American GT series. Taking place on the best US circuits form Sonoma to Indianapolis, each of the seven race weekends features 90-min double-header races.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/50/1756288_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230323025000 +0100" stop="20230323034000 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">GT World Challenge Europe Sprint Cup</title>
<desc lang="fr">Join Motorvision TV as it brings you all the action from the European sports car racing series.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/25/1760725_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230323034000 +0100" stop="20230323043000 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">DTM</title>
<desc lang="fr">The DTM - Deutsche Tourenwagen Masters - is the premier German touring car championship. In 2022, the competition is in its 23rd season and features 16 races across 8 weekends. Motorvision.TV shows the best bits from each event.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/25/2125719_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230323043000 +0100" stop="20230323050000 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Sachsenring, Germany</title>
<desc lang="fr">League of super sports cars.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/43/1884373_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230323050000 +0100" stop="20230323052500 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Car History (The Audi Story) S3 (n°35)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«The Audi Story»Selling more than a million cars per year, Audi is now one of the most successful car manufacturers in the world. The brand with the four rings does stand for innovation, superior technology and outstanding design. In the '80s Audi revolutionized the automotive world with the Audi Quattro, which not only changes the world of rally sports but also brings the all-wheel drive to everyday cars.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/15/1740326_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230323052500 +0100" stop="20230323055000 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Car People (Alex Renner Motors Dubai) S2 (n°23)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Alex Renner Motors Dubai»On the outskirts of Dubai, where the desert still prevails, a young man from Germany is working hard to make his dream come true: Alex Renner wants to run the most luxurious garage in the Arabian Golf.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/02/18/36/2149177_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230323055000 +0100" stop="20230323061500 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Magic NumberThree</title>
<desc lang="fr">Want an everyday car with extra power under the bonnet? The BMW 3-Series, Nissan 370 Z or Citroen CS DS3 are rather average cars. But as M-version, Nismo or Musketier, they get wild and become really powerful. While the Bavarian competitor comes with an output of431 hp, the Nismo from Japan offers an output of 344 PS. The Citroen musketeer on the other hand is as strong as 222 French horses.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1760716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230323061500 +0100" stop="20230323064000 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">WeatherTech SportsCar Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Road to Racing.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1760716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230323064000 +0100" stop="20230323073500 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Scarborough Gold Cup Part 2</title>
<desc lang="fr">King of the Roads.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/27/1760732_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230323073500 +0100" stop="20230323082000 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Australian V8 Superboats Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Australian V8 Superboat Championship is one of the most important watersports series from down under. Drivers compete in three different classes: the LS Class, Group A and Unlimited, which features hardly any restrictions regarding engine sizes. In 2022, a total of seven rounds are scheduled before a new champion is crowned.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/02/22/26/1784522_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230323082000 +0100" stop="20230323085000 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Powerboat: P1 USA AquaX Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">See all the action from the USA series of P1 AquaX, an exciting Jet Ski racing event, operated by Powerboat P1. P1 AquaX is an international motorboat racing competition organised by the Union Internationale Motornautique.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/38/1763103_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230323085000 +0100" stop="20230323091500 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">P1 Offshore Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">The P1 Offshore Powerboat Championship promises tightly fought offshore racing with powerboats reaching top speeds of up to 100 miles per hour. Five events are schedules for the 2022 season and Motorvision.TV brings you all the thrilling action from each event!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/54/1804798_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230323091500 +0100" stop="20230323094500 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Motonautisme : Championnat du monde de Formule 1</title>
<desc lang="fr">In 2022, the UIM is once again hosting its Formula 1 World Championship in Powerboat. In the 37th season, ten teams with 19 drivers from eleven countries have signed up to fight for the title of the new world champion in three Grand Prix.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/21/2061231_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230323094500 +0100" stop="20230323101000 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">UIM Aquabike World Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">Caution, danger of splashing! Since 1992, the Aquabike World Championship has been the most important racing series in the sport of jet skiing and one of the fastest competitions in water sports. On specially designed race courses or on the high seas, the participants engage in thrilling races in the ski and runabout categories and fascinate with all kinds of stunts on their more than 300 hp jet skis.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/05/2038331_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230323101000 +0100" stop="20230323110000 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Wanaka, Oxbow Track, Neuseeland</title>
<desc lang="fr">The New Zealand Jetsprint Championship is the most important sprint boat competition from New Zealand, the country where the sport was founded in 1981. Jetsprinting is comparable to rally sports, but there is only one boat on the track at any given time and boats drive at very high speeds. The up to 500 HP strong jet sprint boats therefore try to achieve the best time on the tracks.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/18/1774193_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230323110000 +0100" stop="20230323112500 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Car History (The Story of Automotive Advertising, Part 3) S3 (n°34)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«The Story of Automotive Advertising, Part 3»Whether as a TV spot, as product placement in cinema film or video, or on the Internet, in no other industry are brands, models and advertising campaigns as closely linked as in the automotive industry. And nowhere else is advertising so much fun as in automotive advertising.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/15/1740326_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230323112500 +0100" stop="20230323115000 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Car People (Rolls-Royce Show Room) S2 (n°22)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Rolls-Royce Show Room»Welcome, welcome! This is it. One of many, but one of very few in this particular city. It's a dream like car....car? can we even call it a car? It's a Rolls Royce.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/02/18/36/2149177_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230323115000 +0100" stop="20230323122000 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Porsche Garage and Chip Tuning</title>
<desc lang="fr">THE STABLE is the only Porsche garage in San Francisco for historic 911 models. Mike Fonfora put Marco Wendlandt's new Porsche 911 to the acid test to make sure, that Marco isn't disappointed when he sees his treasure for the very first time. The Chip Tuners from Race Chip have improved the Porsche Macan. The smallest SUV from Porsche offers now 480 hp, which are an additional 80 hp compared to the production model. Performmaster enhanced a power machine, too. Their Mercedes C 63 AMG T-model comes with an output of 612 hp and reaches a top speed of 310 km/h.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1760716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230323122000 +0100" stop="20230323124500 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">WeatherTech SportsCar Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Road to Racing.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/25/1760725_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230323124500 +0100" stop="20230323133500 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Scarborough Gold Cup Part 1</title>
<desc lang="fr">King of the Roads.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1763086_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230323133500 +0100" stop="20230323140000 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Dream Cars S2</title>
<desc lang="fr">They guarantee an exclusive appearance and, More than any other car, stand for status, prestige and perfection: international limousines from Rolls Royce, Bentley, Mercedes, BMW and Jaguar. They are the highlight of the worldwide automotive works and are the defining scale when it comes to magnificent luxury and elegant comfort. DreamCars shows the most expensive, most luxurious and most exclusive limousines in the world.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/50/1752909_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230323140000 +0100" stop="20230323143000 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 2</title>
<desc lang="fr">Exciting sports show that follows the hottest action from the world's most unique motor sport events. Viewers will have a chance to visit some interesting competitions- from IDEMITSU 600 Super Endurance at the Chang Interna-tional Circuit in Thailand, the winter edition of the Maroc Challenge in Morocco, to the Hispania Rally, the only European rally to take place in the desert, and many more. Viewers will also find out all the news from the world of motor sports.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/40/1752403_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230323143000 +0100" stop="20230323145500 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Go Green! S3</title>
<desc lang="fr">From concept to reality - these are important steps for car manufacturers - especially when it comes to environmentally friendly technologies. Go Green! checks out the ecological developments in the motor industry.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748432_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230323145500 +0100" stop="20230323152000 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Bike World</title>
<desc lang="fr">Bike World is the magazine on MOTORVISION TV for all fans of the lifestyle on two wheels. Whether on the road, off-road or on the race track: Bike World brings the latest trends from the world of motorcycles into living rooms around the world. Watch the latest tests of new two-wheelers, exciting reports from the hottest events and thrilling insights into superbike racing.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/32/1837877_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230323152000 +0100" stop="20230323154500 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Perfect Ride S3</title>
<desc lang="fr">1964 saw the introduction of the Ford Mustang, which is considered to be the ancestor of all pony cars. In the first year Ford sold more than 680,000 units of this car. It's a record that no other vehicle was able to break. To this day, people around the world value it for its strength, superior V8 and reasonable price. Perfect Ride reviews the Mustang and its relatives, the Challenger and Camaro.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/09/2153087_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230323154500 +0100" stop="20230323161500 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">MotorStories (L.A. Road Trip - BMW i8) (n°5)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«L.A. Road Trip - BMW i8»Petrolheads in California can only think about horsepower and engine sizes. The hybrid sports car BMW i8 combines these classic values with green thinking and sets new environmental trends. But how do conservative petrolheads respond to such a futuristic and clean car? On the Road Trip through LA some octane junkies who usually drive a Porsche 911, Chevy Corvette or tuned bikes test the BMW i8.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Documentaire</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748434_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230323161500 +0100" stop="20230323164000 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Made In... S2</title>
<desc lang="fr">Kempten in Allgau. The ABT Sportsline company with ? 115 year tradition resides at the foot of the Alps. ABT Sportsline is the largest Volkswagen group-tuning company in the world and works closely with Audi.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/24/02/1748419_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230323164000 +0100" stop="20230323170000 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Manthey Racing</title>
<desc lang="fr">Racing in the Green Hell.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/40/1752403_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230323170000 +0100" stop="20230323172500 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Car History (Auto Union) S3 (n°36)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Auto Union»The Auto Union is the incredible story of the 'Fantastic Four': Horch, Audi, DKW and Wanderer. With the sign of the four rings, they are the second-largest automotive group in Germany behind Opel in the 1930s. The four brands of Auto Union are automobile pacemakers, build technical milestones and the fastest car in the world. Today, the name is long gone, but the brand lives on.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/15/1740326_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230323172500 +0100" stop="20230323174500 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Car People (Vehicle Inspector Thomas Eschenbach) S2 (n°24)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Vehicle Inspector Thomas Eschenbach»Small incident but a big impact. After accidents, a damage appraisal should give a bit of clarity to the situation. The man to do this: Vehicle inspector Thomas Eschenbach.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/02/18/36/2149177_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230323174500 +0100" stop="20230323181500 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Stars of AMG</title>
<desc lang="fr">Mercedes' tuning company AMG starts its own battle of the stars - at least when it comes to horsepower. The C63 AMG, E 63 S AMG and S 63 AMG outdo each other with their performance data. AMG stands for Aufrecht, Melcher and Grossasbach - the founders' names and the founding site. But you could also read it as absolute motoring geniuses, because all stars of AMG offer ultimate driving pleasure.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1760716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230323181500 +0100" stop="20230323184000 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">WeatherTech SportsCar Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Road to Racing.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/59/1763095_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230323184000 +0100" stop="20230323193000 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Macau Bike Grand Prix</title>
<desc lang="fr">King of the Roads.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/37/1760719_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230323193000 +0100" stop="20230323202500 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Rolex Monterey Motorsports Reunion</title>
<desc lang="fr">Rolex Monterey Motorsports Reunion was established in 1974 under Monterey Historic Automobile Races moniker by Steve Earle. Today, it is an annual event held at Laguna Seca, California with over 500 historic racecars participating.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/40/1752403_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230323202500 +0100" stop="20230323205000 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Car History (Porsche Racing) S3 (n°27)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Porsche Racing»The Porsche 356, the 550 Spyder and the 917: None is faster, none is more reliable and none is more successful. They make Porsche number 1 in motorsports. In the 50s, 60s and 70s, there is hardly a race and barely a rally, that Porsche does not win. From the beginning, Porsche takes the knowledge gained from racing and uses it for series production.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/15/1740326_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230323205000 +0100" stop="20230323211500 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Classic Ride S7</title>
<desc lang="fr">Whoever believes in the socialist era of the East there was only oil smelly two-stroke Trabant and Wartburg or license production cars á la Lada, is wrong. Companies like Tatra from Czechoslovakia introduced in the fifties advanced, even pioneering automobiles. Unfortunately, the clientele was exclusive, and in the west countries the streamlined cars are big rarities. Today, these cars are cult and interesting collectibles. Classic Ride presents a lover and his extraordinary Tatra T87 of 1937.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/24/2125716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230323211500 +0100" stop="20230323214000 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Car History (SAAB) S2 (n°17)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«SAAB»Saab, the iconic brand from Sweden, is a rolling manifesto of &quot;otherness&quot;. A Saab is the perfect car for all non-conformists who have a sense of aesthetics, quality and comfort. They cars are considered to be individual and innovative. But in the end, Saab is insolvent as well. The fans remain though and keep the brand alive. Car History documents the rise and fall of this unique company.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/15/1740326_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230323214000 +0100" stop="20230323220500 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Hans-Joachim Stuck</title>
<desc lang="fr">Portrait of Hans-Joachim Stuck, one of the best race drivers in Germany. He stopped racing after participating in the 2011 24 Hours of Nürburgring.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/19/1774199_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230323220500 +0100" stop="20230323225500 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Le Mans Classic</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Le Mans Classic is a vintage sports car event that took place for the first time in 2002 on the site of the 24-hour race of Le Mans. All participating drivers are at a top level as far as driving is concerned.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/20/2162901_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230323225500 +0100" stop="20230323232500 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Car History (Corvette and Porsche 911) S3 (n°33)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Corvette and Porsche 911»50 years Porsche 911 and 60 years Chevrolet Corvette. Two legends, two dreamcars with two opponents philosophies.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/15/1740326_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230323232500 +0100" stop="20230323235000 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Car People (MK Limousine Service) S2 (n°21)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«MK Limousine Service»The life of a VIP - have you ever wanted to be a star and be transported around a city, in a nice limousine. Sounds like a dream, right? Well it's not, you, too, can have the limousine experience, and feel like a star.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/02/18/36/2149177_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230323235000 +0100" stop="20230324001500 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Luxury Tuning</title>
<desc lang="fr">Tuning is on the hunt for speeders and parking offenders with the legendary supercars police fleet from Dubai. Back in Europe, MTM and Alpina improve the performance of Audis and BMWs. The Audi S8 MTM Talladega R features an impressive output of 802 hp. And the Stuck brothers Johannes and Ferdinand beat the Alpina D5 around the track and delight us with their driving tricks. Hopefully the police isn't watching.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1760716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230324001500 +0100" stop="20230324004000 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">WeatherTech SportsCar Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Road to Racing.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/40/1752403_A.jpg" />
</programme>