<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Voo -->
<programme start="20230418022500 +0200" stop="20230418025000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Drift : Championnat de France</title>
<desc lang="fr">When it comes to national drift competitions, the French Championship is one of the most important ones. 32 drivers compete in the spectacular main event.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/37/1760720_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230418025000 +0200" stop="20230418034000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">e-Trophée Andros</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Andros Trophy is the French national ice racing championship. The idea appeared long time ago in 1985 when professional racer Max Mamers and the owner of the Andros company, Frédéric Gervoson, met as rugby fans. They spent the winter racing with friends on ice circuits. In 2003 the trophy gained an international aspect with a race at Sherbrooke in Canada. In 2020, the racing series is repositioning itself as an electric racing series.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/43/1884375_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230418034000 +0200" stop="20230418042500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Hi-Tec Drift Allstars Series Australia</title>
<desc lang="fr">The latest drifting competition on Motorvision.TV brings you the best drifters from Australia. Join us for thrilling duels, smoking wheels and non-stop drift battles for the Drift All Stars Series title.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/25/1760725_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230418042500 +0200" stop="20230418051500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">National Legend Cars</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Legends Cars National Championship brings back racing from yesteryear. The series features 5/8 scale replicas of pre-war 1930s Fords, Chevys and Dodges that are equipped with 125bhp-motorcycle engines. These cars are well known for delivering high-octane battles on race tracks around Great Britain.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/40/1752403_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230418051500 +0200" stop="20230418055000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">AWD Safari Challenge</title>
<desc lang="fr">Every year, the British All Wheel Drive Club organises the AWDC Safari Championship, which has become the largest off-road event in the UK. Modified 4x4 vehicles of all brands can participate in the competition. Those who want to score points here must complete the challenging courses of mud, slush and scree in the shortest possible time.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/40/1975310_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230418055000 +0200" stop="20230418060000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 4</title>
<desc lang="fr">When their ambitions exceed their driving skills, when well-secured racing professionals are thrown out of corners, we always have a camera at hand. Breathtaking stunts by professional drivers and slapstick-action in highly-tuned tin can rockets. Spectacular scenes where nobody gets hurt.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/31/00/1748416_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230418060000 +0200" stop="20230418063000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Go Green! S2</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Geneva Motor Show - the first major European motor show of the year. More than almost any other event, the car show on Lake Geneva represents a variety of studies, exotic and super sports cars.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748432_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230418063000 +0200" stop="20230418065000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Perfect Ride S3</title>
<desc lang="fr">Audi A3, BMW 5 Series and Mercedes CLS have been bestsellers for years. In order to attract even more buyers and close the niches between the different vehicle classes, manufacturers extend their model series every so often: Proven technology under the bonnet, but a redesigned body. The results are cars between two worlds such as A3 Sedan, 5 Series Gran Turismo and CLS Shooting Brake.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/19/1748438_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230418065000 +0200" stop="20230418071500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Top Ten Show S1</title>
<desc lang="fr">Almost every compact car is now available in a sporty version. And funnily enough the little racers usually have more power under the bonnet than you might think.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/40/1752467_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230418071500 +0200" stop="20230418074000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 2</title>
<desc lang="fr">Street Racers is your backstage pass to the world of Formula E. Every two weeks, the magazine takes a look behind the scenes of the most important electric car racing series and provides reviews, current news, exciting interviews and gripping background reports from the world of Formula E.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/59/1880083_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230418074000 +0200" stop="20230418083000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">GT World Challenge Asia</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Fanatec GT World Challenge Asia is back for another season with five scheduled events for the 2022 season. Unlike its European and North American counterparts, GT World Challenge Asia also features GT4 entries.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/30/2013488_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230418083000 +0200" stop="20230418085500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">MXGP of Sardegna, Riola Sardo</title>
<desc lang="fr">Lap after lap of international motorsports action. This is coverage from the FIM (Fédération Internationale de Motocyclisme) Motocross World Championship where riders from all over the globe compete in high-octane, fast-paced motocross racing. Competitors battle it out in races lasting 35 minutes plus 2 laps per race.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/32/1907968_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230418085500 +0200" stop="20230418092000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Grand Prix of France, Nice, Palais Nikaia</title>
<desc lang="fr">FIM SuperEnduro World Championship has been held since 2007. Its circuits are built inside stadiums or arenas, recreating obstacles such as rocks, boulders and logs. The championship consists of eight Grands Prix spread around the globe on courses that are mostly off-road. These events are split into two days and two different races, after which the points towards the world championship are awarded. Each round includes a motocross test and an extreme test, in addition to the enduro test.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/22/1748447_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230418092000 +0200" stop="20230418101000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Australian Motocross Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Australian ProMX Championship is the nation's premier motocross championship. The series acts as a successful development platform for young Australian talent and is designed as a tiered system with three dedicated classes: MX3 for younger drivers, the MX2 for senior drivers and the MX1, which is the elite category in the championship.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/07/2125726_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230418101000 +0200" stop="20230418110500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Grand Prix of Austria, Wiener Neustadt</title>
<desc lang="fr">FIM X-Trial World Championship is the most prestigious indoor motorcycle trials tournament of the world, organised by the Fédération Internationale de Motocyclisme. The programme presents the highlights of the rounds where the participants have to take on the challenging tracks full of steep climbs and huge rocks.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/13/2162902_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230418110500 +0200" stop="20230418120000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Australian Superbike Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">Founded in 1980, the Australian Superbike Championship is one of the most important motorcycle racing competitions in Oceania. It is well respected as a springboard for riders and teams who aspire an international career in motorcycling. The 2022 season is contested in five classes: Superbike, Supersport, Supersport 300, the Yamaha R3 Cup and the Oceania Junior Cup.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1763086_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230418120000 +0200" stop="20230418125000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Ferrari Challenge Europe</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Ferrari Challenge Europe is back for another season on Motorvision.TV. The longest-running single-make series championship in the history of the Prancing Horse-company promises high performance and talented drivers on challenging tracks around Europe. Seven events are scheduled for the 2022 season including the Finali Mondiali, which brings together the final stages of all Ferrari Challenge divisions around the world.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/25/55/2162175_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230418125000 +0200" stop="20230418131500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Championnat d'Europe de courses de camions</title>
<desc lang="fr">The FIA European Truck Racing Championship is the biggest, most imposing racing series in the world. The racing trucks are equipped with 1200 hp engines doing up to 100 miles per hour. On a grid with 26 big rigs the 5.5-ton machines doing battle there's guaranteed action-packed lights-to-flag racing galore.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/25/00/1748421_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230418131500 +0200" stop="20230418134500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Championnat d'Europe de courses de camions</title>
<desc lang="fr">The FIA European Truck Racing Championship is the biggest, most imposing racing series in the world. The racing trucks are equipped with 1200 hp engines doing up to 100 miles per hour. On a grid with 26 big rigs the 5.5-ton machines doing battle there's guaranteed action-packed lights-to-flag racing galore.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/25/00/1748421_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230418134500 +0200" stop="20230418142500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">GP Czech Republic, Autodrom Most</title>
<desc lang="fr">NASCAR, America's most popular racing series, is now well established in Europe and there is no better proof than its European division: the NASCAR Whelen Euro Series. This year, 17 teams from nine different countries with a total of 39 cars prove once again that the NWES with its pure racing character is one of the best touring car series on the old continent. Motorvision.TV shows highlights from every race weekend.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748423_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230418142500 +0200" stop="20230418151500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Asian Le Mans Series</title>
<desc lang="fr">Asian sports car racing endurance series created by the Automobile Club de l'Ouest and based in Asia aims to attract teams and drivers from Asian countries. The Asian Le Mans Series is the symbol of the Spirit of Le Mans, and holds the same passion for creating world class endurance racing.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/20/00/2125604_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230418151500 +0200" stop="20230418160500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">WeatherTech SportsCar Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">Catch the action from the sports car racing series organized by the International Motor Sports Association. It is America's premier sports car racing series where almost all premium manufacturers are represented. This includes companies such as Acura, Aston Martin, Audi, BMW, Cadillac, Chevrolet, Ferrari, Honda, Lamborghini, Lexus, Mazda, Mercedes-AMG and Porsche.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/40/1752403_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230418160500 +0200" stop="20230418165000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">NW200 Races Part 2</title>
<desc lang="fr">King of the Roads.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/38/1760724_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230418165000 +0200" stop="20230418171500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Autódromo Internacional do Algarve, Portugal</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Michelin Le Mans Cup is an International sports car racing endurance series inspired by the 24 Hours of Le Mans race and run by the Automobile Club de l'Ouest.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/01/06/2177304_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230418171500 +0200" stop="20230418175000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Season Review</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Michelin Le Mans Cup is an International sports car racing endurance series inspired by the 24 Hours of Le Mans race and run by the Automobile Club de l'Ouest.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/01/06/2177304_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230418175000 +0200" stop="20230418180000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 5</title>
<desc lang="fr">When their ambitions exceed their driving skills, when well-secured racing professionals are thrown out of corners, we always have a camera at hand. Breathtaking stunts by professional drivers and slapstick-action in highly-tuned tin can rockets. Spectacular scenes where nobody gets hurt.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/31/00/1748416_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230418180000 +0200" stop="20230418182000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Go Green! S3</title>
<desc lang="fr">2007 saw the launch of a successor to the Fiat Cinquecento. The Fiat Twin-Air is greener version of the Fiat 500 and comes with a two-cylinder turbo engine. The sound of its high-torque engine alone makes this car fun and seductive. Plus: Bloggers from around the world get the chance to put the Volvo C30 E to the extreme test in the ice and snow of Northern Sweden.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748432_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230418182000 +0200" stop="20230418185000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Perfect Ride S3</title>
<desc lang="fr">The 2012 Mercedes A-Class managed to shake off its image as a vehicle for retired people. But AMG tops it all and presents the hottest A-Class ever. Its impressive 360-hp engine is the most powerful production four-cylinder in the world. Plus: Musketier Tuning turns the Citroen DS 3 into a defening driving machine. Perfect Ride discusses the differences between the tuned and the production model.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/19/1748438_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230418185000 +0200" stop="20230418191000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Top Ten Show S1</title>
<desc lang="fr">There are cars-- or let's say vehicles, which turn every head on the street. And that's not necessarily because they're beautiful, but because there are exceptionally weird. Some of these drivable oddballs are unique customizations, while others are simply classics. We'll show you the ten strangest vehicles ever built.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/39/1752442_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230418191000 +0200" stop="20230418193500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 10</title>
<desc lang="fr">Street Racers is your backstage pass to the world of Formula E. Every two weeks, the magazine takes a look behind the scenes of the most important electric car racing series and provides reviews, current news, exciting interviews and gripping background reports from the world of Formula E.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/59/1880083_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230418193500 +0200" stop="20230418202500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">GT World Challenge Asia</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Fanatec GT World Challenge Asia is back for another season with five scheduled events for the 2022 season. Unlike its European and North American counterparts, GT World Challenge Asia also features GT4 entries.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/30/2013488_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230418202500 +0200" stop="20230418205000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Dream Cars S2</title>
<desc lang="fr">DreamCars presents the most expensive, most luxurious and fastest dream cars from Germany. Whether it's the Porsche 918 Spyder, Mercedes S-Class, BMW M6 or Audi A8: the premium cars from Germany define the benchmark for comfort, status, dynamics and driving pleasure.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/50/1752909_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230418205000 +0200" stop="20230418211500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 5</title>
<desc lang="fr">Exciting sports show that follows the hottest action from the world's most unique motor sport events. Viewers will have a chance to visit some interesting competitions- from IDEMITSU 600 Super Endurance at the Chang Interna-tional Circuit in Thailand, the winter edition of the Maroc Challenge in Morocco, to the Hispania Rally, the only European rally to take place in the desert, and many more. Viewers will also find out all the news from the world of motor sports.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1760716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230418211500 +0200" stop="20230418214500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Bike World</title>
<desc lang="fr">Bike World is the magazine on MOTORVISION TV for all fans of the lifestyle on two wheels. Whether on the road, off-road or on the race track: Bike World brings the latest trends from the world of motorcycles into living rooms around the world. Watch the latest tests of new two-wheelers, exciting reports from the hottest events and thrilling insights into superbike racing.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/32/1837877_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230418214500 +0200" stop="20230418221500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Perfect Ride S6</title>
<desc lang="fr">What's hot and what's not. There are quests to be undertaken, the search for the ideal auto, for the perfect race track for the ultimate accessory gadget. What are the preferred rides of the race legends?</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/09/2153087_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230418221500 +0200" stop="20230418223500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Supercars S6</title>
<desc lang="fr">There are details which set super cars apart from normal cars and these details are essential. Super cars are the biggest, loudest and most expensive cars on the highway; they're four-wheeled works of arts.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748406_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230418223500 +0200" stop="20230418232000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Spotted</title>
<desc lang="fr">Frank Slopianka is highly ambitious and committed to the drag racing event 'Race@Airport'. The US car dealer from Berlin takes about eleven seconds to finish the quarter mile with his 700-hp Camaro. Tuning company Mansory promises additional acceleration and horse power for Lamborghini cars. A good example is the Mansory Carbonado, a rebuilt Aventador Convertible.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/21/07/1884377_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230418232000 +0200" stop="20230418234500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">BMW M1 Meeting</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Austrian racing scene is now richer by one attraction, having added the Histo Cup Austria. 10.000 motor racing fans make their way to the Salzburgring in Austria to admire over 200 historical race cars in action.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1760716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230418234500 +0200" stop="20230419000000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 7</title>
<desc lang="fr">When their ambitions exceed their driving skills, when well-secured racing professionals are thrown out of corners, we always have a camera at hand. Breathtaking stunts by professional drivers and slapstick-action in highly-tuned tin can rockets. Spectacular scenes where nobody gets hurt.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/31/00/1748416_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230419000000 +0200" stop="20230419002000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Go Green! S2</title>
<desc lang="fr">For many years, the BMW 3 Series has been on top of its competition. But that might be about to change, because Mercedes launches its all-new C-Class Coupe. Go Green takes a look at the Mercedes-Benz C 350 Blue Efficiency. Plus: The third generation of the Toyota Prius received a face lift. If you don't want to spend money on the new model, you could also buy a used one from the second generation.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748432_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230419002000 +0200" stop="20230419004500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Perfect Ride S2</title>
<desc lang="fr">The duel of the city runabouts. The Audi A1 Quattro versus its significantly cheaper competitor, the Renault Clio RS. Pressing the Gas pedal stylishly! One of the most radical roadsters in the world, the Morgan Plus 8.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/19/1748438_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230419004500 +0200" stop="20230419011000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Top Ten Show S1</title>
<desc lang="fr">Most manufacturers sell their models in other countries. The production figures, therefore, easily rise into the hundreds of thousands. But time and time again, the manufacturers create very special works of art which are limited, exclusive and therefore rather expensive. On this episode of our Top Ten Show we'll show you the rarest series of cars.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/50/1752909_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230419011000 +0200" stop="20230419014000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 13</title>
<desc lang="fr">Street Racers is your backstage pass to the world of Formula E. Every two weeks, the magazine takes a look behind the scenes of the most important electric car racing series and provides reviews, current news, exciting interviews and gripping background reports from the world of Formula E.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/59/1880083_A.jpg" />
</programme>