<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Voo -->
<programme start="20230429023000 +0200" stop="20230429025500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Dream Cars S2</title>
<desc lang="fr">They are wild, they are busrting with power and they are cult, the American Muscle Cars. Whether it is the Ford Mustang, the Chevrolet Camaro or the Corvette, Muscle Cars are coveted all over the world because of their rebellious design, impeteous horsepower and their stunning speed. Dream Cars presents the most spectacular and fastest US-Sport- and Musclecars.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/50/1752909_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230429025500 +0200" stop="20230429032000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 5</title>
<desc lang="fr">Exciting sports show that follows the hottest action from the world's most unique motor sport events. Viewers will have a chance to visit some interesting competitions- from IDEMITSU 600 Super Endurance at the Chang Interna-tional Circuit in Thailand, the winter edition of the Maroc Challenge in Morocco, to the Hispania Rally, the only European rally to take place in the desert, and many more. Viewers will also find out all the news from the world of motor sports.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1760716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230429032000 +0200" stop="20230429034500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Bike World</title>
<desc lang="fr">Bike World is the magazine on MOTORVISION TV for all fans of the lifestyle on two wheels. Whether on the road, off-road or on the race track: Bike World brings the latest trends from the world of motorcycles into living rooms around the world. Watch the latest tests of new two-wheelers, exciting reports from the hottest events and thrilling insights into superbike racing.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/32/1837877_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230429034500 +0200" stop="20230429041000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Perfect Ride S6</title>
<desc lang="fr">What's hot and what's not. There are quests to be undertaken, the search for the ideal auto, for the perfect race track for the ultimate accessory gadget. What are the preferred rides of the race legends?</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/09/2153087_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230429041000 +0200" stop="20230429043500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Supercars</title>
<desc lang="fr">A synergy of high-octane power, speed, luxury and prestige. Supercars features some of the most desirable automobiles in the world, whether it be an agile sports car to a comfortable limousine. It features the likes of prestige brands filled with rich heritage and motorsport pedigree; such as Bentley, BMW M, Mercedes AMG, Aston Martin, Maserati, Porsche and Ferrari to niche-market, lightweight Lotuses, KTMs and Caterhams. Supercars has everything a petrolhead needs to get up to speed on the latest and greatest of high-performance road machines.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748406_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230429043500 +0200" stop="20230429052000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Spotted</title>
<desc lang="fr">They are extremely loud, extremely fast and extremely honed: the compact cars Mercedes A45 AMG Performmaster and MTM Audi RS3 R. Ferrari and Rolls-Royce, two of the world's most famous car brands, don't need any tuning. MOTORVISION TV - #SPOTTED explains the myth of Ferrari and takes a look behind the scenes of the Rolls Royce Bespoke production.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/21/07/1884377_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230429052000 +0200" stop="20230429060000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Offroad Legends</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Land Rover Defender makes the hearts of offraod fans leap since over 70 years. Can the modern Landy follow in the footsteps of the old icon? And: How does offroad driving work exactly? We let an offroad beginner onto rough grounds.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/00/2125714_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230429060000 +0200" stop="20230429062500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Go Green! S3</title>
<desc lang="fr">Electric engines fight fossil fuel and the resulting pollution of the environment. They promise a quiet and clean urban environment and have huge potential in densely populated parts of the world. A newly developed production approach for e-cars leads to 50% less noise, too. That spares the worker's ears and the environment. But many people still don't seem to be positive about e-mobility.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748432_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230429062500 +0200" stop="20230429065500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Perfect Ride S6</title>
<desc lang="fr">N-Line.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/09/2153087_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230429065500 +0200" stop="20230429072000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Top Ten Show S1</title>
<desc lang="fr">Today is all about 'Coupés'. It's all about beautiful shapes and sporty elegance. We'll show you pioneering Coupés in terms of design. And to make this competition more exciting, we're going to set horsepower limit of 400.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/40/1752467_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230429072000 +0200" stop="20230429074500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 1</title>
<desc lang="fr">Street Racers is your backstage pass to the world of Formula E. Every two weeks, the magazine takes a look behind the scenes of the most important electric car racing series and provides reviews, current news, exciting interviews and gripping background reports from the world of Formula E.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/59/1880083_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230429074500 +0200" stop="20230429083500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Race 1, Al Alula, Saudi Arabia</title>
<desc lang="fr">Extreme E is a racing series for SUVs with electric motors that has been held worldwide since 2021. In the race, all teams compete with the same vehicles, which are powered by two electric motors and are allowed to produce a maximum of 500kW (680HP).</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/20/33/1951083_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230429083500 +0200" stop="20230429090000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Drift : Championnat de France</title>
<desc lang="fr">The French Drift Championship is one of the most important national championships in the European drift sport and attracts the interest of around 300 pilots every year. However, only the 32 best drivers can compete in the main event. To survive in the 1-on-1-battles, they must impress the judges with speed, precision and spectacular drift maneuvers.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/59/1763095_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230429090000 +0200" stop="20230429095000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">e-Trophée Andros</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Andros Trophy is the French national ice racing championship. The idea appeared long time ago in 1985 when professional racer Max Mamers and the owner of the Andros company, Frédéric Gervoson, met as rugby fans. They spent the winter racing with friends on ice circuits. In 2003 the trophy gained an international aspect with a race at Sherbrooke in Canada. In 2020, the racing series is repositioning itself as an electric racing series.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/43/1884375_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230429095000 +0200" stop="20230429104500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Hi-Tec Drift Allstars Series Australia</title>
<desc lang="fr">The latest drifting competition on Motorvision.TV brings you the best drifters from Australia. Join us for thrilling duels, smoking wheels and non-stop drift battles for the Drift All Stars Series title.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/40/1752403_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230429104500 +0200" stop="20230429113500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">National Legend Cars</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Legends Cars National Championship brings back racing from yesteryear. The series features 5/8 scale replicas of pre-war 1930s Fords, Chevys and Dodges that are equipped with 125bhp-motorcycle engines. These cars are well known for delivering high-octane battles on race tracks around Great Britain.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/40/1752403_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230429113500 +0200" stop="20230429120000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">G Series Andorra</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Andorra-Pas de la Casa Circuit offers an excellent quality on the ice surface thanks to their geographical location. A thousand meters long and ten wide route that combines a wide straight line with curves of all kinds, completely covered with ice and snow.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/25/1760728_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230429120000 +0200" stop="20230429122500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Go Green! S3</title>
<desc lang="fr">For 125 years combustion engines have been responsible for our movement, but it comes at a high price due to their toxic emissions. This only works for our earth and environment on a long-term basis, if the emissions from those cars get reduced dramatically. Go Green sustainable mobility shows developments on how manufacturers want to decrease the consumption of their cars even further.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748432_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230429122500 +0200" stop="20230429125500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Perfect Ride S6</title>
<desc lang="fr">Changing your car like your underwear? That's possible now. With Book by Cadillac, the customer no longer chooses a car, but a brand. Unlimited vehicle changes, no additional costs apart from refueling. And the price is fair. Plus: Volvo launches its new electric offensive and presents the Polestar 1 as its first electric car. Additional plug-in hybrids will follow until 2020.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/09/2153087_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230429125500 +0200" stop="20230429132000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Top Ten Show S1</title>
<desc lang="fr">Today we'll talk about the world's best-selling cars. Which producer scored the highest last year? Which model was a market leader? Who broke the one million mark?</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/40/1752467_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230429132000 +0200" stop="20230429134500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 24</title>
<desc lang="fr">Street Racers is your backstage pass to the world of Formula E. Every two weeks, the magazine takes a look behind the scenes of the most important electric car racing series and provides reviews, current news, exciting interviews and gripping background reports from the world of Formula E.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/59/1880083_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230429134500 +0200" stop="20230429144000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Race 4, Sardegna, Italy</title>
<desc lang="fr">Extreme E is a racing series for SUVs with electric motors that has been held worldwide since 2021. In the race, all teams compete with the same vehicles, which are powered by two electric motors and are allowed to produce a maximum of 500kW (680HP).</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/20/33/1951083_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230429144000 +0200" stop="20230429150500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">The Genius of Colin Chapman</title>
<desc lang="fr">Designer, engineer, and team boss, Colin Chapman was one of the driving forces behind Formula One throughout the 1960s and '70s. A man whose name became synonymous with motorsport innovation, Chapman's racing career began with an unimpressive start behind the wheel before the Briton came to realize that his real talents lay elsewhere.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/49/1774755_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230429150500 +0200" stop="20230429155500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Rallye Monte Carlo Historique</title>
<desc lang="fr">The infamous Monte-Carlo Rally is one of the world's oldest rally events in the world. To pay tribute to its long-lasting history, the Automobile Club de Monaco organizes the Rallye Monte-Carlo Historique. The catch is: Only cars that competed in the Monte-Carlo Rally at least 40 years ago are allowed to take part in the historic edition of the Monte-Carlo Rally.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/37/1760720_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230429155500 +0200" stop="20230429162000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Ferry Porsche</title>
<desc lang="fr">Portrait of Ferdinand &quot;Ferry&quot; Porsche, the father of the Porsche 911. He started his automobile legacy when he built the Porsche 935 after World War II.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/19/1774199_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230429162000 +0200" stop="20230429164500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Car History (Lancia) S2 (n°15)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Lancia»Lancia - Legendary racing successes, technological innovations and exclusive vehicles, made this brand world famous. But Lancia hasn't just enjoyed success in its history. The Italian car manufacturer had to endure severe misfortunes and economic mismanagement as well. Nonetheless, the legend lives on to this day. Car History looks back on the ups and downs in the history of Lancia.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/15/1740326_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230429164500 +0200" stop="20230429171000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">The Rallye World Championship 1982</title>
<desc lang="fr">The African continent is always a difficult terrain for rally drivers. That wasn't any different for the 1982 World Rally Championship, when heat, dust, mud and hardly passable routes posed major challenges for drivers, co-drivers and engines.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/24/2125717_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230429171000 +0200" stop="20230429173500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Car History (Volvo) S2 (n°19)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Volvo»Volvo Classic Cars are always solid, always safe, but not always beautiful. Since 1927 the Swedish car company produces cars, which are a little bit different. But no matter if their individual models are curvy or boxy; a Volvo is always an individual car. Get ready for a ride through the history of Volvo on this episode of Car History.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/15/1740326_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230429173500 +0200" stop="20230429180000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Classic Ride S2</title>
<desc lang="fr">One real eye catcher is the very rare AMC Pacer from the movie 'Waynes World'. This car has caught the attention of famous German Music-Manager Andreas Laesker.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/24/2125716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230429180000 +0200" stop="20230429182000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Go Green! S3</title>
<desc lang="fr">Neither e-cars nor hydrogen compulsion can guarantee clean mobility on their own. Sustainable mobility only works if there is more than just replacing one drive concept with another one. The key to the mobility of the future is connectivity. A positive side effect is that cities can be freed from long lines of parking cars. Part 3 of Sustainable Mobility shows how that can work.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748432_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230429182000 +0200" stop="20230429185000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Perfect Ride S2</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Porsche 911. Modern design, advanced technology, everything is new but still: For 50 years, still unmistakable. And we also test the world's first series-produced plug-in hybrid with diesel engine: the Volvo V60!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/19/1748438_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230429185000 +0200" stop="20230429191500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Top Ten Show S1</title>
<desc lang="fr">Today we'll be taking a look at some extreme cars from around the world: Supercars! We're going to be showing you the top ten most beautiful supercars of recent times.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/50/1752909_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230429191500 +0200" stop="20230429194000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 21</title>
<desc lang="fr">Street Racers is your backstage pass to the world of Formula E. Every two weeks, the magazine takes a look behind the scenes of the most important electric car racing series and provides reviews, current news, exciting interviews and gripping background reports from the world of Formula E.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/59/1880083_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230429194000 +0200" stop="20230429203000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Race 3, Kangerlussuaq, Greenland</title>
<desc lang="fr">Extreme E is a racing series for SUVs with electric motors that has been held worldwide since 2021. In the race, all teams compete with the same vehicles, which are powered by two electric motors and are allowed to produce a maximum of 500kW (680HP).</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/20/33/1951083_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230429203000 +0200" stop="20230429205500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Tour European Rally Historic</title>
<desc lang="fr">Motorvision TV brings you all the action from the independent rally series taking place around Europe.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/48/2123747_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230429205500 +0200" stop="20230429212000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Rallye Sierra Morena, Spain</title>
<desc lang="fr">Amazing challenge around Europe includes 19 special stages. The top crew will become Tour European Rally champion in one of the most beautiful European rallies.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/28/1760738_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230429212000 +0200" stop="20230429214500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Championnat de Belgique des Rallyes</title>
<desc lang="fr">Motorvision TV brings you all the action from one of the most competitive national rallies in Europe.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/21/2149178_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230429214500 +0200" stop="20230429221500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Sharqiyah International Baja</title>
<desc lang="fr">In 2022, Sharqiyah International Baja will once again invite spectators and drivers to thrilling rally action in the desert. Motorvision.TV shows the highlights of this year's edition of the challenging desert rally.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/15/35/1806257_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230429221500 +0200" stop="20230429224000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">A Tour European Rally Promo Event</title>
<desc lang="fr">Organised as a promo event by the TER, the Artic Lapland Rally is the coldest rally competition in the world. Despite temperatures dropping to -35°C, the rally attracts more than 200,000 spectators to Rovaniemi, the capital of Finnish Lappland. It's hated, but also loved among the 150 drivers taking part every year. MOTORVISION TV shows you the highlights from the 2020 Arctic Lapland Rally.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/55/1999411_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230429224000 +0200" stop="20230429233000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Baja Hail Toyota Rally</title>
<desc lang="fr">In 2020, Saudi Arabia hosta the Baja Hail Rally for the 16th time. This year, two rounds of the event take place in the kingdom. Not only do they serve as preparation for the 2021 Dakar Rally, but they also represent the last two rounds of the official FIA World Championship for Cross Country Bajas. MOTORVISION TV shows the highlights from both events.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/33/1786567_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230429233000 +0200" stop="20230430000000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Rallye Classique de Majorque</title>
<desc lang="fr">Aucune description</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/24/1760723_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230430000000 +0200" stop="20230430002500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Go Green! S3</title>
<desc lang="fr">After 100 years of traditional pressing and welding carmakers revolutionize production methods and make it much more sustainable. That requires a complete rethinking of their strategies: carbon instead of metal, renewable raw materials instead of plastics and electric engine instead of combustion engines. We have a look on their strategies and goals when it comes to produce more sustainably.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748432_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230430002500 +0200" stop="20230430005500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Perfect Ride S6</title>
<desc lang="fr">In addition to SUVs, small cars are also a segment that is recording growth on the German market. A Picanto for less than 10,000 Euros is enough to satisfy the needs of mobility. The Audi A1 offers much more: advantages of the luxury class, but also a high price. Plus: Perfect Ride takes a look at a sporty Korean: the Kia Ceed GT.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/09/2153087_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230430005500 +0200" stop="20230430011500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Top Ten Show S1</title>
<desc lang="fr">Manufacturers are continuously bombarding us with newer and even better models all the time, which claim to be the latest innovation in design. But there are cars that were super-chic 40 years ago and are still celebrated as works of art today. So let's have a look at ten golden oldies of the car world on this Top Ten Show.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/50/1752909_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230430011500 +0200" stop="20230430014000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 19</title>
<desc lang="fr">Street Racers is your backstage pass to the world of Formula E. Every two weeks, the magazine takes a look behind the scenes of the most important electric car racing series and provides reviews, current news, exciting interviews and gripping background reports from the world of Formula E.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/59/1880083_A.jpg" />
</programme>