<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Voo -->
<programme start="20230403022500 +0200" stop="20230403031500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Grand Prix de Monaco historique</title>
<desc lang="fr">Do you miss the thrilling motorsports from yesteryear? Take a trip with Motorvision.TV to the French Riviera, when the Grand Prix de Monaco Historique turns back the wheel of time and brings back legendary racing cars for one more adrenaline-filled race featuring high speeds, risky maneuvers and head-to-head fights that we all love in motorsports.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/54/2007077_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230403031500 +0200" stop="20230403034000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Car History (Ferrari) S1 (n°8)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Ferrari»Ferrari - the name alone gets your heart racing. Wherever the iconic fire red legend from Maranello is, the car with the jumping horse on its emblem is always at the center of attention. Car History recounts the story of Ferrari, from the very first sports car up to the Ferrari FF, and shows historical footage from the Formula One and interviews with seven times world champion Michael Schumacher.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/15/1740326_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230403034000 +0200" stop="20230403040500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Legendary Races: Targa Florio and Mille Miglia</title>
<desc lang="fr">Italy was home to two of the most famous road races of the 20th century: the Targa Florio and the Mille Miglia. From their very inception, these city to city road races were linked with both glamour and mortality, as racers lost their lives in pursuit of pace. The Targa, for example, was set on the mountain roads of Sicily and featured hairpin bends and dramatic changes of elevation. The Mille Miglia, on the other hand, made legends of marques like Alfa Romeo, Maserati, Mercedes-Benz, and Porsche.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/27/07/1774755_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230403040500 +0200" stop="20230403043500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Car History (Citroen) S2 (n°22)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Citroen»Always ahead of the time, always different from the others: For Citroen, the joy of the extravagance has always been the engine for automotive revolution. But for some time, Citroen mutated from exceptional to mass produced cars. Car History recalls the evolution of Citroen and reveals the secret behind three of its cult cars: the Gooddess, the Gangers' limousine and the Duck.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/15/1740326_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230403043500 +0200" stop="20230403050000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Classic Ride S7</title>
<desc lang="fr">With the M3, BMW brings race car technology to the road! 120 years Mercedes motorsport history. In celebration, Motorvision TV starts at the Nürburgring in Germany, with DTM legends Bernd Schneider and Ellen Lohr! Turbo-Power in the DTM. The Ford Sierra RS Cosworth teaches the racing competition the meaning of fear.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/24/2125716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230403050000 +0200" stop="20230403052500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Sabine Schmitz</title>
<desc lang="fr">&quot;&quot;Queen of the Nordschleife&quot;&quot;.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/19/1774199_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230403052500 +0200" stop="20230403060000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Rallye Sport 1984</title>
<desc lang="fr">1984. The rally professionals and Drift-artists, Hannu Mikkola, Walter Röhrl, Björn Waldegaard, Marku Alen and the rally- Amazon, Michele Mouton, fighting fiercly in Europe and Africa for the World Championship title.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/24/2125717_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230403060000 +0200" stop="20230403065000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">British Truck Racing</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Brisith Truck Racing Championship features some of the heaviest racing machines you'll ever see. Each truck weighs more than five tonnes and produces in excess of 1000bhp. The 2022 season features a total of 7 events that are contested around the United Kingdom.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1760716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230403065000 +0200" stop="20230403074000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">British Truck Racing</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Brisith Truck Racing Championship features some of the heaviest racing machines you'll ever see. Each truck weighs more than five tonnes and produces in excess of 1000bhp. The 2022 season features a total of 7 events that are contested around the United Kingdom.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/37/1760720_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230403074000 +0200" stop="20230403083000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Asian Le Mans Series</title>
<desc lang="fr">Asian sports car racing endurance series created by the Automobile Club de l'Ouest and based in Asia aims to attract teams and drivers from Asian countries. The Asian Le Mans Series is the symbol of the Spirit of Le Mans, and holds the same passion for creating world class endurance racing.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/20/00/2125604_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230403083000 +0200" stop="20230403092000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">WeatherTech SportsCar Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">Catch the action from the sports car racing series organized by the International Motor Sports Association. It is America's premier sports car racing series where almost all premium manufacturers are represented. This includes companies such as Acura, Aston Martin, Audi, BMW, Cadillac, Chevrolet, Ferrari, Honda, Lamborghini, Lexus, Mazda, Mercedes-AMG and Porsche.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/40/1752403_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230403092000 +0200" stop="20230403105500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">GT World Challenge Europe Sprint Cup</title>
<desc lang="fr">Join Motorvision TV as it brings you all the action from the European sports car racing series.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/50/1756288_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230403105500 +0200" stop="20230403120000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">DTM</title>
<desc lang="fr">The DTM - Deutsche Tourenwagen Masters - is the premier German touring car championship. In 2022, the competition is in its 23rd season and features 16 races across 8 weekends. Motorvision.TV shows the best bits from each event.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/25/2125719_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230403120000 +0200" stop="20230403122500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Car History (VW Golf) S2 (n°23)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«VW Golf»The Volkswagen Golf is a reasonable car. it's not really exiting, but a bestseller! With more than 30 million units sold, the Golf is one of the most successful cars in automotive history. The models of the first generation have been cult objects for years, especially the Golf GTI and the Golf Cabriolet. Car History tells the story of the Volkswagen Golf and reveals its secret to success.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/15/1740326_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230403122500 +0200" stop="20230403124500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Car People (Vintage Car Assessor Thomas Eschenbach) S3 (n°27)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Vintage Car Assessor Thomas Eschenbach»Laim, Munich, where Thomas Eschenbach's office is located. For 17 years he has been working as a surveyor for car damages and appraisals. His specialty: surveying and appraising classic cars.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/02/18/36/2149177_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230403124500 +0200" stop="20230403131000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Touareg JE Design</title>
<desc lang="fr">Phoenix Racing takes part in motorsports since the end of the 1990s and can look back at an impressive Wall of Fame. Tuning visits the team at the Nuerburgring. Plus: Tuning checks out the VW Touareg after it got the JE Design treatment and takes a look at the Oldtimer Grand Prix at the Nuerburgring, where thousands of fans of vintage old motorsports cars get together.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1760716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230403131000 +0200" stop="20230403135500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Southern Races Part 2</title>
<desc lang="fr">King of the Roads.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/37/1760719_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230403135500 +0200" stop="20230403142500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Tour European Rally Historic</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Tour European Rally Historic is a brand new independent rally series that made its debut in 2019. It offers an exciting mix of great rallies and outstanding venues.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/10/1763098_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230403142500 +0200" stop="20230403145000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Rali Bae Ceredigion</title>
<desc lang="fr">Tour European Rally is an up-and-coming rally series that combines some of Europe's most breathtaking and challenging rally events into one pan-European rally series. Each season consists of 5-6 individual events, plus annual TER promo events.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/54/1853467_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230403145000 +0200" stop="20230403151500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Championnat de Belgique des Rallyes</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Belgian Rally Championship is one of the most fiercely contested rally championships at a national level. It also attracts prominent guest entrants such as Thierry Neuville, Craig Breen and Stéphane Lefebvre.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/27/24/2149178_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230403151500 +0200" stop="20230403154000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Arctic Lapland Rally - A Tour European Rally Promo Event</title>
<desc lang="fr">Organised as a promo event by the TER, the Artic Lapland Rally is the coldest rally competition in the world. Despite temperatures dropping to -35°C, the rally attracts more than 200,000 spectators to Rovaniemi, the capital of Finnish Lappland. It's hated, but also loved among the 150 drivers taking part every year. MOTORVISION TV shows you the highlights from the 2020 Arctic Lapland Rally.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/55/1999411_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230403154000 +0200" stop="20230403160500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Rallye : Rallye Dakar</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Dakar Rally coverage which is an annual rally raid organised by the Amaury Sport Organisation.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/36/2118143_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230403160500 +0200" stop="20230403170000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Dubai International Baja</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Dubai International Baja, formerly known as the Dubai International Rally, is the oldest motorsport event in the United Arab Emirates. It is part of the reformed FIA World Cup for Cross-Country Bajas and based at the famous Dubai Autodrome. It will see international drivers taking on a demanding 407-kilometer stage running through the Al Qudra desert.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/27/08/1776289_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230403170000 +0200" stop="20230403180000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Australian Offroad Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">Founded in 2007, the Australian Off-Road Championship is the official Enduro championship of Motorcycling Australia. It provides a platform for all Australians that enjoy tight bush trails and fast open tracks. But its goal is not just to produce the nation's biggest off-road event, but also to produce top level off-road competitors who then move on to represent Australia in international Enduro competitions.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/46/1762227_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230403180000 +0200" stop="20230403182000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Go Green! S2</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Opel Ampera is the first electric family saloon that is designed to convince anyone that's wary of electric cars. After its introduction at the 2011 Geneva Motor Show, the mid-range car is now available for sale. Plus: Blacktrail, a 20-kilogramm electric bike with an output of 14 hp and a maximum torque of 280 Nm. It's the fastest and lightest e-bike in the world.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748432_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230403182000 +0200" stop="20230403184500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Perfect Ride S2</title>
<desc lang="fr">Europe's best show cars fight it out for the &quot;Tuning Crown&quot; at the Tuning World Bodensee. And: Clean and quiet, with zero emissions! Traveling with the Nissan Leaf electric car in the Norwegian capital Oslo.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/19/1748438_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230403184500 +0200" stop="20230403191000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Top Ten Show S1</title>
<desc lang="fr">On this episode we decide what's hot and what's not in the glamorous world of cars. This time we've decided to focus on the fastest cars.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/40/1752403_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230403191000 +0200" stop="20230403193500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 1</title>
<desc lang="fr">Street Racers is your backstage pass to the world of Formula E. Every two weeks, the magazine takes a look behind the scenes of the most important electric car racing series and provides reviews, current news, exciting interviews and gripping background reports from the world of Formula E.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/28/50/1880083_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230403193500 +0200" stop="20230403202000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">GT World Challenge Europe Sprint Cup</title>
<desc lang="fr">Join Motorvision TV as it brings you all the action from the European sports car racing series.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/50/1756288_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230403202000 +0200" stop="20230403205000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">MXGP of Patagonia, Vilal La Angostura</title>
<desc lang="fr">Lap after lap of international motorsports action. This is coverage from the FIM (Fédération Internationale de Motocyclisme) Motocross World Championship where riders from all over the globe compete in high-octane, fast-paced motocross racing. Competitors battle it out in races lasting 35 minutes plus 2 laps per race.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/32/1907968_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230403205000 +0200" stop="20230403211500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Grand Prix of Hungary, Budapest, Papp Laszlo SportAre</title>
<desc lang="fr">FIM SuperEnduro World Championship has been held since 2007. Its circuits are built inside stadiums or arenas, recreating obstacles such as rocks, boulders and logs. The championship consists of eight Grands Prix spread around the globe on courses that are mostly off-road. These events are split into two days and two different races, after which the points towards the world championship are awarded. Each round includes a motocross test and an extreme test, in addition to the enduro test.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/22/1748447_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230403211500 +0200" stop="20230403220500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Australian Motocross Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Australian ProMX Championship is the nation's premier motocross championship. The series acts as a successful development platform for young Australian talent and is designed as a tiered system with three dedicated classes: MX3 for younger drivers, the MX2 for senior drivers and the MX1, which is the elite category in the championship.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/31/43/1763097_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230403220500 +0200" stop="20230403225500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Grand Prix of Spain, Barcelona</title>
<desc lang="fr">FIM X-Trial World Championship is the most prestigious indoor motorcycle trials tournament of the world, organised by the Fédération Internationale de Motocyclisme. The programme presents the highlights of the rounds where the participants have to take on the challenging tracks full of steep climbs and huge rocks.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/13/2162902_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230403225500 +0200" stop="20230404000000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Australian Superbike Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">Founded in 1980, the Australian Superbike Championship is one of the most important motorcycle racing competitions in Oceania. It is well respected as a springboard for riders and teams who aspire an international career in motorcycling. The 2022 season is contested in five classes: Superbike, Supersport, Supersport 300, the Yamaha R3 Cup and the Oceania Junior Cup.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1763086_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230404000000 +0200" stop="20230404002500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Car History (BMW M) S2 (n°16)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«BMW M»The Motorsport division of BMW has been a success story since its inception, but they are not just celebrating success on the race tracks. The road cars with the letter M on the rear fascinate car drivers from around the world and quickly gained a large cult following. Car History looks back on BMW M which was founded in 1972 as BMW Motorsport GmbH.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/15/1740326_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230404002500 +0200" stop="20230404004500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Car People (Race Queen Sabine Schmitz) S1 (n°5)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Race Queen Sabine Schmitz»Sabine Schmitz is the queen of the Nordschleife. In 1996 she won The 24 Hours Nuerburgring in a BMW M3 as the first woman. In the next year she repeated her triumph right again. The Nordschleife has influenced her life.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/02/18/36/2149177_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230404004500 +0200" stop="20230404011000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">All-American Heroes</title>
<desc lang="fr">They are the automotive icons from America: Chevy, Ford Mustang and Corvette. They are extremely popular with the members of the tuning and refining community. They guarantee their owners finest V8 sound a true feeling of freedom. Fans of historic racing cars and rockabilly pay homage to their heroes at the Race 61. Plus: Tuning fathoms the history of the Ford Mustang from the very first to the latest model. It's a wild herd of Mustangs that just waits to be unleashed on the streets. And when all horses are captured again, Tuning releases the Corvette Z06 with the collective power of 659 horses.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1760716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230404011000 +0200" stop="20230404013500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">WeatherTech SportsCar Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Road to Racing.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/37/1760720_A.jpg" />
</programme>