<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Voo -->
<programme start="20230324013000 +0100" stop="20230324020000 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">MXGP of Lativa, Kegums</title>
<desc lang="fr">The FIM Motocross World Championship - also known as the MXGP - is the premier championship of motocross racing. In 2022, the championship and will be contested over 18 rounds in Europe, the Middle East, Asia and South America. Motorvision.TV takes viewers behind the scenes of every single event, presents interviews with all drivers and shows the most exciting moments from every weekend.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/32/1907968_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230324020000 +0100" stop="20230324022500 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Trial des Nations</title>
<desc lang="fr">The yearly Trial des Nations is the most important Motorcycle trials competition in the world and takes place after the Trial World Championship has concluded. In this event, drivers don't compete for themselves. Instead, four drivers work together as a team and compete for their own country. In 2019, the event takes place on Ibiza.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/37/1763099_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230324022500 +0100" stop="20230324025500 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Grand Prix of Germany, Riesa, SachsenArena</title>
<desc lang="fr">FIM SuperEnduro World Championship has been held since 2007. Its circuits are built inside stadiums or arenas, recreating obstacles such as rocks, boulders and logs. The championship consists of eight Grands Prix spread around the globe on courses that are mostly off-road. These events are split into two days and two different races, after which the points towards the world championship are awarded. Each round includes a motocross test and an extreme test, in addition to the enduro test.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/22/1748447_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230324025500 +0100" stop="20230324034000 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Australian Motocross Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Australian ProMX Championship is the nation's premier motocross championship. The series acts as a successful development platform for young Australian talent and is designed as a tiered system with three dedicated classes: MX3 for younger drivers, the MX2 for senior drivers and the MX1, which is the elite category in the championship.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1765320_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230324034000 +0100" stop="20230324043000 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Australian Superbike Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">Founded in 1980, the Australian Superbike Championship is one of the most important motorcycle racing competitions in Oceania. It is well respected as a springboard for riders and teams who aspire an international career in motorcycling. The 2022 season is contested in five classes: Superbike, Supersport, Supersport 300, the Yamaha R3 Cup and the Oceania Junior Cup.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/48/1853102_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230324043000 +0100" stop="20230324050000 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Enduro - Red Bull Romaniacs</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Red Bull Romaniacs is known for being the hardest Enduro Rally in the world. If you make it here you count yourself amongst the world's toughest enduro drivers. In 2019, the event acts as the fifth stop of the World Enduro Super Series and provides brilliant off-road action in the wilderness of Romania. MOTORVISION TV shows the best moments in this highlight recap.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/48/1853102_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230324050000 +0100" stop="20230324052500 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Car History (Auto Union) S3 (n°36)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Auto Union»The Auto Union is the incredible story of the 'Fantastic Four': Horch, Audi, DKW and Wanderer. With the sign of the four rings, they are the second-largest automotive group in Germany behind Opel in the 1930s. The four brands of Auto Union are automobile pacemakers, build technical milestones and the fastest car in the world. Today, the name is long gone, but the brand lives on.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/15/1740326_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230324052500 +0100" stop="20230324055000 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Car People (Vehicle Inspector Thomas Eschenbach) S2 (n°24)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Vehicle Inspector Thomas Eschenbach»Small incident but a big impact. After accidents, a damage appraisal should give a bit of clarity to the situation. The man to do this: Vehicle inspector Thomas Eschenbach.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/02/18/36/2149177_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230324055000 +0100" stop="20230324061500 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Stars of AMG</title>
<desc lang="fr">Mercedes' tuning company AMG starts its own battle of the stars - at least when it comes to horsepower. The C63 AMG, E 63 S AMG and S 63 AMG outdo each other with their performance data. AMG stands for Aufrecht, Melcher and Grossasbach - the founders' names and the founding site. But you could also read it as absolute motoring geniuses, because all stars of AMG offer ultimate driving pleasure.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1760716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230324061500 +0100" stop="20230324064000 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">WeatherTech SportsCar Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Road to Racing.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/25/1760725_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230324064000 +0100" stop="20230324073500 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Macau Bike Grand Prix</title>
<desc lang="fr">King of the Roads.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/37/1760719_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230324073500 +0100" stop="20230324082500 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Rolex Monterey Motorsports Reunion</title>
<desc lang="fr">Rolex Monterey Motorsports Reunion was established in 1974 under Monterey Historic Automobile Races moniker by Steve Earle. Today, it is an annual event held at Laguna Seca, California with over 500 historic racecars participating.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/37/1760720_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230324082500 +0100" stop="20230324085000 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Car History (Porsche Racing) S3 (n°27)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Porsche Racing»The Porsche 356, the 550 Spyder and the 917: None is faster, none is more reliable and none is more successful. They make Porsche number 1 in motorsports. In the 50s, 60s and 70s, there is hardly a race and barely a rally, that Porsche does not win. From the beginning, Porsche takes the knowledge gained from racing and uses it for series production.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/15/1740326_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230324085000 +0100" stop="20230324092000 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Classic Ride S7</title>
<desc lang="fr">Whoever believes in the socialist era of the East there was only oil smelly two-stroke Trabant and Wartburg or license production cars á la Lada, is wrong. Companies like Tatra from Czechoslovakia introduced in the fifties advanced, even pioneering automobiles. Unfortunately, the clientele was exclusive, and in the west countries the streamlined cars are big rarities. Today, these cars are cult and interesting collectibles. Classic Ride presents a lover and his extraordinary Tatra T87 of 1937.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/24/2125716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230324092000 +0100" stop="20230324094000 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Car History (SAAB) S2 (n°17)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«SAAB»Saab, the iconic brand from Sweden, is a rolling manifesto of &quot;otherness&quot;. A Saab is the perfect car for all non-conformists who have a sense of aesthetics, quality and comfort. They cars are considered to be individual and innovative. But in the end, Saab is insolvent as well. The fans remain though and keep the brand alive. Car History documents the rise and fall of this unique company.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/15/1740326_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230324094000 +0100" stop="20230324100500 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Hans-Joachim Stuck</title>
<desc lang="fr">Portrait of Hans-Joachim Stuck, one of the best race drivers in Germany. He stopped racing after participating in the 2011 24 Hours of Nürburgring.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/19/1774199_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230324100500 +0100" stop="20230324110000 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Le Mans Classic</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Le Mans Classic is a vintage sports car event that took place for the first time in 2002 on the site of the 24-hour race of Le Mans. All participating drivers are at a top level as far as driving is concerned.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/20/2162901_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230324110000 +0100" stop="20230324112500 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Car History (The Audi Story) S3 (n°35)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«The Audi Story»Selling more than a million cars per year, Audi is now one of the most successful car manufacturers in the world. The brand with the four rings does stand for innovation, superior technology and outstanding design. In the '80s Audi revolutionized the automotive world with the Audi Quattro, which not only changes the world of rally sports but also brings the all-wheel drive to everyday cars.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/15/1740326_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230324112500 +0100" stop="20230324115000 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Car People (Alex Renner Motors Dubai) S2 (n°23)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Alex Renner Motors Dubai»On the outskirts of Dubai, where the desert still prevails, a young man from Germany is working hard to make his dream come true: Alex Renner wants to run the most luxurious garage in the Arabian Golf.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/02/18/36/2149177_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230324115000 +0100" stop="20230324121500 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Magic NumberThree</title>
<desc lang="fr">Want an everyday car with extra power under the bonnet? The BMW 3-Series, Nissan 370 Z or Citroen CS DS3 are rather average cars. But as M-version, Nismo or Musketier, they get wild and become really powerful. While the Bavarian competitor comes with an output of431 hp, the Nismo from Japan offers an output of 344 PS. The Citroen musketeer on the other hand is as strong as 222 French horses.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1760716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230324121500 +0100" stop="20230324124500 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">WeatherTech SportsCar Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Road to Racing.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/59/1763095_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230324124500 +0100" stop="20230324133500 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Scarborough Gold Cup Part 2</title>
<desc lang="fr">King of the Roads.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/37/1760719_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230324133500 +0100" stop="20230324142500 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Australian V8 Superboats Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Australian V8 Superboat Championship is one of the most important watersports series from down under. Drivers compete in three different classes: the LS Class, Group A and Unlimited, which features hardly any restrictions regarding engine sizes. In 2022, a total of seven rounds are scheduled before a new champion is crowned.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/02/22/26/1784522_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230324142500 +0100" stop="20230324145000 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Powerboat: P1 USA AquaX Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">See all the action from the USA series of P1 AquaX, an exciting Jet Ski racing event, operated by Powerboat P1. P1 AquaX is an international motorboat racing competition organised by the Union Internationale Motornautique.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/37/1763088_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230324145000 +0100" stop="20230324151500 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">P1 Offshore Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">The P1 Offshore Powerboat Championship promises tightly fought offshore racing with powerboats reaching top speeds of up to 100 miles per hour. Five events are schedules for the 2022 season and Motorvision.TV brings you all the thrilling action from each event!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/31/2029804_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230324151500 +0100" stop="20230324154500 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Motonautisme : Championnat du monde de Formule 1</title>
<desc lang="fr">In 2022, the UIM is once again hosting its Formula 1 World Championship in Powerboat. In the 37th season, ten teams with 19 drivers from eleven countries have signed up to fight for the title of the new world champion in three Grand Prix.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/21/2061231_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230324154500 +0100" stop="20230324161000 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">UIM Aquabike World Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">Caution, danger of splashing! Since 1992, the Aquabike World Championship has been the most important racing series in the sport of jet skiing and one of the fastest competitions in water sports. On specially designed race courses or on the high seas, the participants engage in thrilling races in the ski and runabout categories and fascinate with all kinds of stunts on their more than 300 hp jet skis.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/00/1806160_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230324161000 +0100" stop="20230324170000 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Wanaka, Oxbow Track, Neuseeland</title>
<desc lang="fr">The New Zealand Jetsprint Championship is the most important sprint boat competition from New Zealand, the country where the sport was founded in 1981. Jetsprinting is comparable to rally sports, but there is only one boat on the track at any given time and boats drive at very high speeds. The up to 500 HP strong jet sprint boats therefore try to achieve the best time on the tracks.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/31/1774195_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230324170000 +0100" stop="20230324172500 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Car History (Ford - The Beginning of the Modern Era) S3 (n°37)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Ford - The Beginning of the Modern Era»At a time when horses and carriages characterized traffic, visionaries like Henry Ford were working on the mobility of tomorrow. His ideas and approaches have a major share of the individual mobilization in the world. The mass production of the Ford models is clearly one of the milestones in automotive history and Fords work has changed the world of cars forever. CAR HISTORY tells the whole story.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/15/1740326_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230324172500 +0100" stop="20230324175000 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Car People (The Red Baron) S2 (n°25)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«The Red Baron»Peter Goldstern- He's the Pilot who flies the King of Tonga around. He takes the Majesty of Tonga all around the South Pacific in the governments very own bright red aircraft. It would take 24 hours to get to Tonga from Germany.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/02/18/36/2149177_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230324175000 +0100" stop="20230324181500 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">GTs</title>
<desc lang="fr">GT used to stand for 'Gran Turisme', high performance racing cars for long-distance races. Today, FIA passes regulations for several GT classes. Car makers offer GT models as &quot;the icing on the cake&quot; of their model ranges, too. Mercedes even names a model GT and tops it all off with the GT S. Porsche knows to excite with a GTS as well, while J-Sport turns the Subaru GT 86 into a power machine.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1760716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230324181500 +0100" stop="20230324184000 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">WeatherTech SportsCar Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Road to Racing.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/40/1752403_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230324184000 +0100" stop="20230324193000 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Cookstown Road Races Part 1</title>
<desc lang="fr">King of the Roads.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/27/1760732_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230324193000 +0100" stop="20230324195500 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Drift : Championnat de France</title>
<desc lang="fr">When it comes to national drift competitions, the French Championship is one of the most important ones. 32 drivers compete in the spectacular main event.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/50/1756288_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230324195500 +0100" stop="20230324204500 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">e-Trophée Andros</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Andros Trophy is the French national ice racing championship. The idea appeared long time ago in 1985 when professional racer Max Mamers and the owner of the Andros company, Frédéric Gervoson, met as rugby fans. They spent the winter racing with friends on ice circuits. In 2003 the trophy gained an international aspect with a race at Sherbrooke in Canada. In 2020, the racing series is repositioning itself as an electric racing series.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/43/1884375_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230324204500 +0100" stop="20230324214000 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Hi-Tec Drift Allstars Series Australia</title>
<desc lang="fr">The latest drifting competition on Motorvision.TV brings you the best drifters from Australia. Join us for thrilling duels, smoking wheels and non-stop drift battles for the Drift All Stars Series title.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1760716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230324214000 +0100" stop="20230324223000 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">National Legend Cars</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Legends Cars National Championship brings back racing from yesteryear. The series features 5/8 scale replicas of pre-war 1930s Fords, Chevys and Dodges that are equipped with 125bhp-motorcycle engines. These cars are well known for delivering high-octane battles on race tracks around Great Britain.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1760716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230324223000 +0100" stop="20230324225500 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Icelandic Formula Offroad</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Icelandic Formula Off-Road is one of the most extreme racing series in the world and demands everything from the teams and their specially built vehicles. Nearly vertical cliffs have to be climbed, demanding time challenges have to be solved or spectacular aquaplaning stunts have to be performed.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1760716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230324225500 +0100" stop="20230324232500 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Car History (The Story of Automotive Advertising, Part 3) S3 (n°34)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«The Story of Automotive Advertising, Part 3»Whether as a TV spot, as product placement in cinema film or video, or on the Internet, in no other industry are brands, models and advertising campaigns as closely linked as in the automotive industry. And nowhere else is advertising so much fun as in automotive advertising.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/15/1740326_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230324232500 +0100" stop="20230324235000 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Car People (Rolls-Royce Show Room) S2 (n°22)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Rolls-Royce Show Room»Welcome, welcome! This is it. One of many, but one of very few in this particular city. It's a dream like car....car? can we even call it a car? It's a Rolls Royce.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/02/18/36/2149177_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230324235000 +0100" stop="20230325001500 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Porsche Garage and Chip Tuning</title>
<desc lang="fr">THE STABLE is the only Porsche garage in San Francisco for historic 911 models. Mike Fonfora put Marco Wendlandt's new Porsche 911 to the acid test to make sure, that Marco isn't disappointed when he sees his treasure for the very first time. The Chip Tuners from Race Chip have improved the Porsche Macan. The smallest SUV from Porsche offers now 480 hp, which are an additional 80 hp compared to the production model. Performmaster enhanced a power machine, too. Their Mercedes C 63 AMG T-model comes with an output of 612 hp and reaches a top speed of 310 km/h.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1760716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230325001500 +0100" stop="20230325004000 +0100" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">WeatherTech SportsCar Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Road to Racing.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/50/1756288_A.jpg" />
</programme>