<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Voo -->
<programme start="20230530023500 +0200" stop="20230530030000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">AWD Safari Challenge</title>
<desc lang="fr">Watch the exciting Safari Championship organized by the British All Wheel Drive Club, in which modified 4x4 vehicles of all brands can participate.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/51/1975304_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230530030000 +0200" stop="20230530035000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Hi-Tec Drift Allstars Series Australia</title>
<desc lang="fr">The latest drifting competition on Motorvision.TV brings you the best drifters from Australia. Join us for thrilling duels, smoking wheels and non-stop drift battles for the Drift All Stars Series title.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1760716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230530035000 +0200" stop="20230530041500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Arlington</title>
<desc lang="fr">Aucune description</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1760716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230530041500 +0200" stop="20230530051000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Top Fuel Australia Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">Aucune description</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/50/1756288_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230530051000 +0200" stop="20230530060000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">National Legend Cars</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Legends Cars National Championship brings back racing from yesteryear. The series features 5/8 scale replicas of pre-war 1930s Fords, Chevys and Dodges that are equipped with 125bhp-motorcycle engines. These cars are well known for delivering high-octane battles on race tracks around Great Britain.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/25/1760725_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230530060000 +0200" stop="20230530062500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Stunt Heroes (Body Stunt Highlights) S2 (n°14)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Body Stunt Highlights»Today it's Action Concepts most popular and most spectacular body stunts: Jumping from rooftops, falling of a driving car, tumbling down stairs. Despite inevitable wounds, the legendary stunt crew enjoys the job.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Découverte</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/15/35/1790601_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230530062500 +0200" stop="20230530065000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Supercars S2</title>
<desc lang="fr">What a car! It looks like it's been made in a futuristic factory. From a world beyond our recognition. It's fast and extremely powerful. It's unique!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748406_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230530065000 +0200" stop="20230530071500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Classic Ride S6</title>
<desc lang="fr">In 2013 the great Henry Ford would have turned 150 years old. The successful entrepreneur from the United States is best known for introducing the assembly line and mass production of automobiles. Classic Ride pays tribute to Henry Ford and three models that can be considered an important part of his sporting heritage: Ford Thunderbird (1955), Ford Mustang (1964) and Ford Capri (1968).</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/24/2125716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230530071500 +0200" stop="20230530074500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Formula E - Specials</title>
<desc lang="fr">In less than six years the ABB FIA Formula E Championship has grown from ambitious start-up to one of the most innovative sports entertainment properties in the world, attracting a host of the globe's biggest automotive manufacturers. The Story Of Formula E plots the extraordinary rise of the all-electric championship with some of the key players including Lucas Di Grassi, Jean Eric Vergne, Sebastien Buemi, Sam Bird and founder Alejandro Agag.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/12/06/2195752_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230530074500 +0200" stop="20230530083000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">WeatherTech SportsCar Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">The IMSA Weathertech Sportscar Championship is back on MOTORVISION TV. Twelve races are again scheduled for the 2022 season, including four endurance classics. Motorvision TV provides live and extensive highlights coverage of all events.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/40/1752403_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230530083000 +0200" stop="20230530090000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">MXGP of Portugal, Agueda</title>
<desc lang="fr">Lap after lap of international motorsports action. This is coverage from the FIM (Fédération Internationale de Motocyclisme) Motocross World Championship where riders from all over the globe compete in high-octane, fast-paced motocross racing. Competitors battle it out in races lasting 35 minutes plus 2 laps per race.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/20/00/1907968_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230530090000 +0200" stop="20230530092500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Grand Prix of Poland, Krakow, Tauron Arena</title>
<desc lang="fr">FIM SuperEnduro World Championship has been held since 2007. Its circuits are built inside stadiums or arenas, recreating obstacles such as rocks, boulders and logs. The championship consists of eight Grands Prix spread around the globe on courses that are mostly off-road. These events are split into two days and two different races, after which the points towards the world championship are awarded. Each round includes a motocross test and an extreme test, in addition to the enduro test.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/22/1748447_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230530092500 +0200" stop="20230530101500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Australian Motocross Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Australian ProMX Championship is the nation's premier motocross championship. The series acts as a successful development platform for young Australian talent and is designed as a tiered system with three dedicated classes: MX3 for younger drivers, the MX2 for senior drivers and the MX1, which is the elite category in the championship.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/07/2125726_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230530101500 +0200" stop="20230530111000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Grand Prix of Andorra</title>
<desc lang="fr">FIM X-Trial World Championship is the most prestigious indoor motorcycle trials tournament of the world, organised by the Fédération Internationale de Motocyclisme. The programme presents the highlights of the rounds where the participants have to take on the challenging tracks full of steep climbs and huge rocks.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/13/2162902_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230530111000 +0200" stop="20230530120000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Australian Superbike Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">Welcome to the national motorcycle racing championship in Australia, organised by Motorcycling Australia. Get all the action and cutting edge stories, reports and results.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/38/1760724_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230530120000 +0200" stop="20230530125000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">British Truck Racing</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Brisith Truck Racing Championship features some of the heaviest racing machines you'll ever see. Each truck weighs more than five tonnes and produces in excess of 1000bhp. The 2022 season features a total of 7 events that are contested around the United Kingdom.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/37/1760720_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230530125000 +0200" stop="20230530134000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">DTM</title>
<desc lang="fr">The DTM - Deutsche Tourenwagen Masters - is the premier German touring car championship. In 2022, the competition is in its 23rd season and features 16 races across 8 weekends. Motorvision.TV shows the best bits from each event.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/25/2125719_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230530134000 +0200" stop="20230530143500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Ferrari Challenge Europe</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Ferrari Challenge is a single-marque motorsport championship that was created in 1993 and is now the longest-running single-make series championship. The European series is a two-class championship and by far the largest series. It contains 7 races, held on challenging and most prestigious European circuits.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/25/55/2162175_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230530143500 +0200" stop="20230530152000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">GT World Challenge Europe Sprint Cup</title>
<desc lang="fr">Join Motorvision TV as it brings you all the action from the European sports car racing series.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/40/1752403_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230530152000 +0200" stop="20230530160500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">WeatherTech SportsCar Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">The IMSA WeatherTech SportsCar Championhip is an endurance racing championship in North America where up to five different classes compete in eleven events.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/37/1760720_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230530160500 +0200" stop="20230530165500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">GT World Challenge America</title>
<desc lang="fr">It's America's most challenging and scenic circuits. GT World Challenge America offers exclusive GT3 racing in an exciting way with the two-driver, 90-minute SprintX style format with full-service pit stops that provide great racing and high competition. Each event features two races per weekend in a friendly atmosphere. Many manufacturers including Acura, BMW, Bentley, Ferrari, Lamborghini, Mercedes-AMG, Nissan, and Porsche campaign entries in the category.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/25/1760725_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230530165500 +0200" stop="20230530174000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">GT World Challenge Europe Brands Hatch</title>
<desc lang="fr">GT World Challenge Europe arrives at Brands Hatch, showcasing cars from the biggest manufacturers, the likes of Audi, Porsche, Ferrari, and more. View the latest action, updates, and stats from the event!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/50/1756288_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230530174000 +0200" stop="20230530180000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Championnat d'Europe de courses de camions</title>
<desc lang="fr">The FIA European Truck Racing Championship is the biggest, most imposing racing series in the world. The racing trucks are equipped with 1200 hp engines doing up to 100 miles per hour. On a grid with 26 big rigs the 5.5-ton machines doing battle there's guaranteed action-packed lights-to-flag racing galore.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/25/00/1748421_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230530180000 +0200" stop="20230530182500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Stunt Heroes (Car Action Highlights) S2 (n°15)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Car Action Highlights»Ther are million ways to destroy a car: Crashes, flips and jumps. We show the highlights of this seasons car stunts.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Découverte</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/22/36/2200148_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230530182500 +0200" stop="20230530185000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Supercars S2</title>
<desc lang="fr">The evolutionary history of the Infinity FX50, Sebastian Vettel Edition. 1.370 Kg and 620 horsepower - this is the Porsche GT2 RS. This car is the most expensive and fastest serial 911 Porsche all times.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748406_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230530185000 +0200" stop="20230530192000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Classic Ride S6</title>
<desc lang="fr">The VW: Type 166 Amphibious Vehicle is the all-rounder amongst off-road vehicles. Peugeot 205 Turbo 16. The French all-wheel cracker mixes up the World Rally Championship in the 80s. And : Willys Jeep in the Drive Report. The ascetic SUV conquered the World by storm and the hearts of off-road enthusiasts.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/24/2125716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230530192000 +0200" stop="20230530194500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Formula E - Specials</title>
<desc lang="fr">In less than six years the ABB FIA Formula E Championship has grown from ambitious start-up to one of the most innovative sports entertainment properties in the world, attracting a host of the globe's biggest automotive manufacturers. The Story Of Formula E plots the extraordinary rise of the all-electric championship with some of the key players including Lucas Di Grassi, Jean Eric Vergne, Sebastien Buemi, Sam Bird and founder Alejandro Agag.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/12/06/2195752_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230530194500 +0200" stop="20230530203500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">WeatherTech SportsCar Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">The IMSA Weathertech Sportscar Championship is back on MOTORVISION TV. Twelve races are again scheduled for the 2022 season, including four endurance classics. Motorvision TV provides live and extensive highlights coverage of all events.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/25/1760725_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230530203500 +0200" stop="20230530210000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Bike World</title>
<desc lang="fr">Bike World revolves around the speedway and the racers swishing by on their two wheelers. Find out the latest news and reports regarding two-wheel competitions in the world of speed. This is the content to enjoy for all motorcycle enthusiasts across the world. Explore the best motorbikes, top locations, and iconic racers who have a lot of fun doing it.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/32/1837877_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230530210000 +0200" stop="20230530212500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 2</title>
<desc lang="fr">Exciting sports show that follows the hottest action from the world's most unique motor sport events. Viewers will have a chance to visit some interesting competitions- from IDEMITSU 600 Super Endurance at the Chang Interna-tional Circuit in Thailand, the winter edition of the Maroc Challenge in Morocco, to the Hispania Rally, the only European rally to take place in the desert, and many more. Viewers will also find out all the news from the world of motor sports.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1760716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230530212500 +0200" stop="20230530215000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Perfect Ride S6</title>
<desc lang="fr">What's hot and what's not. There are quests to be undertaken, the search for the ideal auto, for the perfect race track for the ultimate accessory gadget. What are the preferred rides of the race legends?</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/20/01/2153087_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230530215000 +0200" stop="20230530221500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Supercars</title>
<desc lang="fr">A synergy of high-octane power, speed, luxury and prestige. Supercars features some of the most desirable automobiles in the world, whether it be an agile sports car to a comfortable limousine. It features the likes of prestige brands filled with rich heritage and motorsport pedigree; such as Bentley, BMW M, Mercedes AMG, Aston Martin, Maserati, Porsche and Ferrari to niche-market, lightweight Lotuses, KTMs and Caterhams. Supercars has everything a petrolhead needs to get up to speed on the latest and greatest of high-performance road machines.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748406_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230530221500 +0200" stop="20230530224000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Go Green! S1</title>
<desc lang="fr">There' s no roaring V8 under this SLS AMG E-Cell's bonnet. Instead, the power suppliers of this athlete are four electric motors with a combined 533 horsepower. It's completely emission-free, and very quiet.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748432_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230530224000 +0200" stop="20230530232000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Spotted</title>
<desc lang="fr">Drag racing is extreme motorsports with high potential for addiction. Top-fuel methanol drag cars are equipped with 5000-hp V8 engines. Pure tension is guaranteed, when pilots and their vehicles accelerate from 0 to 500 kmph in less than five seconds. Not as brutal as dragsters, but just as exciting: V8 sports cars. The Aston Martin DB11 comes with a V8 engine for the very first time.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/20/59/1884377_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230530232000 +0200" stop="20230531000000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Trackmasters</title>
<desc lang="fr">On today's episode we are going old-timer crazy, like the Mercedes S for example with 160 horsepower that lead Rudolf Caracciola to victory in the 1927 opening race. Do not to miss this old-timer grand prix event!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/25/59/1986723_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230531000000 +0200" stop="20230531003000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Stunt Heroes (The Remote Control) S1 (n°3)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«The Remote Control»The Stunt Heroes from Action Concept try out another new stunt: Stuntman Tobi, aka Heidi, operates an Artega GT at full speed with a remote control. This is, however, just a warm-up before the big stunt, in which he drives a car up a steep ramp at 68 mph. The Question is: How high can remote control cars fly? It's an action-packed flying spectacle!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Découverte</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/15/35/1790601_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230531003000 +0200" stop="20230531005500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Supercars S2</title>
<desc lang="fr">The evolutionary history of the Infinity FX50, Sebastian Vettel Edition. 1.370 Kg and 620 horsepower - this is the Porsche GT2 RS. This car is the most expensive and fastest serial 911 Porsche all times.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748406_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230531005500 +0200" stop="20230531012000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Classic Ride S3</title>
<desc lang="fr">It is sexy, spectacular and comes with tremendous speed: the Audi Sport quattro S1, the most exciting rally car ever built. In part 2 of the S1 special, Classic Rides accompanies S1 pilot Michael Gerber during the second day of the Rally Legend. Plus: The whole story of the S1 told with original comments by former world champion Walter Röhrl.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/24/2125716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230531012000 +0200" stop="20230531014500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Formula E - Specials</title>
<desc lang="fr">In less than six years the ABB FIA Formula E Championship has grown from ambitious start-up to one of the most innovative sports entertainment properties in the world, attracting a host of the globe's biggest automotive manufacturers. The Story Of Formula E plots the extraordinary rise of the all-electric championship with some of the key players including Lucas Di Grassi, Jean Eric Vergne, Sebastien Buemi, Sam Bird and founder Alejandro Agag.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/12/06/2195752_A.jpg" />
</programme>