<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Voo -->
<programme start="20230410022500 +0200" stop="20230410031500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Silverstone</title>
<desc lang="fr">Aucune description</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/33/1777567_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230410031500 +0200" stop="20230410034000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Rallye Monte Carlo Historique</title>
<desc lang="fr">The infamous Monte-Carlo Rally is one of the world's oldest rally events in the world. To pay tribute to its long-lasting history, the Automobile Club de Monaco organizes the Rallye Monte-Carlo Historique. The catch is: Only cars that competed in the Monte-Carlo Rally at least 40 years ago are allowed to take part in the historic edition of the Monte-Carlo Rally.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/40/1752403_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230410034000 +0200" stop="20230410040500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Hans Herrmann</title>
<desc lang="fr">Portrait of Hans Herrmann, who was famous Formula 1- and sports car driver in 1950 to 1970. He also won the 24 Hours of Le Mans.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/19/1774199_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230410040500 +0200" stop="20230410043000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Car History (Porsche Racing) S3 (n°27)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Porsche Racing»The Porsche 356, the 550 Spyder and the 917: None is faster, none is more reliable and none is more successful. They make Porsche number 1 in motorsports. In the 50s, 60s and 70s, there is hardly a race and barely a rally, that Porsche does not win. From the beginning, Porsche takes the knowledge gained from racing and uses it for series production.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/15/1740326_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230410043000 +0200" stop="20230410050000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Rallye Corsica 1997</title>
<desc lang="fr">Round six of the FIA World Rally Championship was held on the Mediterranean island of Corsica. With its narrow, twisty mountain roads. 1997 was the 41st running of the tour de course. Based in the island's capital at Ajaccio, the three day event included over two hundred kilometers of new stages.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/24/2125717_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230410050000 +0200" stop="20230410052500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Car History (The Story of Automotive Advertising, Part 3) S3 (n°34)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«The Story of Automotive Advertising, Part 3»Whether as a TV spot, as product placement in cinema film or video, or on the Internet, in no other industry are brands, models and advertising campaigns as closely linked as in the automotive industry. And nowhere else is advertising so much fun as in automotive advertising.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/15/1740326_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230410052500 +0200" stop="20230410060000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Classic Ride S4</title>
<desc lang="fr">The extraordinary story of the Chevrolet Corvair. The Chevrolet Corvair is pretty much unheard of in Europe, despite almost 1.4 million units sold. It was innovative, economical, modern, low priced and the first car which featured a turbocharger upon request. The car was nevertheless criticized, slated and later condemned.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/24/2125716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230410060000 +0200" stop="20230410065000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">BTRDA Rallycross Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">Being a mixture of circuit racing and rallying, rallycross is often considered to be the wildchild of motor sports. One of the most exciting competitions in this genre is the BTRDA Rallycross Championship. Motorvision.TV brings you the highlights from each of their events.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1760716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230410065000 +0200" stop="20230410074000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Ferrari Challenge Europe</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Ferrari Challenge Europe is back for another season on Motorvision.TV. The longest-running single-make series championship in the history of the Prancing Horse-company promises high performance and talented drivers on challenging tracks around Europe. Seven events are scheduled for the 2022 season including the Finali Mondiali, which brings together the final stages of all Ferrari Challenge divisions around the world.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/25/55/2162175_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230410074000 +0200" stop="20230410080500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Championnat d'Europe de courses de camions</title>
<desc lang="fr">The FIA European Truck Racing Championship is the biggest, most imposing racing series in the world. The racing trucks are equipped with 1200 hp engines doing up to 100 miles per hour. On a grid with 26 big rigs the 5.5-ton machines doing battle there's guaranteed action-packed lights-to-flag racing galore.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/25/00/1748421_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230410080500 +0200" stop="20230410090000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Asian Le Mans Series</title>
<desc lang="fr">Asian sports car racing endurance series created by the Automobile Club de l'Ouest and based in Asia aims to attract teams and drivers from Asian countries. The Asian Le Mans Series is the symbol of the Spirit of Le Mans, and holds the same passion for creating world class endurance racing.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/20/00/2125604_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230410090000 +0200" stop="20230410094500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">WeatherTech SportsCar Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">Catch the action from the sports car racing series organized by the International Motor Sports Association. It is America's premier sports car racing series where almost all premium manufacturers are represented. This includes companies such as Acura, Aston Martin, Audi, BMW, Cadillac, Chevrolet, Ferrari, Honda, Lamborghini, Lexus, Mazda, Mercedes-AMG and Porsche.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/50/1756288_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230410094500 +0200" stop="20230410103500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">NW200 Races Part 1</title>
<desc lang="fr">King of the Roads.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/27/1760732_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230410103500 +0200" stop="20230410111500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">GP UK, Brands Hatch Indy Circuit</title>
<desc lang="fr">NASCAR, America's most popular racing series, is now well established in Europe and there is no better proof than its European division: the NASCAR Whelen Euro Series. This year, 17 teams from nine different countries with a total of 39 cars prove once again that the NWES with its pure racing character is one of the best touring car series on the old continent. Motorvision.TV shows highlights from every race weekend.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748423_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230410111500 +0200" stop="20230410120000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">GT World Challenge America</title>
<desc lang="fr">Fanatec GT World Challenge America is the premier North American GT series. Taking place on the best US circuits form Sonoma to Indianapolis, each of the seven race weekends features 90-min double-header races.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/40/1752403_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230410120000 +0200" stop="20230410122000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Go Green! S2</title>
<desc lang="fr">At first glance, the Audi A1 on this episode of Go Green seems to be an ordinary small city car, but it's actually quote special. It's driving almost without any emission. Plus: Spectacular design, unusual proportions and innovative ideas - the new Hyundai Veloster is one of the most extraordinary series cars of late. And: The Porsche Panamera S Hybrid combines driving fun with ecology.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748432_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230410122000 +0200" stop="20230410124500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Perfect Ride S1</title>
<desc lang="fr">Today's episode of Perfect Ride is all about setting off and not stopping until you've reached the peak. We will therefore be revving up to the top! The Audi A1 Quattro may seem small, but it's a tough little fighter.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/19/1748438_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230410124500 +0200" stop="20230410131000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Top Ten Show S1</title>
<desc lang="fr">The 24-hour-race at the German Nurburgring is one of the most famous and dangerous long-distance races in the world and in today's program we'll show you the cars that have won the most titles each year.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/50/1752909_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230410131000 +0200" stop="20230410134000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 7</title>
<desc lang="fr">Street Racers is your backstage pass to the world of Formula E. Every two weeks, the magazine takes a look behind the scenes of the most important electric car racing series and provides reviews, current news, exciting interviews and gripping background reports from the world of Formula E.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/59/1880083_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230410134000 +0200" stop="20230410142500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">GT World Challenge Europe Sprint Cup</title>
<desc lang="fr">Join Motorvision TV as it brings you all the action from the European sports car racing series.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/25/1760725_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230410142500 +0200" stop="20230410145000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Tour European Rally Historic</title>
<desc lang="fr">Motorvision TV brings you all the action from the independent rally series taking place around Europe.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/48/2123747_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230410145000 +0200" stop="20230410151500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Rallye : Tour European Rally</title>
<desc lang="fr">Amazing challenge around Europe includes 19 special stages. The top crew will become Tour European Rally champion in one of the most beautiful European rallies.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/28/1760738_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230410151500 +0200" stop="20230410154000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Championnat de Belgique des Rallyes</title>
<desc lang="fr">Motorvision TV brings you all the action from one of the most competitive national rallies in Europe.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/21/2149178_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230410154000 +0200" stop="20230410163500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Rallye : Abu Dhabi Desert Challenge</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Abu Dhabi Challenge is one of the most prestigious international cross rallies. Motorbike, quad-bike, four wheel and truck competitors battle Abu Dhabi's magnificent desert in a grueling 5-day event. In the past, international motorsports icons like Carlos Sainz, Colin McRae and Heinz Kinigadner followed the call and took on the challenging dunes of the United Arabian Emirates.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/47/1808106_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230410163500 +0200" stop="20230410170000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Dubai International Baja</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Dubai International Baja, formerly known as the Dubai International Rally, is the oldest motorsport event in the United Arab Emirates. It is part of the reformed FIA World Cup for Cross-Country Bajas and based at the famous Dubai Autodrome. It will see international drivers taking on a demanding 407-kilometer stage running through the Al Qudra desert.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/50/1776289_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230410170000 +0200" stop="20230410173000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Rally Clasico Mallorca</title>
<desc lang="fr">Motorvision.TV shows the best moments from the 2022 eMallorca Challenge.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/38/1758023_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230410173000 +0200" stop="20230410180000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Spa-Classic</title>
<desc lang="fr">Created in 2011 on one of the most iconic circuit in the world, the Spa Classic is now one of the major European events for historic racing cars. In 2019, Spa Classic celebrates its ninth staging and features events like nighttime races for touring cars and the Heritage Touring Cup, which pays tribute to the famous Spa-Francorchamps 24 Hours for Touring Cars.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/25/1760725_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230410180000 +0200" stop="20230410182000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Go Green! S2</title>
<desc lang="fr">After the Tsunami and Fukushima - This years Tokyo Motor Show will promote both optimism and fun. The highlights: Mercedes brought the study of the hydrogen-powered F125 to the 'Land of the Rising Sun'.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748432_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230410182000 +0200" stop="20230410185000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Perfect Ride S5</title>
<desc lang="fr">In 1989 Audi introduced the first turbocharged diesel engine. Since then turbochargers became standard and result into smooth running of engines and increased driving pleasure. Perfect Ride reviews the latest TDI engines and previews the Audi RS5 TDI Concept, which shows how sporty diesel engines could be used in future production cars.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/19/1748438_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230410185000 +0200" stop="20230410191000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Top Ten Show S1</title>
<desc lang="fr">In today's show we are going to show you the most affordable hybrid models. The trail-blazers are definitely the Japanese, who have a whole bunch of cars to offer.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/50/1752909_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230410191000 +0200" stop="20230410194000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 3</title>
<desc lang="fr">Street Racers is your backstage pass to the world of Formula E. Every two weeks, the magazine takes a look behind the scenes of the most important electric car racing series and provides reviews, current news, exciting interviews and gripping background reports from the world of Formula E.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/59/1880083_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230410194000 +0200" stop="20230410202500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">GT World Challenge Europe Sprint Cup</title>
<desc lang="fr">Join Motorvision TV as it brings you all the action from the European sports car racing series.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/59/1763095_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230410202500 +0200" stop="20230410205000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">MXGP of Patagonia, Vilal La Angostura</title>
<desc lang="fr">Lap after lap of international motorsports action. This is coverage from the FIM (Fédération Internationale de Motocyclisme) Motocross World Championship where riders from all over the globe compete in high-octane, fast-paced motocross racing. Competitors battle it out in races lasting 35 minutes plus 2 laps per race.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/32/1907968_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230410205000 +0200" stop="20230410212000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Grand Prix of Hungary, Budapest, Papp Laszlo SportAre</title>
<desc lang="fr">FIM SuperEnduro World Championship has been held since 2007. Its circuits are built inside stadiums or arenas, recreating obstacles such as rocks, boulders and logs. The championship consists of eight Grands Prix spread around the globe on courses that are mostly off-road. These events are split into two days and two different races, after which the points towards the world championship are awarded. Each round includes a motocross test and an extreme test, in addition to the enduro test.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/22/1748447_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230410212000 +0200" stop="20230410220500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Australian Motocross Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Australian ProMX Championship is the nation's premier motocross championship. The series acts as a successful development platform for young Australian talent and is designed as a tiered system with three dedicated classes: MX3 for younger drivers, the MX2 for senior drivers and the MX1, which is the elite category in the championship.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/24/2125721_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230410220500 +0200" stop="20230410230000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Grand Prix of Spain, Barcelona</title>
<desc lang="fr">FIM X-Trial World Championship is the most prestigious indoor motorcycle trials tournament of the world, organised by the Fédération Internationale de Motocyclisme. The programme presents the highlights of the rounds where the participants have to take on the challenging tracks full of steep climbs and huge rocks.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/13/2162902_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230410230000 +0200" stop="20230411000000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Australian Superbike Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">Founded in 1980, the Australian Superbike Championship is one of the most important motorcycle racing competitions in Oceania. It is well respected as a springboard for riders and teams who aspire an international career in motorcycling. The 2022 season is contested in five classes: Superbike, Supersport, Supersport 300, the Yamaha R3 Cup and the Oceania Junior Cup.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/48/1853102_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230411000000 +0200" stop="20230411002500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Go Green! S2</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Lexus RX 450h is the second revised hybrid model coming from the Toyota Group. Go Green checks out the full hybrid SUV. Plus: The young car manufactory Artega emphasizes the importance of ecologically sensitive sports cars and presents the electric Artega SE. And: Go Green takes a look at the BMW Active E, which is an electric vehicle based on the BMW 1 Series.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748432_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230411002500 +0200" stop="20230411005000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Perfect Ride S2</title>
<desc lang="fr">Today in Perfect Ride: It's all about performance. Michael Schumacher in a Formula 1 Silver Arrow on the Nordschleife. In Comparison Test: The Eternal Rally counterparts Mitsubishi Lancer EVO and Subaru WRX STI.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/19/1748438_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230411005000 +0200" stop="20230411011500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Top Ten Show S1</title>
<desc lang="fr">Day in day out, R&amp;D departments of car manufacturers ponder over about what constitutes the perfect car. It has to be extraordinary. It has to stand out and it has to be unique. This is how new concepts and models come into fruition. So today, we'll present you the ten most unusual cars of the past few years.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/50/1752909_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230411011500 +0200" stop="20230411014500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 6</title>
<desc lang="fr">Street Racers is your backstage pass to the world of Formula E. Every two weeks, the magazine takes a look behind the scenes of the most important electric car racing series and provides reviews, current news, exciting interviews and gripping background reports from the world of Formula E.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/59/1880083_A.jpg" />
</programme>