<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Voo -->
<programme start="20230516023000 +0200" stop="20230516025500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">AWD Safari Challenge</title>
<desc lang="fr">Watch the exciting Safari Championship organized by the British All Wheel Drive Club, in which modified 4x4 vehicles of all brands can participate.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/51/1975304_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230516025500 +0200" stop="20230516035000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Hi-Tec Drift Allstars Series Australia</title>
<desc lang="fr">The latest drifting competition on Motorvision.TV brings you the best drifters from Australia. Join us for thrilling duels, smoking wheels and non-stop drift battles for the Drift All Stars Series title.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/50/1756288_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230516035000 +0200" stop="20230516041500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">San Antonio Race 1</title>
<desc lang="fr">Aucune description</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/40/1752403_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230516041500 +0200" stop="20230516051000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Top Fuel Australia Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">Aucune description</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/37/1760720_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230516051000 +0200" stop="20230516060000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">National Legend Cars</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Legends Cars National Championship brings back racing from yesteryear. The series features 5/8 scale replicas of pre-war 1930s Fords, Chevys and Dodges that are equipped with 125bhp-motorcycle engines. These cars are well known for delivering high-octane battles on race tracks around Great Britain.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/50/1756288_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230516060000 +0200" stop="20230516062500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Stunt Heroes (The Flying Quad) S2 (n°23)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«The Flying Quad»The Stunt Heroes bring a quad bike to its limits. With a so-called stamp and a pressure of 100 bar the quad bike will learn to fly.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/15/35/1790601_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230516062500 +0200" stop="20230516065000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Supercars S5</title>
<desc lang="fr">Being one step ahead of time has always been a bit pricier. But is the new BMW i8 just an luxurious, avant-garde carrier of technology or can it already be considered as a serious sports car? Why should you pay double the price compared to the BMW M4? Why shouldn't you buy a good looking BMW M5, which has the same price, but is more functional? Supercars reveals the answers.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748406_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230516065000 +0200" stop="20230516071500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Classic Ride S5</title>
<desc lang="fr">For more than 50 years the Porsche 911 has been driving on the roads and race tracks of the world. Each generation set standards in the sports car segment. We look back at the beginnings of this success story. But it is not the only legend from the class of 1963. At the same time Corvette Stingray celebrates its premier and becomes the American sports car dream par excellence.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/24/2125716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230516071500 +0200" stop="20230516074000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 9</title>
<desc lang="fr">Street Racers is your backstage pass to the world of Formula E. Every two weeks, the magazine takes a look behind the scenes of the most important electric car racing series and provides reviews, current news, exciting interviews and gripping background reports from the world of Formula E.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/59/1880083_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230516074000 +0200" stop="20230516083500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Ferrari Challenge Europe</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Ferrari Challenge Europe is back for another season on Motorvision.TV. The longest-running single-make series championship in the history of the Prancing Horse-company promises high performance and talented drivers on challenging tracks around Europe. Seven events are scheduled for the 2022 season including the Finali Mondiali, which brings together the final stages of all Ferrari Challenge divisions around the world.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/25/55/2162175_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230516083500 +0200" stop="20230516090000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">MXGP of Trentino, Pietramurata</title>
<desc lang="fr">Lap after lap of international motorsports action. This is coverage from the FIM (Fédération Internationale de Motocyclisme) Motocross World Championship where riders from all over the globe compete in high-octane, fast-paced motocross racing. Competitors battle it out in races lasting 35 minutes plus 2 laps per race.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/32/1907968_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230516090000 +0200" stop="20230516092500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Grand Prix of Poland, Gliwice</title>
<desc lang="fr">FIM SuperEnduro World Championship has been held since 2007. Its circuits are built inside stadiums or arenas, recreating obstacles such as rocks, boulders and logs. The championship consists of eight Grands Prix spread around the globe on courses that are mostly off-road. These events are split into two days and two different races, after which the points towards the world championship are awarded. Each round includes a motocross test and an extreme test, in addition to the enduro test.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/22/1748447_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230516092500 +0200" stop="20230516101500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Australian Motocross Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Australian ProMX Championship is the nation's premier motocross championship. The series acts as a successful development platform for young Australian talent and is designed as a tiered system with three dedicated classes: MX3 for younger drivers, the MX2 for senior drivers and the MX1, which is the elite category in the championship.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/31/43/1763097_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230516101500 +0200" stop="20230516111000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Grand Prix of France, Bordeaux</title>
<desc lang="fr">FIM X-Trial World Championship is the most prestigious indoor motorcycle trials tournament of the world, organised by the Fédération Internationale de Motocyclisme. The programme presents the highlights of the rounds where the participants have to take on the challenging tracks full of steep climbs and huge rocks.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/13/2162902_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230516111000 +0200" stop="20230516120000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Victoria</title>
<desc lang="fr">Aucune description</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/15/12/2185021_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230516120000 +0200" stop="20230516125000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">DTM</title>
<desc lang="fr">The DTM - Deutsche Tourenwagen Masters - is the premier German touring car championship. In 2022, the competition is in its 23rd season and features 16 races across 8 weekends. Motorvision.TV shows the best bits from each event.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/25/2125719_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230516125000 +0200" stop="20230516134500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Ferrari Challenge Europe</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Ferrari Challenge is a single-marque motorsport championship that was created in 1993 and is now the longest-running single-make series championship. The European series is a two-class championship and by far the largest series. It contains 7 races, held on challenging and most prestigious European circuits.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/25/55/2162175_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230516134500 +0200" stop="20230516143000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">WeatherTech SportsCar Championship</title>
<desc lang="fr">The IMSA WeatherTech SportsCar Championhip is an endurance racing championship in North America where up to five different classes compete in eleven events.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/40/1752403_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230516143000 +0200" stop="20230516152500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Autodromo di Imola, Italy</title>
<desc lang="fr">European Le Mans Series believes in the team spirit during long distance performance. The duty of the ELMS is to offer its competitors a full season to race their cars on some of the best tracks in Europe, while keeping tight control of the costs associated with running in a top European wide series. The champions are offered a place on the grid of the 24 Heures du Mans, which gives an extra, important dimension to the title race across the three categories.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/08/39/2182076_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230516152500 +0200" stop="20230516161000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">GT World Challenge Europe Sprint Cup</title>
<desc lang="fr">Join Motorvision TV as it brings you all the action from the European sports car racing series.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/50/1756288_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230516161000 +0200" stop="20230516165500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">GT World Challenge Europe Sprint Cup</title>
<desc lang="fr">Join Motorvision TV as it brings you all the action from the European sports car racing series.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/25/1760725_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230516165500 +0200" stop="20230516174500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">GT World Challenge America</title>
<desc lang="fr">It's America's most challenging and scenic circuits. GT World Challenge America offers exclusive GT3 racing in an exciting way with the two-driver, 90-minute SprintX style format with full-service pit stops that provide great racing and high competition. Each event features two races per weekend in a friendly atmosphere. Many manufacturers including Acura, BMW, Bentley, Ferrari, Lamborghini, Mercedes-AMG, Nissan, and Porsche campaign entries in the category.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/50/1756288_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230516174500 +0200" stop="20230516180000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 4</title>
<desc lang="fr">When their ambitions exceed their driving skills, when well-secured racing professionals are thrown out of corners, we always have a camera at hand. Breathtaking stunts by professional drivers and slapstick-action in highly-tuned tin can rockets. Spectacular scenes where nobody gets hurt.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/31/00/1748416_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230516180000 +0200" stop="20230516182500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Stunt Heroes (Jump'n Crash) S2 (n°24)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Jump'n Crash»The Stunt Heroes in offroad fever: having fun with quad bikes. Furthermore: jumps and crashes - cars flying over the air ramp.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/15/35/1790601_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230516182500 +0200" stop="20230516185000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Supercars S5</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Porsche 911 GTS is the latest model in the iconic 911 sports car range. With an output of 430 HP it closes the gap between the S model and the GT3. Supercars gets the chance to take a ride in the new Porsche 911 GTS in California. Plus: The Roding Roadster is a small series lightweight sports car from Bavaria and uses technology from BMW under its bonnet.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748406_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230516185000 +0200" stop="20230516191500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Classic Ride S5</title>
<desc lang="fr">1963 saw the launch of the Chevrolet Corvette Stingray, which many consider to be the most exciting sports car of all time. The first generation was based on the then popular sports car body shape, a long hood and a crisp hatch back. Thus it can be seen as Chevrolet's answer to established sports car manufacturers like Jaguar and Maserati. Classic Ride pays tribute to the original Stingray.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/24/2125716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230516191500 +0200" stop="20230516194000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 10</title>
<desc lang="fr">Street Racers is your backstage pass to the world of Formula E. Every two weeks, the magazine takes a look behind the scenes of the most important electric car racing series and provides reviews, current news, exciting interviews and gripping background reports from the world of Formula E.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/59/1880083_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230516194000 +0200" stop="20230516203500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Grand Prix of La Réunion, Saint-Denis</title>
<desc lang="fr">The FIM X-Trial World Championship is the world's premier indoor motorcycle trials competition. MOTORVISION TV presents the highlights from the first round of the 2020 season, which takes place in Saint-Denis, France.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/13/2162902_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230516203500 +0200" stop="20230516210000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Bike World</title>
<desc lang="fr">Bike World revolves around the speedway and the racers swishing by on their two wheelers. Find out the latest news and reports regarding two-wheel competitions in the world of speed. This is the content to enjoy for all motorcycle enthusiasts across the world. Explore the best motorbikes, top locations, and iconic racers who have a lot of fun doing it.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/32/1837877_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230516210000 +0200" stop="20230516213000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 2</title>
<desc lang="fr">Exciting sports show that follows the hottest action from the world's most unique motor sport events. Viewers will have a chance to visit some interesting competitions- from IDEMITSU 600 Super Endurance at the Chang Interna-tional Circuit in Thailand, the winter edition of the Maroc Challenge in Morocco, to the Hispania Rally, the only European rally to take place in the desert, and many more. Viewers will also find out all the news from the world of motor sports.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1760716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230516213000 +0200" stop="20230516215500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Perfect Ride S6</title>
<desc lang="fr">What's hot and what's not. There are quests to be undertaken, the search for the ideal auto, for the perfect race track for the ultimate accessory gadget. What are the preferred rides of the race legends?</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/19/1748438_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230516215500 +0200" stop="20230516222000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Supercars S6</title>
<desc lang="fr">There are details which set super cars apart from normal cars and these details are essential. Super cars are the biggest, loudest and most expensive cars on the highway; they're four-wheeled works of arts.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748406_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230516222000 +0200" stop="20230516224500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Go Green!</title>
<desc lang="fr">Energy saving is becoming a more and more important goal for the world's leading car manufacturers. Motorvision TV explores the environment-friendly solutions emerging in the car industry. presenting the latest ideas from research and development teams. Find out what are the best ways to go green when it comes to your vehicle.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748432_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230516224500 +0200" stop="20230516233000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Spotted</title>
<desc lang="fr">With its Model S, American carmaker Tesla wants to establish electric engines in the full size class. For the very first time it is possible to attain driving ranges over 400 kilometers. Its tremendous acceleration becomes an image boost for the brand. Porsche stands for lots of speed and horsepower, too. With its Panamera Sport Turismo, the sports car manufacturer taps into a new market.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/21/07/1884377_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230516233000 +0200" stop="20230517000000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Trackmasters</title>
<desc lang="fr">It's time once again for the VLN Endurance Racing Championship! While the drivers are already out there doing test laps, we will be taking you behind the scenes and showing what really goes on in the pit lanes.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/25/59/1986723_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230517000000 +0200" stop="20230517003000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Stunt Heroes (The Examination) S1 (n°4)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«The Examination»This is what it looks like when the Stunt Heroes from Action Concept perform a long jump: A vehicle jumps at full speed over four cars, which explode one after the other. It's a matter of precision and timing. Up-and-coming stuntwoman Tina has to prove, what she can do. It's a spectacular, action-packed stunt with guaranteed bruising!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/15/35/1790601_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230517003000 +0200" stop="20230517005500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Supercars S3</title>
<desc lang="fr">Missile.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/1748406_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230517005500 +0200" stop="20230517012000 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Classic Ride S1</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Roadrunner's Paradise near Berlin is one of several meeting points for fans of Hot Rods in Germany. Here the rebels come together and celebrate the good old times. Since it is a tradition for real outlaws, every Hot Rod needs to do the eighth of a mile track during the meeting. Plus: A BMW 2800 which was turned into a racing car and then ended up in a junkyard is put to the test.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/24/2125716_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230517012000 +0200" stop="20230517014500 +0200" channel="MotorVisionTV.fr">
<title lang="fr">Episode 8</title>
<desc lang="fr">Street Racers is your backstage pass to the world of Formula E. Every two weeks, the magazine takes a look behind the scenes of the most important electric car racing series and provides reviews, current news, exciting interviews and gripping background reports from the world of Formula E.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport mécanique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/59/1880083_A.jpg" />
</programme>