<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Voo -->
<programme start="20230507020000 +0200" stop="20230507022500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Paw Patrol, la Pat'Patrouille (Everest, la petite nouvelle !) S2 (6/26)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Everest, la petite nouvelle !»The PAW Patrol rolls out in their new PAW Patroller to save Jake when he gets stranded in the ice fields, but a new pup also pops up to lend a paw, the brave ranger, Everest!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/55/1728948_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507022500 +0200" stop="20230507024500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Paw Patrol, la Pat'Patrouille (La moufette / Le baleineau) S3 (20/26)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«La moufette / Le baleineau»When Everest gets sprayed by a skunk, the pups delicately try to tell her she needs a bath! // The pups put a new spin on freeze tag after they fly far north to help free a baby whale that's trapped under the ice.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/25/01/2128927_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507024500 +0200" stop="20230507030500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Paw Patrol, la Pat'Patrouille (Tracker, le ranger de la jungle) S3 (15/26)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Tracker, le ranger de la jungle»Ryder and the pups are on their way to the jungle to help Carlos move a massive relic to the museum when he falls into a deep pit. Carlos is saved by a big eared pup named Tracker. For his bravery Tracker is made an honorary member of the Paw Patrol.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/05/52/1994535_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507030500 +0200" stop="20230507033000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Paw Patrol, la Pat'Patrouille (La Pat' Patrouille des mers : Les Chiens pirates) S4 (19/26)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«La Pat' Patrouille des mers : Les Chiens pirates»Carlos and Tracker get stranded on an island in the search for buried treasure.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/05/08/2126277_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507033000 +0200" stop="20230507035000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Paw Patrol, la Pat'Patrouille (Mission Paw Mission Secrète : Grosse Frayeur / Il Faut Sauver Monsieur le Maire) S4 (7/26)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Mission Paw Mission Secrète : Grosse Frayeur / Il Faut Sauver Monsieur le Maire»While on safari with Carlos and Tracker, Mayor Humdinger steals a magic mask.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/55/1728948_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507035000 +0200" stop="20230507041500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Paw Patrol, la Pat'Patrouille (Mission secrète : La couronne) S4 (4/26)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Mission secrète : La couronne»Chase and the team are called to Barkingburg to keep an eye on the crown.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/05/27/2128668_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507041500 +0200" stop="20230507043500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Paw Patrol, la Pat'Patrouille (Liberty Meets a New Friend / Pups Save the Pup Pup Boogie Contest) S9 (n°1)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Liberty Meets a New Friend / Pups Save the Pup Pup Boogie Contest»Liberty mistakenly brings a bear into town, thinking it's someone's pet. She must fix her mistake and rescue Chickaletta. // Francois' hot-air balloon goes out of control before the Pup Pup Boogie Contest. The Pups, with Liberty, race to the rescue.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/40/2145448_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507043500 +0200" stop="20230507050000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Paw Patrol, la Pat'Patrouille (All Paws on Deck) S9 (n°16)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«All Paws on Deck»Ryder calls on every member of the Paw Patrol to stop a hi-tech kid inventor from demolishing Adventure Bay so she can build her own dream city in its place.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/25/09/2142707_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507050000 +0200" stop="20230507051000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Baby Shark : l'aventure sous l'eau (Coule ou flotte) S1 (n°10)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Coule ou flotte»Sink or Swim: The Sharks go on the family game show Sink or Swim and find they're in hot water with their competition, the Fishes. (S1, ep 8b).</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/17/2138424_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507051000 +0200" stop="20230507052000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Mini Chef (Pizza) S1 (n°1)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Pizza»</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/05/01/2155932_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507052000 +0200" stop="20230507054500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Paw Patrol, la Pat'Patrouille (Galinetta et Roucoco / La leçon de snowboard) S8 (1/26)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Galinetta et Roucoco / La leçon de snowboard»Chickaletta and Roosterio run away from a chicken show and get stuck on top of a runaway drone. // When Bettina wanders up Jake's mountain and gets caught in a snowstorm, it's up to the Paw Patrol to bring her safely down.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/25/08/2142706_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507054500 +0200" stop="20230507060000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Les aventures de Paddington (Paddington pizzaiolo) S2 (11/27)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Paddington pizzaiolo»Paddington the Pizza Chef: Baaz's niece Simi is visiting &amp; he wants to create the perfect pizza to surprise her with but it's not easy with hungry animals around! (S2, ep 11b).</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/25/07/2145243_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507060000 +0200" stop="20230507060500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Peppa Pig (Les flaques d'eau de mer) S2 (10/52)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Les flaques d'eau de mer»Peppa and George are at the seaside with Granny and Grandpa Pig. Peppa and George like sandy beaches, but this is a different kind of beach, with lots of rocks and little rock pools to explore. Peppa, George, Granny and Grandpa Pig have fun with a little crab, a seashell and a fossil. Peppa rescues a little fish in her bucket and puts it back in the sea.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/38/1956757_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507060500 +0200" stop="20230507061000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Peppa Pig (Le jour de sortie de Teddy) S2 (4/52)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Le jour de sortie de Teddy»Peppa and her family are having a picnic lunch. Mr Zebra the Postman and Zoë Zebra are having a picnic too, so they decide to have one big picnic together. When it's time to go home, Peppa is having such a good time that, when it's home time, she leaves her teddy behind. But all ends well when Zoë Zebra and Mr Zebra the Postman make a very special delivery to Peppa's house...</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/06/12/1757213_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507061000 +0200" stop="20230507061500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Peppa Pig (Emilie Eléphant) S2 (2/52)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Emilie Eléphant»There's a new pupil at the playgroup, Emily Elephant. Everybody wants to be her friend because she is very good at building blocks and can make a loud noise with her trunk.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/33/1757182_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507061500 +0200" stop="20230507062000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Anna et ses amis (Shooting Star) S1 (13/78)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Shooting Star»Anna and her friends want to watch Shooting Stars - but Froga is scared of the dark! With a little encouragement (and a visit to her Night Tomato) Froga conquers her fears and has a wonderful and memorable night with her friends.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/06/50/2131501_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507062000 +0200" stop="20230507063000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Anna et ses amis (Circus Celebration) S1 (n°14)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Circus Celebration»Bubu's DVD of his favourite circus show does not work. So the others create their own circus acts in the backyard instead. (S1, ep 14).</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/06/51/2131502_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507063000 +0200" stop="20230507065500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Blue et ses amis (Une journée de sport avec Blue) S3 (n°8)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Une journée de sport avec Blue»Coach Josh and friends are playing all the sports and getting ready for a soccer game! But Magenta isn't ready for the big game.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/06/51/2136137_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507065500 +0200" stop="20230507074000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Bubulle Guppies (Le style Guppy) S4 (n°4)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Le style Guppy»The Guppies hit the road to see a concert by Stylee, a singing sensation known for her fabulous styles!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Emission Enfants</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/25/14/2188826_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507074000 +0200" stop="20230507080500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Deer Squad : Les Super-cerfs (Fin de partie / Jeunesse éternelle) S2 (13/20)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Fin de partie / Jeunesse éternelle»Kai invents a new Virtual Reality training game, but Stu and Safia enter the game and want to be the winners! // The Deer Squad must help the city's residents when they break out in spots thanks to Sir Steel's new face cream.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/24/20/2126283_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507080500 +0200" stop="20230507081500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Les aventures de Paddington (Paddington et le test de la beauté) S1 (27/54)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Paddington et le test de la beauté»Mr. Gruber gives Paddington a Chinese fingertrap and Paddington gets stuck to Mr. Curry while auditioning for a play.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/13/14/2183798_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507081500 +0200" stop="20230507083500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Paw Patrol, la Pat'Patrouille (La Pat' Patrouille des mers sauve Pat'lantis) S4 (26/26)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«La Pat' Patrouille des mers sauve Pat'lantis»Sid Swashbuckle the Pirate and his first pup mate Arrby steal the giant pearl-making shell that gives Puplantis its magic.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/06/40/2154751_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507083500 +0200" stop="20230507090000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Paw Patrol, la Pat'Patrouille (La Pat' Patrouille des mers sauve l'épave d'un bateau / La Pat' Patrouille des mers sauve une baleine) S5 (3/26)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«La Pat' Patrouille des mers sauve l'épave d'un bateau / La Pat' Patrouille des mers sauve une baleine»Sid the Pirate and his First Mate Arrby have taken the sunken sloop! A wiggling whale has knocked the diving bell upside down.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/24/12/2126294_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507090000 +0200" stop="20230507092000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Paw Patrol, la Pat'Patrouille (La Pat'Patrouille des Mers et Sid Laratisse) S5 (9/26)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«La Pat'Patrouille des Mers et Sid Laratisse»The ferris wheel has been stolen by Sid the Pirate and Arrby. The pups set out to bring it back to Adventure Bay! However, Sid comes up with an even more sneaky plan: to steal the Sea Patroller!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/06/05/2152789_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507092000 +0200" stop="20230507094500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Paw Patrol, la Pat'Patrouille (Les Super Chiens jumeaux) S6 (12/26)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Les Super Chiens jumeaux»Super-bandit, Ladybird, shrieks havoc in Adventure Bay taking all of the town's treasures - including Mayor Goodway! The Mighty Pups team up with new super pals, The Mighty Twins, to save the day - and the Mayor - in this super heroic adventure!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/06/11/2152787_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507094500 +0200" stop="20230507100500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Paw Patrol, la Pat'Patrouille (La Super Patrouille, Puissance Maximale : l'attaque des trois super méchants) S7 (4/26)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«La Super Patrouille, Puissance Maximale : l'attaque des trois super méchants»Harold, Ladybird, and the Copycat team up and the three super baddies take the Mighty Pups' mighty meteor! The Mighty Pups have to get their meteor back and Charge Up to stop them before the team of baddies destroys Adventure Bay!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/25/27/2188823_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507100500 +0200" stop="20230507103000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Paw Patrol, la Pat'Patrouille (La pierre de l'espace / Le maire adjoint) S4 (17/26)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«La pierre de l'espace / Le maire adjoint»Everest, the Turbots and a Space Rock get trapped in a cave. // Mayor Goodway goes missing and Mayor Humdinger causes havoc in Adventure Bay.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/55/1728948_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507103000 +0200" stop="20230507105000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Paw Patrol, la Pat'Patrouille (La Pat'Patrouille et le petit loup blanc / L'explorateur égaré) S6 (19/26)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«La Pat'Patrouille et le petit loup blanc / L'explorateur égaré»After an unexpected snowstorm, Everest takes care of a wolf cub when they work together to make sure the Paw Patrol can find them. Touring Travis accidentally takes Chickaletta to the North Pole, where they encounter crocodiles?</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/13/02/2126379_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507105000 +0200" stop="20230507111500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Paw Patrol, la Pat'Patrouille (All Paws on Deck) S9 (n°16)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«All Paws on Deck»Ryder calls on every member of the Paw Patrol to stop a hi-tech kid inventor from demolishing Adventure Bay so she can build her own dream city in its place.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/25/09/2142707_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507111500 +0200" stop="20230507112000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Peppa Pig (Le voyage en train) S3 (18/52)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Le voyage en train»Madame Gazelle emmène Peppa et ses amis pour une balade en train, où elles devront cocher ce qu'elles voient sur leurs feuilles d'activité...</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/24/2126349_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507112000 +0200" stop="20230507112500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Peppa Pig (La journée des jeunes talents) S3 (20/52)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«La journée des jeunes talents»C'est la Journée du talent à la garderie de Peppa. Madame Gazelle veut que chacun montre à la classe son talent particulier...</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/18/47/1903833_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507112500 +0200" stop="20230507113500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Barbapapa *2019 (Barbaprank!) S1 (25/52)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Barbaprank!»It is pranks day. The Barbababies have fun finding new pranks... until Barbabright spots the track of a dinosaur.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Emission Enfants</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/25/01/2130955_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507113500 +0200" stop="20230507120000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Barbapapa *2019 (Where Did It Go Barbabravo? / The Big Bad Hen) S1 (8/52)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Where Did It Go Barbabravo? / The Big Bad Hen»Like a secret agent, Barbabravo leads the investigation equipped with his gadgets to find out who stole Barbapapa's cake. // Barbalala is convinced she heard a giant hen prowling around the house. The Barbababies organize themselves to stand guard.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Emission Enfants</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/24/18/2126506_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507120000 +0200" stop="20230507122000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Blaze et les Monster Machines (Le super lot géant) S4 (6/20)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Le super lot géant»At the Axle City Fair, Blaze and AJ realize they don't have enough coins to use the new Supersize Prize Machine. So to earn money, Blaze gets three different jobs, transforming into super-cool vehicles to take care of business.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/25/00/2134420_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507122000 +0200" stop="20230507124500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Blaze et les Monster Machines (Des bolides lumineux) S3 (n°6)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Des bolides lumineux»A light thief (Melissa Rauch) is on the loose, leaving all of Axle City in the dark! Gabby outfits Blaze with special lights to help him track down the light thief and restore the missing lights.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/14/2155613_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507124500 +0200" stop="20230507130500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Paw Patrol, la Pat'Patrouille (Pups Save the Tooth Fairy / Pups Solve the Mystery of the Missing Art) S9 (n°7)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Pups Save the Tooth Fairy / Pups Solve the Mystery of the Missing Art»Julius loses his tooth and has a dream that the Paw Patrol saves a bumbling Tooth Fairy. // When all the paintings mysteriously disappear from the Art Museum festival, the PAW Patrol must solve the Missing Art Mystery and return all the paintings.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/40/2145448_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507130500 +0200" stop="20230507133000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Paw Patrol, la Pat'Patrouille (Pups Stop the Return of Humsquatch / Pups Save a Lonely Ghost) S9 (12/25)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Pups Stop the Return of Humsquatch / Pups Save a Lonely Ghost»Pups Stop the Return of Humsquatch: When Eddie and Emmy get impatient at the carnival, they hide in Mayor Humdinger's Humsquatch costume to chase everyone out. (S9, ep 12a).</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/52/2145242_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507133000 +0200" stop="20230507135000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Deer Squad : Les Super-cerfs (Les mini héros / Un visage dans l'espace) S2 (14/20)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Les mini héros / Un visage dans l'espace»When the younger animals in the forest want to be like their heroes Deer Squad, things don't go as planned as Sir Steel steps in. // The Deer Squad have to save the day in Space when Sir Steel's plan to project his face on the moon goes wrong!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/24/16/2126326_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507135000 +0200" stop="20230507140000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Deer Squad : Les Super-cerfs (Le festival des lumières) S2 (n°19)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Le festival des lumières»Lola's plan to help a family of hedgehogs over the winter doesn't go to plan when Sir Steel wants to brighten things up.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/49/2126299_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507140000 +0200" stop="20230507142000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Paw Patrol, la Pat'Patrouille (Everest, la petite nouvelle !) S2 (6/26)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Everest, la petite nouvelle !»The PAW Patrol rolls out in their new PAW Patroller to save Jake when he gets stranded in the ice fields, but a new pup also pops up to lend a paw, the brave ranger, Everest!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/55/1728948_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507142000 +0200" stop="20230507144500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Paw Patrol, la Pat'Patrouille (La moufette / Le baleineau) S3 (20/26)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«La moufette / Le baleineau»When Everest gets sprayed by a skunk, the pups delicately try to tell her she needs a bath! // The pups put a new spin on freeze tag after they fly far north to help free a baby whale that's trapped under the ice.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/25/01/2128927_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507144500 +0200" stop="20230507150500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Paw Patrol, la Pat'Patrouille (Tracker, le ranger de la jungle) S3 (15/26)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Tracker, le ranger de la jungle»Ryder and the pups are on their way to the jungle to help Carlos move a massive relic to the museum when he falls into a deep pit. Carlos is saved by a big eared pup named Tracker. For his bravery Tracker is made an honorary member of the Paw Patrol.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/05/52/1994535_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507150500 +0200" stop="20230507153000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Paw Patrol, la Pat'Patrouille (La Pat' Patrouille des mers : Les Chiens pirates) S4 (19/26)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«La Pat' Patrouille des mers : Les Chiens pirates»Carlos and Tracker get stranded on an island in the search for buried treasure.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/05/08/2126277_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507153000 +0200" stop="20230507155000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Paw Patrol, la Pat'Patrouille (Mission Paw Mission Secrète : Grosse Frayeur / Il Faut Sauver Monsieur le Maire) S4 (7/26)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Mission Paw Mission Secrète : Grosse Frayeur / Il Faut Sauver Monsieur le Maire»While on safari with Carlos and Tracker, Mayor Humdinger steals a magic mask.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/55/1728948_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507155000 +0200" stop="20230507161500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Paw Patrol, la Pat'Patrouille (Mission secrète : La couronne) S4 (4/26)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Mission secrète : La couronne»Chase and the team are called to Barkingburg to keep an eye on the crown.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/05/27/2128668_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507161500 +0200" stop="20230507163500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Paw Patrol, la Pat'Patrouille (Liberty Meets a New Friend / Pups Save the Pup Pup Boogie Contest) S9 (n°1)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Liberty Meets a New Friend / Pups Save the Pup Pup Boogie Contest»Liberty mistakenly brings a bear into town, thinking it's someone's pet. She must fix her mistake and rescue Chickaletta. // Francois' hot-air balloon goes out of control before the Pup Pup Boogie Contest. The Pups, with Liberty, race to the rescue.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/40/2145448_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507163500 +0200" stop="20230507170000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Paw Patrol, la Pat'Patrouille (All Paws on Deck) S9 (n°16)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«All Paws on Deck»Ryder calls on every member of the Paw Patrol to stop a hi-tech kid inventor from demolishing Adventure Bay so she can build her own dream city in its place.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/25/09/2142707_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507170000 +0200" stop="20230507171000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Baby Shark : l'aventure sous l'eau (Coule ou flotte) S1 (n°10)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Coule ou flotte»Sink or Swim: The Sharks go on the family game show Sink or Swim and find they're in hot water with their competition, the Fishes. (S1, ep 8b).</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/17/2138424_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507171000 +0200" stop="20230507172000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Mini Chef (Pizza) S1 (n°1)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Pizza»</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/05/01/2155932_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507172000 +0200" stop="20230507174500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Paw Patrol, la Pat'Patrouille (Galinetta et Roucoco / La leçon de snowboard) S8 (1/26)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Galinetta et Roucoco / La leçon de snowboard»Chickaletta and Roosterio run away from a chicken show and get stuck on top of a runaway drone. // When Bettina wanders up Jake's mountain and gets caught in a snowstorm, it's up to the Paw Patrol to bring her safely down.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/25/08/2142706_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507174500 +0200" stop="20230507175500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Les aventures de Paddington (Paddington pizzaiolo) S2 (11/27)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Paddington pizzaiolo»Paddington the Pizza Chef: Baaz's niece Simi is visiting &amp; he wants to create the perfect pizza to surprise her with but it's not easy with hungry animals around! (S2, ep 11b).</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/25/07/2145243_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507175500 +0200" stop="20230507180000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Peppa Pig (Tous à la piscine) S2 (20/52)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Tous à la piscine»Maman Cochon emmène toute la famille à la piscine. Papa Cochon, ravi de cette sortie, déchante quand il est pris pour cible dans le grand bain...</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/24/02/2136871_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507180000 +0200" stop="20230507180500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Peppa Pig (Jour de brume) S2 (18/52)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Jour de brume»Papa et maman Pig emmènent Peppa et George au terrain de jeux mais un épais brouillard se lève pendant qu'ils sont en chemin. Ils décident alors de rentrer à la maison, mais cela va se révéler difficile...</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/28/1664688_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507180500 +0200" stop="20230507181000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Peppa Pig (L'anniversaire de George) S2 (26/52)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«L'anniversaire de George»Peppa's friend Pedro wears glasses. In addition, his father is an optician, so Pedro knows everything about glasses and eyes. According to Pedro, Peppa absolutely needs glasses. To see if that is really the case, Peppa can go to the optician ...</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/06/29/1715971_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507181000 +0200" stop="20230507181500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Anna et ses amis (A Very Busy Afternoon) S1 (17/78)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«A Very Busy Afternoon»A Very Busy Afternoon: Froga organises a gathering to share jam sandwiches with everyone, Ron and Christopher want to show off their acrobatic frisbee skills, (S1, ep 17).</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/06/2132698_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507181500 +0200" stop="20230507182500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Anna et ses amis (The Four-Leaf Clover) S1 (18/78)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«The Four-Leaf Clover»The Four-Leaf Clover: Anna and her friends have organized a hula hoop competition and Froga relies on her four-leaf clover to help her! Froga is convinced there is no way she'll ever win. (S1, ep 18).</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/06/12/2132699_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507182500 +0200" stop="20230507184500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Barbapapa *2019 (Boris / Né pour être sauvage) S1 (3/52)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Boris / Né pour être sauvage»The barbababies find a lost baby elephant and secretly look after it. How will Barbapapa and Barbamama react to Boris? // Boris the elephant misses home. The Barbapapa decide to bring him back to Africa. On the spot, they help Boris to acclimatize.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Emission Enfants</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/23/2126323_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507184500 +0200" stop="20230507191000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Blue et ses amis (Du nouveau à l'école de Blue) S3 (17/18)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Du nouveau à l'école de Blue»Join Josh and Blue at school for a day of trying new things! Josh is excited to try being Teacher for the Day, but Blue seems nervous to try something. What could it be?</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/06/07/2136140_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507191000 +0200" stop="20230507193000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Paw Patrol, la Pat'Patrouille (La moustache de Monsieur Hellinger / La fête foraine) S8 (5/26)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«La moustache de Monsieur Hellinger / La fête foraine»The Pups must help to find Mayor Humdinger's mustache after he accidentally shaves it off before it's about to be on the cover of a magazine. // When a carnival train gets stuck in a tunnel, it results in a mountainside funhouse-style wild ride.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/24/31/2163473_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507193000 +0200" stop="20230507195000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Deer Squad : Les Super-cerfs (Le Numéro de voltige de Lola / Le Monstre des égouts) S1 (n°17)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Le Numéro de voltige de Lola / Le Monstre des égouts»Lola is worried her air display will not be impressive enough, but when Sir Steel joins, the air display goes wrong in a spectacular way! // When Sir Steel's dog Muffin's ball goes missing down the sewers, Bobbi has to face his fear of the dark.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/25/05/2150915_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507195000 +0200" stop="20230507201500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Deer Squad : Les Super-cerfs (Le parc au trésor / À pas de géant) S2 (n°215)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Le parc au trésor / À pas de géant»Bobbi and Jade find an underground cavern in 'Treasure Park', and then in 'Baddy Long Legs', Rammy is so focused on meditation that he fails to focus on a real crisis! (S2, ep 15).</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/24/19/2126381_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507201500 +0200" stop="20230507203500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Les aventures de Paddington (Paddington and the Bone / Paddington Joins a Band) S1 (17/27)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Paddington and the Bone / Paddington Joins a Band»Mr. Gruber has been loaned a T-Rex Skeleton, but Lucky the dog has stolen the priceless bone and buried it somewhere. // The kids decide to form a rock band with Paddington, but what instrument should he play, and what is rock music?</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/24/21/2126466_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507203500 +0200" stop="20230507204500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Mini Chef (Guacamole) S1 (n°12)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Guacamole»Tiny Chef hosts his own tiny cooking show, and with his best friends Olly, Ruby and Henry, cooks up tasty dishes and amazing adventures, putting love into every dish he makes.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/12/03/2160485_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507204500 +0200" stop="20230507210500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Barbapapa *2019 (L'océan fuchsia / Zéro déchet) S1 (n°15)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«L'océan fuchsia / Zéro déchet»Chemical sprays are making the countryside rosy! The Barbapapas' build an aviary to protect sick birds. // When they see a beach covered with rubbish, the Barbapapa family decides to clean the beach and use the trash to make a miniature golf course.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Emission Enfants</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/24/25/2126472_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507210500 +0200" stop="20230507213000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Barbapapa *2019 (Hiccupism / Silence please) S1 (32/52)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Hiccupism / Silence please»Barbabeau can't paint. He has a hiccup he can't get rid of. Just when he's about to give up, he accidentally creates a new artistic movement. // Barbalib wants to compete in a writing contest but his brothers and sisters stop her from concentrating.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Emission Enfants</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/59/2126487_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507213000 +0200" stop="20230507215000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Baby Shark : l'aventure sous l'eau (Baby Shark, le maire / Coule ou flotte) S1 (n°8)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Baby Shark, le maire / Coule ou flotte»The fate of the city's squidapple supply lies in Baby's fins when he accidentally assumes the role of Mayor on a big day. // The Sharks go on the family game show Sink or Swim and find they're in hot water with their competition, the Fishes.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/15/2126543_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507215000 +0200" stop="20230507220500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Baby Shark : l'aventure sous l'eau (Daddy Shack) S1 (n°14)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Daddy Shack»Daddy Shack: After a selfish fish takes over the putt-putt, Baby Shark and William must find a champion mini-golf player to defeat him. (S1, ep 12a).</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/21/07/2141682_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507220500 +0200" stop="20230507221000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Anna et ses amis (Hide and Seek) S1 (16/78)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Hide and Seek»Anna and her friends are outside playing Ron's favorite game, Hide-and-Seek! Anna is the Seeker and quickly finds Froga, Christopher and Bubu. When the friends work together to try to find Ron, they realize he's found the best hiding spot of all.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/05/2132690_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507221000 +0200" stop="20230507222000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Anna et ses amis (The Swing) S1 (n°2)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«The Swing»When Anna and Froga discover the old seat of their swing, they are excited to hang it on the apple tree. But the ropes to attach it have gone missing!The two friends' search for the missing ropes turns out to be more difficult than they had imagined!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/22/2126264_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507222000 +0200" stop="20230507222500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Anna et ses amis (The Photo) S1 (5/78)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«The Photo»Polaroid camera, she decides to take pictures of all her friends. Everyone thinks it's a great idea and Anna makes some great portraits. But things get complicated when she tries to take a group shot of everyone!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/06/19/2126572_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507222500 +0200" stop="20230507223500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Anna et ses amis (The Bicycle) S1 (9/78)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«The Bicycle»Bubu impresses his friends with a brand new bike he won in a contest. He encourages everyone else to ride it, Anna discovers why: Bubu doesn't know how to ride a two-wheeler!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/06/04/2130244_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507223500 +0200" stop="20230507224000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Anna et ses amis (The Mosquito) S1 (12/78)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«The Mosquito»Froga is petrified of a pesky mosquito, so her friends try everything they can think of to chase it away: they dance, fidget, make loud noises and even try to befriend it. When Bubu activates his homemade stink bomb launcher, it causes such a stink!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/06/00/2130951_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507224000 +0200" stop="20230507225000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Anna et ses amis (Froga's Hat) S1 (29/78)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Froga's Hat»Froga finds a sun hat she thought she lost forever and organizes a celebration picnic! But when the precious hat gets stained with jam, Froga's friends try to fix it - only making things worse. In the end, Anna's solution is the best of all.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/06/10/2132688_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507225000 +0200" stop="20230507225500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Peppa Pig (Le voyage en montgolfière) S2 (25/52)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Le voyage en montgolfière»Peppa and her family are at the school fête. The top prize in the raffle is a trip in a Hot Air Balloon. Peppa wins! Mummy Pig, Daddy Pig, George and Peppa climb into the balloon. Everyone enjoys the flight until the balloon gets caught in a tree. Luckily, the balloon has landed in a very familiar garden.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/06/35/1761176_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507225500 +0200" stop="20230507230000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Peppa Pig (Georges attrape un rhume) S2 (24/52)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Georges attrape un rhume»Peppa wins a ride in Miss Rabbit's hot air balloon and the whole family comes along. Peppa drops Teddy and Papa Pig saves him. But if they get stuck in a tree, who will come and save them?</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/02/25/04/2152462_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507230000 +0200" stop="20230507230500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Peppa Pig (L'examen de la vue) S2 (16/52)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«L'examen de la vue»Peppa's friend Pedro wears glasses. In addition, his father is an optician, so Pedro knows everything about glasses and eyes. According to Pedro, Peppa absolutely needs glasses. To see if that is really the case, Peppa can go to the optician ...</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/13/1659416_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507230500 +0200" stop="20230507231000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Peppa Pig (Betsy la tondeuse) S2 (27/52)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Betsy la tondeuse»Papa Pig waited a long time to mow the lawn. It's fun to play in at first, but when Peppa and George loose their ball in it, they call Grandpa Pig. And Betsy, the super lawn mower, will take that!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/21/47/1670372_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507231000 +0200" stop="20230507231400 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Peppa Pig (Le voyage sur la Lune) S3 (21/52)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Le voyage sur la Lune»Peppa et George partent avec maman Cochon à la présentation par mademoiselle Lapin du camion des mamans sapeurs pompiers...</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/29/2126431_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507231400 +0200" stop="20230507232000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Peppa Pig (Grand-père à l'aire de jeux) S3 (22/52)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Grand-père à l'aire de jeux»Papa Pig perd son titre de Champion de saut de flaques durant les Papa-Olympics. Tout le monde l'aide à s'entraîner en vue des prochains Papa-Olympics...</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/06/00/2126446_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507232000 +0200" stop="20230507232500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Peppa Pig (Goldie, le poisson rouge) S3 (23/52)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Goldie, le poisson rouge»Goldie le poisson n'a pas l'air heureux et ne mange pas sa nourriture, alors Peppa, George et Maman Cochon l'emmènent faire un tour en bus pour voir le docteur Hamster, le vétérinaire...</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/24/19/2126374_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507232500 +0200" stop="20230507233500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Barbapapa *2019 (The Competition Prize) S1 (n°8)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«The Competition Prize»The Barbabies win a touchpad. They all want to use it and snaffle it one after another.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Emission Enfants</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/25/08/2161191_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230507233500 +0200" stop="20230508000000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Barbapapa *2019 (Pour maman / Barbacarambolage) S1 (n°18)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Pour maman / Barbacarambolage»The barbababies prepare a show for Barbamama's birthday. While Barbalala finishes up, they go to the carnival where Barbabeau gets stuck in an attraction. // Three separate stories telescope into a big final bouquet in the middle of the courtyard.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Emission Enfants</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/59/2126287_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230508000000 +0200" stop="20230508002000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Blaze et les Monster Machines (Les T-Rex égarés) S4 (7/20)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Les T-Rex égarés»Blaze and Zeg are in Dinosaur Valley, showing off their amazing robot powers to their dinosaur friends. But when they discover three lost little Tyrannosauruses, they must use their robot powers to get the babies home safely.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/25/02/2135004_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230508002000 +0200" stop="20230508004500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Blaze et les Monster Machines (Animal Island) S3 (9/20)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Animal Island»Lazard steals their special animal power from all the animals on Animal Island. Lazard does this because he himself has no special strength. At least; he thinks so.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/06/2126371_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230508004500 +0200" stop="20230508010500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Paw Patrol, la Pat'Patrouille (Le maire en chocolat / Wendini la magicienne) S8 (2/26)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Le maire en chocolat / Wendini la magicienne»Encased in a huge chocolate bunny, Humdinger is carried away by hungry raccoons and ends up floating in Adventure Bay with a curious dolphin. // When a magic trick goes awry, the Adventure Bay Easter Festival is overrun by wild bunnies.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/06/42/2126266_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230508010500 +0200" stop="20230508013000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Paw Patrol, la Pat'Patrouille (Ruben l'extraterrestre / L'anniversaire d'Alex) S8 (3/26)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Ruben l'extraterrestre / L'anniversaire d'Alex»Rubble dreams that he's been taken aboard a spaceship and meets his alien double. When the ship crashes on an alien planet, he needs help.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/06/44/2126310_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230508013000 +0200" stop="20230508015000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Deer Squad : Les Super-cerfs (La roue de Métal / Le bongo de Bobbi) S2 (16/20)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«La roue de Métal / Le bongo de Bobbi»When Bobbi and Jade find an underground cavern, they end up in danger when Sir Steel goes treasure hunting!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/12/2126429_A.jpg" />
</programme>