<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Voo -->
<programme start="20230521021000 +0200" stop="20230521023000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Blaze et les Monster Machines (L'anniversaire de Starla) S6 (11/24)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«L'anniversaire de Starla»Starla's wild west birthday party is in trouble when her cake gets carried off by a runaway train. Can she, Blaze and AJ catch up and save the cake before it's too late?</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/11/2126404_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521023000 +0200" stop="20230521025000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Blaze et les Monster Machines (Le trésor du tigre) S6 (13/24)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Le trésor du tigre»The Tiger Treasure: Blaze, AJ, and Stripes put their explorer skills to the test as they follow the trail to the fabled Tiger Treasure. (S6, ep 14).</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/06/00/2126272_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521025000 +0200" stop="20230521031000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Blaze et les Monster Machines (La plus rapide de tous) S6 (18/24)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«La plus rapide de tous»When a greedy queen casts a spell to make a few of our friends go slow, Blaze and AJ must race her for the magical cure.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/06/00/2126316_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521031000 +0200" stop="20230521033000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Blaze et les Monster Machines (Megabot) S6 (18/20)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Megabot»Megabot!: Blaze and AJ help their amazing new friend Megabot get to Axle City in time for the big Robot Parade. (S6, ep 20).</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/06/54/2126345_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521033000 +0200" stop="20230521035500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Blaze et les Monster Machines (Pirate Musical!) S6 (20/23)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Pirate Musical!»In the first ever Blaze Musical, Blaze, AJ, Crusher, and Pickle are on a daring quest to find the pieces of the Broken Key and unlock a secret treasure.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/24/18/2126370_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521035500 +0200" stop="20230521041500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Blaze et les Monster Machines (Histoires au coin du feu) S6 (22/23)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Histoires au coin du feu»It's a campout under the stars! Blaze, AJ, Starla, Crusher, and Pickle are gathered around the campfire to tell the most amazing stories they can make up! And the best part? Whoever tells the best story wins the last marshmallow!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/04/00/2126371_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521041500 +0200" stop="20230521043500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Blaze et les Monster Machines (Sparkle à la rescousse) S7 (n°1)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Sparkle à la rescousse»When Crusher sends Blaze away with one of his latest cheats, Blaze's little sister Sparkle comes to save the day and bring her brother back in time so they can race together to win the Teamwork Trophy!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/04/00/2126371_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521043500 +0200" stop="20230521044500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Santiago des mers (The Pirate Parade) S1 (n°11)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«The Pirate Parade»The Pirate Parade: It's time for the annual Pirate Parade! That is, unless Escarlata has anything to say about it. (S1, ep 11b).</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/24/28/2152455_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521044500 +0200" stop="20230521050000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Baby Shark : l'aventure sous l'eau (La journée du oui) S1 (n°7)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«La journée du oui»Baby convinces Daddy to say &quot;yup&quot; to everything for a day. What's the worst that could happen?</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/01/2136141_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521050000 +0200" stop="20230521051000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Baby Shark : l'aventure sous l'eau (Swimming With the Sharks) S1 (n°26)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Swimming With the Sharks»When Baby and his family become reality TV stars, they start to lose sight of what makes them the Sharks.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/48/2126268_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521051000 +0200" stop="20230521052000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Mini Chef (Mac and Cheese) S1 (n°8)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Mac and Cheese»Mac and Cheese: Tiny Chef makes rainy day Mac N Cheese but a leaky roof creates chaos in his tree stump kitchen! (S1, ep 8a).</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/15/2162247_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521052000 +0200" stop="20230521054500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Paw Patrol, la Pat'Patrouille (Un essaim de papillons / Où est La Galinetta d'or ?) S5 (7/26)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Un essaim de papillons / Où est La Galinetta d'or ?»The statue of Chickaletta has been stolen by Mayor Humdinger and is making its way through Adventure Bay's underground tunnel system.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/59/2126489_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521054500 +0200" stop="20230521060000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Les aventures de Paddington (La musique et Paddington) S2 (21/27)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«La musique et Paddington»The Adventures of Paddington is a new version of a familiar bear. It's a heartwarming show about being curious, being good to others, and being part of a loving family.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/07/16/2181238_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521060000 +0200" stop="20230521060500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Peppa Pig (L'embouteillage) S2 (13/52)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«L'embouteillage»Granny and Grandpa Pig have invited Peppa and her family to lunch. On the way, Peppa, George, Mummy Pig and Daddy Pig get caught in a very long traffic jam. They still haven't arrived by the time lunch is ready, so Grandpa Pig decides to bring the lunch to them - in his wheelbarrow. There's enough delicious food for everyone in the traffic jam.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/06/10/1658352_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521060500 +0200" stop="20230521061000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Peppa Pig (Les flaques d'eau de mer) S2 (10/52)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Les flaques d'eau de mer»Peppa and George are at the seaside with Granny and Grandpa Pig. Peppa and George like sandy beaches, but this is a different kind of beach, with lots of rocks and little rock pools to explore. Peppa, George, Granny and Grandpa Pig have fun with a little crab, a seashell and a fossil. Peppa rescues a little fish in her bucket and puts it back in the sea.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/38/1956757_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521061000 +0200" stop="20230521061500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Peppa Pig (Le jour de sortie de Teddy) S2 (4/52)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Le jour de sortie de Teddy»Peppa and her family are having a picnic lunch. Mr Zebra the Postman and Zoë Zebra are having a picnic too, so they decide to have one big picnic together. When it's time to go home, Peppa is having such a good time that, when it's home time, she leaves her teddy behind. But all ends well when Zoë Zebra and Mr Zebra the Postman make a very special delivery to Peppa's house...</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/06/12/1757213_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521061500 +0200" stop="20230521062000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Anna et ses amis (The Collection) S1 (19/78)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«The Collection»The Collection: Upon seeing Ron's stick collection, Froga learns for the first time what &quot;a collection&quot; is. Anna would like to create one of her own. (S1, ep 19).</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/06/14/2132707_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521062000 +0200" stop="20230521063000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Anna et ses amis (Fixing Things) S1 (20/78)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Fixing Things»Bubu catches a cold, he's unable to fix Ron's spinning top and Christopher's broken piano. While Bubu is resting, she &quot;fixes&quot; the broken items for him. Christopher's piano starts playing bubbles, Froga realizes she should leave the fixing to Bubu.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/06/16/2132708_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521063000 +0200" stop="20230521065500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Blue et ses amis (Blue est triste) S1 (6/17)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Blue est triste»Blue's feeling sad, so we play Blue's Clues to figure out why. Along the way to figuring out Blue's Clues, we help our Felt Friends and Blues' friends from her school deal with emotions and feelings in different situations.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/2126477_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521065500 +0200" stop="20230521074000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Blaze et les Monster Machines (Les chemins de la gloire) S1 (1/20)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Les chemins de la gloire»Crusher is doing everything he can to keep the other monster machines away from the world championship racing at the Monster Dome; he tries with bubbles, mud balls and robotic knights.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/06/04/2193753_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521074000 +0200" stop="20230521080500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Deer Squad : Les Super-cerfs (Au pied de l'arc-en-ciel / Grillés !) S2 (1/20)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Au pied de l'arc-en-ciel / Grillés !»The search for gold at the end of the rainbow leads the Deer Squad to an amazing Frost Mountain and a new deer friend! // The Deer Squad have to deal with a cheesy situation thanks to Sir Steel's latest invention - The Giant Toaster!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/06/07/2126428_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521080500 +0200" stop="20230521082500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Les aventures de Paddington (Paddington Plans a Party / Paddington Learns the Violin) S1 (9/27)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Paddington Plans a Party / Paddington Learns the Violin»Mr Brown has forgotten to get Mrs Brown a Birthday present, Paddington decides to hold a surprise party. // Judy does not like Violin lessons so hides from Ms Potts. Paddington takes up the challenge. Watch out ears!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/07/05/2126596_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521082500 +0200" stop="20230521083500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Les aventures de Paddington (Paddington et l'album souvenir) S1 (18/54)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Paddington et l'album souvenir»Paddington decides to make a scrapbook of memories and tries to include all his friends to show Aunt Lucy.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/06/36/2178722_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521083500 +0200" stop="20230521084500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Mini Chef (Apple Pie) S1 (n°6)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Apple Pie»Guacamole: Tiny Chef makes guacamole and has to learn to share when his friends want to help using a new kitchen tool. (S1, ep 6a).</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/12/04/2159917_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521084500 +0200" stop="20230521090500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Barbapapa *2019 (Les sept aliments / Un portrait au poil) S1 (n°26)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Les sept aliments / Un portrait au poil»The Barbababies think their food can make them change colours and shapes. They decide to find the right food for each of them. // Barbabeau lacks inspiration, he can't create anymore. The whole family helps by suggesting new subjects to paint.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Emission Enfants</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/24/2126351_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521090500 +0200" stop="20230521093000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Barbapapa *2019 (L'arbre de Barbapapa / L'anniversaire des barbabébés) S1 (1/52)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«L'arbre de Barbapapa / L'anniversaire des barbabébés»Barbapapa and Barbamama return to the tree they were born under. It's in bad condition. They must rescue it quickly without disturbing the nearby animals. // It's the Barbababies's birthday. They all want to do something different with Barbapapa!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Emission Enfants</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/00/2126279_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521093000 +0200" stop="20230521095000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Baby Shark : l'aventure sous l'eau (Captain Varech / Riquiqui le Tardigrade) S1 (n°9)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Captain Varech / Riquiqui le Tardigrade»As Super Shark and Captain Kelp, Baby Shark and William set out to save playtime-but is Captain Kelp just a sidekick? // Baby Shark adopts a teensy tiny pet, but is he ready for a big responsibility?</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/27/2126544_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521095000 +0200" stop="20230521100500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Baby Shark : l'aventure sous l'eau (Best in Flow) S2 (n°2)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Best in Flow»A brash young Baby Shark puts the life skills he learns from his parents to the test in his own backyard - which just happens to be the ocean!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/11/09/2182527_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521100500 +0200" stop="20230521101000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Anna et ses amis (Hide and Seek) S1 (16/78)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Hide and Seek»Anna and her friends are outside playing Ron's favorite game, Hide-and-Seek! Anna is the Seeker and quickly finds Froga, Christopher and Bubu. When the friends work together to try to find Ron, they realize he's found the best hiding spot of all.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/05/2132690_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521101000 +0200" stop="20230521102000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Anna et ses amis (Bubble Trouble) S1 (21/78)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Bubble Trouble»Bubble Trouble: Bubu's bubble maker invention works so well, it creates an enormous bubble that Christopher gets trapped in! His friends are desperate to rescue him! (S1, ep 21).</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/06/29/2133350_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521102000 +0200" stop="20230521102500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Anna et ses amis (Une rencontre mystérieuse) S1 (65/78)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Une rencontre mystérieuse»Mysterious Visitor: Bubu is eager to meet a real space alien so he builds a homemade antenna and sound box to communicate with outer space. (S1, ep 65).</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/06/08/2126450_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521102500 +0200" stop="20230521103500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Anna et ses amis (The Squeaky Boots) S1 (n°66)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«The Squeaky Boots»The Squeaky Boots: Christopher leads the friends in a fun game of hide and seek, but Froga soon realizes that her new boots are letting out a noisy squeak! (S1, ep 66).</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/22/2126264_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521103500 +0200" stop="20230521104000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Anna et ses amis (The Greedy Gobbler) S1 (n°67)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«The Greedy Gobbler»The Greedy Gobbler: While Bubu and Christopher want to enjoy an hazelnut snack, their hazelnuts go missing! Then Anna, Froga and Ron's chocolate snack also disappears! (S1, ep 67).</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/22/2126264_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521104000 +0200" stop="20230521105000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Anna et ses amis (A Longchair for Ron) S1 (n°68)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«A Longchair for Ron»A sleeping spider squats Ron's swing, and he can't take a nap. He laments to Anna and Froga that he wishes he had a deck chair to sleep on. This gives them the idea to surprise him with one.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/22/2126264_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521105000 +0200" stop="20230521105600 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Peppa Pig (Emilie Eléphant) S2 (2/52)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Emilie Eléphant»There's a new pupil at the playgroup, Emily Elephant. Everybody wants to be her friend because she is very good at building blocks and can make a loud noise with her trunk.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/33/1757182_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521105600 +0200" stop="20230521110000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Peppa Pig (L'ami de George) S2 (6/52)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«L'ami de George»Rebecca Rabbit has a little bother called Richard who is the same age as George. George and Richard each have a toy dinosaur but George and Richard are not very good at sharing their toys. Mummy Pig shows George and Richard that they can have much more fun at the playground if they play together, just like their big sisters.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/21/48/1768900_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521110000 +0200" stop="20230521110500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Peppa Pig (La mare aux petits bateaux) S2 (12/52)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«La mare aux petits bateaux»Peppa and George learn that throwing waste away is fun, especially if you can divide it into special bins so that the waste can be reused. So recycle!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/04/59/1903833_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521110500 +0200" stop="20230521111000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Peppa Pig (Monsieur l'épouvantail) S2 (7/52)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Monsieur l'épouvantail»Peppa and George go to the beach with Grandpa and Grandma Pig and find tide pools there. Peppa doesn't like it at first, but when she discovers what can be experienced with and in such pools and she even rescues a fish, she wants one too.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/07/01/1670366_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521111000 +0200" stop="20230521111500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Peppa Pig (Le jeu &quot;Spéciale jour de pluie&quot;) S4 (9/52)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Le jeu &quot;Spéciale jour de pluie&quot;»Baby Alexander is too young to talk, until Peppa teaches him his first word.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/04/59/1903833_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521111500 +0200" stop="20230521112000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Peppa Pig (La bosse de maman Rabbit) S4 (10/52)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«La bosse de maman Rabbit»Granddad Dog takes Peppa, George and Danny Dog to visit Grampy Rabbit's lighthouse.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/06/43/1781663_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521112000 +0200" stop="20230521112500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Peppa Pig (Pedro le cow-boy) S4 (11/52)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Pedro le cow-boy»Peppa, George, Suzy Sheep, Wendy Wold and Danny Dog visit Pedro Pony who's pretending to be a cowboy. He welcomes them to his cowboy camp. The group imagine they are in the Wild West and do cowboy things, such as eating beans, singing sings, telling stories and sleeping in the tent at night. But even cowboys can get scared, especially when wild animals are lurking outside the tent. The fun goes on until evening, when Peppa and friends need to go home.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/04/59/1903833_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521112500 +0200" stop="20230521113500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Barbapapa *2019 (The Treasure Hunt) S1 (22/52)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«The Treasure Hunt»Mr. Strict's twins visit the barbababies. The barbababies organize a treasure hunt for the twins and enjoy the great outdoors.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Emission Enfants</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/06/00/2137882_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521113500 +0200" stop="20230521120000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Barbapapa *2019 (It's Only a Mystery... / The Battle) S1 (6/52)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«It's Only a Mystery... / The Battle»Taking after his favourite detective, Barbabravo looks for a case to solve. Can he solve the mystery of the missing ice statue? // Inspired by their favourite heroes, the Barbababies make costumes. But no heroes are possible without villains...</desc>
<category lang="fr">Emission Enfants</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/25/02/2130251_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521120000 +0200" stop="20230521122000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Blaze et les Monster Machines (Glacier Monster Machine) S5 (10/21)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Glacier Monster Machine»Gasquatch invites Blaze and AJ to his ice cream party! But he forgot something important - the ice cream! So, Blaze transforms into an Ice Cream Truck and races to reach Gasquatch's house in time!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/02/19/1740378_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521122000 +0200" stop="20230521124500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Blaze et les Monster Machines (Le pouvoir du recyclage) S5 (8/20)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Le pouvoir du recyclage»When Axle City is visited by a littering raccoon, it's up to Blaze to save the day as a Super Recycling Truck! He cleans up the town and rescues his friends - just in time for a final showdown with the Litter Critter!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/08/05/2126502_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521124500 +0200" stop="20230521130500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Blaze et les Monster Machines (Semi-Remorque Blaze) S5 (13/20)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Semi-Remorque Blaze»When a windstorm blows away the supplies for Stripes' Animal Party, Blaze transforms into the one Monster Machine strong enough to haul it all back - a Big Rig! There's nothing he can't pull with that Big Rig Force!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/04/00/2126529_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521130500 +0200" stop="20230521133000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Blaze et les Monster Machines (La voleuse de bonbons) S5 (19/20)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«La voleuse de bonbons»Officer Blaze just got his biggest case yet: tracking down the mischievous Treat Thief! With help from Officer Anna, Blaze sets out to stop the thief and recover every stolen treat!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/29/03/2126553_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521133000 +0200" stop="20230521135000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Blaze et les Monster Machines (Derby Dino) S6 (n°2)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Derby Dino»Today, dinosaur Blaze is teaming up with his prehistoric pal Zeg to compete in... the Dino Derby! But will this dino duo have what it takes to outrace the rest and become Dino Derby champions?</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/04/01/2126577_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521135000 +0200" stop="20230521140000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Blaze et les Monster Machines (Le badge de course de Sparkle) S6 (n°5)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Le badge de course de Sparkle»It's more Blaze family fun in this high octane, action-packed adventure as Blaze and his sister Sparkle team up to make it back to the Monster Dome in time for a big race.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/11/01/2126387_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521140000 +0200" stop="20230521142500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Blaze et les Monster Machines (L'anniversaire de Starla) S6 (11/24)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«L'anniversaire de Starla»Starla's wild west birthday party is in trouble when her cake gets carried off by a runaway train. Can she, Blaze and AJ catch up and save the cake before it's too late?</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/11/2126404_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521142500 +0200" stop="20230521144500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Blaze et les Monster Machines (Le trésor du tigre) S6 (13/24)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Le trésor du tigre»The Tiger Treasure: Blaze, AJ, and Stripes put their explorer skills to the test as they follow the trail to the fabled Tiger Treasure. (S6, ep 14).</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/06/00/2126272_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521144500 +0200" stop="20230521151000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Blaze et les Monster Machines (La plus rapide de tous) S6 (18/24)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«La plus rapide de tous»When a greedy queen casts a spell to make a few of our friends go slow, Blaze and AJ must race her for the magical cure.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/06/00/2126316_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521151000 +0200" stop="20230521153000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Blaze et les Monster Machines (Megabot) S6 (18/20)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Megabot»Megabot!: Blaze and AJ help their amazing new friend Megabot get to Axle City in time for the big Robot Parade. (S6, ep 20).</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/06/54/2126345_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521153000 +0200" stop="20230521155000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Blaze et les Monster Machines (Pirate Musical!) S6 (20/23)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Pirate Musical!»In the first ever Blaze Musical, Blaze, AJ, Crusher, and Pickle are on a daring quest to find the pieces of the Broken Key and unlock a secret treasure.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/24/18/2126370_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521155000 +0200" stop="20230521161500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Blaze et les Monster Machines (Histoires au coin du feu) S6 (22/23)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Histoires au coin du feu»It's a campout under the stars! Blaze, AJ, Starla, Crusher, and Pickle are gathered around the campfire to tell the most amazing stories they can make up! And the best part? Whoever tells the best story wins the last marshmallow!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/04/00/2126371_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521161500 +0200" stop="20230521163500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Blaze et les Monster Machines (Sparkle à la rescousse) S7 (n°1)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Sparkle à la rescousse»When Crusher sends Blaze away with one of his latest cheats, Blaze's little sister Sparkle comes to save the day and bring her brother back in time so they can race together to win the Teamwork Trophy!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/04/00/2126371_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521163500 +0200" stop="20230521164500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Santiago des mers (The Pirate Parade) S1 (n°11)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«The Pirate Parade»The Pirate Parade: It's time for the annual Pirate Parade! That is, unless Escarlata has anything to say about it. (S1, ep 11b).</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/24/28/2152455_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521164500 +0200" stop="20230521170000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Baby Shark : l'aventure sous l'eau (La journée du oui) S1 (n°7)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«La journée du oui»Baby convinces Daddy to say &quot;yup&quot; to everything for a day. What's the worst that could happen?</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/01/2136141_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521170000 +0200" stop="20230521171000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Baby Shark : l'aventure sous l'eau (Swimming With the Sharks) S1 (n°26)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Swimming With the Sharks»When Baby and his family become reality TV stars, they start to lose sight of what makes them the Sharks.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/48/2126268_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521171000 +0200" stop="20230521172000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Mini Chef (Mac and Cheese) S1 (n°8)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Mac and Cheese»Mac and Cheese: Tiny Chef makes rainy day Mac N Cheese but a leaky roof creates chaos in his tree stump kitchen! (S1, ep 8a).</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/15/2162247_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521172000 +0200" stop="20230521174500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Paw Patrol, la Pat'Patrouille (Un essaim de papillons / Où est La Galinetta d'or ?) S5 (7/26)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Un essaim de papillons / Où est La Galinetta d'or ?»The statue of Chickaletta has been stolen by Mayor Humdinger and is making its way through Adventure Bay's underground tunnel system.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/59/2126489_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521174500 +0200" stop="20230521175500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Les aventures de Paddington (La musique et Paddington) S2 (21/27)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«La musique et Paddington»The Adventures of Paddington is a new version of a familiar bear. It's a heartwarming show about being curious, being good to others, and being part of a loving family.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/07/16/2181238_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521175500 +0200" stop="20230521180000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Peppa Pig (La vente de charité) S2 (19/52)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«La vente de charité»Peppa and George want to go to the playground with Papa and Mama Pig. But a fog sets in and they get lost. When Papa Pig thinks they are back home, the fog clears and they are... in the playground!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/49/1665705_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521180000 +0200" stop="20230521180500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Peppa Pig (Tous à la piscine) S2 (20/52)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Tous à la piscine»Peppa and George learn to swim, just like Kelly and Karel Konijn. And that swimming is fun through all your life, Papa Pig shows.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/24/02/2136871_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521180500 +0200" stop="20230521181000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Peppa Pig (Jour de brume) S2 (18/52)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Jour de brume»Peppa and George make everyone laugh when they dress up as Mama Pig and Papa Pig.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/28/1664688_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521181000 +0200" stop="20230521181500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Anna et ses amis (Prank Day) S1 (23/78)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Prank Day»Prank Day: Today is Prank day, Anna and her friends must compete to elect the best prankster of all. Everyone's doing a great except Christopher, or so it seems. (S1, ep 23).</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/06/24/2133814_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521181500 +0200" stop="20230521182500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Anna et ses amis (A Present for Ron) S1 (24/78)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«A Present for Ron»Christopher loves Ron's rock collection so much, he wants to add another beautiful rock to it! They set off on a journey to find the most amazing rock they can find. When they discover it - they must figure out a creative solution to get it to Ron!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/06/25/2133815_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521182500 +0200" stop="20230521184500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Barbapapa *2019 (Pour maman / Barbacarambolage) S1 (n°18)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Pour maman / Barbacarambolage»The barbababies prepare a show for Barbamama's birthday. While Barbalala finishes up, they go to the carnival where Barbabeau gets stuck in an attraction. // Three separate stories telescope into a big final bouquet in the middle of the courtyard.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Emission Enfants</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/59/2126287_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521184500 +0200" stop="20230521191000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Blue et ses amis (Les nouvelles lunettes de Magenta) S1 (9/17)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Les nouvelles lunettes de Magenta»It's an exciting day for Magenta because she's getting glasses! We play a special game of Blue and Magenta's Clues to find out what Magenta wants to do when she gets her glasses and we get to go with her to meet.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/06/40/1727198_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521191000 +0200" stop="20230521193000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Paw Patrol, la Pat'Patrouille (Une balade en raquettes / L'étang aux canards) S5 (12/26)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Une balade en raquettes / L'étang aux canards»When Mayor Goodway and the twins are late getting back from a snowshoeing, Jake and Everest call the Paw Patrol to search for them.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/05/25/2154762_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521193000 +0200" stop="20230521195000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Deer Squad : Les Super-cerfs (Héros d'un jour / Danse avec les robots) S1 (7/20)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Héros d'un jour / Danse avec les robots»A meteor hits Earth and Mister Steel's heroic demeanor forces Deer Squad to save everyone. A dance competition in Middenbos turns into a mess.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/06/52/2126325_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521195000 +0200" stop="20230521201500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Deer Squad : Les Super-cerfs (Perruque en fuite / Ça tourne !) S2 (3/20)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Perruque en fuite / Ça tourne !»When Sir Steel's high-tech wig malfunctions and goes on the rampage in Platinum City the Deer Squad race to the rescue. // The Deer Squad must think fast to save Lady Fluffpot when Sir Steel's filming turns into a Disaster Movie!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/06/11/2126458_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521201500 +0200" stop="20230521203500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Les aventures de Paddington (Paddington Flies a Kite / Paddington the Detective) S1 (13/27)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Paddington Flies a Kite / Paddington the Detective»It's a windy day and Jonathan wishes to play kite with his dad. Since Mr. Brown is stuck at home, Paddington takes Jonathan to the park.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/13/03/2126585_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521203500 +0200" stop="20230521204500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Mini Chef (Pizza) S1 (n°1)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Pizza»</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/04/01/2155932_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521204500 +0200" stop="20230521210500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Barbapapa *2019 (Boris / Né pour être sauvage) S1 (3/52)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Boris / Né pour être sauvage»The barbababies find a lost baby elephant and secretly look after it. How will Barbapapa and Barbamama react to Boris? // Boris the elephant misses home. The Barbapapa decide to bring him back to Africa. On the spot, they help Boris to acclimatize.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Emission Enfants</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/23/2126323_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521210500 +0200" stop="20230521213000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Barbapapa *2019 (Le plus tendre des liens / L'empire orange) S1 (5/52)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Le plus tendre des liens / L'empire orange»While the family makes pottery, Barbabravo and Barbabright try to set the world record for the largest cheese soufflé. // The Barbapapas decide to go to the park. While her brother and sisters play , Barbalib can't help to control everything.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Emission Enfants</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/25/04/2155913_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521213000 +0200" stop="20230521215000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Baby Shark : l'aventure sous l'eau (Filouland / Les chevaliers de la mer profonde) S1 (n°10)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Filouland / Les chevaliers de la mer profonde»Jealous of Baby Shark's popularity, Shadow rebrands the Wreck as his own personal amusement park. // When Baby Shark and friends are playing knights and royals, Vola wants to be more than just a princess.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/26/2162949_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521215000 +0200" stop="20230521220500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Baby Shark : l'aventure sous l'eau (La bestiole baveuse) S1 (n°3)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«La bestiole baveuse»A game of Barnacle Ball turns into a rescue mission after Hank's pet rock, Rocky, is hit into the Lair of the Slobber Slug.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/18/2126485_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521220500 +0200" stop="20230521221000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Anna et ses amis (Party Time) S1 (22/78)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Party Time»Anna and Froga want to throw a party..... since it is not a particular party day they decide to celebrate &quot;Tomato Day&quot;, But Christopher ate all of the tomatoes ... so they need to find another name... Anna finds the perfect name: Friendship party!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/06/30/2133351_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521221000 +0200" stop="20230521222000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Anna et ses amis (Impatient Christopher) S1 (27/78)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Impatient Christopher»Christopher can hardly wait for his birthday tomorrow, he delivers invitations to his friends, he tries to figure out what present they are preparing for him. Christopher learns that sleeping is the fastest way for tomorrow to come sooner!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/06/31/2134999_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521222000 +0200" stop="20230521222500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Anna et ses amis (The Key) S1 (n°69)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«The Key»The Key: Because of her fear of spiders, Froga locks herself and Ron in the greenhouse to collecting Strawberries for the friends' Strawberry Snack time Musical Feast. (S1, ep 69).</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/22/2126264_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521222500 +0200" stop="20230521223500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Anna et ses amis (Fruits Surprise) S1 (n°70)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Fruits Surprise»When Froga and Christopher realize that Anna and Bubu may be making a &quot;fruit surprises&quot; for Snack Time, they try everything they can to preserve the two surprises. Froga and Christopher realized how difficult preserving a surprise can be!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/22/2126264_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521223500 +0200" stop="20230521224000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Anna et ses amis (Bubu's New Blue Jeans) S1 (n°71)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Bubu's New Blue Jeans»Christopher has prepared his annual obstacle race and is excited for all the friends to participate. Bubu's new blue jeans are still drying so he has to wear his brand-new pair to the event, he becomes overly concerned of getting them dirty.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/22/2126264_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521224000 +0200" stop="20230521225000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Anna et ses amis (Everywhere at Once) S1 (n°72)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Everywhere at Once»Anna has prepared her ice cream for everyone but forgets to place it in the freezer. - as she is trying to help all her friends at once, the ice cream melts! Is it ruined or can it be saved?</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/22/2126264_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521225000 +0200" stop="20230521225500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Peppa Pig (Le garage de Papy Dog) S2 (17/52)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Le garage de Papy Dog»It is amazing what Grandpa Dog provides everyone within his garage. And fortunately, otherwise you have bad luck with your bad luck as a breakdown! But when something goes wrong with the new car wash, Papa Pig suddenly turns out to be the great savior.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/28/1661344_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521225500 +0200" stop="20230521230000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Peppa Pig (Le voyage en montgolfière) S2 (25/52)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Le voyage en montgolfière»Peppa et sa famille sont à la fête de l'école. Le gros lot de la tombola est un voyage en Montgolfière. Peppa gagne : toute la famille apprécie le vol jusqu'à ce que le ballon s'accroche à un arbre...</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/06/35/1761176_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521230000 +0200" stop="20230521230500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Peppa Pig (Georges attrape un rhume) S2 (24/52)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Georges attrape un rhume»Peppa et George adorent sauter dans les flaques de boue, même quand il pleut. Mais quand George enlève son chapeau, il prend froid. Après beaucoup de repos, de lait chaud et de miel, George se sent beaucoup mieux. Maintenant il est très heureux de porter son chapeau, même quand il ne pleut pas...</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/02/25/04/2152462_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521230500 +0200" stop="20230521231000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Peppa Pig (L'examen de la vue) S2 (16/52)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«L'examen de la vue»Peppa's friend Pedro wears glasses. In addition, his father is an optician, so Pedro knows everything about glasses and eyes. According to Pedro, Peppa absolutely needs glasses. To see if that is really the case, Peppa can go to the optician ...</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/13/1659416_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521231000 +0200" stop="20230521231500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Peppa Pig (Le jardin de Peppa et George) S4 (12/52)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Le jardin de Peppa et George»Granpa Pig comes for a visit and brings Peppa and George seeds for a flower garden. They plant them, but birds want to eat them. Daddy Pig must help out with scaring the birds away. Soon beautiful flowers grow out in the garden, and one of them is taller than the house.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/06/17/1778125_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521231500 +0200" stop="20230521232000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Peppa Pig (La vétérinaire volante) S4 (13/52)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«La vétérinaire volante»The Flying Vet: Doctor Hamster is having a busy day - there are lots of helpless animals that need her help!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/27/26/1915914_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521232000 +0200" stop="20230521232500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Peppa Pig (Kylie Kangeroo) S5 (n°14)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Kylie Kangeroo»Peppa and George meet Kylie Kangaroo and her brother Joey. Peppa shows Kylie how to jump up and down in muddy puddles, but who can jump the highest?</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/13/15/2196073_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521232500 +0200" stop="20230521233500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Barbapapa *2019 (Zero Waste) S1 (50/52)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Zero Waste»When they see a beach covered with rubbish, the Barbapapa family decides to clean the beach and use the trash to make a miniature golf course.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Emission Enfants</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/24/25/2126472_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230521233500 +0200" stop="20230522000000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Barbapapa *2019 (The Competition Prize / Marvelous Moustaches) S1 (n°8)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«The Competition Prize / Marvelous Moustaches»The Barbabies win a touchpad. They all want to use it and snaffle it one after another. // Barbazoo collects photos of moustached celebrities. Unfortunately, it's impossible to find the last one: Charles Horseshoe-Furlip. He suspects a conspiracy...</desc>
<category lang="fr">Emission Enfants</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/27/2126536_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230522000000 +0200" stop="20230522002000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Blaze et les Monster Machines (Mail Truck Blaze) S7 (n°2)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Mail Truck Blaze»When three big mail deliveries are needed around the world, there's only one monster machine who can deliver it all: Mail Truck Blaze! He'll swim across seas, climb mountains, and venture to the Monster Dome --because mail trucks ALWAYS deliver!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/04/00/2126371_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230522002000 +0200" stop="20230522004500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Blaze et les Monster Machines (Sparkle à la rescousse) S7 (n°1)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Sparkle à la rescousse»When Crusher sends Blaze away with one of his latest cheats, Blaze's little sister Sparkle comes to save the day and bring her brother back in time so they can race together to win the Teamwork Trophy!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/04/00/2126371_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230522004500 +0200" stop="20230522010500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Paw Patrol, la Pat'Patrouille (La biblio-mobile / Monsieur Hellinger voit les choses en grand) S5 (8/26)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«La biblio-mobile / Monsieur Hellinger voit les choses en grand»When Ms. Marjorie brings her bookmobile to Everest and the kids of the mountains, Maynard accidentally sets the van rolling and goes off on a wild ride. // Mayor Humdinger has been carving his face into the cliffs of Adventure Bay!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/40/2145448_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230522010500 +0200" stop="20230522013000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Paw Patrol, la Pat'Patrouille (Au pays des papayes / La récolte de maïs) S5 (10/26)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Au pays des papayes / La récolte de maïs»Carlos and Tracker make PawPaw juice with the Paw Patrol when they find out Mayor Goodway and Chickaletta are in trouble.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/04/2126507_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230522013000 +0200" stop="20230522015000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Deer Squad : Les Super-cerfs (Une pluie de peluches / Le bal masqué) S2 (4/20)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Une pluie de peluches / Le bal masqué»Jade's first sleepover is an eventful occasion when Stu &amp; Safia make it rain teddies across the city and Central Forest! // Sir Steel is put out when he discovers he's not been invited to Lady Fluffpot's party but the Deer Squad are.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/31/2126474_A.jpg" />
</programme>