<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Voo -->
<programme start="20230524020500 +0200" stop="20230524022500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Les aventures de Paddington (Paddington and the Summer Games / Paddington Goes Camping) S1 (16/27)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Paddington and the Summer Games / Paddington Goes Camping»The Browns are having their annual summer games. Will Paddington be good at any of them? // Mrs. Brown has bought an old camper van and decides to take the family on a camping holiday.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/06/10/2132686_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524022500 +0200" stop="20230524024700 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Les aventures de Paddington (Paddington and the Fundraiser Day / Paddington's Alien Adventure) S1 (18/33)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Paddington and the Fundraiser Day / Paddington's Alien Adventure»The town hall is leaking and needs a new roof, and Paddington must stay silent to raise the money. // Will the strange radio messages Jonathan is receiving mean visitors are arriving from another world? Paddington forms a greeting committee!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/06/2132694_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524024700 +0200" stop="20230524025200 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Peppa Pig (L'hélicoptère de mademoiselle Rabbit) S3 (34/52)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«L'hélicoptère de mademoiselle Rabbit»Miss Rabbit emmène Peppa et sa famille, à l'exception de Papa Pig, pour une sortie à bord de son hélicoptère de sauvetage...</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/00/2126492_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524025200 +0200" stop="20230524025600 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Peppa Pig (Bébé Alexandre) S3 (35/52)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Bébé Alexandre»Les cousins de Peppa viennent en visite. Alexandre, un bébé, ne parle pas encore. Peppa lui enseigne son premier mot...</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/01/2126493_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524025600 +0200" stop="20230524030000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Peppa Pig (Le phare de Papy Rabbit) S3 (36/52)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Le phare de Papy Rabbit»Papy Chien propose à Peppa, George et Danny le chien d'aller visiter le phare de Papy Rabbit...</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/01/2126494_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524030000 +0200" stop="20230524030500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Peppa Pig (Le jour de repos de mademoiselle Rabbit) S3 (37/52)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Le jour de repos de mademoiselle Rabbit»Miss Rabbit has hurt her ankle, so her sister and her friends offer to fill in for her at the ice cream stand, the supermarket - and everywhere else she works!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/13/15/2196073_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524030500 +0200" stop="20230524033000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Bubulle Guppies (La saison des ninjas) S5 (n°11)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«La saison des ninjas»The guppies learn about the different seasons. In ancient Japan, if Gil wants to become a ninja, he has to be patient for many seasons.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Emission Enfants</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/09/03/2140154_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524033000 +0200" stop="20230524035000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Blue et ses amis (Cache-cache avec Blue) S2 (n°2)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Cache-cache avec Blue»Josh, Blue, and all our friends are playing Hide and Seek, and Blue knows the BEST hiding spot! As we play Blue's Clues to figure out the best place to hide, we search for our hiding friends and play Snail and Seek with Magenta and Blue.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/06/30/2126589_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524035000 +0200" stop="20230524041500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Blue et ses amis (La chasse au trésor de Blue) S2 (n°3)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«La chasse au trésor de Blue»Cap'n McStripes (that's ''pirate'' for Josh) and Blue are playing pirates, but where is the treasure?! We play Blue's Clues to figure it out.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/06/05/2130246_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524041500 +0200" stop="20230524043500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Santiago des mers (Les épreuves du pirate protecteur) S2 (n°5)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Les épreuves du pirate protecteur»On the first anniversary of becoming Pirate Protector, Santiago must complete a series of challenges meant to test his abilities and prove he's worthy all without the help of his tools or best mateys.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/06/48/2126318_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524043500 +0200" stop="20230524044500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Santiago des mers (Santiago et Bonnie à la rescousse) S1 (18/21)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Santiago et Bonnie à la rescousse»Santiago and Bonnie to the Rescue: After getting stranded at the bottom of a crevice, Bonnie and Santiago must team up to save the day. (S1, ep 17a).</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/24/28/2152455_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524044500 +0200" stop="20230524050000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Baby Shark : l'aventure sous l'eau (Détective Baby Shark) S1 (n°9)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Détective Baby Shark»Detective Baby Shark: When Grandma's shortcake goes missing before the bake-off, it's a case for Detective Baby Shark and William Watson! (S1, ep 7b).</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/26/2162949_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524050000 +0200" stop="20230524051000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Baby Shark : l'aventure sous l'eau (Le Fort de l'Aquamitié) S2 (n°1)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Le Fort de l'Aquamitié»Fort Fin-ship: When Baby and his friends build a clubhouse, Hank has no idea what to put in his personal nook. (S2, ep 1a).</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/08/31/2182123_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524051000 +0200" stop="20230524052000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Mini Chef (Bread) S1 (n°1)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Bread»Tiny Chef hosts his own tiny cooking show, and with his best friends Olly, Ruby and Henry, cooks up tasty dishes and amazing adventures, putting love into every dish he makes.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/12/02/2156638_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524052000 +0200" stop="20230524054500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Paw Patrol, la Pat'Patrouille (L'anniversaire surprise d'Astrid / La Pat' Patrouille sauve une tour de pizzas) S5 (26/26)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«L'anniversaire surprise d'Astrid / La Pat' Patrouille sauve une tour de pizzas»Ace's birthday and the puppies are building a nice birthday present for her. Mayor Humdinger wants the present himself. Adventure Bay wants to break the world record for highest pizza makers. But of course Mayor Humdinger wants that too.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/11/2126546_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524054500 +0200" stop="20230524060000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Les aventures de Paddington (Paddington n'est pas lui-même) S2 (19/27)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Paddington n'est pas lui-même»The Adventures of Paddington is a new version of a familiar bear. It's a heartwarming show about being curious, being good to others, and being part of a loving family.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/10/00/2126452_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524060000 +0200" stop="20230524060500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Peppa Pig (La panne de courant) S2 (47/52)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«La panne de courant»One day all the lights suddenly go out and Peppa's house is plunged into darkness. There has been a power cut. Peppa is surprised to find that even the television won't work without electricity. While the family wait for the electricity to come on again, Peppa and George have fun looking for a torch and thinking of games to play in the dark.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/06/07/1662218_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524060500 +0200" stop="20230524061000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Peppa Pig (L'anniversaire de Papa Pig) S2 (50/52)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«L'anniversaire de Papa Pig»Today is Daddy Pig's birthday, but he has to go to work. While he is away, Mummy Pig, Peppa and George prepare a special birthday surprise.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/06/39/1764100_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524061000 +0200" stop="20230524061500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Peppa Pig (Sleepover) S2 (n°51)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Sleepover»Peppa is going for a sleepover at Zoë Zebra's house. Suzy Sheep, Rebecca Rabbit, Candy Cat and Emily Elephant are all coming to the sleepover too. The girls are are too excited to go to sleep. They stay up playing games and having fun. They play songs on a piano, have a midnight feast and take it in turns to tell a story. At last they feel sleepy. They all snuggle up in their sleeping bags and fall asleep.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/13/15/2196073_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524061500 +0200" stop="20230524062000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Anna et ses amis (The Mystery Present) S1 (37/78)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«The Mystery Present»Bubu, Froga and Anna are looking for Anna's Ukulele, a bouncy ball and another item belonging to Froga. When searching, they find a beautiful present. Why is it here? Who is it for? What's inside? Our friends are planning to find out!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/06/24/2133813_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524062000 +0200" stop="20230524063000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Anna et ses amis (The Friendship Bouquet) S1 (38/78)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«The Friendship Bouquet»Froga is devastated because her sunflowers have withered in her garden and she cannot make her annual sunflower bouquet. Luckily, Anna, with her friends, searches for a solution to replace Froga's cherished sunflowers with something better!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/06/01/2134415_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524063000 +0200" stop="20230524065500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Blue et ses amis (Les Rythmes de Blue) S2 (n°1)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Les Rythmes de Blue»Josh starts a band and uses Blue's Clues to find out which instrument Blue wants to play.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/06/12/2126574_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524065500 +0200" stop="20230524071500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Paw Patrol, la Pat'Patrouille (Pups Save a Humdinger Doll / Pups Save a Sand Sculpture Contest) S9 (n°5)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Pups Save a Humdinger Doll / Pups Save a Sand Sculpture Contest»With Tracker's help, the PAW Patrol must rescue Mayor Humdinger who has been mistaken for Big Hairy's missing toy doll. // When Mayor Humdinger tries to cheat at the Adventure Bay sand sculpture contest, his machine goes out-of-control.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/40/2145448_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524071500 +0200" stop="20230524073000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Paw Patrol, la Pat'Patrouille (Pups Save Daring Danny X) S3 (n°8)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Pups Save Daring Danny X»Daring Danny X takes his ambitions too far when he attempts a jump over Rattle Snake Canyon! The Paw Patrol wows with a mid-air rescue.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/10/04/2194955_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524073000 +0200" stop="20230524075000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Deer Squad : Les Super-cerfs (L'Échangeur / Touche pas à mon oeuf) S1 (n°9)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«L'Échangeur / Touche pas à mon oeuf»Professor Scratch's Switcheroo device causes chaos when Sir Steel uses it to get Deer Squad's Powers. // Rammy must learn to trust his friends when he chooses to take care of an abandoned egg, all while dealing with a mysterious ant invasion.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/21/23/2126380_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524075000 +0200" stop="20230524081500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Deer Squad : Les Super-cerfs (La course aux rebonds / Qu'est-ce qui ne va pas, Lola ?) S2 (n°207)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«La course aux rebonds / Qu'est-ce qui ne va pas, Lola ?»It's Deer Squad to the rescue when Stu and Safia bounce off to space on their super bouncy mega trampolines./ A bad mood crystal causes Lola and many animals to become unusually grumpy!Jade has to help Deer Squad to restore joy around Central Forest.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/26/05/2126289_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524081500 +0200" stop="20230524083500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Les aventures de Paddington (Paddington and the Bone / Paddington Joins a Band) S1 (17/27)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Paddington and the Bone / Paddington Joins a Band»Mr. Gruber has been loaned a T-Rex Skeleton, but Lucky the dog has stolen the priceless bone and buried it somewhere. // The kids decide to form a rock band with Paddington, but what instrument should he play, and what is rock music?</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/24/21/2126466_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524083500 +0200" stop="20230524084500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Mini Chef (Popcorn) S1 (n°2)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Popcorn»Tiny Chef hosts his own tiny cooking show, and with his best friends Olly, Ruby and Henry, cooks up tasty dishes and amazing adventures, putting love into every dish he makes.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/07/05/2157060_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524084500 +0200" stop="20230524090500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Barbapapa *2019 (Les Barbapapa des cavernes / Les petits monstres) S1 (19/52)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Les Barbapapa des cavernes / Les petits monstres»The barbababies discover a strange cave. Barbalib tells the story of the caves Barbapapa and how they transformed. // The Barbababies have a sleepover in the living room. Fearing the monsters in the closet, they set up wacky traps to catch them.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Emission Enfants</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/42/2126425_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524090500 +0200" stop="20230524093000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Barbapapa *2019 (The Treasure Hunt / Going into the Wild) S1 (22/52)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«The Treasure Hunt / Going into the Wild»Mr. Strict's twins visit the barbababies. The barbababies organize a treasure hunt for the twins and enjoy the great outdoors. // The Barbapapas are off to a new adventure... in the garden. But living in nature is more complicated than they expected.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Emission Enfants</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/05/00/2126455_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524093000 +0200" stop="20230524095000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Baby Shark : l'aventure sous l'eau (Il était une fois dans l'eau / Le monstre gluant) S1 (n°13)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Il était une fois dans l'eau / Le monstre gluant»When an underwater storm rains on Baby Shark and William's fun, they doubt whether they can have an adventure indoors. // William and Vola enter a Young Scientist Contest and their competitive spirit gets them into a sticky situation.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/21/27/2126538_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524095000 +0200" stop="20230524100500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Baby Shark : l'aventure sous l'eau (La journée du oui) S1 (n°7)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«La journée du oui»Baby convinces Daddy to say &quot;yup&quot; to everything for a day. What's the worst that could happen?</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/01/2136141_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524100500 +0200" stop="20230524101000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Anna et ses amis (The Great Friendship Show) S1 (34/78)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«The Great Friendship Show»The Great Friendship Show: Anna and her friends write a poem. Bubu prefers to paint. And the friends do so too. Froga is not so keen on painting. For Ron, it's poetry. (S1, ep 34).</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/06/26/2133348_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524101000 +0200" stop="20230524102000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Anna et ses amis (Leaf Portraits) S1 (n°39)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Leaf Portraits»When Ron discovers that some leaves resemble his friends, like clouds are making shapes in the sky. Anna, Froga and Christopher are amazed by his discoveries. The leaves are blown away, and the wind takes the &quot;Leaf Portraits&quot;.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/22/2126264_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524102000 +0200" stop="20230524102500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Anna et ses amis (The Funny Photo) S1 (n°77)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«The Funny Photo»While flipping through her Funny Photo Album, Froga is surprised to learn she has no funny picture of Anna! Setting off to remedy this, Froga instills the assistance of her friends to try to score a hilarious photo of Anna.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/22/2126264_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524102500 +0200" stop="20230524103500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Anna et ses amis (The Gift Box) S1 (n°78)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«The Gift Box»The Gift Box: The friends are having a gift exchange and Bubu ends up with a present from Christopher. But he mistakes the box itself for the actual gift. (S1, ep 78).</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/22/2126264_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524103500 +0200" stop="20230524104000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Anna et ses amis (Strawberries) S1 (1/78)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Strawberries»Anna and Froga are excited to make the best strawberry pie ever with the first strawberries of the season. Anna makes a plan to distract Christopher while they make the pie!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/06/03/2126550_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524104000 +0200" stop="20230524105000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Anna et ses amis (The Swing) S1 (n°2)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«The Swing»When Anna and Froga discover the old seat of their swing, they are excited to hang it on the apple tree. But the ropes to attach it have gone missing!The two friends' search for the missing ropes turns out to be more difficult than they had imagined!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/22/2126264_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524105000 +0200" stop="20230524105600 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Peppa Pig (Les étoiles) S2 (49/52)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Les étoiles»George loves space and when he needs to sleep, he turns on his space mobile. Peppa doesn't understand that until Daddy Pig tells her about the stars. And when she gets to look through the telescope at Grandpa Pig, Peppa is over ... the space is super!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/02/22/07/2150417_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524105600 +0200" stop="20230524110000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Peppa Pig (Travailler et s'amuser) S3 (1/52)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Travailler et s'amuser»When Peppa and Suzy learn that grown ups must work all day, they decide to play at working in a store. But they quickly get tired of it.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/24/16/2126329_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524110000 +0200" stop="20230524110500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Peppa Pig (L'arc en ciel) S3 (2/52)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«L'arc en ciel»Peppa and her family are on holiday in their trailer van. They decide to go to Duck Land, a special park where they can see the ducks in the river, and are surprised when they learn that their van can convert into a boat!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/15/2126330_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524110500 +0200" stop="20230524111000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Peppa Pig (La toux de Pedro) S3 (3/52)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«La toux de Pedro»Pedro gets a contagious cough at daycare and some of the other children soon catch it. When it's time to go the grown-ups catch it too, including Madame Gazelle. Peppa calls Doctor Brown Bear who gives them terrible-tasting medicine, but who will look after him when he is sick?</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/24/17/2126331_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524111000 +0200" stop="20230524111500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Peppa Pig (La péniche) S5 (18/52)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«La péniche»Peppa et sa famille vont au musée. Peppa aime bien la galerie des portraits des rois et des reines, alors que George préfère le hall des dinosaures.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/06/08/2126449_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524111500 +0200" stop="20230524112000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Peppa Pig (Le nounours de la garderie) S4 (19/52)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Le nounours de la garderie»George's New Dinosaur: George pays a visit to Mr Fox's Shop after his favourite toy, Mr Dinosaur breaks. With all the additional features surely Dino Roar is a good replacement?</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/06/50/1869550_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524112000 +0200" stop="20230524112500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Peppa Pig (Le train de Papy Pig à la rescousse !) S4 (20/52)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Le train de Papy Pig à la rescousse !»Miss Rabbit's train has broken down, so Grandpa Pig lends her his toy train, Trudy.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/04/13/2180060_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524112500 +0200" stop="20230524113500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Barbapapa *2019 (Silence Please) S1 (52/52)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Silence Please»Barbalib wants to compete in a writing contest but his brothers and sisters stop her from concentrating.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Emission Enfants</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/09/02/2139499_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524113500 +0200" stop="20230524120000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Barbapapa *2019 (Même pas cap ! / Roy) S1 (10/52)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Même pas cap ! / Roy»On a ski trip, the Barbapapas build a giant igloo. Barbabravo and Barbalib challenge each other to find out who is braver. // Barbabright creates a vacuuming robot that's also very good at soccer. The Barbababies organise a match against the robots.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Emission Enfants</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/06/53/2155899_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524120000 +0200" stop="20230524122000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Blaze et les Monster Machines (Knights in Sparkling Armor) S7 (n°5)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Knights in Sparkling Armor»When Crusher and Pickle are trapped inside a cage over a bubbling slime swap, it's up to Blaze, AJ, and Sparkle to become...Knights! Will they be able to rescue Crusher and Pickle from the swamp before it's too late?</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/04/00/2126371_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524122000 +0200" stop="20230524124500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Blaze et les Monster Machines (The Super Skateboard) S7 (n°13)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«The Super Skateboard»It's Grammy's birthday but Crusher doesn't have enough money for a special gift! So, Blaze and AJ help him do different jobs and earn the money for Grammy's present. But, they have to hurry so they can be back in time for Grammy's birthday party!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/04/00/2126371_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524124500 +0200" stop="20230524130500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Paw Patrol, la Pat'Patrouille (Pups Save a T-Rex Tyke / Pups Save a Playful Elephant Calf) S9 (n°15)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Pups Save a T-Rex Tyke / Pups Save a Playful Elephant Calf»When a baby T-Rex gets lost, Ryder and the pups go on a daring mission to the Dino Wilds to help find him. // When Everest joins the Paw Patrol for a visit to the jungle, she makes friends with a clumsy elephant calf and then must help rescue him.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/57/2147014_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524130500 +0200" stop="20230524133000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Paw Patrol, la Pat'Patrouille (Il faut sauver le moisso-matic / Faucon X le hardi) S5 (24/26)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Il faut sauver le moisso-matic / Faucon X le hardi»Farmer Yumi has a robot that helps with the corn harvest. That works great, until Chickaletta gets into the machine. Danny wears a bird suit as a mascot for the Adventure Bay basketball team. Two eagles thinks that he is a real bird.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/21/00/2124921_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524133000 +0200" stop="20230524135000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Deer Squad : Les Super-cerfs (La puissance du cristal / Un Métal en toc) S2 (8/20)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«La puissance du cristal / Un Métal en toc»Dinky the baby turtle is given a special courage crystal by Jade but Sir Steel thinks will boost his Mech Suit's powers. // What's worse than Sir Steel? Two Sir Steels! Can the Deer Squad spot the real one with Muffin's help?</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/10/2126312_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524135000 +0200" stop="20230524140500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Deer Squad : Les Super-cerfs (Duck Dilemma) S1 (n°2)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Duck Dilemma»Duck Dilemma: Kai invents a Roboduck to babysit the ducklings, but it goes haywire and takes down all the technology in Platinum City. (S1, ep 2b).</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/09/02/2143541_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524140500 +0200" stop="20230524142500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Les aventures de Paddington (Paddington and the Summer Games / Paddington Goes Camping) S1 (16/27)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Paddington and the Summer Games / Paddington Goes Camping»The Browns are having their annual summer games. Will Paddington be good at any of them? // Mrs. Brown has bought an old camper van and decides to take the family on a camping holiday.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/06/10/2132686_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524142500 +0200" stop="20230524144500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Les aventures de Paddington (Paddington and the Fundraiser Day / Paddington's Alien Adventure) S1 (18/33)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Paddington and the Fundraiser Day / Paddington's Alien Adventure»The town hall is leaking and needs a new roof, and Paddington must stay silent to raise the money. // Will the strange radio messages Jonathan is receiving mean visitors are arriving from another world? Paddington forms a greeting committee!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/06/2132694_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524144500 +0200" stop="20230524145000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Peppa Pig (L'hélicoptère de mademoiselle Rabbit) S3 (34/52)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«L'hélicoptère de mademoiselle Rabbit»Miss Rabbit emmène Peppa et sa famille, à l'exception de Papa Pig, pour une sortie à bord de son hélicoptère de sauvetage...</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/00/2126492_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524145000 +0200" stop="20230524145500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Peppa Pig (Bébé Alexandre) S3 (35/52)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Bébé Alexandre»Les cousins de Peppa viennent en visite. Alexandre, un bébé, ne parle pas encore. Peppa lui enseigne son premier mot...</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/01/2126493_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524145500 +0200" stop="20230524150000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Peppa Pig (Le phare de Papy Rabbit) S3 (36/52)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Le phare de Papy Rabbit»Papy Chien propose à Peppa, George et Danny le chien d'aller visiter le phare de Papy Rabbit...</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/01/2126494_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524150000 +0200" stop="20230524150500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Peppa Pig (Le jour de repos de mademoiselle Rabbit) S3 (37/52)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Le jour de repos de mademoiselle Rabbit»Miss Rabbit has hurt her ankle, so her sister and her friends offer to fill in for her at the ice cream stand, the supermarket - and everywhere else she works!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/13/15/2196073_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524150500 +0200" stop="20230524153000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Bubulle Guppies (La saison des ninjas) S5 (n°11)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«La saison des ninjas»The guppies learn about the different seasons. In ancient Japan, if Gil wants to become a ninja, he has to be patient for many seasons.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Emission Enfants</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/09/03/2140154_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524153000 +0200" stop="20230524155000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Blue et ses amis (Cache-cache avec Blue) S2 (n°2)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Cache-cache avec Blue»Josh, Blue, and all our friends are playing Hide and Seek, and Blue knows the BEST hiding spot! As we play Blue's Clues to figure out the best place to hide, we search for our hiding friends and play Snail and Seek with Magenta and Blue.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/06/30/2126589_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524155000 +0200" stop="20230524161500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Blue et ses amis (La chasse au trésor de Blue) S2 (n°3)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«La chasse au trésor de Blue»Cap'n McStripes (that's ''pirate'' for Josh) and Blue are playing pirates, but where is the treasure?! We play Blue's Clues to figure it out.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/06/05/2130246_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524161500 +0200" stop="20230524163500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Santiago des mers (Les épreuves du pirate protecteur) S2 (n°5)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Les épreuves du pirate protecteur»On the first anniversary of becoming Pirate Protector, Santiago must complete a series of challenges meant to test his abilities and prove he's worthy all without the help of his tools or best mateys.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/06/48/2126318_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524163500 +0200" stop="20230524164500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Santiago des mers (Santiago et Bonnie à la rescousse) S1 (18/21)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Santiago et Bonnie à la rescousse»Santiago and Bonnie to the Rescue: After getting stranded at the bottom of a crevice, Bonnie and Santiago must team up to save the day. (S1, ep 17a).</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/24/28/2152455_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524164500 +0200" stop="20230524170000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Baby Shark : l'aventure sous l'eau (Détective Baby Shark) S1 (n°9)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Détective Baby Shark»Detective Baby Shark: When Grandma's shortcake goes missing before the bake-off, it's a case for Detective Baby Shark and William Watson! (S1, ep 7b).</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/26/2162949_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524170000 +0200" stop="20230524171000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Baby Shark : l'aventure sous l'eau (Le Fort de l'Aquamitié) S2 (n°1)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Le Fort de l'Aquamitié»Fort Fin-ship: When Baby and his friends build a clubhouse, Hank has no idea what to put in his personal nook. (S2, ep 1a).</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/08/31/2182123_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524171000 +0200" stop="20230524172000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Mini Chef (Bread) S1 (n°1)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Bread»Tiny Chef hosts his own tiny cooking show, and with his best friends Olly, Ruby and Henry, cooks up tasty dishes and amazing adventures, putting love into every dish he makes.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/12/02/2156638_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524172000 +0200" stop="20230524174500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Paw Patrol, la Pat'Patrouille (L'anniversaire surprise d'Astrid / La Pat' Patrouille sauve une tour de pizzas) S5 (26/26)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«L'anniversaire surprise d'Astrid / La Pat' Patrouille sauve une tour de pizzas»Ace's birthday and the puppies are building a nice birthday present for her. Mayor Humdinger wants the present himself. Adventure Bay wants to break the world record for highest pizza makers. But of course Mayor Humdinger wants that too.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/11/2126546_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524174500 +0200" stop="20230524175500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Les aventures de Paddington (Paddington n'est pas lui-même) S2 (19/27)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Paddington n'est pas lui-même»The Adventures of Paddington is a new version of a familiar bear. It's a heartwarming show about being curious, being good to others, and being part of a loving family.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/10/00/2126452_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524175500 +0200" stop="20230524180000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Peppa Pig (Richard Rabbit vient jouer à la maison) S3 (8/52)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Richard Rabbit vient jouer à la maison»Richard Rabbit comes to play with George, and Suzy Sheep comes to play with Peppa! The boys and girls don't want to play the same games, but they all like jumping up and down in muddy puddles.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/14/2126358_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524180000 +0200" stop="20230524180500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Peppa Pig (La course rigolote) S3 (9/52)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«La course rigolote»Daddy Pig finds it hard work when he runs a race to raise money for the school roof, but it's easier to run when a wasp is chasing him!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/24/22/2126384_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524180500 +0200" stop="20230524181000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Peppa Pig (La lessive) S3 (10/52)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«La lessive»Daddy Pig hangs his clean football shirt out to dry, but Peppa, George and Mummy splash it with mud. They put it in the wash, but Peppa puts her red dress in too - which turns Daddy's shirt pink!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/04/59/1903833_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524181000 +0200" stop="20230524181500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Anna et ses amis (King for a Day) S1 (n°41)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«King for a Day»Today the friends play King For A Day, someone throws the crown on Christopher's head! Then the crown leaves his head and ends on his cousin, Benjy, who just came for a day visit. Benjy only wants to play with his cousin, and do whatever he wants.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/22/2126264_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524181500 +0200" stop="20230524182500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Anna et ses amis (The Vegetable Pie) S1 (42/78)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«The Vegetable Pie»Froga's strawberries are sick so she's going to miss this year's vegetable picking. When Bubu offers her a walkie-talkie to use, she agrees to let him baby-sit her sick plant for her. But soon, Froga loses confidence in Bubu's ability to help.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/22/2126264_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524182500 +0200" stop="20230524184500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Barbapapa *2019 (Barbibul a un secret / Trop trop la classe) S1 (n°22)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Barbibul a un secret / Trop trop la classe»Barbabright acts strangely. What is he hiding ? The Barbabbabies will do anything to find out. // The Barbapapa decide to save energy. But their efforts are undermined by Barbabright and Barbabelle who build a secret energy-consuming project.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Emission Enfants</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2126364_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524184500 +0200" stop="20230524191000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Blue et ses amis (La grande fête de Blue) S2 (n°5)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«La grande fête de Blue»Show us your dance moves! Josh and Blue are having a dance party, and we play Blue's Clues to figure out Blue's favorite dance. As we groove to find clues, we learn Magenta's favorite dance and help Bunny Jo learn a new dance!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/06/38/2158940_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524191000 +0200" stop="20230524193000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Paw Patrol, la Pat'Patrouille (Une chaleur écrasante / Alex l'apprenti fermier) S4 (15/26)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Une chaleur écrasante / Alex l'apprenti fermier»It's hot in Adventure Bay and everyone wants ice cream. Unfortunately, everything is finished and the delivery is late. Captain Turbot and Francois compete against each other in a bag-jumping competition.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/55/1728948_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524193000 +0200" stop="20230524195000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Deer Squad : Les Super-cerfs (La Tour de l'espace / C'est magique) S1 (10/20)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«La Tour de l'espace / C'est magique»Mr. Steel wants to go to the moon and orders Professor Sketch to turn the Steel Tower into a rocket! A magician lures the audience away from Rammy's presentation, who gets so angry that he takes it out on the man's hat.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/21/31/2126406_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524195000 +0200" stop="20230524201500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Deer Squad : Les Super-cerfs (Lady Monkey Mech / Critter Care Calamity) S2 (9/20)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Lady Monkey Mech / Critter Care Calamity»Sir Steel wrecks havoc during Harvest Parade in 'Lady Monkey Mech', then in 'Critter Care Calamity', Pollen from Bobbi's snuffleblooms makes everyone start getting super sneezes!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/06/53/2126342_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524201500 +0200" stop="20230524203500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Les aventures de Paddington (Paddington Builds a Scarecrow / Paddington Plays Hide and Seek) S1 (27/27)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Paddington Builds a Scarecrow / Paddington Plays Hide and Seek»Paddington accidentally ruins Mr. Browns lovely lawn and must repair it. But the birds take a liking to the seeds so he builds a Scarecrow. // Mrs. Bird is a champion hide and seeker but where is she? Paddington, Jonathan and Judy mus go find her.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/06/57/2126284_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524203500 +0200" stop="20230524204500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Mini Chef (Freeze Pops) S1 (n°3)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Freeze Pops»Tiny Chef hosts his own tiny cooking show, and with his best friends Olly, Ruby and Henry, cooks up tasty dishes and amazing adventures, putting love into every dish he makes.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/12/03/2157528_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524204500 +0200" stop="20230524210500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Barbapapa *2019 (Hiccupism / Silence please) S1 (32/52)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Hiccupism / Silence please»Barbabeau can't paint. He has a hiccup he can't get rid of. Just when he's about to give up, he accidentally creates a new artistic movement. // Barbalib wants to compete in a writing contest but his brothers and sisters stop her from concentrating.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Emission Enfants</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/59/2126487_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524210500 +0200" stop="20230524213000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Barbapapa *2019 (Pour maman / Barbacarambolage) S1 (n°18)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Pour maman / Barbacarambolage»The barbababies prepare a show for Barbamama's birthday. While Barbalala finishes up, they go to the carnival where Barbabeau gets stuck in an attraction. // Three separate stories telescope into a big final bouquet in the middle of the courtyard.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Emission Enfants</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/59/2126287_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524213000 +0200" stop="20230524215000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Baby Shark : l'aventure sous l'eau (Coach Mamie Shark / Programme chargé) S1 (n°14)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Coach Mamie Shark / Programme chargé»Baby Shark's Barnacle Ball team hires an expert coach with unusual methods. // Baby Shark bites off more than he can chew before his big dance party with Grandma Shark.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/24/15/2126463_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524215000 +0200" stop="20230524220500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Baby Shark : l'aventure sous l'eau (Le défi du requin) S1 (n°8)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Le défi du requin»Shadow challenges Baby Shark to a Shark-Off to prove who's the sharkiest shark.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/26/2162949_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524220500 +0200" stop="20230524221000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Anna et ses amis (Hiccups) S1 (n°40)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Hiccups»Froga gets a terrible hiccup, each of her friends come up with creative solutions to help her to get rid of it. No matter how hard they try, though, the hiccups put their patience and good humor to the test!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/22/2126264_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524221000 +0200" stop="20230524222000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Anna et ses amis (Give-Away Day) S1 (45/78)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Give-Away Day»Froga gets a new beautiful Sunflower Plant and decides to put it in her greenhouse. But she realizes that has been using her greenhouse to store all the items she doesn't know what to do with anymore. Now there's no room for her plant!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/22/2126264_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524222000 +0200" stop="20230524222500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Anna et ses amis (The Detectives) S1 (3/78)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«The Detectives»Froga is desperate. Her favourite toy Super Pebble has disappeared! Now Anna and Ron work with Froga play detectives. Thanks to a thoughtful gift from Christopher, Froga ends up finding her missing Super stone herself!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/06/03/2126560_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524222500 +0200" stop="20230524223500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Anna et ses amis (Super Christopher) S1 (n°4)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Super Christopher»Christopher visits Anna with his &quot; Super Christopher&quot; costume, ready for adventure! But being a superhero comes with a whole set of challenges. Christopher isn't just a superhero. He's also a super friend.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/22/2126264_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524223500 +0200" stop="20230524224000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Anna et ses amis (The Photo) S1 (5/78)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«The Photo»Polaroid camera, she decides to take pictures of all her friends. Everyone thinks it's a great idea and Anna makes some great portraits. But things get complicated when she tries to take a group shot of everyone!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/06/19/2126572_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524224000 +0200" stop="20230524225000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Anna et ses amis (We Love Nature) S1 (6/78)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«We Love Nature»Anna and her friends are planning an amazing picnic in nature. But Bubu's bag is too heavy, Christophe can't resist eating all the strawberries! (S1, ep 6).</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/06/20/2126573_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524225000 +0200" stop="20230524225500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Peppa Pig (Princesse Peppa) S3 (14/52)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Princesse Peppa»Granny and Grandpa Pig come for a dinner party with Mummy and Daddy Pig. Peppa and George are too tired to go to bed, until they are told a story.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/13/15/2196073_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524225500 +0200" stop="20230524230000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Peppa Pig (Teddy Maternello) S3 (15/52)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Teddy Maternello»Peppa brings home a teddy from daycare to look after, but she is worried that he will not have a very exciting time.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/24/16/2126321_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524230000 +0200" stop="20230524230500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Peppa Pig (La fête des pirates de Danny) S3 (16/52)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«La fête des pirates de Danny»It is Danny Dog's birthday, and with the help of Granddad Dog and Grandpa Pig the children take part in a pirate treasure hunt.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/15/2126409_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524230500 +0200" stop="20230524231000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Peppa Pig (La visite de monsieur Patate) S3 (17/52)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«La visite de monsieur Patate»Madame Gazelle takes Peppa and her friends on a train ride, where they must tick off what they see on their activity sheets. Meanwhile Pedro keeps losing his ticket.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/24/13/2126430_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524231000 +0200" stop="20230524231400 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Peppa Pig (Le concours d'animaux) S4 (21/52)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Le concours d'animaux»There is a pet competition at playgroup, and everyone has brought in their pets. Dr Hamster is the judge, but finds it hard to choose the best pet.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/06/03/1894475_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524231400 +0200" stop="20230524232000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Peppa Pig (La toile d'araignée) S4 (22/52)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«La toile d'araignée»Peppa, George and Mummy Pig are in Daddy Pig's study, and they see that it is a complete mess and full of spider webs. They see a spider, which Peppa names Mister Skinnylegs, but Mummy Pig is afraid and tells Daddy Pig to get rid of it. They set out to find a new home for Mister Skinnylegs.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/58/2126263_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524232000 +0200" stop="20230524232500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Peppa Pig (Une nuit mouvementée) S4 (23/52)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Une nuit mouvementée»Peppa's family are staying at Cousin Chloe's house. After a long day everyone is tired and wants to go to sleep. But baby Alexander's crying is keeping everyone awake!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/06/21/1964197_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524232500 +0200" stop="20230524233500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Barbapapa *2019 (Hiccupism) S1 (32/52)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Hiccupism»Everyday fun with Barbapapa and his family ? a very special group of colourful creatures who can change into all shapes and sizes. Join in all the adventures and fun with this big happy family! This animated series is based on the successful series of children's books by Annette Tison and Talus Taylor. The first Barbapapa book was published in 1970 and has since been translated into over 30 languages.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Emission Enfants</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/10/05/2194956_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230524233500 +0200" stop="20230525000000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Barbapapa *2019 (L'herbe est toujours plus verte ailleurs / Quand je serai grand) S1 (38/52)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«L'herbe est toujours plus verte ailleurs / Quand je serai grand»Barbabright coats the house in magic product to prevent water leakage. The next day, The house deflates like a balloon. // A bird builds its nest on Barbazoo's belly. Barbazoo wants to become a big tree to shelter animals. This becomes complicated.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Emission Enfants</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/29/04/2126403_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230525000000 +0200" stop="20230525002000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Blaze et les Monster Machines (Paramedic Power) S7 (n°9)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Paramedic Power»When Blaze's friends need help, Ambulance Blaze, Paramedic AJ and Paramedic Gabby have all the tools they need to save the day!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/04/00/2126371_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230525002000 +0200" stop="20230525004500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Blaze et les Monster Machines (Knights in Sparkling Armor) S7 (n°5)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Knights in Sparkling Armor»When Crusher and Pickle are trapped inside a cage over a bubbling slime swap, it's up to Blaze, AJ, and Sparkle to become...Knights! Will they be able to rescue Crusher and Pickle from the swamp before it's too late?</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/04/00/2126371_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230525004500 +0200" stop="20230525010500 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Paw Patrol, la Pat'Patrouille (Pups Save the Tooth Fairy / Pups Solve the Mystery of the Missing Art) S9 (n°7)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Pups Save the Tooth Fairy / Pups Solve the Mystery of the Missing Art»Julius loses his tooth and has a dream that the Paw Patrol saves a bumbling Tooth Fairy. // When all the paintings mysteriously disappear from the Art Museum festival, the PAW Patrol must solve the Missing Art Mystery and return all the paintings.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/40/2145448_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230525010500 +0200" stop="20230525013000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Paw Patrol, la Pat'Patrouille (Le grand singe / Le petit chat perché) S4 (11/26)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Le grand singe / Le petit chat perché»After a visit to the jungle, a big hairy monkey hitchhike to Adventure Bay. A kitten from Mayor Humdinger flies off to play with baby eagles.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/55/1728948_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230525013000 +0200" stop="20230525015000 +0200" channel="NickJr.be">
<title lang="fr">Deer Squad : Les Super-cerfs (Le concours de tournesol / Le voleur de lune) S2 (10/20)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Le concours de tournesol / Le voleur de lune»Ricardo hosts a sunflower competition, but Lola is worried hers is ill - surely a little Wood Power will perk it up? // Lady Fluffpot wants a statue made of moon rock, but the deer know that messing with the moon is a bad idea!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Dessin animé</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/07/03/2126367_A.jpg" />
</programme>