<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Bouygues -->
<programme start="20230513060000 +0200" stop="20230513070500 +0200" channel="PenthousePassion.fr">
<title lang="fr">Gianna Dior and Friends Love Big Dick</title>
<desc lang="fr">Gianna Dior and her friends are sensational cock teasers! These delicious tarts titillate with a sexy striptease before diving headfirst into a big cock, purely for their own slutty satisfaction!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Téléfilm</category>
<category lang="fr">Pornographie</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>-18</value><icon src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/2/2d/Moins18.svg/200px-Moins18.svg.png" /></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230513070500 +0200" stop="20230513072000 +0200" channel="PenthousePassion.fr">
<title lang="fr">Sexy Work Fantasies</title>
<desc lang="fr">Policewoman, Layla (Price) is talking to her partner, Ricky (Mancini) about a suspect in a swinger's club. She reveals she's done that before and is getting wet just thinking about her experiences... it might be Ricky's lucky day!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Téléfilm</category>
<category lang="fr">Pornographie</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>-18</value><icon src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/2/2d/Moins18.svg/200px-Moins18.svg.png" /></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230513072000 +0200" stop="20230513073900 +0200" channel="PenthousePassion.fr">
<title lang="fr">The Art of Seduction</title>
<desc lang="fr">Olive is inspired by the party and asks Ryan to come home early the next night, she has a little surprise for him. The surprise is Casey! As Olive watches Casey and Ryan fuck she plays with herself! Ryan licks pussy, gets a BJ, cowgirl, reverse cowgirl, doggy and mish before they all reach climax!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Film</category>
<category lang="fr">Pornographie</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>-18</value><icon src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/2/2d/Moins18.svg/200px-Moins18.svg.png" /></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230513073900 +0200" stop="20230513080000 +0200" channel="PenthousePassion.fr">
<title lang="fr">My Best Friend's Mom Swallows</title>
<desc lang="fr">Delivery boy, Ricky (Spanish), is having trouble with his girlfriend when he's delivering a package to sexy MILF, Kit Mercer. She invites him in to tell her what's wrong and discovers he's frustrated because his girlfriend won't have sex with him. But Kit and her kitty know just how to take care of a frustrated Ricky!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Film</category>
<category lang="fr">Pornographie</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>-18</value><icon src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/2/2d/Moins18.svg/200px-Moins18.svg.png" /></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230513080000 +0200" stop="20230513082300 +0200" channel="PenthousePassion.fr">
<title lang="fr">White Girls Like It Dark</title>
<desc lang="fr">Adira (Allure) has been especially naughty trying to get her stepfather's (Prince Yahshua) attention, but so far nothing has worked. She's very interested in seeing that BBC she's sure is hidden in his pants. Mom's out of town and today she's determined to succeed!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Film</category>
<category lang="fr">Pornographie</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>-18</value><icon src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/2/2d/Moins18.svg/200px-Moins18.svg.png" /></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230513082300 +0200" stop="20230513084300 +0200" channel="PenthousePassion.fr">
<title lang="fr">My Teenage Stepdaughter</title>
<desc lang="fr">After getting stood up on a date with his wife, Tyler Steel gets a surprise comfort from his step daughter, Brooke Haze. She thinks her vagina will make him feel better. Going into various positions Brooke makes sure she stays wet.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Film</category>
<category lang="fr">Pornographie</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>-18</value><icon src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/2/2d/Moins18.svg/200px-Moins18.svg.png" /></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230513084300 +0200" stop="20230513090000 +0200" channel="PenthousePassion.fr">
<title lang="fr">Stella Cox Nymphomaniac</title>
<desc lang="fr">Two cocks at once for Stella Cox means double the pleasure, double the intensity, now she wants a 3-way with Ash Hollywood because girls are more gentle and will ease her into double penetration - Ash buckles on her strap-on for the job and pleases Stella with anal - enter Pablo Ferrari, right into her pussy for a lovely DP. Then it's Pablo's turn for anal with the hungry girl, doggy style. Ash finally removes the strap-on so Stella can lick her shaved pussy and get it ready for Pablo's dick. The three just keep going at it until Pablo explodes all over Stella's sweet pussy, so Ash can lick it up! Yum!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Film</category>
<category lang="fr">Pornographie</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>-18</value><icon src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/2/2d/Moins18.svg/200px-Moins18.svg.png" /></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230513090000 +0200" stop="20230513092200 +0200" channel="PenthousePassion.fr">
<title lang="fr">My Black Masseuse</title>
<desc lang="fr">Vanessa (Vega) is a tattoo artist who just worked a whole day on her client's back and she's exhausted. Her grateful client treats her to a massage with Jax (Slayher) who's been told to give her the &quot;full package!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Film</category>
<category lang="fr">Pornographie</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>-18</value><icon src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/2/2d/Moins18.svg/200px-Moins18.svg.png" /></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230513092200 +0200" stop="20230513094100 +0200" channel="PenthousePassion.fr">
<title lang="fr">Euro Girls Love Black Dick</title>
<desc lang="fr">Darrell (Deeps) has planned a special birthday surprise for his friend CJ (CJaybangz), and her name is Angelika (Grays)! This beautiful Ukrainian blonde is more than happy to accommodate both friends… together!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Film</category>
<category lang="fr">Pornographie</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>-18</value><icon src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/2/2d/Moins18.svg/200px-Moins18.svg.png" /></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230513094100 +0200" stop="20230513100000 +0200" channel="PenthousePassion.fr">
<title lang="fr">Family Cums First</title>
<desc lang="fr">Jerome Brown (Dillon Cox) has some one on one time with his foxy step mom, Mrs. White (Alana Cruise), when he expresses that he feels funny down in the sac, every time he sees her. The two make love in the master bedroom and Mrs. White shows why Jerome's father married her. A quick hint, she knows how to handle a black man's cock, especially, when she's getting it wet with her mouth.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Film</category>
<category lang="fr">Pornographie</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>-18</value><icon src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/2/2d/Moins18.svg/200px-Moins18.svg.png" /></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230513100000 +0200" stop="20230513102400 +0200" channel="PenthousePassion.fr">
<title lang="fr">I'm Banging My Big Butt Stepmom</title>
<desc lang="fr">Peter (Green) is home alone. Now he can watch porn and jerk off in the living room without being bothered, at least until his stepmom (Rose Monroe) comes home and interrupts. She's amused but understands he hasn't finished and that that is important, so she offers her beautiful round butt to help him take it to completion!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Film</category>
<category lang="fr">Pornographie</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>-18</value><icon src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/2/2d/Moins18.svg/200px-Moins18.svg.png" /></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230513102400 +0200" stop="20230513104500 +0200" channel="PenthousePassion.fr">
<title lang="fr">MILFs Desperate for Dick</title>
<desc lang="fr">Amber's (Jayne) been waiting all day for her husband's package to be delivered and she's getting fed up, in fact she's fed up with her husband too, who's going to be late again. All this waiting, waiting for what?! Then there's a knock at the door….salvation! Mugur has arrived to deliver! And boy does he! In the kitchen, on the counter, on the table, in the pussy, and in her mouth! A desperate MILF's delivery dream!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Film</category>
<category lang="fr">Pornographie</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>-18</value><icon src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/2/2d/Moins18.svg/200px-Moins18.svg.png" /></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230513104500 +0200" stop="20230513110000 +0200" channel="PenthousePassion.fr">
<title lang="fr">Bra Bustin Babes</title>
<desc lang="fr">Sasha/Tammy's boyfriend, Chris cheats on her and she always takes him back. Admittedly, she writes, the thought of him with another woman turns her on and she loves making him beg for forgiveness. Forgiveness comes in the form of erotic fun. All is forgiven…for now.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Film</category>
<category lang="fr">Pornographie</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>-18</value><icon src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/2/2d/Moins18.svg/200px-Moins18.svg.png" /></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230513110000 +0200" stop="20230513111400 +0200" channel="PenthousePassion.fr">
<title lang="fr">Supreme Vixens</title>
<desc lang="fr">Kenna James likes to collect photos and videos of her girlfriends having sex. She's got an incriminating video on Britney, who Annie has fucked, that could get her in a lot of trouble with her husband…Or she can pay Kenna and have the video erased. Kenna also likes what she saw on the video and wants a sample of Britney herself before she releases the incriminating evidence. Britney is hesitant at first, but warms up… a lot once she gets going!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Film</category>
<category lang="fr">Pornographie</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>-18</value><icon src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/2/2d/Moins18.svg/200px-Moins18.svg.png" /></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230513111400 +0200" stop="20230513114500 +0200" channel="PenthousePassion.fr">
<title lang="fr">The Fetish Spa</title>
<desc lang="fr">Aubrey Black and Adreena Winters, dressed in latex, lace, fishnets and tall black boots are two dirty hotties who cannot stop exploring each other's mouths and bodies. These two love to suck nipples, pussy munch, and scissors themselves (and me) into a hot frenzy!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Film</category>
<category lang="fr">Pornographie</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>-18</value><icon src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/2/2d/Moins18.svg/200px-Moins18.svg.png" /></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230513114500 +0200" stop="20230513120100 +0200" channel="PenthousePassion.fr">
<title lang="fr">Lesbians at Work</title>
<desc lang="fr">Karlee Grey is looking for a house and hot Jayden Cole is her realtor. Karlee's having a tough time making up her mind about which house to purchase and when the subject is brought up, suggests maybe if they became intimate her trust issues would disappear. Sounds insanely sane to me! And thank goodness Jayden knows where the homeowner keeps toys! With the trust walls broken by fingers, tongues and toys I think Jayden just sold a house!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Film</category>
<category lang="fr">Pornographie</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>-18</value><icon src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/2/2d/Moins18.svg/200px-Moins18.svg.png" /></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230513120100 +0200" stop="20230513134300 +0200" channel="PenthousePassion.fr">
<title lang="fr">Teen Massage</title>
<desc lang="fr">Teens and massages! I can't think of a better combination for dirty sexy fun, especially with teens who are looking to get a job in the business and need a little &quot;demonstration&quot; of what the client will be expecting! Teens are open to anything… that's not work!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Film</category>
<category lang="fr">Pornographie</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>-18</value><icon src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/2/2d/Moins18.svg/200px-Moins18.svg.png" /></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230513134300 +0200" stop="20230513140000 +0200" channel="PenthousePassion.fr">
<title lang="fr">Penthouse Pets' Dirty Desires</title>
<desc lang="fr">Miss Moody surprises her lover, Marica with an anniversary cake, but Marica wants more than sweets. She has a taste for lust and wants the icing cumming out of Miss Moody's pussy.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Film</category>
<category lang="fr">Pornographie</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>-18</value><icon src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/2/2d/Moins18.svg/200px-Moins18.svg.png" /></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230513140000 +0200" stop="20230513151800 +0200" channel="PenthousePassion.fr">
<title lang="fr">Big Titty MILF Massage</title>
<desc lang="fr">These busty women need more than a massage! They need trained, skilled hands run all over their hungry naked bodies, followed by young strong dick in their pussy. Sounds like a perfect big titty MILF massage… with a happy ending!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Film</category>
<category lang="fr">Pornographie</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>-18</value><icon src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/2/2d/Moins18.svg/200px-Moins18.svg.png" /></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230513151800 +0200" stop="20230513153200 +0200" channel="PenthousePassion.fr">
<title lang="fr">DPs in Uniform</title>
<desc lang="fr">Naughty girls Billie Star and Jennifer Mendez, are pulling a home burglary! Officer Erik Everhard catches them and realizes it's Billie again who once more does not want to go to jail! He tells her to figure out a way to convince his colleagues (Josh, Thomas Stone). These girls know just the trick!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Film</category>
<category lang="fr">Pornographie</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>-18</value><icon src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/2/2d/Moins18.svg/200px-Moins18.svg.png" /></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230513153200 +0200" stop="20230513154500 +0200" channel="PenthousePassion.fr">
<title lang="fr">He's My Stepdaddy</title>
<desc lang="fr">Lexi Lore is caught practicing how to strip by her step father, Jay Smooth, but when she gets asked to help her practice and he accepts, it turns into more than just a practice session. Lets just hope her mom doesn't find out!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Film</category>
<category lang="fr">Pornographie</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>-18</value><icon src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/2/2d/Moins18.svg/200px-Moins18.svg.png" /></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230513154500 +0200" stop="20230513160000 +0200" channel="PenthousePassion.fr">
<title lang="fr">Below the Belt</title>
<desc lang="fr">Hilary's (Gabbie Carter) finally found her mojo and she's all about doing it! First she does it to Alexa, then to Brandon, and then, opps!, she does it to Galahad (Damon Dice)! She didn't mean to do it with a closed fist to Galahad, she meant to do it with spread open legs, knocking him out with her big boobs and wet pussy! She succeeds in the most naughty way and quickly they both &quot;go down&quot; for the count!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Film</category>
<category lang="fr">Pornographie</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>-18</value><icon src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/2/2d/Moins18.svg/200px-Moins18.svg.png" /></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230513160000 +0200" stop="20230513162300 +0200" channel="PenthousePassion.fr">
<title lang="fr">Avery Black and Friends Love Black Cock</title>
<desc lang="fr">Alex (Coal) is getting wet panties wondering how big her teacher's (Isiah Maxwell) cock really is and how it tastes. He actually does see some potential in her and invites her over to his place to help discover and expose that potential!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Film</category>
<category lang="fr">Pornographie</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>-18</value><icon src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/2/2d/Moins18.svg/200px-Moins18.svg.png" /></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230513162300 +0200" stop="20230513164300 +0200" channel="PenthousePassion.fr">
<title lang="fr">Guilty Pleasures</title>
<desc lang="fr">Alexis needs money and tries to get work at a strip club, but she doesn't perform well with a stripper pole. Mugur, the manager, tries to show her how to dance, but she still doesn't get it, and she still needs the money. Mugur has one more way she can pass the audition using moves Alexis is very good at, you go girl!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Film</category>
<category lang="fr">Pornographie</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>-18</value><icon src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/2/2d/Moins18.svg/200px-Moins18.svg.png" /></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230513164300 +0200" stop="20230513170000 +0200" channel="PenthousePassion.fr">
<title lang="fr">My Black Man Obsession</title>
<desc lang="fr">Kiara (Lord) is showing Joss (Lescaf) a place he might rent. It's hot today and Kiara lets Joss know it's okay to take his shirt off. He's even more comfortable once he takes out his BBC and negotiations get interesting!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Film</category>
<category lang="fr">Pornographie</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>-18</value><icon src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/2/2d/Moins18.svg/200px-Moins18.svg.png" /></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230513170000 +0200" stop="20230513172000 +0200" channel="PenthousePassion.fr">
<title lang="fr">Mommy has Big Big Boobs</title>
<desc lang="fr">Timmy (Juan &quot;El Caballo&quot; Loco) has been called over to his hot MILF neighbor's (Linzee Ryder) house under the pretense of trying on some shorts, but he thinks the sex thirsty woman likes him and is trying to get into his pants. She is, but her fast approach freaks him out. He says he'd feel better if she'd just slow down. That's exactly what she does, she takes his cock in her mouth nice… and slow… yup, much better!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Film</category>
<category lang="fr">Pornographie</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>-18</value><icon src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/2/2d/Moins18.svg/200px-Moins18.svg.png" /></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230513172000 +0200" stop="20230513173900 +0200" channel="PenthousePassion.fr">
<title lang="fr">4Way Lovers</title>
<desc lang="fr">Vince (Karter) is fooling around with his secretary, Kaisa (Nord), and his wife, Cherry (Kiss) is fooling around with her trainer, Darrell (Deeps). Upon the discover they both have revenge fucks... together!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Film</category>
<category lang="fr">Pornographie</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>-18</value><icon src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/2/2d/Moins18.svg/200px-Moins18.svg.png" /></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230513173900 +0200" stop="20230513180000 +0200" channel="PenthousePassion.fr">
<title lang="fr">Interracial Cuckold</title>
<desc lang="fr">Jon Jon gets a surprise favor from his yoga client, Carmen Valentina, who wants to play with his dick while her husband watches.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Film</category>
<category lang="fr">Pornographie</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>-18</value><icon src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/2/2d/Moins18.svg/200px-Moins18.svg.png" /></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230513180000 +0200" stop="20230513190500 +0200" channel="PenthousePassion.fr">
<title lang="fr">Gianna Dior and Friends Love Big Dick</title>
<desc lang="fr">Gianna Dior and her friends are sensational cock teasers! These delicious tarts titillate with a sexy striptease before diving headfirst into a big cock, purely for their own slutty satisfaction!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Téléfilm</category>
<category lang="fr">Pornographie</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>-18</value><icon src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/2/2d/Moins18.svg/200px-Moins18.svg.png" /></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230513190500 +0200" stop="20230513192000 +0200" channel="PenthousePassion.fr">
<title lang="fr">Sexy Work Fantasies</title>
<desc lang="fr">Policewoman, Layla (Price) is talking to her partner, Ricky (Mancini) about a suspect in a swinger's club. She reveals she's done that before and is getting wet just thinking about her experiences... it might be Ricky's lucky day!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Téléfilm</category>
<category lang="fr">Pornographie</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>-18</value><icon src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/2/2d/Moins18.svg/200px-Moins18.svg.png" /></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230513192000 +0200" stop="20230513193900 +0200" channel="PenthousePassion.fr">
<title lang="fr">The Art of Seduction</title>
<desc lang="fr">Olive is inspired by the party and asks Ryan to come home early the next night, she has a little surprise for him. The surprise is Casey! As Olive watches Casey and Ryan fuck she plays with herself! Ryan licks pussy, gets a BJ, cowgirl, reverse cowgirl, doggy and mish before they all reach climax!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Film</category>
<category lang="fr">Pornographie</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>-18</value><icon src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/2/2d/Moins18.svg/200px-Moins18.svg.png" /></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230513193900 +0200" stop="20230513200000 +0200" channel="PenthousePassion.fr">
<title lang="fr">My Best Friend's Mom Swallows</title>
<desc lang="fr">Delivery boy, Ricky (Spanish), is having trouble with his girlfriend when he's delivering a package to sexy MILF, Kit Mercer. She invites him in to tell her what's wrong and discovers he's frustrated because his girlfriend won't have sex with him. But Kit and her kitty know just how to take care of a frustrated Ricky!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Film</category>
<category lang="fr">Pornographie</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>-18</value><icon src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/2/2d/Moins18.svg/200px-Moins18.svg.png" /></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230513200000 +0200" stop="20230513202300 +0200" channel="PenthousePassion.fr">
<title lang="fr">White Girls Like It Dark</title>
<desc lang="fr">Adira (Allure) has been especially naughty trying to get her stepfather's (Prince Yahshua) attention, but so far nothing has worked. She's very interested in seeing that BBC she's sure is hidden in his pants. Mom's out of town and today she's determined to succeed!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Film</category>
<category lang="fr">Pornographie</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>-18</value><icon src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/2/2d/Moins18.svg/200px-Moins18.svg.png" /></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230513202300 +0200" stop="20230513204300 +0200" channel="PenthousePassion.fr">
<title lang="fr">My Teenage Stepdaughter</title>
<desc lang="fr">After getting stood up on a date with his wife, Tyler Steel gets a surprise comfort from his step daughter, Brooke Haze. She thinks her vagina will make him feel better. Going into various positions Brooke makes sure she stays wet.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Film</category>
<category lang="fr">Pornographie</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>-18</value><icon src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/2/2d/Moins18.svg/200px-Moins18.svg.png" /></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230513204300 +0200" stop="20230513210000 +0200" channel="PenthousePassion.fr">
<title lang="fr">Stella Cox Nymphomaniac</title>
<desc lang="fr">Two cocks at once for Stella Cox means double the pleasure, double the intensity, now she wants a 3-way with Ash Hollywood because girls are more gentle and will ease her into double penetration - Ash buckles on her strap-on for the job and pleases Stella with anal - enter Pablo Ferrari, right into her pussy for a lovely DP. Then it's Pablo's turn for anal with the hungry girl, doggy style. Ash finally removes the strap-on so Stella can lick her shaved pussy and get it ready for Pablo's dick. The three just keep going at it until Pablo explodes all over Stella's sweet pussy, so Ash can lick it up! Yum!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Film</category>
<category lang="fr">Pornographie</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>-18</value><icon src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/2/2d/Moins18.svg/200px-Moins18.svg.png" /></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230513210000 +0200" stop="20230513212200 +0200" channel="PenthousePassion.fr">
<title lang="fr">My Black Masseuse</title>
<desc lang="fr">Vanessa (Vega) is a tattoo artist who just worked a whole day on her client's back and she's exhausted. Her grateful client treats her to a massage with Jax (Slayher) who's been told to give her the &quot;full package!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Film</category>
<category lang="fr">Pornographie</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>-18</value><icon src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/2/2d/Moins18.svg/200px-Moins18.svg.png" /></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230513212200 +0200" stop="20230513214100 +0200" channel="PenthousePassion.fr">
<title lang="fr">Euro Girls Love Black Dick</title>
<desc lang="fr">Darrell (Deeps) has planned a special birthday surprise for his friend CJ (CJaybangz), and her name is Angelika (Grays)! This beautiful Ukrainian blonde is more than happy to accommodate both friends… together!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Film</category>
<category lang="fr">Pornographie</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>-18</value><icon src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/2/2d/Moins18.svg/200px-Moins18.svg.png" /></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230513214100 +0200" stop="20230513220000 +0200" channel="PenthousePassion.fr">
<title lang="fr">Family Cums First</title>
<desc lang="fr">Jerome Brown (Dillon Cox) has some one on one time with his foxy step mom, Mrs. White (Alana Cruise), when he expresses that he feels funny down in the sac, every time he sees her. The two make love in the master bedroom and Mrs. White shows why Jerome's father married her. A quick hint, she knows how to handle a black man's cock, especially, when she's getting it wet with her mouth.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Film</category>
<category lang="fr">Pornographie</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>-18</value><icon src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/2/2d/Moins18.svg/200px-Moins18.svg.png" /></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230513220000 +0200" stop="20230513222400 +0200" channel="PenthousePassion.fr">
<title lang="fr">I'm Banging My Big Butt Stepmom</title>
<desc lang="fr">Peter (Green) is home alone. Now he can watch porn and jerk off in the living room without being bothered, at least until his stepmom (Rose Monroe) comes home and interrupts. She's amused but understands he hasn't finished and that that is important, so she offers her beautiful round butt to help him take it to completion!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Film</category>
<category lang="fr">Pornographie</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>-18</value><icon src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/2/2d/Moins18.svg/200px-Moins18.svg.png" /></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230513222400 +0200" stop="20230513224500 +0200" channel="PenthousePassion.fr">
<title lang="fr">MILFs Desperate for Dick</title>
<desc lang="fr">Amber's (Jayne) been waiting all day for her husband's package to be delivered and she's getting fed up, in fact she's fed up with her husband too, who's going to be late again. All this waiting, waiting for what?! Then there's a knock at the door….salvation! Mugur has arrived to deliver! And boy does he! In the kitchen, on the counter, on the table, in the pussy, and in her mouth! A desperate MILF's delivery dream!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Film</category>
<category lang="fr">Pornographie</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>-18</value><icon src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/2/2d/Moins18.svg/200px-Moins18.svg.png" /></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230513224500 +0200" stop="20230513230000 +0200" channel="PenthousePassion.fr">
<title lang="fr">Bra Bustin Babes</title>
<desc lang="fr">Sasha/Tammy's boyfriend, Chris cheats on her and she always takes him back. Admittedly, she writes, the thought of him with another woman turns her on and she loves making him beg for forgiveness. Forgiveness comes in the form of erotic fun. All is forgiven…for now.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Film</category>
<category lang="fr">Pornographie</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>-18</value><icon src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/2/2d/Moins18.svg/200px-Moins18.svg.png" /></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230513230000 +0200" stop="20230513231400 +0200" channel="PenthousePassion.fr">
<title lang="fr">Supreme Vixens</title>
<desc lang="fr">Kenna James likes to collect photos and videos of her girlfriends having sex. She's got an incriminating video on Britney, who Annie has fucked, that could get her in a lot of trouble with her husband…Or she can pay Kenna and have the video erased. Kenna also likes what she saw on the video and wants a sample of Britney herself before she releases the incriminating evidence. Britney is hesitant at first, but warms up… a lot once she gets going!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Film</category>
<category lang="fr">Pornographie</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>-18</value><icon src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/2/2d/Moins18.svg/200px-Moins18.svg.png" /></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230513231400 +0200" stop="20230513234500 +0200" channel="PenthousePassion.fr">
<title lang="fr">The Fetish Spa</title>
<desc lang="fr">Aubrey Black and Adreena Winters, dressed in latex, lace, fishnets and tall black boots are two dirty hotties who cannot stop exploring each other's mouths and bodies. These two love to suck nipples, pussy munch, and scissors themselves (and me) into a hot frenzy!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Film</category>
<category lang="fr">Pornographie</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>-18</value><icon src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/2/2d/Moins18.svg/200px-Moins18.svg.png" /></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230513234500 +0200" stop="20230514000000 +0200" channel="PenthousePassion.fr">
<title lang="fr">Lesbians at Work</title>
<desc lang="fr">Karlee Grey is looking for a house and hot Jayden Cole is her realtor. Karlee's having a tough time making up her mind about which house to purchase and when the subject is brought up, suggests maybe if they became intimate her trust issues would disappear. Sounds insanely sane to me! And thank goodness Jayden knows where the homeowner keeps toys! With the trust walls broken by fingers, tongues and toys I think Jayden just sold a house!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Film</category>
<category lang="fr">Pornographie</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>-18</value><icon src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/2/2d/Moins18.svg/200px-Moins18.svg.png" /></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230514000000 +0200" stop="20230514011500 +0200" channel="PenthousePassion.fr">
<title lang="fr">Reform School Girls</title>
<desc lang="fr">Reform School Academy holds the naughtiest teens that love to get into trouble and it's up to a few busty MILFs to set them straight. A bossy teen flirts with her dean to get her own room, a manipulator tries to get out of detention, a princess gets it on with her lawyer and two lovely roommates make each other comfortable while no instructors are around. This is Reform School Girls, beautiful babes, uniforms and hot girl on girl action! Class is now in session.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Film</category>
<category lang="fr">Pornographie</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>-18</value><icon src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/2/2d/Moins18.svg/200px-Moins18.svg.png" /></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230514011500 +0200" stop="20230514012800 +0200" channel="PenthousePassion.fr">
<title lang="fr">Big Titty Secretary Seductions</title>
<desc lang="fr">Ellen (McKenzie Lee) is afraid she's getting fired and begs Steve (Brad Sterling) to let her keep her job! She'll even get down on her knees… hmmm… with her big breasts peeking through, Brad likes the sound of that, naughty girl!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Film</category>
<category lang="fr">Pornographie</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>-18</value><icon src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/2/2d/Moins18.svg/200px-Moins18.svg.png" /></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230514012800 +0200" stop="20230514014600 +0200" channel="PenthousePassion.fr">
<title lang="fr">Beach Blonde Booty</title>
<desc lang="fr">Tony (Rubino) has brought Sloan (Harper) to a private beach, and Sloan loves being naked! Lucky Tony gets to bury his face in between her ample booty which only gets Sloan asking for more... much more!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Film</category>
<category lang="fr">Pornographie</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>-18</value><icon src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/2/2d/Moins18.svg/200px-Moins18.svg.png" /></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230514014600 +0200" stop="20230514020000 +0200" channel="PenthousePassion.fr">
<title lang="fr">Teacher's Pet</title>
<desc lang="fr">Stella can only think of sex. Nothing makes her hornier than dreaming that two of her teachers might give it to her. Just thinking about it makes her panties wet. Instructors George and Clarke aim to please their student! And please her and themselves they do! One on her young shaved pussy and another over her lovely soft breasts!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Film</category>
<category lang="fr">Pornographie</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>-18</value><icon src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/2/2d/Moins18.svg/200px-Moins18.svg.png" /></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230514020000 +0200" stop="20230514033000 +0200" channel="PenthousePassion.fr">
<title lang="fr">Dark Confessions</title>
<desc lang="fr">Honey Gold loves the sound of her roommate and her boyfriend, Logan Long, banging each other out, but when she meets Logan upfront and confesses to him about a threesome, Honey wants to test drive his stick to see what he's all about.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Film</category>
<category lang="fr">Pornographie</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>-18</value><icon src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/2/2d/Moins18.svg/200px-Moins18.svg.png" /></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230514033000 +0200" stop="20230514034400 +0200" channel="PenthousePassion.fr">
<title lang="fr">Stepmommy Screws Best</title>
<desc lang="fr">Robby Echo makes moves on his low self-esteem step-mother, Lexi Foxy, and makes sure she gets the attention she deserves. Thus, Lexi goes all out on her step son as she blows him so far, he busts in her mouth and her vagina from the back.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Film</category>
<category lang="fr">Pornographie</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>-18</value><icon src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/2/2d/Moins18.svg/200px-Moins18.svg.png" /></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230514034400 +0200" stop="20230514040000 +0200" channel="PenthousePassion.fr">
<title lang="fr">Young Innocent College Sluts</title>
<desc lang="fr">Scarlit's (Scandal) parents feel she needs a tutor; however, she doesn't think so. But Jay (Romero) is cute, smart and making Scarlit horny! Now she realizes what she just might need a tutor for! This time the student's going to be teaching the teacher… and it's nothing you'll learn in school!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Film</category>
<category lang="fr">Pornographie</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>-18</value><icon src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/2/2d/Moins18.svg/200px-Moins18.svg.png" /></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230514040000 +0200" stop="20230514042200 +0200" channel="PenthousePassion.fr">
<title lang="fr">Hot Sweaty Workout Sex</title>
<desc lang="fr">Stacy (Cruz) warms up for her morning run when Mugur joins her. After an energizing workout, she invites him up to her place to &quot;cool down!&quot; And it's hot!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Téléfilm</category>
<category lang="fr">Pornographie</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>-18</value><icon src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/2/2d/Moins18.svg/200px-Moins18.svg.png" /></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230514042200 +0200" stop="20230514044500 +0200" channel="PenthousePassion.fr">
<title lang="fr">Screwed in the Office</title>
<desc lang="fr">Kinuski's boyfriend, Thomas Stone, suggests a &quot;quickie&quot; in the office despite her fear that her boss, Vince Karter, may come in. Once they reach the point of &quot;no return&quot; she makes him leave knowing her boss is coming. Hoping to distract Vince from his suspicions that &quot;something doesn't smell right&quot; she works her sexy charms on him! He goes for it, until Thomas returns, then they ALL go for it!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Film</category>
<category lang="fr">Pornographie</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>-18</value><icon src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/2/2d/Moins18.svg/200px-Moins18.svg.png" /></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230514044500 +0200" stop="20230514050000 +0200" channel="PenthousePassion.fr">
<title lang="fr">Screwing My Daddy's BFF</title>
<desc lang="fr">Anastasia gets grumpy when her secret lover Donnie Rock doesn't bother calling her after their first sexual encounter but makes up for it when she surprises Donnie in her red lingerie onesie. It's like their first experience all over again.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Film</category>
<category lang="fr">Pornographie</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>-18</value><icon src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/2/2d/Moins18.svg/200px-Moins18.svg.png" /></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230514050000 +0200" stop="20230514051700 +0200" channel="PenthousePassion.fr">
<title lang="fr">Office Sexual Therapy</title>
<desc lang="fr">Bella had been a nice experience for Leyla (Amber Nevada) but she discovered that 'wasn't her' and before the weekend is over she knows there is one last task she needs to do... Leo (Tyler Nixon)!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Film</category>
<category lang="fr">Pornographie</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>-18</value><icon src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/2/2d/Moins18.svg/200px-Moins18.svg.png" /></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230514051700 +0200" stop="20230514054100 +0200" channel="PenthousePassion.fr">
<title lang="fr">Appetizer Before Sex</title>
<desc lang="fr">Nelly Kent' guy has cheated on her and she wants payback, so she's invited her guy's brother (Maximo Garcia) over to record a video of her masturbating and... a revenge fuck!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Téléfilm</category>
<category lang="fr">Pornographie</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>-18</value><icon src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/2/2d/Moins18.svg/200px-Moins18.svg.png" /></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230514054100 +0200" stop="20230514060000 +0200" channel="PenthousePassion.fr">
<title lang="fr">The Masseur Banged Me</title>
<desc lang="fr">Alexis (Tae) has been working out a lot and is in need of a massage, especially on her butt! Fortunately, Charles (Dera) is a &quot;glutes specialist!&quot; As a specialist he intends to dive very seriously into the problem area!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Film</category>
<category lang="fr">Pornographie</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>-18</value><icon src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/2/2d/Moins18.svg/200px-Moins18.svg.png" /></rating>
</programme>