<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Bouygues -->
<programme start="20230517054600 +0200" stop="20230517065100 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Caixa Cubo - Da Pá Virada Sessions</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Hamilton e Laginha</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr"> The Da Pá Virada Sessions series portrays the best musicians in Brazilian jazz today. All sessions were recorded in São Paulo and offer a unique experience: they offer a fresh look at the Brazilian music scene. The artists have been selected together with the music editor of Stingray DJAZZ. One of the musical collaborations that can be seen in this series is the duo of Hamilton de Holanda and Mário Laginha. Grammy nominee De Holanda, who has given the ten-string mandolin a new place in Brazilian music, is entering into a collaboration with pianist Mário Laginha. Together they perform gems of Brazilian music that will make the viewer's heart beat faster.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230517065100 +0200" stop="20230517075000 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Nile Rodgers</title>
<desc lang="fr">The popular music performance series Front and Center premiered nationwide on public television in 2016, and now returns for Season 6. The series boasts 22, one-hour episodes and an all-star line-up. This episode features Nile Rodgers. He started his musical career by the end of the '60s. A decade later, he scored a hit with Chic's debut single &quot;Dance Dance Dance,&quot; followed by &quot;Le Freak&quot; from the second album C'est Chic. At Front and Center, Nile Rodgers performs his most well-known songs such as &quot;Get Lucky&quot; and &quot;We Are Family.&quot; In between the songs, Nile Rodgers shares personal stories about his dreams and how they have come true. Enjoy this intimate Front and Center show!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Pop &amp; Rock</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230517075000 +0200" stop="20230517090000 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Liam Gallagher</title>
<desc lang="fr">Liam Gallagher - After leading iconic British rock band Oasis for nearly two decades, Manchester-born singer Liam Gallagher launched his solo career in 2016. He played his first ever U.S. solo show on July 28th of 2017 at Manhattan's McKittrick Hotel in New York City. The rather small venue is known to host the immersive theater experience &quot;Sleep No More&quot;, and its limited capacities made for an intense and intimate concert experience. In a 75-minute long show featuring thirteen songs, Gallagher performed tracks of his 2017 debut album As You Were, next to a list of Oasis fan favorites. Shot in phenomenally sharp 4K, this recording offers viewers the unique opportunity to become part of the audience of this secret session.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230517090000 +0200" stop="20230517101700 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Bixiga 70 - BIRD 2019</title>
<desc lang="fr">Bixiga 70 - BIRD 2019 - Stemming from Brazil's São Paulo, Bixiga 70 is an exciting brass and percussion-based instrumental dance ensemble that combines jazz, funk, and Afro-Brazilian music, incorporating elements from dub, reggae, electronics, cumbia, carimbo, Ethio-jazz, and samba. The name Bixiga 70 is taken from a vibrant neighbourhood in downtown São Paulo. Organic, ritualistic, and sometimes even primal, the band's music appeals to those who seek out mental and physical freedom.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230517101700 +0200" stop="20230517110000 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Null + Void</title>
<desc lang="fr">Null + Void - While few people are familiar with the Null + Void project, many have already heard Kurt Uenala's music. After making his debut under the pseudonym Kap10Kurt in 2003, Uenala caught the attention of the world with the play &quot;Die Sleeping&quot;. This critical and popular success has led to collaborations with several big names in music, including Moby, The Kills, and Dave Gahan, singer of Depeche Mode, for whom Uenala has subsequently signed plays. Spending more and more time in his Manhattan studio, Uenala developed a unique sound made of angular beats and dark soundscapes, which gave rise to a new melancholy solo project called Null + Void. Cryosleep, Uenala's first album under this new banner, includes several titles inspired by retro science fiction, new wave and electronic innovators.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Pop &amp; Rock</category>
<icon src="https://img.bouygtel.fr/CMS/images/6032631D9A9B66AA23AC475B29DC2EEF.jpg" />
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230517110000 +0200" stop="20230517115500 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Music Meeting</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Oum 2018</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Oum - Music Meeting Festival 2018 - Oum El Ghait Benessahraoui, who is better known as Oum, gives a unique glance at ethnic Morrocan musical esthetics. The singer-songwriter is considered to be the ambassador of Morrocan culture, too. Deeply influenced by gospel, jazz, soul and R&amp;B genres, today Oum mixes more and more African music genres, such as Sufi, Hassani, or Afrobeat. Yet, the singer's voice still echoes the colours of Aretha Franklin, Ella Fitzgerald or Whitney Houston. It is the African American vocal tradition that made a huge impact on Oum since her early days as the singer. Performing from Music Meeting Festival in Nijmegen, The Netherlands, Oum charms the stage with an exotic sonic journey to the undiscovered lands of North Africa.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230517115500 +0200" stop="20230517133100 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Dickey Betts</title>
<desc lang="fr">Dickey Betts - Calling Dickey Betts the second guitarist in the Allman Brothers Band does him a disservice. After the tragic death of Duane Allman in 1971, Betts became co-captain with Gregg Allman, leading the group through ups and downs over the decades. Known as one of the most influential guitar players of all time, Betts has mastered a seamless style of lyrical melody and rhythm — marrying country, jazz, blues, and rock into one sound. Betts has one of the most distinctive voices in music today, and on July 21, 2018, he brought down the house at the St. George's Theatre in Staten Island. Catch him performing the legendary Allman Brothers songs!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Pop &amp; Rock</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230517133100 +0200" stop="20230517141300 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Nelida Karr : Womex 2018</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Nelida Karr</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">One of the participants in 2018 was Nelida Karr, who not only sings and plays the guitar, but also takes care of piano, cello and percussion. Her own compositions are brimming with the many cultural influences she acquired during her childhood in Malabo.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<icon src="https://img.bouygtel.fr/CMS/images/BD1A4F239A69EC884BEAFFB08B575969.jpg" />
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230517141300 +0200" stop="20230517150200 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Classical:NEXT 2019</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Clarinet Factory</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Classical:NEXT 2019 - Clarinet Factory - Considered to be one of the most unique ensembles to feature on the Czech scene in the last 25 years, the style of the Clarinet Factory hovers between contemporary and classical music, jazz and world music. As winners of the Classic Prague Awards in 2017 for 'Best Crossover Project', the quartet combines their classic music training and clarinet art with jazz, minimalism and improvisation to create their very own music without borders, capable of communicating directly with all audiences. The Clarinet Factory also experiment with electronics, both ambient and dance-oriented, and the four musicians remain ever fascinated with the possibilities of their instrument, considering their work as a music laboratory.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Classique</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230517150200 +0200" stop="20230517160400 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Caixa Cubo - Da Pá Virada Sessions</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Paulo Novaes - New Year's Eve Special</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Paulo Novaes - New Year's Eve Special - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the artists taking part in this series is Paulo Novaes. Coming from a family of musicians, Paulo Novaes has already lived through a lifetime of music in spite of his young age. Paulo is the cousin of singer Bruna Caram, with whom he performed in São Paulo, Madrid, Barcelona, Lisbon, and other major cities. As a singer, composer, and instrumentalist, his creativity is enjoyed in many forms.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230517160400 +0200" stop="20230517170600 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Kintsugi</title>
<desc lang="fr">Kintsugi - Kintsugi is made up of three musicians whose eclectic musical backgrounds mix Japanese stories drawn from the depths of time: the epic life of Yoshitsune, sung and played by Kakushin Nishihara, a Tokyo sub-modern and underground artist : the incredible collision between Serge Teyssot-Gay's electric guitar (Noir Désir), Gaspar Claus' cello and the indescribable art of the Japanese Kakushin Nishihara, traditional biwa virtuoso and shamanic singer.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Pop &amp; Rock</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230517170600 +0200" stop="20230517183300 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Avishai Cohen's Big Vicious</title>
<desc lang="fr">Avishai Cohen's Big Vicious - The phrasing and the pure and feverish sound of Israeli trumpeter Avishai Cohen, adopted New Yorker, make him a respected and beloved breath of the contemporary jazz scene. Inspired leader, he summons here an astonishing instrumental ensemble with two drummers and two guitarists. This musical bias allows him to freely combine the rock spirit of Jimi Hendrix with the electric jazz of Miles Davis. The result is an unprecedented fusion that is as innovative as it is exciting. Enjoy Avishai Cohen's &quot;Big Vicious&quot; show at Jazz sous les pommiers 2019.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230517183300 +0200" stop="20230517192000 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Etenesh Wassie Trio : WOMEX 2018</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Etenesh Wassie Trio</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr"> In 2018 WOMEX took place in Las Palmas in Gran Canaria. One of the participants was the Ethiopian diva Etenesh Wassie with her trio. She mixes the contemporary energy of jazz and punk with her in-depth knowledge of the Ethiopian repertoire. The result is compelling, inspired, and truly unique.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Musique</category>
<category lang="fr">Musicale</category>
<icon src="https://img.bouygtel.fr/CMS/images/A5539A1D83657FE964693E3151A5A56C.jpg" />
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230517192000 +0200" stop="20230517203200 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Chloé - Trabendo Paris</title>
<desc lang="fr">Chloé - Trabendo Paris - Chloé has, without a doubt, led an entire generation to her electronic music playground - one that goes beyond strictly club and techno. As much a film music enthusiast as an accomplished guitar player, she stumbled into the electronic scene early on, developing an unwavering curiosity for sound machines. Chloé is a composer, and she gives life to artistic ideas. The challenge is to stay unwavering in spite of self-doubt that arises throughout the creative process. It is precisely this inner questioning, this contradiction, that nourishes and motivates Chloé's work. Chloé dedicates a full set to her 2017 album Endless Revisions. At Trabendo Paris, she plays these brand-new songs only a few weeks after the album was released.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Pop &amp; Rock</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230517203200 +0200" stop="20230517210000 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Songbook</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Half Moon Run</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Songbook - Half Moon Run - &quot;I never heard anyone say that, and yeah, I know exactly what it means. It has to go in there, this has to be a song.&quot; Every song has its own story, and we all think it's a story we've heard before, but we haven't. Songbook finds and captures these intriguing stories by pulling you into the process of writing and composing. Known for its pristine sound, cinematic 4k video and eye for detail, Songbook live-captured episodes emphasize the paramount importance of quality. It addresses the on-the-spot elements of blending song and location at the right moment. Both the magical location and remarkable music interaction will get the attention they deserve. Simply because Songbook isn't just a live music session, it lives.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230517210000 +0200" stop="20230517220300 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">De La Soul - Garorock</title>
<desc lang="fr">De La Soul - Garorock - There is a packed crowd for this De La Soul set at the 2019 Garorock Festival, and with good reason: they witness an unmissable concert by an incomparable group! Having released regular albums since 1989's 3 Feet High and Rising, the Long Island hip-hop stalwarts of De La Soul have been doing the rounds on a suitably named Gods of Rap tour alongside Public Enemy and the Wu-Tang Clan. With an opening that includes call and response, mic checks and arms waving in the air, the audience gets more than a touch of vintage appeal, something that has led to terms like &quot;heritage rap&quot; being associated with the group. But despite their long and influential career, the De La Soul impact has perennial relevance for much of contemporary music. They pushed boundaries back then and they continue to venture out further.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230517220300 +0200" stop="20230517230600 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Caixa Cubo - Da Pá Virada Sessions</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Quartabe</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr"> The Da Pá Virada Sessions series portrays the best musicians in Brazilian jazz today. All sessions were recorded in São Paulo and offer a unique experience: they offer a fresh look at the Brazilian music scene. The artists have been selected together with the music editor of Stingray DJAZZ. Among the bands featured in this series is Quartabê, a unique Brazilian quartet that draws from a wide variety of influences, including São Paulo's avant-garde movement, free improvisation, pop, and electronic music. Each of these influences is reflected in Quartabê's rousing live performances! Joana Queiroz (tenor saxophone and clarinets), Maria Beraldo Bastos (clarinets), Mariá Portugal (drums), and Chicão (keys) write, arrange, improvise and sing music that is all theirs.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230517230600 +0200" stop="20230518000500 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">The Bloody Beetroots</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Bloody Beetroots - The Bloody Beetroots is the creation of Sir Bob Cornelius Rifo. Inspired by his lifelong love of punk rock and comic books, Rifo unleashed The Bloody Beetroots in late 2006 and has since crafted an intense sound that mixes his classical training, his punk rock obsession, and his passion for electronic music into an edgy rock-meets-dance hybrid sound. In 2019, The Bloody Beetroots released the Heavy EP, which sees Rifo revisiting his classic electro style and features collaborations with Ephwurd and Dr. Fresch, in addition to three new solo originals. Enjoy his show at Nameless Music Festival 2019!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230518000500 +0200" stop="20230518013900 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Jazz à Ramatuelle</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Antonio Faraò</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Jazz à Ramatuelle: Antonio Faraò - In 1998, Antonio Faraò won the prestigious Concours Martial Solal, awarded to him by Herbie Hancock! Since then, this talented Italian jazz pianist has made his mark as a player of elegance and lyricism, which has allowed him to collaborate with the best European and American musicians. On his last album &quot;Evan&quot;, recorded in the United States, he leads an all-star band starring Joe Lovano on tenor saxophone. On a beautiful summer night at the French Jazz à Ramatuelle festival, Faraò performs at the breathtaking Theatre de Verdure in the company of saxophone legend Dave Liebman. With refined ballads, a feline groove, elegance, and lyricism, this musical meeting sparkles - if you watch closely you might even see some bright new stars lighting up in the night sky above Ramatuelle!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230518013900 +0200" stop="20230518030000 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Lalah Hathaway - Sing Jazz 2018</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Lalah Hathaway</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Lalah Hathaway - Sing Jazz 2018 - Winner of five Grammys in four consecutive years, including the Grammy for best R&amp;B album in 2017, Lalah Hathaway is a force impossible to ignore. The American artist has shared the scene with Prince, Snoop Dogg, Stevie Wonder, Anita Baker, Mary J. Blige, Frank Ocean and many others, an irrefutable proof of her keen musical sense and enormous talent. With a 26-year career, Hathaway is still highly sought after by the biggest names in music. See her transform the 2018 Sing Jazz festival scene into a real R&amp;B club, where she flaunts her voice and stage presence out of the ordinary.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<icon src="https://img.bouygtel.fr/CMS/images/6567CF2FB8596434001F28DC7238E322.jpg" />
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230518030000 +0200" stop="20230518041500 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Arnaud Rebotini : Le Trabendo</title>
<desc lang="fr">Arnaud Rebotini - Trabendo Paris - Arnaud Rebotini is one of hexagonal electro's major figures and the founding father of electroclash group Black Strobe. 2017 saw the release of his soundtrack for 120 Beats Per Minute. At the end of this successful year, Rebotini put on an amazing set at Trabendo Paris. Rebotini's show is all but static - his exciting beats are supported by vocals that make the crowd go wild. This show is a feast for the eyes and ears. Enjoy Rebotini's energizing show and high-end visual effects in native 4K!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230518041500 +0200" stop="20230518050100 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Invisible World : WOMEX 2018</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Invisible World</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">One of the participants was the band Invisible World, which operates at the crossroads where Eastern European and Mediterranean influences come together and break new ground. Invisible World is led by the inventive Czech bassist Tomáš Liška, together with the Turkish violinist Efe Turumtay, the Serbian accordionist Nikola Zarić and the Moravian drummer Kamil Slezák.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Musique</category>
<category lang="fr">Musicale</category>
<icon src="https://img.bouygtel.fr/CMS/images/A5539A1D83657FE964693E3151A5A56C.jpg" />
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230518050100 +0200" stop="20230518060100 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Nubiyan Twist : Music Meeting</title>
<desc lang="fr">Nubiyan Twist - Music Meeting - Since 1985, the Dutch city of Nijmegen has been welcoming the International Music Meeting Festival every Pentecost. Ranging from jazz and improvisational music to traditional music and unique crossovers, this adventurous festival is all about musical encounters and international collaborations. In 2019, the band Nubiyan Twist performs at the International Music Meeting Festival. This London-based group operates on the intersection of soul and jazz.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>