<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Bouygues -->
<programme start="20230523060000 +0200" stop="20230523073100 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Banda Magda live at BIRD Rotterdam</title>
<desc lang="fr">Banda Magda: live at BIRD Rotterdam - An irresistible live act, Banda Magda is full of humour, unflagging energy, and quirky sensibility. A tight-knit group of musicians, they turn the songs of Greek-born founder, singer, and composer Magda Giannikou into engaging gems that have taken the band to legendary venues like Carnegie Hall and, for this performance, BIRD Rotterdam. Banda Magda moves from samba to French chanson, Greek folk music to Colombian cumbia and Afro-Peruvian landó. Their songs capture the best of mid-century ballads and cinematic arrangements, drawing from the band's global background and unrestrained musicality. A joy to experience, Banda Magda makes music for a new generation that's been inspired by ones before.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230523073100 +0200" stop="20230523080900 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Classical:NEXT 2019</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Trio Zukan</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Classical:NEXT 2019 - Trio Zukan - In 2014, Trio Zukan emerged from the combination of three uncommon instruments: accordion, percussion and txistu. The repertoire for this instrumental combination was non-existent at the beginning, so its members decided to promote a project with different composers, with the intention of creating a new repertoire. Today, Zukan has commissioned, revised and released more than a dozen pieces by national and international composers such as: María Eugenia Luc, Mikel Chamizo, Isabel Urrutia, Francisco José Domínguez, Vassilis Filippou, etc. The group is one of the most consolidated groups on the contemporary music scene in the Basque Country. They have performed in Quincena Musical Donostia, Bernaola Festival, Musikagileak Circuit, BBVA Cycle and Attacca Basel, among others.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Classique</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230523080900 +0200" stop="20230523090000 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Classical:NEXT 2019</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Jeditah</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Classical:NEXT 2019 - Jeditah - Jeditah is an experimental songwriter, producer and singer from Amsterdam. She works with Brendan Jan Walsh on cello and Jordy Pama on synths and electronics. From an early age on, Jeditah has been immersed in the world of music, travelling with her parents as a music collective. She finds inspiration in the works of acclaimed artists like Björk, James Blake, Laurie Anderson and PJ Harvey. When she began experimenting with making her own music, she first only utilized her own voice, lowering and altering it, and eventually adding electronic beats and synths. With Electric AlleyCat, Jeditah has established her position as a singer and songwriter. In between performing and recording with the band, she creates layered soundscapes from old recordings and homemade samples.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Classique</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230523090000 +0200" stop="20230523101000 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Ricardo Herz Trio : Da Pá Virada Sessions</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Ricardo Herz Trio</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Da Pá Virada sessions bring the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each sessions are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the bands that are taking part in this series are the Ricardo Herz Trio, which consists of Ricardo Herz on violin, Michi Ruzitschka on nylon string guitar, and Pedro Ito on percussions. Band leader Ricardo Herz is a classically-trained musician, who also studied jazz at the prestigious Berklee College of Music.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230523101000 +0200" stop="20230523111100 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Frequencerz @ Airbeat One</title>
<desc lang="fr">Frequencerz @ Airbeat One - Frequencerz is a Dutch hardstyle duo formed by Pepijn Hol and Niels Koster. In 2009, they signed their contract with the Fusion Records label. Since then, they've released a good number of albums, such as Medium Rare, S.T.F.U. / G.T.F.O, and Phaser. With their performances for huge crowds at Defqon.1, Decibel Outdoor, and The Qontinent, they've established themselves as one of the biggest hardstyle acts of today. Their show at the German Airbeat One festival underlines their reputation. Expect nothing but spectacular light shows, non-stop jumpstyle, and a crazy crowd!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230523111100 +0200" stop="20230523124900 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Moderat at Stereolux 2016</title>
<desc lang="fr">Moderat at Stereolux 2016 - Since the German bands Modeselektor (Gernot Bronsert and Sebastian Szary) and Apparat (Sascha Ring) joined forces in 2009, they have been hugely successful as the electronic music supergroup Moderat. In 2012, the formation produced the soundtrack of Xavier Dolan's film Laurence Anyways, released as A New Error. According to Les Inrockuptibles, their album II includes &quot;the rhythmic punch of the one (Modeselektor) and atmospheric finesse of the other (Apparat) combine perfectly.&quot; In 2016, the threesome returned with an eagerly anticipated third album, III, which they present in this program, live on stage at Stereolux in Nantes, France.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230523124900 +0200" stop="20230523133300 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Moonlight Benjamin : WOMEX 2018</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Moonlight Benjamin</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Numerous musicians, booking agents, news agencies and media companies from all over the world have been attending the &quot;World Music Exhibition&quot; World Music Expo (WOMEX) since 1994. Over the years, this music fair has settled in several European cities, including Berlin, Brussels, Marseille, Stockholm, Seville, Cardiff and Budapest. In 2018 WOMEX took place in Las Palmas in Gran Canaria. One of the participants was the Haitian singer Moonlight Benjamin. With her band she mixes voodoo blues, Haitian rock and Creole roll into a swirling brew that is thrilling with exciting riffs and heavy grooves. Her powerful voice and fiery electric guitars do the rest.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Musique</category>
<category lang="fr">Musicale</category>
<icon src="https://img.bouygtel.fr/CMS/images/41EF9581D0AC7362E0307A78095BA3AD.jpg" />
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230523133300 +0200" stop="20230523142700 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Caixa Cubo - Da Pá Virada Sessions</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Os Capoeira</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Os Capoeira - Da Pá Virada Sessions - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the bands taking part in this series is Os Capoeira. This ensemble practices the traditional Brazilian martial art from Bahia it is named after, combining elements of dance, acrobatics, and percussive music. Moreover, Os Capoeira runs a cultural center in São Paulo. Let yourself be inspired by Os Capoeira's unique take on Brazilian culture!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230523142700 +0200" stop="20230523150200 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Classical:NEXT 2019</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">reConvert Project</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Classical:NEXT 2019 - reConvert Project - The concept of percussion has been altered significantly by the evolution of the instrument. The methods of the innovative reConvert Project are unique and dedicated to changing the face of the percussionist world, by working actively with composers such as Georges Aperghis, Simon Steen Andersen, Michael Maierhof and Jorge Sánchez-Chiong and premiering over a dozen works written to help train emerging young composers. The reConvert philosophy is based on the re-examination of the aesthetic use of percussion instruments, where musical discourse is analysed and adapted to their creative needs. With numerous works using unconventional instruments and staging, a whole new experience is created for the listener.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Classique</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230523150200 +0200" stop="20230523163500 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Jazz à Ramatuelle</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Parisien meets Kühn &amp; Portal</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Jazz à Ramatuelle: Parisien meets Kühn &amp; Portal - Since his first appearance at Jazz in Ramatuelle in 2010, saxophonist Émile Parisien has made his mark among the most talented musicians of his generation. On the soprano saxophone, his favorite instrument, he invented a unique lyrical style. As part of his participation in the 2016 edition of Jazz à Ramatuelle, Parisien invited two European jazz legends to join his ensemble: the German pianist Joachim Kühn (*1944) and the legendary multi-instrumentalist Michel Portal (*1935). Over 80 years old, the latter is an incomparable saxophonist, clarinetist and bandoneonist, a musical adventurer who skilfully combines jazz, classical music and film music.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230523163500 +0200" stop="20230523173600 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">  Creamfields</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Green Velvet, MK, Carl Cox &amp; deadmau5</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Creamfields - Having burst onto the ever-growing festival scene two decades ago, Creamfields has secured its spot as being one of the - if not the - biggest weekend dedicated to electronic music in the UK. Currently, the clubbing and raving pilgrimage attracts an impressive 70,000 festival-goers over the weekend. Continuously offering up the very best in EDM, house, trance, drum and bass, grime, and more, Creamfields has hosted some massive names over the past twenty years. This 2019 edition of Creamfields presents Green Velvet, MK, Carl Cox, Deadmau5, Camelphat, Nicole Moudaber, Dimitri Vegas &amp; Like Mike, and many more!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230523173600 +0200" stop="20230523194900 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam</title>
<desc lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam - New Cool Collective is one of the foremost Dutch jazz ensembles. Pioneering new blends of music styles since 1993, NCC has performed in various formations, from small combos to larger ensembles and even big bands! The ensemble's high energy is cut out for the dance floors, as dance, Latin, salsa, afrobeat and boogaloo all meet in a jazzy mix. NCC includes saxophonist Benjamin Herman, guitarist Rory Ronde, drummer Joost Kroon, percussionists Frank van Dok and Jos de Haas, pianist Willem Friede, bassist Leslie Lopez, and trumpeter David Rockefeller.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230523194900 +0200" stop="20230523210000 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Caixa Cubo - Da Pá Virada Sessions</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Giana Viscardi</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Giana Viscardi - Da Pá Virada Sessions - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the bands taking part in this series is the duo of Giana Viscardi and Gustavo Marques. After starting their career together, Giana Viscardi and Gustavo Marques released music in many places around the world. After returning to Brazil, they worked together on Giana's album &quot;ORUM&quot;, performing in Africa, Europe, and Brazil. In this episode, Giana Viscardi and Gustavo Marques perform conductor and arranger Letieres Leite's arrangements of their work.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230523210000 +0200" stop="20230523222400 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Mosè in Egitto</title>
<desc lang="fr">Mosè in Egitto - The spectacular Milan Cathedral - the fifth-largest church in the world, which took six centuries to build - provides the setting for this lavish performance of Gioachino Rossini's opera &quot;Mosè&quot;. Rossini created &quot;Mosè in Egitto&quot; for the Teatro San Carlo in Naples in 1818-19 but later revised and expanded it for the Paris Opera. The French opera &quot;Moïse et Pharaon&quot;, of which Mosè is the Italian transcript, is a dropsical affair, decked out with ballet sequences, and embellished with the kind of effects Cecil B de Mille would later favor when dealing with Biblical epics. There is nothing of that here. In this pared-down Mosè, the action focuses on Moses's confrontations with the Egyptians and Amenofi's (Pharaoh's son) love for Moses's niece Anaide.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Opéra</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230523222400 +0200" stop="20230523231800 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Rooted With Wings</title>
<desc lang="fr">Rooted With Wings - Rooted with Wings is a visual dance documentary that explores the work of internationally acclaimed choreographer and dancer Tero Saarinen, granting the viewer a unique lens into this extraordinary artist's creative process. The film brings to light how Saarinen's dance works evolve from an idea or concept into a finished performance and features stunningly captured dance sequences and behind-the-scenes material from around the globe. The film follows Saarinen over five years, from 2014 to 2018, through several premieres of new works and tours in Finland, France, Korea, Kenya, and the US, while bringing to light his approach to his life as a global nomad in dance.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Documentaire</category>
<category lang="fr">Sport</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230523231800 +0200" stop="20230524002700 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Michelle David - Jazz in Duketown</title>
<desc lang="fr">Michelle David - Jazz in Duketown - Jazz in Duketown is the largest free outdoor jazz festival in the Netherlands. It's a real gathering for jazz addicts, inviting internationally renowned artists. The talented American singer Michelle David performs pop and gospel music that feeds the heart and soothes the soul. Having grown up with the church, she started singing at the age of four. A year later she joined her first band, The Mission of Love. In 1980 she enrolled at Fiorello H. LaGuardia High School of Music &amp; Art and Performing Arts in New York City, known from the film 'Fame'. During this time, she appeared as an extra in the legendary comedy film 'Ghostbusters'. Musicals and tours with the bands of Diana Ross and Michael Bolton followed.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230524002700 +0200" stop="20230524014800 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Rocky Mountain Way</title>
<desc lang="fr">Rocky Mountain Way - The Colorado Music Hall of Fame hosted a concert for the induction of rock 'n' roll legends Joe Walsh and the late Dan Fogelberg, along with the honoring of the famed Caribou Ranch recording studio near Nederland, Colorado, where Walsh and Fogelberg both recorded some of their best work. The concert, dubbed &quot;The Rocky Mountain Way,&quot; took place on Sunday, August 13, 2017, at Fiddler's Green. It featured performances from an all-star list of musicians including The Lumineers, Garth Brooks, Amy Grant &amp; Vince Gill, The Nitty Gritty Dirt Band, Richie Furay, Randy Owen of Alabama, Todd Park Mohr, Michael Martin Murphey, and surprise guests paying tribute to Dan Fogelberg and Caribou Ranch. Joe Walsh reunited his Caribou recording band Barnstorm for the performance.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Pop &amp; Rock</category>
<icon src="https://img.bouygtel.fr/CMS/images/C48609F1056AF07359F069F8FE7DB1AC.jpg" />
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230524014800 +0200" stop="20230524030000 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Caixa Cubo - Da Pá Virada Sessions</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Samba das Flores</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Samba das Flores - Da Pá Virada Sessions - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the bands taking part in this series is the ensemble Samba das Flores, which dedicates itself to exploring the world's different rhythms, thus keeping the Brazilian heritage alive. The individual voices of the ensemble members color Samba das Flores's unique sound. Let Brazilian culture and global rhythms inspire you during this Samba das Flores performance!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230524030000 +0200" stop="20230524035000 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Sing Jazz 2018</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">House of the Gipsies</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">House of the Gipsies - Sing Jazz 2018 - Since the Gypsy Kings made their triumphal debut on the music scene with their wild Spanish rumba four decades ago, no band has dared to follow in their footsteps ... until now! House of the Gipsies updates the raw rhythms of nomadic tribes in Rajasthan, India, collaborating with Manganiyar musicians Manjoor, Nehru and Dilawar Khan. The result is a unique sound that can be described as Indo-Gypsy fusion, which is part of the evolution of the Spanish rumba. Do not miss this eclectic performance sure to please music lovers of all generations, presented at the 2018 Sing Jazz Festival.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<icon src="https://img.bouygtel.fr/CMS/images/E537F830342471D10D4F174FE9E53A46.jpg" />
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230524035000 +0200" stop="20230524045100 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Runtown : La Machine de Moulin Rouge</title>
<desc lang="fr">Runtown - La Machine de Moulin Rouge - Enjoy Runtown's first concert in Paris, where the Nigerian superstar brings many guests to his show. One of the most talented Nigerian afrobeat scenes will make you rediscover his greatest hits. Nigeria is a very creative country when it comes to the music scene. Runtown is no exception. His first single, &quot;Party Like It's 1980,&quot; paved the way for &quot;Gallardo,&quot; which caught the entire international scene's attention. Runtown's inspiration comes from the greats, from Salif Keita and Fela Kuti to Otis Redding and Bob Marley. An exceptional event not to be missed.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230524045100 +0200" stop="20230524055300 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Mariana Aydar : Da Pá Virada Sessions</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Mariana Aydar</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Mariana Aydar - Da Pá Virada Sessions - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the artists taking part in this episode is vocalist Mariana Aydar, who masters the música popular brasileira repertoire (MPB) like no other. She was born in a family of musicians, and has been dubbed the &quot;hottest singer of the moment&quot; by Veja, one of Brazil's leading newsmagazines. For her performance at Da Pá Virada Sessions, Aydar (vocals and triangle) is joined by Cosme Vieira (accordion) and Feeh Silva (zabumba).</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230524055300 +0200" stop="20230524065500 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Dickey Betts: Ramblin'</title>
<desc lang="fr">Dickey Betts: Ramblin' - Surrounded by music from an early age, Dickey Betts (lead guitar) has created a distinctive sound fusion of different genres such as blues, rock, country, and jazz. This concert shows an intimate performance of the band, in which Dickey Betts is accompanied by Damon Fowler (lead/slide guitarist) and his son Duane Betts (lead guitar). The band also includes long-time band members Frankie Lombardi (drums), Steve Camilleri (drums), Pedro Arevalo (bass), and Mike Kach (keyboard). In addition, guitarist Devon Allman makes a special guest appearance on the song &quot;Midnight Rider.&quot; Other songs in this exceptional performance include &quot;Ramblin' Man,&quot; &quot;Jessica,&quot; and more.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Pop &amp; Rock</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>