<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Bouygues -->
<programme start="20230506051500 +0200" stop="20230506061500 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">  Creamfields</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Green Velvet, MK, Carl Cox &amp; deadmau5</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Creamfields - Having burst onto the ever-growing festival scene two decades ago, Creamfields has secured its spot as being one of the - if not the - biggest weekend dedicated to electronic music in the UK. Currently, the clubbing and raving pilgrimage attracts an impressive 70,000 festival-goers over the weekend. Continuously offering up the very best in EDM, house, trance, drum and bass, grime, and more, Creamfields has hosted some massive names over the past twenty years. This 2019 edition of Creamfields presents Green Velvet, MK, Carl Cox, Deadmau5, Camelphat, Nicole Moudaber, Dimitri Vegas &amp; Like Mike, and many more!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230506061500 +0200" stop="20230506072100 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Caixa Cubo - Da Pá Virada Sessions</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Martina</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Martina - Da Pá Virada Sessions - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the artists taking part in this series is Martina Marana. Vocalist, instrumentalist, and composer Martina Marana uses the power of irony to show how women instrumentalists are misjudged. In her music, Martina breaks free of sexist labels, reclaiming her own power as musician and composer. A gifted lyricist, Marana makes uncompromising, unique music.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230506072100 +0200" stop="20230506083600 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Arsenik à l'Olympia</title>
<desc lang="fr">Arsenik - Olympia, Paris - The mythical duo Arsenik is a rap group from France, made up of two brothers, Lino and Calbo. The team performs at Olympia Paris to celebrate their 20 years since their first album, Quelques gouttes suffisent… It's a unique concert: Arsenik plays the entire album with numerous special guests for the first time. The album has sold over 300,000 copies in France. Today it's being considered a classic, and it continues to be cited in the top five of the best French rap albums of all generations. Enjoy Arsenik's live show in Olympia Paris!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Rap &amp; Techno</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230506083600 +0200" stop="20230506090000 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Subsurface</title>
<desc lang="fr">Subsurface - The Finnish choreographer, dancer, and film maker Thomas Freundlich created the dance short film 'Subsurface'. Set to music by the internationally renowned avant-garde accordionist Kimmo Pohjonen, the film uses archaic elements of nature as metaphors for the multiple levels of a relationship. The dancers Jussi Väänänen and Katja Koukkula wear beautiful costumes by Jenni Ahtiainen during this enthralling seven-minute opus.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Film</category>
<category lang="fr">Court métrage</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230506090000 +0200" stop="20230506094700 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Invisible World : WOMEX 2018</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Invisible World</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">One of the participants was the band Invisible World, which operates at the crossroads where Eastern European and Mediterranean influences come together and break new ground. Invisible World is led by the inventive Czech bassist Tomáš Liška, together with the Turkish violinist Efe Turumtay, the Serbian accordionist Nikola Zarić and the Moravian drummer Kamil Slezák.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Musique</category>
<category lang="fr">Musicale</category>
<icon src="https://img.bouygtel.fr/CMS/images/A5539A1D83657FE964693E3151A5A56C.jpg" />
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230506094700 +0200" stop="20230506104100 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Caixa Cubo - Da Pá Virada Sessions</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Tribute to Gilberto Gil</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Tribute to Gilberto Gil - Da Pá Virada Sessions - The series Da Pá Virada sessions presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the bands taking part in this series is Caixa Cubo. This trio usually explores Brazil's rhythmically rich landscapes, combining them with modern Brazilian jazz trends. Yet in this singular performance, Caixa Cubo teams up with vocalist Zé Leônidas, selecting special repertoire together with Dani Gurgel from Da Pá Virada Sessions and Rokas Kučinskas from Stingray DJAZZ.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230506104100 +0200" stop="20230506114300 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Caixa Cubo - Da Pá Virada Sessions</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Bloco do O</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Bloco do O - Da Pá Virada Sessions - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the bands taking part in this series is Bloco do Ó, a traditional street band associated with the Brazilian carnival. A &quot;bloco&quot; is a group of people who drive through the streets in trucks, playing music and providing fun to anyone who will listen. Immerse yourself in Bloco de Ó's world of cheerful melodies and spectacular costumes!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230506114300 +0200" stop="20230506125400 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Irène Drésel</title>
<desc lang="fr">Irène Drésel - The world of Irène Drésel can be described as high-colored techno, sensual, and bold. It's a hypnotic world where languid and sporty BPMs rub shoulders with crystalline melodies, foiling the expectations of techno listeners. A polymorphic artist who has left the frenzy of Paris for the calm of the countryside, Irène Drésel tends to her universe down to the smallest details, as evidenced on stage by the roses that gracefully overhang the cold steel of her machines. Irène Drésel composes alone, but she is accompanied live by a percussionist, Sizo Del Givry. Enjoy their 2019 show at Trabendo Paris!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Rap &amp; Techno</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230506125400 +0200" stop="20230506134800 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">WOMEX 2018</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">The Garifuna Collektive</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr"> In 2018 WOMEX took place in Las Palmas in Gran Canaria. One of the participants was The Garifuna Collective. These young and old musicians from the Caribbean keep Andy Palacio's legacy alive.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Musique</category>
<category lang="fr">Musicale</category>
<icon src="https://img.bouygtel.fr/CMS/images/BD1A4F239A69EC884BEAFFB08B575969.jpg" />
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230506134800 +0200" stop="20230506150000 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Isle of Wight 2018: Part I</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Isle of Wight Festival, held in Newport, England is a rock-pop music festival that annually serves as the first major event opening the British festival summer. The tradition of the festival first saw the light of day in 1969, opening eleven days after the closing of legendary Woodstock and was regarded as the European counterpart to the legendary &quot;counterculture&quot; festival. In 1970, its line-up was stars-studded with gigs by Jimi Hendrix, The Who, The Doors, Joni Mitchell, Supertramp, Leonard Cohen and many more, establishing the name of the festival. In 2002, the festival was revived after 30 years of silence and brought back the sounds of contemporary musical legends to the Isle of Wight.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Pop &amp; Rock</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230506150000 +0200" stop="20230506163400 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Charlie Parker : &quot;Bird with Strings&quot; revisited à la Philharmonie de Paris</title>
<desc lang="fr">Charlie Parker - Bird with Strings Revisited - In the late 1940s, jazz saxophonist Charlie &quot;Bird&quot; Parker expressed his wish to record with a classical string section rather than his usual jazz quintet. This desire was fulfilled in 1949 and 1950 when he recorded two albums with oboe, harp, string section and a jazz rhythm section, released as 'Charlie Parker with Strings'. Fast forward 70 years, when saxophonists Olivier Bogé, Géraldine Laurent, Pierrick Pédron, Thomas de Pourquery, and Jaleel Shaw follow in the jazz legend's footsteps, revisiting the repertoire of those original albums in this 2019 concert at The Philharmonie de Paris. Bastien Stil conducts Christophe Dal Sasso's new orchestral arrangements in this genre-blending concert, which opens with Dal Sasso's very own Overture pour cinq saxophones et orchestra.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<icon src="https://img.bouygtel.fr/CMS/images/F0063316707C2A1E40D1DB5CDC61234F.jpg" />
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230506163400 +0200" stop="20230506173000 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">The Go! Team @ Route du Rock Hivers</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Go! Team @ Route du Rock Hivers - Originating from Brighton, UK, The Go! Team blends garage/indie rock with distorted guitars and a popping brass section. The creative force behind this six-piece band is Ian Parton. According to him, the band samples everything from Bollywood to hip-hop. Although the samples are at the heart of the band's sound, every song is kicked off by the melody. At Route du Rock Hivers 2018, The Go! Team presents its latest album, Semicircle. Its opening track Mayday is built around a drum loop based on Morse code. This is only the beginning of the endless variety of sound effects The Go! Team experiments with. At their 4K show at Rock Hivers 2018, you will enjoy a blend of noisy pop, hip-hop collages, awesome grooves, irresistible soul arrangements and much more!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Pop &amp; Rock</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230506173000 +0200" stop="20230506183500 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Caixa Cubo - Da Pá Virada Sessions</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Amilton Godoy</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Amilton Godoy - Da Pá Virada Sessions - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the artists taking part in this series is pianist Amilton Godoy. He is not only a well-known soloist in his homeland Brazil, but he is also considered one of the world's greatest pianists today, regularly guesting with international top orchestras and conductors. Godoy frequently teaches workshops throughout Brazil and abroad.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230506183500 +0200" stop="20230506195400 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">The Opera Locos</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Opera Locos - In The Opera Locos (&quot;The Opera of Crazies&quot;), a comic opera show from the Spanish theater company Yllana and theatre producer Rami Eldar, five eccentric opera singers perform some of the greatest opera arias. Classical arias from George Bizet's Carmen, W. A. Mozart's The Magic Flute, and Giuseppe Verdi's Rigoletto are combined with classics from the pop and rock repertoire. During the performance, the five characters reveal their hidden passions, personalities, and desires, leading to unpredictable, hilarious situations that audiences of all ages will appreciate. The soloists are Florian Laconi (tenor), Margaux Toqué (mezzo soprano), Michaël Koné (countertenor), Laurent Arcaro (baritone), and Diane Fourès (soprano). This performance was recorded at Théâtre Libre in Paris, France.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Musique</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230506195400 +0200" stop="20230506210000 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Audience Music</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">The Band Perry</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">This series features groundbreaking concerts, in-depth artist interviews and unique stories with host Ted Stryker. This concert series gives the audience an intimate view of music's most influential artists today. Shot in 4K, host Ted Stryker interviews musicians across all genres, creating the most unique music show on TV today. This episode features The Band Perry, the famous country band consisting of siblings Kimberly, Reid and Neil Perry. Throughout high school they had different bands, but towards the end of high school the three came together as The Band Perry. After being signed to Republic Nashville, they released their first album, and conquered the charts with the song &quot;If I Die Young.&quot; Since then, they have scored numerous hits and have won various awards.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230506210000 +0200" stop="20230506213800 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Echoes Series: Ed O'Brien</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Ed O'Brien</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Echoes Series: Ed O'Brien - Echoes is a modern live music show hosted by Jehnny Beth (lead singer in the British band Savages). It presents leading and emerging bands and artists from the contemporary scene. The show takes place underneath the Palais de Tokyo museum in Paris, in the club of brutalist architecture, the &quot;Yoyo.&quot; The live sets are 30 minutes long and take place on a customized stage, creating closeness with the audience. The intimate, immersive space lends to the atmosphere of the show. The artistic direction by Antoine Carlier follows a minimalist, refined and pure aesthetic, allowing the artists' energy and emotions to take center stage. This episode features guitarist Ed O'Brien, a member of rock band Radiohead. His set includes the songs &quot;Mass,&quot; &quot;Olympik,&quot; and &quot;Brasil.&quot;</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230506213800 +0200" stop="20230506224100 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Caixa Cubo - Da Pá Virada Sessions</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Frederico Heliodoro</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr"> The Da Pá Virada Sessions series portrays the best musicians in Brazilian jazz today. All sessions were recorded in São Paulo and offer a unique experience, offering a fresh look at the Brazilian music scene. The artists have been selected together with the music editor of Stingray DJAZZ. Among the bands featured in this series is Caixa Cubo. Typically, this versatile trio explores the rhythmically rich Brazilian landscapes, combining them with modern Brazilian jazz trends. For this program, however, Caixa Cubo works together with vocalist Zé Leônidas, with a special repertoire that has been put together with Dani Gurgel from Da Pá Virada Sessions and Rokas Kučinskas from Stingray DJAZZ.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<icon src="https://img.bouygtel.fr/CMS/images/9F406FF67871F985172B3D646330A780.jpg" />
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230506224100 +0200" stop="20230506233700 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Beth Hart - Front And Center</title>
<desc lang="fr">The popular music performance series Front and Center premiered nationwide on public television in 2016, and now returns for Season 6. The series boasts 22, one-hour episodes and an all-star line-up. Today's guest is Beth Hart, active in the music scene since the '90s, releasing her third live album. Her intimate show showcases her amazing voice, and her piano playing skills, which she proves with the song &quot;Jazz Man.&quot; One of the performance's highlights includes the ballad &quot;Leave the Light On,&quot; as well as the final song &quot;No Place Like Home.&quot; During her performance, Beth Hart is supported by Jon Nichols, Bill Ransom, Bob Marinelli, and Sonny Landreth.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230506233700 +0200" stop="20230507014400 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Carl Cox - Carl Cox</title>
<desc lang="fr">Carl Cox - It was at the age of 15 that Carl bought a set of turntables and began working as a mobile DJ. Disco was the first music that captivated him but by the early '80s, Cox had moved on to playing the same music as other young London DJs - rare groove, New York hip-hop, and electro. A musical ambassador and a veteran of acid house, a champion of techno, a dance music pioneer, label owner, King of Ibiza - you name it, Carl Cox has been there and done it, never losing sight of his passions - playing music, breaking tunes, and celebrating life. Enjoy his show at Family Piknik 2019!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230507014400 +0200" stop="20230507030000 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Oumou Sangaré @ Jazz Sous Les Pommiers</title>
<desc lang="fr">Salif Keita described her as the &quot;Tina Turner of Mali.&quot; Indeed, Oumou Sangaré is one of Africa's most important female voices. While maintaining her political views as a champion of women's rights in Africa, her vocal talent has brought this singer to shine at some of the most important venues around the world. At Jazz Sous Les Pommiers 2017, Oumou Sangaré presents her latest album, Mogoya. She is accompanied by a group that combines traditional African instruments with a modern band set-up, featuring young French musicians. Recorded in spectacular 4K in a beautiful musical setting, Sangaré will surely make you sing and dance!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230507030000 +0200" stop="20230507041100 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Michelle David - Jazz in Duketown</title>
<desc lang="fr">Michelle David - Jazz in Duketown - Jazz in Duketown is the largest free outdoor jazz festival in the Netherlands. It's a real gathering for jazz addicts, inviting internationally renowned artists. The talented American singer Michelle David performs pop and gospel music that feeds the heart and soothes the soul. Having grown up with the church, she started singing at the age of four. A year later she joined her first band, The Mission of Love. In 1980 she enrolled at Fiorello H. LaGuardia High School of Music &amp; Art and Performing Arts in New York City, known from the film 'Fame'. During this time, she appeared as an extra in the legendary comedy film 'Ghostbusters'. Musicals and tours with the bands of Diana Ross and Michael Bolton followed.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230507041100 +0200" stop="20230507051200 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Runtown : La Machine de Moulin Rouge</title>
<desc lang="fr">Runtown - La Machine de Moulin Rouge - Enjoy Runtown's first concert in Paris, where the Nigerian superstar brings many guests to his show. One of the most talented Nigerian afrobeat scenes will make you rediscover his greatest hits. Nigeria is a very creative country when it comes to the music scene. Runtown is no exception. His first single, &quot;Party Like It's 1980,&quot; paved the way for &quot;Gallardo,&quot; which caught the entire international scene's attention. Runtown's inspiration comes from the greats, from Salif Keita and Fela Kuti to Otis Redding and Bob Marley. An exceptional event not to be missed.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230507051200 +0200" stop="20230507064500 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Jazz à Ramatuelle</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Antonio Faraò</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Jazz à Ramatuelle: Antonio Faraò - In 1998, Antonio Faraò won the prestigious Concours Martial Solal, awarded to him by Herbie Hancock! Since then, this talented Italian jazz pianist has made his mark as a player of elegance and lyricism, which has allowed him to collaborate with the best European and American musicians. On his last album &quot;Evan&quot;, recorded in the United States, he leads an all-star band starring Joe Lovano on tenor saxophone. On a beautiful summer night at the French Jazz à Ramatuelle festival, Faraò performs at the breathtaking Theatre de Verdure in the company of saxophone legend Dave Liebman. With refined ballads, a feline groove, elegance, and lyricism, this musical meeting sparkles - if you watch closely you might even see some bright new stars lighting up in the night sky above Ramatuelle!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>