<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Bouygues -->
<programme start="20230526045900 +0200" stop="20230526062700 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Lee Ranaldo</title>
<desc lang="fr">Lee Ranaldo - After being one of the pillars of Sonic Youth, Lee Ranaldo released the solo album Electric Trim. The album was recorded in Barcelona and New York, with a dream-team including producer Raul Refree Fernandez, singer Sharon Van Etten, and guitarist/composer Nels Cline. To top it off, Lee Ranaldo collaborated with New York author Jonathan Lethem for the lyrics of most of the album's songs. Enjoy this special occasion and watch the 4K recording of Electric Trim at the French theatre L'Epicerie Moderne in 2018. This free-minded musician will surprise you with a unique blend of psychedelic music and folk rock!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230526062700 +0200" stop="20230526071000 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Fedde le Grand @ Pacha Festival</title>
<desc lang="fr">Pacha Festival - Fedde Le Grand is considered one of the most important artists of house music, a style in constant evolution. He is known around the world for his simple &quot;Put Your Hands Up For Detroit&quot;, &quot;Rhythm Of The Night&quot;, &quot;The Creeps&quot;, and &quot;Let Me Think About It&quot;. Fedde Le Grand has received countless awards and has offered remixes of the greatest international artists such as Coldplay, Madonna, Will.i.am, Robbie Williams and, more recently, Michael Jackson (&quot;Love Never Felt So Good&quot;) and Faithless (&quot;Insomnia&quot;). His electrifying DJ set at Bali's Pacha Festival thrills the view with his breathtaking lights, fireworks, and delirious crowd!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230526071000 +0200" stop="20230526082300 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">STUFF. Live at BIRD Rotterdam</title>
<desc lang="fr">With their inexhaustible energy, STUFF is impossible to get off the stage! The band was formed in 2012 when drummer Lander Gyselinck was asked by a local bar to make live music between sets of DJs, and he gathered a number of musician friends. The band is considered an avant-garde jazz band that plays a mix of funk, hip-hop and electro. Andrew Claes (saxophone), Dries Laheye (bass guitar), Lander Gyselinck (drummer), Mixmonster Menno (samples) and Joris Caluwaerts (keyboard) share a fabulous musical connection. The eagerness with which the musicians conquer every stage and the great pleasure with which they do so makes the heart of every music lover melt.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230526082300 +0200" stop="20230526090000 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Songbook</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">José James</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Songbook - &quot;I never heard anyone say that, and yeah, I know exactly what it means. It has to go in there, this has to be a song.&quot; Every song has its own story, and we all think it's a story we've heard before, but we haven't. Songbook finds and captures these intriguing stories by pulling you into the process of writing and composing. Known for its pristine sound, cinematic 4k video, and eye for detail, Songbook live-captured episodes emphasize the paramount importance of quality. It addresses the on-the-spot elements of blending song and location at the right moment. Both the magical location and remarkable music interaction will get the attention they deserve. Simply because Songbook isn't just a live music session, it lives. This episode of Songbook features eclectic R&amp;B artist José James.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230526090000 +0200" stop="20230526102100 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">HVOB</title>
<desc lang="fr">HVOB - The two musicians behind HVOB are Anna Müller and Paul Wallner. Anna Müller composes, produces, and provides the captivating, hypnotic vocals. The final production of the tracks is done in collaboration with Paul Wallner in his Vienna studio. HVOB are carving their path not just with their distinctive sound but with their live performances as well. The duo always plays live and performs with a drummer - a concept as innovative as it is successful: HVOB has just been voted number two best live act by the most influential German electronic music magazine &quot;De:bug.&quot; Enjoy their 2019 show at Trabendo Paris!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Contemporain</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230526102100 +0200" stop="20230526110400 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">City Beats</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">London</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">City Beats - Episode 1 - London - DJ-producer Carly Foxx is on a musical journey, immersing herself in the life of five iconic European cities to find inspiration for a series of new tracks. In this episode, Carly Foxx steps outside of her comfort zone to draw inspiration for her music track from urban youths in London's grime scene. With fresh eyes, she explores what makes this city unique to the people who live there. Carly interviews people on the street and asks them about the London music scene, which is very lively and diverse. To better understand the urban music scene, Carly pays a visit to RepreZent Radio, where she interviews grime artists. She records street sounds such as a bus driving by, the ticking against a metal door, and police sirens.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Documentaire</category>
<category lang="fr">Téléréalité</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230526110400 +0200" stop="20230526120300 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Caixa Cubo - Da Pá Virada Sessions</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Andre Marques</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Andre Marques - Da Pá Virada Sessions - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the artists taking part in this series is pianist, composer, and arranger André Marques. He has been building a solid career, releasing his music with numerous groups: he is a member of the Latin Grammy-nominated Trio Curupira, the André Marques Sexteto, and he leads the Brazilian music orchestra Vintena Brasileira. In this episode of Da Pá Virada Sessions, André Marques performs an intimate solo piano recital.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230526120300 +0200" stop="20230526133700 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Jazz à Ramatuelle</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Antonio Faraò</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Jazz à Ramatuelle: Antonio Faraò - In 1998, Antonio Faraò won the prestigious Concours Martial Solal, awarded to him by Herbie Hancock! Since then, this talented Italian jazz pianist has made his mark as a player of elegance and lyricism, which has allowed him to collaborate with the best European and American musicians. On his last album &quot;Evan&quot;, recorded in the United States, he leads an all-star band starring Joe Lovano on tenor saxophone. On a beautiful summer night at the French Jazz à Ramatuelle festival, Faraò performs at the breathtaking Theatre de Verdure in the company of saxophone legend Dave Liebman. With refined ballads, a feline groove, elegance, and lyricism, this musical meeting sparkles - if you watch closely you might even see some bright new stars lighting up in the night sky above Ramatuelle!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230526133700 +0200" stop="20230526141300 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Classical:NEXT 2019</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Tagg &amp; Petersen</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Classical:NEXT 2019 - Tagg &amp; Petersen - The Kathleen Tagg / Andre Petersen piano duo brings together two of South Africa's most celebrated pianists: one eclectic-experimental classical and one jazz artist, in a unique and highly personal collaboration. Drawing inspiration from the rich sonic tapestries of classical music, nuances of South African jazz and traditional musics from sub-Saharan Africa, this duo explodes the concept of what two pianos can sound like: a bass guitar, goema drum, marimba and uhadi-plus mixing fully composed scores with improvisation in a bold, vital and highly entertaining mix with performances of original compositions and works by iconic South African jazz composers such as Abdullah Ibrahim, Bheki Mseleku and Moses Molelekwa.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Classique</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230526141300 +0200" stop="20230526150100 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Eleanor Dubinsky - Nublu 2019</title>
<desc lang="fr">The music of vocalist, guitarist and cellist Eleanor Dubinsky lives on the narrow ledge where jazz, international music and pop meet emotionally heartfelt songwriting. The musician and her versatile band deliver dynamic compositions that explore the fragile link between human emotions and human responsibility. The core of Eleanor's artistic mission is to enter into dialogue and achieve self-realization through music.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230526150100 +0200" stop="20230526161100 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">BIGYUKI : BIRD 2019</title>
<desc lang="fr">BIGYUKI - BIRD 2019 - BIGYUKI's is New York City's secret musical weapon! His unprecedented sound has attracted the attention of many, including Grammy Award-winning and nominated artists such as Q-Tip, Bilal, Talib Kweli, Harvey Mason, Marcus Strickland, Mark Giuliana, and Meshell Ndegeocello. BIGYUKI's music offers a soulful exploration into the wondrous soundscapes of his infinitely virtuosic mind. Infusing elements of jazz, classical music, hip-hop, soul, rock, dance, and electronica, BIGYUKI reaches a new and inspiring level, with support from guitarist Randy Runyon and drummer Smithsoneon. It is hard to believe that just three musicians can create a sound this massive.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230526161100 +0200" stop="20230526170500 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">WOMEX 2018</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">The Garifuna Collektive</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr"> In 2018 WOMEX took place in Las Palmas in Gran Canaria. One of the participants was The Garifuna Collective. These young and old musicians from the Caribbean keep Andy Palacio's legacy alive.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Musique</category>
<category lang="fr">Musicale</category>
<icon src="https://img.bouygtel.fr/CMS/images/BD1A4F239A69EC884BEAFFB08B575969.jpg" />
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230526170500 +0200" stop="20230526184100 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Atys en folie</title>
<desc lang="fr">Atys en Folie - Atys en folie is a parody of Jean-Baptiste Lully's lyrical tragedy Atys (1676). Atys, Lully's most famous opera, was a constant subject of parody throughout the 18th century. Stage director Jean-Philippe Desrousseaux drew on several parodies to create this original production for singers, puppets, and musicians to revive the work. Princes, princesses, and kings are relegated to peasants, market gardeners, and fishmongers in the countryside. Among the performers are Alain Buet, Marie Lenormand, and Arnaud Marzorati. Gaëlle Trimardeau, Bruno Coulon and Jean-Philippe Desrousseaux feature as puppeteers. The music is performed by ensemble La Clique des Lunaisiens, conducted by Arnaud Marzorati. This performance was recorded at Teatru Manoel in Valletta, Malta, in 2017.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Opéra</category>
<category lang="fr">Opérette</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230526184100 +0200" stop="20230526193000 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Ben Frost</title>
<desc lang="fr">Ben Frost - Australian Ben Frost produces under his Bedroom Community label albums inspired by post-classical electronic music, structured sound art and minimalism. His numerous collaborations testify to his desire to develop an artistic form combining music, texts, technology and performance. In this fascinating concert delivered at the Sónar Reykjavík 2018 festival, Frost once again displays his ingenuity as he presents the pieces of the album The Centre Cannot Hold. The award-winning visual artist MFO signs visual effects and lighting.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Pop &amp; Rock</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230526193000 +0200" stop="20230526202400 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">&quot;We Love Ella&quot; : The Amazing Keystone Big Band</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Amazing Keystone Big Band - &quot;We Love Ella&quot; - The Amazing Keystone Big Band performs material from their album &quot;We Love Ella&quot; at this 2019 recording from Salle Pleyel in Paris, France. Led by trombonist Bastien Ballaz, saxophonist Jon Boutellier, pianist Fred Nardin and trumpeter David Enhco, The Amazing Keystone Big Band helps young and adult audiences all over the world discover jazz in all its guises. &quot;We Love Ella&quot; is a reinvention of legendary vocalist Ella Fitzgerald's greatest successes.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<icon src="https://img.bouygtel.fr/CMS/images/C88B1D8822AE4BC8696F6B6B529F30C3.jpg" />
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230526202400 +0200" stop="20230526210000 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Classical:NEXT 2019</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Clarinet Factory</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Classical:NEXT 2019 - Clarinet Factory - Considered to be one of the most unique ensembles to feature on the Czech scene in the last 25 years, the style of the Clarinet Factory hovers between contemporary and classical music, jazz and world music. As winners of the Classic Prague Awards in 2017 for 'Best Crossover Project', the quartet combines their classic music training and clarinet art with jazz, minimalism and improvisation to create their very own music without borders, capable of communicating directly with all audiences. The Clarinet Factory also experiment with electronics, both ambient and dance-oriented, and the four musicians remain ever fascinated with the possibilities of their instrument, considering their work as a music laboratory.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Classique</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230526210000 +0200" stop="20230526215100 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Lee Scratch Perry</title>
<desc lang="fr">Lee &quot;Scratch&quot; Perry is a Jamaican musician, a pioneer in the development of dub music in the 1970s. He remixes existing reggae tracks with studio effects, creating a new sound. During the early 2000s, Perry won a Grammy for Best Reggae album, and was ranked in the Rolling Stone list of 100 Greatest Artists of All Time. He has collaborated with a variety of great artists, most notably Bob Marley, whose compositions he still incorporates in his show. During his 2017 show at Philharmonie de Paris, you will enjoy well-known reggae songs like Punk Reggae Party, Sun Is Shining, and Soul Fire. Recorded in 4K, it promises to be a groovy and spectacular show!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230526215100 +0200" stop="20230526224400 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Ramón Valle &amp; Reinier Baas : Music Meeting 2020</title>
<desc lang="fr">Ramón Valle &amp; Reinier Baas - Music Meeting 2020 - Since 1985, the Dutch city of Nijmegen has been welcoming the International Music Meeting Festival every Pentecost. Ranging from jazz and improvisational music to traditional music and unique crossovers, this adventurous festival is all about musical encounters and international collaborations. Disrupted by COVID-19, the festival's 2020 edition had to adapt to new challenges. It now presents this exclusive concert by pianist Ramón Valle and guitarist Reinier Baas, filmed at Concertgebouw De Vereeniging in Nijmegen.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230526224400 +0200" stop="20230526234900 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Panorama do Choro : Da Pá Virada Sessions</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Panorama do Choro</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Panorama do Choro - Da Pá Virada Sessions - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the bands taking part in this series is Panorama de Coro. This ensemble combines jazz and traditional Brazilian music. The resulting music has a festive, almost street-like atmosphere. Panorama de Coro consists of Roberta Valente (pandeiro and percussion), Alexandre Ribeiro (clarinet), Gian Correa (7-string guitar), Henrique Araujo (cavaquinho), João Poleto (flute and tenor saxophone) and Yves Finzetto (pandeiro and percussion).</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230526234900 +0200" stop="20230527020200 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam</title>
<desc lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam - New Cool Collective is one of the foremost Dutch jazz ensembles. Pioneering new blends of music styles since 1993, NCC has performed in various formations, from small combos to larger ensembles and even big bands! The ensemble's high energy is cut out for the dance floors, as dance, Latin, salsa, afrobeat and boogaloo all meet in a jazzy mix. NCC includes saxophonist Benjamin Herman, guitarist Rory Ronde, drummer Joost Kroon, percussionists Frank van Dok and Jos de Haas, pianist Willem Friede, bassist Leslie Lopez, and trumpeter David Rockefeller.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230527020200 +0200" stop="20230527030000 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">IDLES - Echoes Series: Idles</title>
<desc lang="fr">Echoes Series: Idles - Echoes is a modern live music show hosted by Jehnny Beth (lead singer in the British band Savages). It presents leading and emerging bands and artists from the contemporary scene. The show takes place underneath the Palais de Tokyo museum in Paris, in the club of brutalist architecture, the &quot;Yoyo.&quot; The live sets are 30 minutes long and take place on a customized stage, creating closeness with the audience. The intimate, immersive space lends to the atmosphere of the show. The artistic direction by Antoine Carlier follows a minimalist, refined and pure aesthetic, allowing the artists' energy and emotions to take center stage. This episode features the band Idles. Their set includes the songs &quot;Colossus,&quot; &quot;Love Song,&quot; and &quot;Television.&quot;</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230527030000 +0200" stop="20230527051500 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam</title>
<desc lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam - New Cool Collective is one of the foremost Dutch jazz ensembles. Pioneering new blends of music styles since 1993, NCC has performed in various formations, from small combos to larger ensembles and even big bands! The ensemble's high energy is cut out for the dance floors, as dance, Latin, salsa, afrobeat and boogaloo all meet in a jazzy mix. NCC includes saxophonist Benjamin Herman, guitarist Rory Ronde, drummer Joost Kroon, percussionists Frank van Dok and Jos de Haas, pianist Willem Friede, bassist Leslie Lopez, and trumpeter David Rockefeller.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230527051500 +0200" stop="20230527060600 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Caixa Cubo - Da Pá Virada Sessions</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Giana Viscardi - New Year's Eve Special</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Giana Viscardi - New Year's Eve Special - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the bands taking part in this series is the duo of Giana Viscardi and Gustavo Marques. After starting their career together, Giana Viscardi and Gustavo Marques released music in many places around the world. After returning to Brazil, they worked together on Giana's album &quot;ORUM&quot;, performing in Africa, Europe, and Brazil.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>