<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Bouygues -->
<programme start="20230323042100 +0100" stop="20230323051000 +0100" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">James Arthur</title>
<desc lang="fr">James Arthur - British pop singer James Arthur, best known for his power ballads &quot;Impossible&quot; (2013) and &quot;Say You Won't Let Go&quot; (2016), gives an intimate concert at New York City's Iridium. After winning the ninth season of UK's The X Factor in 2011, his powerful voice quickly helped him rise to the top of international pop charts.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230323051000 +0100" stop="20230323060400 +0100" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">&quot;We Love Ella&quot; : The Amazing Keystone Big Band</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Amazing Keystone Big Band - &quot;We Love Ella&quot; - The Amazing Keystone Big Band performs material from their album &quot;We Love Ella&quot; at this 2019 recording from Salle Pleyel in Paris, France. Led by trombonist Bastien Ballaz, saxophonist Jon Boutellier, pianist Fred Nardin and trumpeter David Enhco, The Amazing Keystone Big Band helps young and adult audiences all over the world discover jazz in all its guises. &quot;We Love Ella&quot; is a reinvention of legendary vocalist Ella Fitzgerald's greatest successes.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<icon src="https://img.bouygtel.fr/CMS/images/C88B1D8822AE4BC8696F6B6B529F30C3.jpg" />
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230323060400 +0100" stop="20230323074000 +0100" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Opera Imaginaire</title>
<desc lang="fr">Opera Imaginaire - To celebrate Le Concert Spirituel's 30th anniversary, conductor Hervé Niquet collaborated with the Baroque Music Center of Versailles to build his opéra imaginaire. For this unique project, Le Concert Spirituel presents an original performance of unpublished operas by Lully, Rameau, Charpentier, and many other French baroque composers. You will find yourself captivated by a tearful lover, intrigued by the passage to the underworld, and fascinated by the descents of the Gods. The program includes many favorite passages, such as Lully's Armide, Charpentier's Medea, and Campra's Carnaval de Venise. Experience all the magic of Louis XIV's French opera as Le Concert Spirituel transforms the Théâtre des Champs-Elysées into a true French baroque scene.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Opéra</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230323074000 +0100" stop="20230323081300 +0100" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Classical:NEXT 2019</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Ensemble HOPE</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Classical:NEXT 2019 - Ensemble HOPE - The Ensemble HOPE is dedicated to the performance and creation of music of today. As well as exploring new forms of contemporary electro-acoustic technology, it integrates written musical tradition, improvisation and an adapted classical repertoire. The &quot;Cristal Baschet&quot; and the &quot;Euphone&quot; form the basis of the ensemble's sophisticated instrumental collection. The new works reflect these neglected and little-known instruments. The Ensemble HOPE, consisting of Frederic Bousquet (Euphone), Marc Antoine Millon (Bass Cristal) and Armelle Marq (soprano voice), is also actively engaged in developing a new generation of Euphones. In this concert from 2019's Classical:NEXT!, the ensemble performs Frederic Bousquet's &quot;Vénus&quot;, &quot;Epilogue&quot; and &quot;en transit,&quot; Henry Purcell's &quot;Dido's lament,&quot; arranged by M.A.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Classique</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230323081300 +0100" stop="20230323090000 +0100" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Classical:NEXT 2019</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Clarinet Factory</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Classical:NEXT 2019 - Clarinet Factory - Considered to be one of the most unique ensembles to feature on the Czech scene in the last 25 years, the style of the Clarinet Factory hovers between contemporary and classical music, jazz and world music. As winners of the Classic Prague Awards in 2017 for 'Best Crossover Project', the quartet combines their classic music training and clarinet art with jazz, minimalism and improvisation to create their very own music without borders, capable of communicating directly with all audiences. The Clarinet Factory also experiment with electronics, both ambient and dance-oriented, and the four musicians remain ever fascinated with the possibilities of their instrument, considering their work as a music laboratory.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Classique</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230323090000 +0100" stop="20230323102600 +0100" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Kenny Loggins and Friends: Live on Soundstage</title>
<desc lang="fr">Kenny Loggins - Daryl Hall started Live From Daryl's House, the free monthly web show in late 2007, after having the idea of &quot;playing with my friends and putting it up on the internet.&quot; The show has since garnered acclaim from Rolling Stone, SPIN, Daily Variety, CNN, BBC, and Yahoo! Music. The influential blogger Bob Lefsetz cited Live From Daryl's House as a perfect example of a veteran artist reinventing himself in the digital age by collaborating with both established colleagues and newer performers. Kenny Loggins' remarkable four-decade-plus career has brought him from the top of the charts to the toast of the Grammys. He's had smash hits on Hollywood's favorite soundtracks, rocked worldwide stages, and found his way into people's hearts while bringing his soulful, beautiful voice to platinum albums in a wide variety of genres.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230323102600 +0100" stop="20230323112600 +0100" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Caixa Cubo - Da Pá Virada Sessions</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Paulo Novaes - New Year's Eve Special</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Paulo Novaes - New Year's Eve Special - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the artists taking part in this series is Paulo Novaes. Coming from a family of musicians, Paulo Novaes has already lived through a lifetime of music in spite of his young age. Paulo is the cousin of singer Bruna Caram, with whom he performed in São Paulo, Madrid, Barcelona, Lisbon, and other major cities. As a singer, composer, and instrumentalist, his creativity is enjoyed in many forms.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230323112600 +0100" stop="20230323133900 +0100" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam</title>
<desc lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam - New Cool Collective is one of the foremost Dutch jazz ensembles. Pioneering new blends of music styles since 1993, NCC has performed in various formations, from small combos to larger ensembles and even big bands! The ensemble's high energy is cut out for the dance floors, as dance, Latin, salsa, afrobeat and boogaloo all meet in a jazzy mix. NCC includes saxophonist Benjamin Herman, guitarist Rory Ronde, drummer Joost Kroon, percussionists Frank van Dok and Jos de Haas, pianist Willem Friede, bassist Leslie Lopez, and trumpeter David Rockefeller.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230323133900 +0100" stop="20230323150000 +0100" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">lovelytheband</title>
<desc lang="fr">Formed in West Hollywood in 2016, lovelytheband features former Oh Honey member Mitchy Collins along with guitarist Jordan Greenwald and drummer Sam Price. The band debuted in July 2017 with the Christian Medice-produced &quot;Broken,&quot; a sprightly and infectious single that quickly racked up over three million digital streams. Signing with Another Century Records, lovelytheband released their debut EP &quot;Everything I Could&quot; in September of that year and joined Vance Joy and AWOLNATION on tour. In April 2018, &quot;Broken&quot; was still going strong and hit number one on the Billboard Alternative Songs Airplay chart. That August, lovelytheband returned with their full-length debut album, Finding It Hard to Smile.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Pop &amp; Rock</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230323150000 +0100" stop="20230323171500 +0100" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam</title>
<desc lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam - New Cool Collective is one of the foremost Dutch jazz ensembles. Pioneering new blends of music styles since 1993, NCC has performed in various formations, from small combos to larger ensembles and even big bands! The ensemble's high energy is cut out for the dance floors, as dance, Latin, salsa, afrobeat and boogaloo all meet in a jazzy mix. NCC includes saxophonist Benjamin Herman, guitarist Rory Ronde, drummer Joost Kroon, percussionists Frank van Dok and Jos de Haas, pianist Willem Friede, bassist Leslie Lopez, and trumpeter David Rockefeller.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230323171500 +0100" stop="20230323180900 +0100" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Rooted With Wings</title>
<desc lang="fr">Rooted With Wings - Rooted with Wings is a visual dance documentary that explores the work of internationally acclaimed choreographer and dancer Tero Saarinen, granting the viewer a unique lens into this extraordinary artist's creative process. The film brings to light how Saarinen's dance works evolve from an idea or concept into a finished performance and features stunningly captured dance sequences and behind-the-scenes material from around the globe. The film follows Saarinen over five years, from 2014 to 2018, through several premieres of new works and tours in Finland, France, Korea, Kenya, and the US, while bringing to light his approach to his life as a global nomad in dance.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Documentaire</category>
<category lang="fr">Sport</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230323180900 +0100" stop="20230323191100 +0100" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Richie Hawtin at Family Piknik</title>
<desc lang="fr">Richie Hawtin at Family Piknik 2017 - Born in Britain and raised in Canada, Richie Hawtin is one of the biggest names in today's electro minimal and is one of the instigators of electro house. Hawtin, who rightly calls himself an artist, is always looking for new concepts and ways to push technological boundaries. Let yourself be carried away by the unique and dancing techno rhythms of this innovative DJ with this highly creative set delivered as part of the 2017 edition of the Family Piknik festival.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230323191100 +0100" stop="20230323210000 +0100" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Omer Avital Qantar - Jazz in Duketown</title>
<desc lang="fr">Jazz in Duketown is the largest free open-air jazz festival in the Netherlands. Jazz fanatics and other music lovers eagerly look forward to the performances of the many internationally renowned artists every year. In 2019 Israeli-American double bass player Omer Avital is one of them. Together with his quintet, consisting of saxophonists Asaf Yuria and Alexander Levin, drummer Ofri Nehemya and pianist Eden Ladin, he performs a strong repertoire from his album 'Qantar': vibrantly energetic, idiosyncratic jazz with oriental influences.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230323210000 +0100" stop="20230323213200 +0100" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Audience Music</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">X Ambassadors</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">X Ambassadors - Enjoy ground-breaking concerts, in-depth artist interviews, and unique stories with host Ted Stryker. This concert series gives the audience an intimate view of music's most influential artists today. Shot in 4K, host Ted Stryker interviews musicians across all genres, creating one of the most unique music shows on TV today. This episode features the alternative rock band X Ambassadors, founded in 2009. After self-releasing the debut EP &quot;Ambassadors EP&quot;, which featured &quot;Litost&quot;, a song that would later be added to the soundtrack of sci-fi blockbuster The Host, the band had its break-through when Imagine Dragons lead singer Dan Reynolds initiated their signage to a major music label.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230323213200 +0100" stop="20230323223200 +0100" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Nubiyan Twist : Music Meeting</title>
<desc lang="fr">Nubiyan Twist - Music Meeting - Since 1985, the Dutch city of Nijmegen has been welcoming the International Music Meeting Festival every Pentecost. Ranging from jazz and improvisational music to traditional music and unique crossovers, this adventurous festival is all about musical encounters and international collaborations. In 2019, the band Nubiyan Twist performs at the International Music Meeting Festival. This London-based group operates on the intersection of soul and jazz.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230323223200 +0100" stop="20230323234800 +0100" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Bixiga 70 - BIRD 2019</title>
<desc lang="fr">Bixiga 70 - BIRD 2019 - Stemming from Brazil's São Paulo, Bixiga 70 is an exciting brass and percussion-based instrumental dance ensemble that combines jazz, funk, and Afro-Brazilian music, incorporating elements from dub, reggae, electronics, cumbia, carimbo, Ethio-jazz, and samba. The name Bixiga 70 is taken from a vibrant neighbourhood in downtown São Paulo. Organic, ritualistic, and sometimes even primal, the band's music appeals to those who seek out mental and physical freedom.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230323234800 +0100" stop="20230324005700 +0100" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Skunk Anansie</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Skunk Anansie</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Les Vieilles Charrues - British alternative rock group Skunk Anansie celebrates its 25th anniversary with the album 25LIVE@25. These 90s rock scene icons, whose hair-raising shows have become legendary, celebrate their storied career with this 25-song project. With a selection of recordings taken from various 2017 live performances, Skunk Anansie once again proves its unbeatable power on stage. The setlist includes &quot;Because of You,&quot; &quot;The Skank Heads,&quot; and &quot;Tear the Place Up.&quot; Don't miss the triumphant return of these pillars of rock to the stage of the 28th edition of Les Vieilles Charrues in Carhaix, France, in 2019!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Pop &amp; Rock</category>
<icon src="https://img.bouygtel.fr/CMS/images/B4E861F64DDE40332C246A17882C053A.jpg" />
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230324005700 +0100" stop="20230324015900 +0100" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Nilüfer Yanya - Echoes Series: Nilufer Yanya</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Jane Birkin, Leonie Pernet &amp; Rone Yoyo</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Echoes Series - Episode 5 - Echoes is a modern live music show hosted by Jehnny Beth (lead singer in the British band Savages). It presents leading and emerging bands and artists from the contemporary scene. The show takes place underneath the Palais de Tokyo museum in Paris, in the club of brutalist architecture, the &quot;Yoyo.&quot; The live sets are 30 minutes long and take place on a customized stage, creating closeness with the audience. Once the bands have performed, Jehnny Beth invites everyone to sit at her roundtable for a group conversation. The open discussions in every episode allow the audience to understand the rapport, artistic exchange, and intellectual debates that run through this eclectic musical universe. The intimate, immersive space lends to the atmosphere of the show.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230324015900 +0100" stop="20230324024000 +0100" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Null + Void</title>
<desc lang="fr">Null + Void - While few people are familiar with the Null + Void project, many have already heard Kurt Uenala's music. After making his debut under the pseudonym Kap10Kurt in 2003, Uenala caught the attention of the world with the play &quot;Die Sleeping&quot;. This critical and popular success has led to collaborations with several big names in music, including Moby, The Kills, and Dave Gahan, singer of Depeche Mode, for whom Uenala has subsequently signed plays. Spending more and more time in his Manhattan studio, Uenala developed a unique sound made of angular beats and dark soundscapes, which gave rise to a new melancholy solo project called Null + Void. Cryosleep, Uenala's first album under this new banner, includes several titles inspired by retro science fiction, new wave and electronic innovators.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Pop &amp; Rock</category>
<icon src="https://img.bouygtel.fr/CMS/images/6032631D9A9B66AA23AC475B29DC2EEF.jpg" />
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230324024000 +0100" stop="20230324030000 +0100" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">The Entrepeneurs - Songbook</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">The Entrepeneurs</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">The Entrepeneurs - Songbook - &quot;I never heard anyone say that, and yeah, I know exactly what it means. It has to go in there, this has to be a song.&quot; Every song has its own story, and we all think it's a story we've heard before, but we haven't. Songbook finds and captures these intriguing stories by pulling you into the process of writing and composing. Known for its pristine sound, cinematic 4k video and eye for detail, Songbook live-captured episodes emphasize the paramount importance of quality. It addresses the on-the-spot elements of blending song and location at the right moment. Both the magical location and remarkable music interaction will get the attention they deserve. Simply because Songbook isn't just a live music session, it lives.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230324030000 +0100" stop="20230324040300 +0100" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Runtown : La Machine de Moulin Rouge</title>
<desc lang="fr">Runtown - La Machine de Moulin Rouge - Enjoy Runtown's first concert in Paris, where the Nigerian superstar brings many guests to his show. One of the most talented Nigerian afrobeat scenes will make you rediscover his greatest hits. Nigeria is a very creative country when it comes to the music scene. Runtown is no exception. His first single, &quot;Party Like It's 1980,&quot; paved the way for &quot;Gallardo,&quot; which caught the entire international scene's attention. Runtown's inspiration comes from the greats, from Salif Keita and Fela Kuti to Otis Redding and Bob Marley. An exceptional event not to be missed.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230324040300 +0100" stop="20230324050800 +0100" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Caixa Cubo - Da Pá Virada Sessions</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Martina</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Martina - Da Pá Virada Sessions - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the artists taking part in this series is Martina Marana. Vocalist, instrumentalist, and composer Martina Marana uses the power of irony to show how women instrumentalists are misjudged. In her music, Martina breaks free of sexist labels, reclaiming her own power as musician and composer. A gifted lyricist, Marana makes uncompromising, unique music.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>