<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Bouygues -->
<programme start="20230407050300 +0200" stop="20230407063300 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Clubbing Experience with Nina Kraviz @ Kappa FuturFestival</title>
<desc lang="fr">Nina Kraviz - When you're into techno, you're into Nina Kraviz. The Siberian DJ and producer has become one of the biggest names of the techno scene. From world famous stages, to intimate shows in smaller venues, Nina's hypnotic style of mixing, combined with her acid-like techno is loved by many. Kraviz went solo and made a splash in 2009, when she issued productions on Efdemin's Naïf, Jus-Ed's Underground Quality, and Matt Edwards' Rekids. Following additional singles on Rekids and Rosa, as well as the Mr. Jones EP in 2013, Kraviz founded the Trip label in 2014. Enjoy her show at Kappa FuturFestival 2019!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Musique</category>
<category lang="fr">Clips</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230407063300 +0200" stop="20230407071600 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">City Beats</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Europe</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">City Beats - Episode 6 - Europe - DJ-producer Carly Foxx is on a musical journey, immersing herself in the life of five iconic European cities to find inspiration for a series of new tracks. In this episode, Carly Foxx looks back at her journey to the music dance capitals of Europe to inspire her final track. She starts with the Balaeric beat that represents Ibiza while adding authentic bongo and guitar recordings. Then she shifts to London, where she discovers new areas and urban culture while talking to filmmaker DJ Don Letts. Carly captures the grime sound with the help of MC Yizzy and records vocals from a group of London women. Her next trip brings her to Berlin, where she produces an acid house flavored track with the 303 synthesizers.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Documentaire</category>
<category lang="fr">Téléréalité</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230407071600 +0200" stop="20230407083100 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">At L'Aéronef Lille 2017</title>
<desc lang="fr">At L'Aéronef Lille 2017 - Gossip fans, rejoice: Beth Ditto makes a big comeback! With her new album, the fiery singer launches into a solo career. With the boundless energy, undeniable humor, and legendary generosity that characterize her, the American phenomenon presents brand-new songs. Beth Ditto is more than a singer: she is an inescapable figure of the world's pop culture. As the lead singer of indie rock band Gossip (1999-2016), this young woman pulled off spectacular stage performances and gave hilarious interviews, greatly contributing to her sympathy capital. Her 2017 album mixes blues, pop, country, and rock, paying tribute to her native Arkansas in twelve eclectic and unifying pieces. Experience Beth Ditto as never before in this appearance at L'Aéronef Lille 2017!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Contemporain</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230407083100 +0200" stop="20230407090000 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Songbook</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Luwten</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Songbook - Luwten - &quot;I never heard anyone say that, and yeah, I know exactly what it means. It has to go in there, this has to be a song.&quot; Every song has its own story, and we all think it's a story we've heard before, but we haven't. Songbook finds and captures these intriguing stories by pulling you into the process of writing and composing. Known for its pristine sound, cinematic 4k video and eye for detail, Songbook live-captured episodes emphasize the paramount importance of quality. It addresses the on-the-spot elements of blending song and location at the right moment. Both the magical location and remarkable music interaction will get the attention they deserve. Simply because Songbook isn't just a live music session, it lives. This episode of Songbook features Dutch singer-songwriter Tessa Douwstra, better known as Luwten.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230407090000 +0200" stop="20230407101700 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Lalah Hathaway - Sing Jazz 2018</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Lalah Hathaway</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Lalah Hathaway - Sing Jazz 2018 - Winner of five Grammys in four consecutive years, including the Grammy for best R&amp;B album in 2017, Lalah Hathaway is a force impossible to ignore. The American artist has shared the scene with Prince, Snoop Dogg, Stevie Wonder, Anita Baker, Mary J. Blige, Frank Ocean and many others, an irrefutable proof of her keen musical sense and enormous talent. With a 26-year career, Hathaway is still highly sought after by the biggest names in music. See her transform the 2018 Sing Jazz festival scene into a real R&amp;B club, where she flaunts her voice and stage presence out of the ordinary.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<icon src="https://img.bouygtel.fr/CMS/images/E537F830342471D10D4F174FE9E53A46.jpg" />
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230407101700 +0200" stop="20230407110700 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Lucibela - WOMEX 2018</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Lucibela</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Numerous musicians, booking agents, news agencies and media companies from all over the world have been attending the &quot;World Music Exhibition&quot; World Music Expo (WOMEX) since 1994. Over the years, this music fair has settled in several European cities, including Berlin, Brussels, Marseille, Stockholm, Seville, Cardiff and Budapest. In 2018 WOMEX took place in Las Palmas in Gran Canaria. One of the participants was singer Lucibela, from the Cape Verde island of São Nicolau. </desc>
<category lang="fr">Musique</category>
<category lang="fr">Musicale</category>
<icon src="https://img.bouygtel.fr/CMS/images/BD1A4F239A69EC884BEAFFB08B575969.jpg" />
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230407110700 +0200" stop="20230407115900 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Caixa Cubo - Da Pá Virada Sessions</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Karin Fernandes</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Karin Fernandes - Da Pá Virada Sessions - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the artists taking part in this series is pianist Karin Fernandes. She is dedicated to the performance of 20th and 21st century piano repertoire and has premiered numerous new compositions. As a soloist, Karin Fernandes has performed with prestigious Brazilian orchestras.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230407115900 +0200" stop="20230407133800 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Meute</title>
<desc lang="fr">Meute - When the bass sounds and the confetti explodes, there is no doubt that Meute is a different kind of band. The band creates a whole new genre by mixing fanfare music with hypnotic techno. Meute liberates electronic music of the classic model of the DJ console. This group breaks the codes by provoking a real interaction with the audience, who will be unable to do anything but stomp their feet. This brass and percussion ensemble revolutionizes techno music while ultimately bringing it back to its roots. The eleven musicians in their iconic red jackets have already taken over the biggest festivals in Europe! Watch them on Festival 4K with their show at Trianon Paris, 2019.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230407133800 +0200" stop="20230407140900 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Audience Music</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Imagine Dragons</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Enjoy groundbreaking concerts, in-depth artist interviews, and unique stories with host Ted Stryker. This concert series gives the audience an intimate view of music's most influential artists today. Shot in 4K, host Ted Stryker interviews musicians across all genres, creating one of the most unique music shows on TV today. This episode features the multi-platinum, Grammy Award-winning band Imagine Dragons. They bring their passionately inventive alt-rock sound to a special, one-hour concert, just one month after releasing their hit song &quot;Natural.&quot; &quot;Living in a dog-eat-dog world can bring out the worst in you, and sometimes, the best,&quot; says the band's singer Dan Reynolds.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230407140900 +0200" stop="20230407150100 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Audience Music</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Sofi Tukker</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Sofi Tukker - Enjoy ground-breaking concerts, in-depth artist interviews, and unique stories with host Ted Stryker. This concert series gives the audience an intimate view of music's most influential artists today. Shot in 4K, host Ted Stryker interviews musicians across all genres, creating one of the most unique music shows on TV today. This episode features a playful performance of the New York City-based electro-pop duo Sofi Tukker. The duo's name is a stylized merge of the birth names of its members Sophie Hawley-Weld and Tucker Halpern. The two started producing music together in 2014, when they met at Rhode Island's Brown University.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230407150100 +0200" stop="20230407160600 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Caixa Cubo - Da Pá Virada Sessions</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Frederico Heliodoro</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr"> The Da Pá Virada Sessions series portrays the best musicians in Brazilian jazz today. All sessions were recorded in São Paulo and offer a unique experience, offering a fresh look at the Brazilian music scene. The artists have been selected together with the music editor of Stingray DJAZZ. Among the bands featured in this series is Caixa Cubo. Typically, this versatile trio explores the rhythmically rich Brazilian landscapes, combining them with modern Brazilian jazz trends. For this program, however, Caixa Cubo works together with vocalist Zé Leônidas, with a special repertoire that has been put together with Dani Gurgel from Da Pá Virada Sessions and Rokas Kučinskas from Stingray DJAZZ.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<icon src="https://img.bouygtel.fr/CMS/images/1F0038DC9654FF74032EAA43A24C280B.jpg" />
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230407160600 +0200" stop="20230407170500 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Nile Rodgers</title>
<desc lang="fr">The popular music performance series Front and Center premiered nationwide on public television in 2016, and now returns for Season 6. The series boasts 22, one-hour episodes and an all-star line-up. This episode features Nile Rodgers. He started his musical career by the end of the '60s. A decade later, he scored a hit with Chic's debut single &quot;Dance Dance Dance,&quot; followed by &quot;Le Freak&quot; from the second album C'est Chic. At Front and Center, Nile Rodgers performs his most well-known songs such as &quot;Get Lucky&quot; and &quot;We Are Family.&quot; In between the songs, Nile Rodgers shares personal stories about his dreams and how they have come true. Enjoy this intimate Front and Center show!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Pop &amp; Rock</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230407170500 +0200" stop="20230407183700 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">China Moses</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">&quot;Whatever&quot; at Jazz à Ramatuelle</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">China Moses: &quot;Whatever&quot; at Jazz à Ramatuelle - In 1988, Dee Dee Bridgewater was one of the first great jazz singers to perform at the Jazz Festival in Ramatuelle. In 2016, the story seems to repeat itself as her daughter China Moses took the stage at Ramatuelle. Over the years, China Moses has become a mature performer with a unique style: rocky voice, sharp sense of swing, and intense/energetic stage presence. After signing compilations dedicated to Dinah Washington and blues, Moses released in 2016 an album of his own compositions, entitled &quot;Whatever&quot;. Get ready for a most entertaining performance combining jazz, soul, and hip-hop.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230407183700 +0200" stop="20230407192700 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Ben Frost</title>
<desc lang="fr">Ben Frost - Australian Ben Frost produces under his Bedroom Community label albums inspired by post-classical electronic music, structured sound art and minimalism. His numerous collaborations testify to his desire to develop an artistic form combining music, texts, technology and performance. In this fascinating concert delivered at the Sónar Reykjavík 2018 festival, Frost once again displays his ingenuity as he presents the pieces of the album The Centre Cannot Hold. The award-winning visual artist MFO signs visual effects and lighting.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Pop &amp; Rock</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230407192700 +0200" stop="20230407202200 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">The Go! Team @ Route du Rock Hivers</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Go! Team @ Route du Rock Hivers - Originating from Brighton, UK, The Go! Team blends garage/indie rock with distorted guitars and a popping brass section. The creative force behind this six-piece band is Ian Parton. According to him, the band samples everything from Bollywood to hip-hop. Although the samples are at the heart of the band's sound, every song is kicked off by the melody. At Route du Rock Hivers 2018, The Go! Team presents its latest album, Semicircle. Its opening track Mayday is built around a drum loop based on Morse code. This is only the beginning of the endless variety of sound effects The Go! Team experiments with. At their 4K show at Rock Hivers 2018, you will enjoy a blend of noisy pop, hip-hop collages, awesome grooves, irresistible soul arrangements and much more!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Pop &amp; Rock</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230407202200 +0200" stop="20230407210000 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Classical:NEXT 2019</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Jeditah</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Classical:NEXT 2019 - Jeditah - Jeditah is an experimental songwriter, producer and singer from Amsterdam. She works with Brendan Jan Walsh on cello and Jordy Pama on synths and electronics. From an early age on, Jeditah has been immersed in the world of music, travelling with her parents as a music collective. She finds inspiration in the works of acclaimed artists like Björk, James Blake, Laurie Anderson and PJ Harvey. When she began experimenting with making her own music, she first only utilized her own voice, lowering and altering it, and eventually adding electronic beats and synths. With Electric AlleyCat, Jeditah has established her position as a singer and songwriter. In between performing and recording with the band, she creates layered soundscapes from old recordings and homemade samples.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Classique</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230407210000 +0200" stop="20230407215900 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Shawn Mendes</title>
<desc lang="fr">Shawn Mendes - Having been discovered via social media, Shawn Mendes is the youngest artist to debut his album in the top 25. The Canadian singer, songwriter and model, rose to fame by posting cover videos on Vine. Since then he became known for hits such as &quot;Stitches&quot; and &quot;There's Nothing Holdin' Me Back.&quot; On July 9, 2016, the singer, songwriter and performer surprised his fans with a free pop-up show at the Melrose Ballroom in Astoria, NYC. Enjoy this intimate concert and witness how Shawn Mendes enthralls his audience with his amazing songs!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Pop &amp; Rock</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230407215900 +0200" stop="20230407225100 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Caixa Cubo - Da Pá Virada Sessions</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Giana Viscardi</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Giana Viscardi - Da Pá Virada Sessions - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the bands taking part in this series is the duo of Giana Viscardi and Gustavo Marques. After starting their career together, Giana Viscardi and Gustavo Marques released music in many places around the world. After returning to Brazil, they worked together on Giana's album &quot;ORUM&quot;, performing in Africa, Europe, and Brazil. In this episode, Giana Viscardi and Gustavo Marques perform conductor and arranger Letieres Leite's arrangements of their work.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230407225100 +0200" stop="20230407235500 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Sleaford Mods</title>
<desc lang="fr">Sleaford Mods - Perhaps you know Sleaford Mods from their collaboration with The Prodigy on The Day Is My Enemy album for which they recorded the track &quot;Ibiza&quot; together. Jason Williamson and Andrew Fearn are Sleaford Mods, the electronic punk duo hailing from Nottingham. Up until 2012, Jason Williamson worked together with Simon Parfrement, who left the music production to Andrew Fearn. In 2015, Sleaford Mods was nominated for the IMPALA Album of the Year Award for their album Key Markets. At the 2019 We Love Green festival in Paris, they play tracks from their latest album Eton Alive.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230407235500 +0200" stop="20230408020800 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam</title>
<desc lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam - New Cool Collective is one of the foremost Dutch jazz ensembles. Pioneering new blends of music styles since 1993, NCC has performed in various formations, from small combos to larger ensembles and even big bands! The ensemble's high energy is cut out for the dance floors, as dance, Latin, salsa, afrobeat and boogaloo all meet in a jazzy mix. NCC includes saxophonist Benjamin Herman, guitarist Rory Ronde, drummer Joost Kroon, percussionists Frank van Dok and Jos de Haas, pianist Willem Friede, bassist Leslie Lopez, and trumpeter David Rockefeller.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230408020800 +0200" stop="20230408030000 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Audience Music</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Yungblud</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Yungblud - Watch groundbreaking concerts, in-depth artist interviews, and stories with host Ted Stryker. This concert series gives the audience an intimate view of music's most influential artists today. Shot in 4K, Stryker interviews musicians across all genres, creating the most unique music show on TV today. This episode features the English singer songwriter Yungblud. He grew up near Manchester in a musical family. His father owned a guitar shop, where he got his first guitar lessons. He released his first album, 21st Century Liability in 2018. In the same year, Yungblud recorded the song &quot;Falling Skies&quot; with Charlotte Lawrence, which was featured in the Netflix series 13 Reasons Why. Enjoy his exciting show at Audience Music 2019!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230408030000 +0200" stop="20230408051500 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam</title>
<desc lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam - New Cool Collective is one of the foremost Dutch jazz ensembles. Pioneering new blends of music styles since 1993, NCC has performed in various formations, from small combos to larger ensembles and even big bands! The ensemble's high energy is cut out for the dance floors, as dance, Latin, salsa, afrobeat and boogaloo all meet in a jazzy mix. NCC includes saxophonist Benjamin Herman, guitarist Rory Ronde, drummer Joost Kroon, percussionists Frank van Dok and Jos de Haas, pianist Willem Friede, bassist Leslie Lopez, and trumpeter David Rockefeller.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230408051500 +0200" stop="20230408060700 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Cabaret Contemporain</title>
<desc lang="fr">Cabaret Contemporain - &quot;Cabaret Contemporain&quot;: an explosive performance by musicians, composers, and improvisers who cross all musical boundaries with an innovative approach to the world of sound. Transforming life into dream and music into dance, the acoustic instruments are processed through an electronic filter which combines musical genres and codes. This performance is animated by the search for a new vocabulary of sounds. Enjoy this stunning live performance at the Suona Francese Festival in Rome's amazing Maxxi museum! Featuring Fabrizio Rat (piano), Giani Caserotto (guitar), Ronan Courty (bass), and Simon Drappier (bass).</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Pop &amp; Rock</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>