<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Bouygues -->
<programme start="20230505050200 +0200" stop="20230505062800 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Ryan Porter &amp; The West Coast Get Down</title>
<desc lang="fr">Ryan Porter &amp; The West Coast Get Down - BIRD - Los Angeles-born saxophonist Kamasi Washington and trombonist Ryan Porter co-founded West Coast Get Down - a musical collective fusing jazz and funk with hip-hop. It is partly because of this collective that jazz saw a resurgence in Los Angeles, subtly eclipsing the long-established jazz mecca of the world, New York City. The two musicians join forces and take the vibes of Los Angeles to jazz club BIRD in Rotterdam, the Netherlands.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230505062800 +0200" stop="20230505071700 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Sing Jazz 2018</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">House of the Gipsies</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">House of the Gipsies - Sing Jazz 2018 - Since the Gypsy Kings made their triumphal debut on the music scene with their wild Spanish rumba four decades ago, no band has dared to follow in their footsteps ... until now! House of the Gipsies updates the raw rhythms of nomadic tribes in Rajasthan, India, collaborating with Manganiyar musicians Manjoor, Nehru and Dilawar Khan. The result is a unique sound that can be described as Indo-Gypsy fusion, which is part of the evolution of the Spanish rumba. Do not miss this eclectic performance sure to please music lovers of all generations, presented at the 2018 Sing Jazz Festival.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<icon src="https://img.bouygtel.fr/CMS/images/E537F830342471D10D4F174FE9E53A46.jpg" />
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230505071700 +0200" stop="20230505082900 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Live at Vieilles Charrues</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Christine &amp; the Queens</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Live aux Vieilles Charrues - French singer Héloïse Létissier, aka Christine and the Queens, originates from Nantes, France. Her debut album Chaleur Humaine earned her a Victories of Music award in 2015, paving the way for future success. A versatile artist skilled in music and dance, she surrounds herself with the best. Among others, she collaborated with dancer and choreographer Marion Motin, who accompanied Madonna. In 2018, Christine and the Queens shortened her name to Chris and hit the international scene with a self-titled album. Her artistic work opens up a new perspective on femininity and masculinity, a hot topic today. In this concert, she inspires her audience at Les Vieilles Charrues in Carhaix, France, to dance all night long.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230505082900 +0200" stop="20230505090000 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Echoes Series: Beak</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Beak</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Echoes Series: Beak - Echoes is a modern live music show hosted by Jehnny Beth (lead singer in the British band Savages). It presents leading and emerging bands and artists from the contemporary scene. The show takes place underneath the Palais de Tokyo museum in Paris, in the club of brutalist architecture, the &quot;Yoyo.&quot; The live sets are 30 minutes long and take place on a customized stage, creating closeness with the audience. The intimate, immersive space lends to the atmosphere of the show. The artistic direction by Antoine Carlier follows a minimalist, refined and pure aesthetic, allowing the artists' energy and emotions to take center stage. This episode features the electronic project Beak. Their set includes the songs &quot;The Brazilian,&quot; &quot;Brean Down,&quot; and &quot;Allé Sauvage.&quot;</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230505090000 +0200" stop="20230505102100 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">HVOB</title>
<desc lang="fr">HVOB - The two musicians behind HVOB are Anna Müller and Paul Wallner. Anna Müller composes, produces, and provides the captivating, hypnotic vocals. The final production of the tracks is done in collaboration with Paul Wallner in his Vienna studio. HVOB are carving their path not just with their distinctive sound but with their live performances as well. The duo always plays live and performs with a drummer - a concept as innovative as it is successful: HVOB has just been voted number two best live act by the most influential German electronic music magazine &quot;De:bug.&quot; Enjoy their 2019 show at Trabendo Paris!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Contemporain</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230505102100 +0200" stop="20230505110400 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Null + Void</title>
<desc lang="fr">Null + Void - While few people are familiar with the Null + Void project, many have already heard Kurt Uenala's music. After making his debut under the pseudonym Kap10Kurt in 2003, Uenala caught the attention of the world with the play &quot;Die Sleeping&quot;. This critical and popular success has led to collaborations with several big names in music, including Moby, The Kills, and Dave Gahan, singer of Depeche Mode, for whom Uenala has subsequently signed plays. Spending more and more time in his Manhattan studio, Uenala developed a unique sound made of angular beats and dark soundscapes, which gave rise to a new melancholy solo project called Null + Void. Cryosleep, Uenala's first album under this new banner, includes several titles inspired by retro science fiction, new wave and electronic innovators.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Pop &amp; Rock</category>
<icon src="https://img.bouygtel.fr/CMS/images/6032631D9A9B66AA23AC475B29DC2EEF.jpg" />
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230505110400 +0200" stop="20230505115900 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Music Meeting</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Oum 2018</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Oum - Music Meeting Festival 2018 - Oum El Ghait Benessahraoui, who is better known as Oum, gives a unique glance at ethnic Morrocan musical esthetics. The singer-songwriter is considered to be the ambassador of Morrocan culture, too. Deeply influenced by gospel, jazz, soul and R&amp;B genres, today Oum mixes more and more African music genres, such as Sufi, Hassani, or Afrobeat. Yet, the singer's voice still echoes the colours of Aretha Franklin, Ella Fitzgerald or Whitney Houston. It is the African American vocal tradition that made a huge impact on Oum since her early days as the singer. Performing from Music Meeting Festival in Nijmegen, The Netherlands, Oum charms the stage with an exotic sonic journey to the undiscovered lands of North Africa.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230505115900 +0200" stop="20230505133700 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Jazz à Ramatuelle</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Kyle Eastwood Quintet</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Jazz à Ramatuelle: Kyle Eastwood Quintet - Bassist Kyle Eastwood (1968) is an explorer, equally at ease with jazz melodies as with pop songs. In the late 1970s, his father Clint took him to see his first jazz concert - a Count Basie performance. Eastwood Jr. was in awe of the drummer and wanted to play an instrument himself. It so happened he wasn't so much interested in jazz, preferring rhythm and blues, Motown and Stax records, funk groups, and North African and Indian music. Eastwood became a brilliant bassist and the composer of highly original soundtracks. His 2015 album &quot;Time Pieces&quot; is a collaboration with brilliant British musicians, such as trumpeter Quentin Collins and saxophonist Brandon Allen. In this broadcast, Eastwood and his fellow musicians revisit the hard bop legacy of Blue Note Records.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230505133700 +0200" stop="20230505141000 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Classical:NEXT 2019 - Lost Heritage</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Lost Heritage</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Classical:NEXT 2019 - Lost Heritage - François Vasseur and Pierre Chataignon make up the French electronic and contemporary music duo Lost Heritage. Living in the region of Geneva, they are two music lovers interested in jazz, classical, urban, and electronic music. François Vasseur is an electronic composer and pianist. He has been working on electronics for many years, starting as a DJ, then as a musician and composer, while also working in the field of cultural mediation and public engagement for organisations like the Verbier Festival, the Geneva Opera and the Lyon Baroque Music Festival. Pierre Chataignon works on various projects across many musical styles, from world music to electronic, as well as in film sound production and voice-over projects that require high quality sound recording, mixing, and production.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Classique</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230505141000 +0200" stop="20230505150100 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Audience Music</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Sofi Tukker</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Sofi Tukker - Enjoy ground-breaking concerts, in-depth artist interviews, and unique stories with host Ted Stryker. This concert series gives the audience an intimate view of music's most influential artists today. Shot in 4K, host Ted Stryker interviews musicians across all genres, creating one of the most unique music shows on TV today. This episode features a playful performance of the New York City-based electro-pop duo Sofi Tukker. The duo's name is a stylized merge of the birth names of its members Sophie Hawley-Weld and Tucker Halpern. The two started producing music together in 2014, when they met at Rhode Island's Brown University.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230505150100 +0200" stop="20230505160500 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Kintsugi</title>
<desc lang="fr">Kintsugi - Kintsugi is made up of three musicians whose eclectic musical backgrounds mix Japanese stories drawn from the depths of time: the epic life of Yoshitsune, sung and played by Kakushin Nishihara, a Tokyo sub-modern and underground artist : the incredible collision between Serge Teyssot-Gay's electric guitar (Noir Désir), Gaspar Claus' cello and the indescribable art of the Japanese Kakushin Nishihara, traditional biwa virtuoso and shamanic singer.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Pop &amp; Rock</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230505160500 +0200" stop="20230505170500 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Caixa Cubo - Da Pá Virada Sessions</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Samba das Flores</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Samba das Flores - Da Pá Virada Sessions - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the bands taking part in this series is the ensemble Samba das Flores, which dedicates itself to exploring the world's different rhythms, thus keeping the Brazilian heritage alive. The individual voices of the ensemble members color Samba das Flores's unique sound. Let Brazilian culture and global rhythms inspire you during this Samba das Flores performance!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230505170500 +0200" stop="20230505183700 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Jazz à Ramatuelle</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Fred Hersch Trio</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Since awakening from a months-long coma in 2008, Fred Hersch has experienced a spectacular physical and artistic rebirth. He filled numerous albums with his piano playing and his own compositions.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230505183700 +0200" stop="20230505192700 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Lucibela - WOMEX 2018</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Lucibela</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Numerous musicians, booking agents, news agencies and media companies from all over the world have been attending the &quot;World Music Exhibition&quot; World Music Expo (WOMEX) since 1994. Over the years, this music fair has settled in several European cities, including Berlin, Brussels, Marseille, Stockholm, Seville, Cardiff and Budapest. In 2018 WOMEX took place in Las Palmas in Gran Canaria. One of the participants was singer Lucibela, from the Cape Verde island of São Nicolau. </desc>
<category lang="fr">Musique</category>
<category lang="fr">Musicale</category>
<icon src="https://img.bouygtel.fr/CMS/images/1D14586B338B45FF536A544BE4E8F5E0.jpg" />
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230505192700 +0200" stop="20230505202300 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Sheryl Crow</title>
<desc lang="fr">Sheryl Crow - Missouri-born country mega-star Sheryl Crow celebrates her return to the stage in an intimate performance at New York City's Iridium. Having sold over million copies of her ten studio albums worldwide over the course of her over three decade-long career, Sheryl Crow has long-established a status of one of America's most successful musicians. With a warm sound made up of elements of country, pop, rock and Americana, Crow has received nine GRAMMY-awards and over thirty nominations.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Pop &amp; Rock</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230505202300 +0200" stop="20230505210000 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Ensemble Offspring</title>
<desc lang="fr">Ensemble Offspring - Ensemble Offspring is Australia's foremost new music ensemble, based in Sydney, made up of flute, clarinet, violin, cello, piano, and percussion. At Classical:NEXT, the ensemble features a line-up of internationally acclaimed core instrumentalists, Claire Edwardes (percussionist/artistic director), Zubin Kanga (piano), Jason Noble (clarinet), and Lamorna Nightingale (flute). With a 23-year history, the group embraces all modes of adventurous music making, which has brought to fruition the creation of over 200 new works. The 2019 Classical:Next showcase programme Solitude features two works written for the ensemble by Kate Moore (&quot;Fern&quot;) and Andrea Keller (&quot;Love in Solitude&quot;).</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Classique</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230505210000 +0200" stop="20230505215900 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Shawn Mendes</title>
<desc lang="fr">Shawn Mendes - Having been discovered via social media, Shawn Mendes is the youngest artist to debut his album in the top 25. The Canadian singer, songwriter and model, rose to fame by posting cover videos on Vine. Since then he became known for hits such as &quot;Stitches&quot; and &quot;There's Nothing Holdin' Me Back.&quot; On July 9, 2016, the singer, songwriter and performer surprised his fans with a free pop-up show at the Melrose Ballroom in Astoria, NYC. Enjoy this intimate concert and witness how Shawn Mendes enthralls his audience with his amazing songs!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Pop &amp; Rock</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230505215900 +0200" stop="20230505225100 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Cabaret Contemporain</title>
<desc lang="fr">Cabaret Contemporain - &quot;Cabaret Contemporain&quot;: an explosive performance by musicians, composers, and improvisers who cross all musical boundaries with an innovative approach to the world of sound. Transforming life into dream and music into dance, the acoustic instruments are processed through an electronic filter which combines musical genres and codes. This performance is animated by the search for a new vocabulary of sounds. Enjoy this stunning live performance at the Suona Francese Festival in Rome's amazing Maxxi museum! Featuring Fabrizio Rat (piano), Giani Caserotto (guitar), Ronan Courty (bass), and Simon Drappier (bass).</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Pop &amp; Rock</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230505225100 +0200" stop="20230505235500 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Jesse Cook - Follow the Road</title>
<desc lang="fr">Celebrated guitarist, composer, and music producer Jesse Cook has been delivering unforgettable concert experiences to audiences across the globe for over 25 years. As far as he has ventured, Jesse has always been fascinated with the mystique of the road that first led him out of Toronto. In his directorial debut, Cook shows us a concert from a rarely seen perspective: the musician's. Born to film director parents, guitarist Jesse Cook taps into this pedigree, and self-directed this story, his fifth Concert Special. The result is &quot;Follow the Road.&quot; Captured in 4K, during his 31-city cross-Canada tour, we follow the band down the TransCanada Highway, against a backdrop of majestic mountains and stunning natural beauty, as they traverse the scenic splendor of the second largest country in the world.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Documentaire</category>
<category lang="fr">Musique</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230505235500 +0200" stop="20230506020800 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam</title>
<desc lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam - New Cool Collective is one of the foremost Dutch jazz ensembles. Pioneering new blends of music styles since 1993, NCC has performed in various formations, from small combos to larger ensembles and even big bands! The ensemble's high energy is cut out for the dance floors, as dance, Latin, salsa, afrobeat and boogaloo all meet in a jazzy mix. NCC includes saxophonist Benjamin Herman, guitarist Rory Ronde, drummer Joost Kroon, percussionists Frank van Dok and Jos de Haas, pianist Willem Friede, bassist Leslie Lopez, and trumpeter David Rockefeller.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230506020800 +0200" stop="20230506030000 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Seine Sessions: Jazz</title>
<desc lang="fr">Seine Sessions: Jazz - The term &quot;jam-session&quot; was coined in the 1920s when black and white musicians gathered in smoke-filled bars after their respective concerts to enjoy the kind of jazz they could not play in traditional sets. Bing Crosby was a regular at these sessions, and had fun marking the first and third beats of musical phrases by clapping hands, which the musicians call &quot;jammin 'the beat&quot;. Today, the Seine Sessions is bringing back the happy years of &quot;jam sessions&quot;, while the best of the jazz, blues, gipsy, and funk Parisian scenes occurs on the boards of the legendary restaurant and jazz club Le Réservoir. This episode, hosted by Eddy King, Sally Zemour, and Virgile Aiana features unique jazz performances by artists playing together for the first time and interviews with Fantazio, Eddy Lopez, Benoît Savard, and many others.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230506030000 +0200" stop="20230506051500 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam</title>
<desc lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam - New Cool Collective is one of the foremost Dutch jazz ensembles. Pioneering new blends of music styles since 1993, NCC has performed in various formations, from small combos to larger ensembles and even big bands! The ensemble's high energy is cut out for the dance floors, as dance, Latin, salsa, afrobeat and boogaloo all meet in a jazzy mix. NCC includes saxophonist Benjamin Herman, guitarist Rory Ronde, drummer Joost Kroon, percussionists Frank van Dok and Jos de Haas, pianist Willem Friede, bassist Leslie Lopez, and trumpeter David Rockefeller.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230506051500 +0200" stop="20230506061500 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">  Creamfields</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Green Velvet, MK, Carl Cox &amp; deadmau5</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Creamfields - Having burst onto the ever-growing festival scene two decades ago, Creamfields has secured its spot as being one of the - if not the - biggest weekend dedicated to electronic music in the UK. Currently, the clubbing and raving pilgrimage attracts an impressive 70,000 festival-goers over the weekend. Continuously offering up the very best in EDM, house, trance, drum and bass, grime, and more, Creamfields has hosted some massive names over the past twenty years. This 2019 edition of Creamfields presents Green Velvet, MK, Carl Cox, Deadmau5, Camelphat, Nicole Moudaber, Dimitri Vegas &amp; Like Mike, and many more!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>