<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Bouygues -->
<programme start="20230502050500 +0200" stop="20230502060500 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Mestrinho : Da Pá Virada Sessions</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Mestrinho</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Mestrinho - Da Pá Virada Sessions - Da Pá Virada sessions bring the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the artists taking part in this series is accordionist Mestrinho, seen in performance with Cainã Cavalcante on guitar, Alex Buck on drums, and Carlinhos Noronha on bass. They combine the subtle rhythms of Brazilian music with the leader's instrumental virtuosity.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230502060500 +0200" stop="20230502073800 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">China Moses</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">&quot;Whatever&quot; at Jazz à Ramatuelle</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">China Moses: &quot;Whatever&quot; at Jazz à Ramatuelle - In 1988, Dee Dee Bridgewater was one of the first great jazz singers to perform at the Jazz Festival in Ramatuelle. In 2016, the story seems to repeat itself as her daughter China Moses took the stage at Ramatuelle. Over the years, China Moses has become a mature performer with a unique style: rocky voice, sharp sense of swing, and intense/energetic stage presence. After signing compilations dedicated to Dinah Washington and blues, Moses released in 2016 an album of his own compositions, entitled &quot;Whatever&quot;. Get ready for a most entertaining performance combining jazz, soul, and hip-hop.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230502073800 +0200" stop="20230502081100 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Classical:NEXT 2019</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Tricia Dawn Williams</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr"> Tricia Dawn Williams - Transition is a portrait of the avant-garde piano stretching almost one hundred years. Each piece on the programme breaks new ground as the music navigates through uncharted waters to depict a new profile for the instrument. Transition by Tricia Dawn Williams is a unique experience that transforms the piano recital into an interdisciplinary performance featuring gesture-control technology, video-art, electronic music and extended piano technique. Born in Malta, of Irish and Welsh descent, Tricia Dawn Williams is committed to contemporary music, multimedia and new technologies. Williams is one of the first concert pianists to collaborate with developers and composers internationally on the application of gesture-control technology.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Classique</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230502081100 +0200" stop="20230502090000 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Classical:NEXT 2019</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Jeditah</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Classical:NEXT 2019 - Jeditah - Jeditah is an experimental songwriter, producer and singer from Amsterdam. She works with Brendan Jan Walsh on cello and Jordy Pama on synths and electronics. From an early age on, Jeditah has been immersed in the world of music, travelling with her parents as a music collective. She finds inspiration in the works of acclaimed artists like Björk, James Blake, Laurie Anderson and PJ Harvey. When she began experimenting with making her own music, she first only utilized her own voice, lowering and altering it, and eventually adding electronic beats and synths. With Electric AlleyCat, Jeditah has established her position as a singer and songwriter. In between performing and recording with the band, she creates layered soundscapes from old recordings and homemade samples.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Classique</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230502090000 +0200" stop="20230502100700 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Sgt. Pepper Tribute at Philharmonie de Paris 2017</title>
<desc lang="fr">Sgt. Pepper Tribute at Philharmonie de Paris 2017 - Celebrated as one of the most influential albums of all times, The Beatles' 1967 Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band marked its time and inspired generations of artists. While the album was purely a recording studio product, Beatles' fans continue to be frustrated by not hearing it live. British musician and composer Ed Harcourt, author of six highly acclaimed albums and collaborator of vocalists Marianne Faithfull, Patti Smith, and trumpeter Erik Truffaz, gathered a supergroup for this occasion with top artists from the British independent rock scene. Join Ed Harcourt and members of The Libertines, Supergrass, The Coral, the Beta Band, and Primal Scream for this special tribute.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230502100700 +0200" stop="20230502110800 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Runtown : La Machine de Moulin Rouge</title>
<desc lang="fr">Runtown - La Machine de Moulin Rouge - Enjoy Runtown's first concert in Paris, where the Nigerian superstar brings many guests to his show. One of the most talented Nigerian afrobeat scenes will make you rediscover his greatest hits. Nigeria is a very creative country when it comes to the music scene. Runtown is no exception. His first single, &quot;Party Like It's 1980,&quot; paved the way for &quot;Gallardo,&quot; which caught the entire international scene's attention. Runtown's inspiration comes from the greats, from Salif Keita and Fela Kuti to Otis Redding and Bob Marley. An exceptional event not to be missed.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230502110800 +0200" stop="20230502124000 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Banda Magda live at BIRD Rotterdam</title>
<desc lang="fr">Banda Magda: live at BIRD Rotterdam - An irresistible live act, Banda Magda is full of humour, unflagging energy, and quirky sensibility. A tight-knit group of musicians, they turn the songs of Greek-born founder, singer, and composer Magda Giannikou into engaging gems that have taken the band to legendary venues like Carnegie Hall and, for this performance, BIRD Rotterdam. Banda Magda moves from samba to French chanson, Greek folk music to Colombian cumbia and Afro-Peruvian landó. Their songs capture the best of mid-century ballads and cinematic arrangements, drawing from the band's global background and unrestrained musicality. A joy to experience, Banda Magda makes music for a new generation that's been inspired by ones before.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230502124000 +0200" stop="20230502132800 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">James Arthur</title>
<desc lang="fr">James Arthur - British pop singer James Arthur, best known for his power ballads &quot;Impossible&quot; (2013) and &quot;Say You Won't Let Go&quot; (2016), gives an intimate concert at New York City's Iridium. After winning the ninth season of UK's The X Factor in 2011, his powerful voice quickly helped him rise to the top of international pop charts.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230502132800 +0200" stop="20230502142200 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Rooted With Wings</title>
<desc lang="fr">Rooted With Wings - Rooted with Wings is a visual dance documentary that explores the work of internationally acclaimed choreographer and dancer Tero Saarinen, granting the viewer a unique lens into this extraordinary artist's creative process. The film brings to light how Saarinen's dance works evolve from an idea or concept into a finished performance and features stunningly captured dance sequences and behind-the-scenes material from around the globe. The film follows Saarinen over five years, from 2014 to 2018, through several premieres of new works and tours in Finland, France, Korea, Kenya, and the US, while bringing to light his approach to his life as a global nomad in dance.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Documentaire</category>
<category lang="fr">Sport</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230502142200 +0200" stop="20230502150200 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Audience Music</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Urban Cone</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Urban Cone - Watch groundbreaking concerts, in-depth artist interviews, and stories with host Ted Stryker. This concert series gives the audience an intimate view of music's most influential artists today. Shot in 4K, Stryker interviews musicians across all genres, creating the most unique music show on TV today. This episode features the Swedish indie pop band Urban Cone. The band was formed in 2010 by Emil Gustafsson, Tim Formgren, Rasmus Flyckt, Jacob William Sjöberg, and Magnus Folkö. Their debut EP Our Youth came about when they were only 16 years old. The album was recorded in Flyckt's living room. The album's debut single &quot;Urban Photograph&quot; reached #2 on Hype Machine. A tour to the U.S. followed, with performances in New York City, Brooklyn, Los Angeles, and San Francisco.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Pop &amp; Rock</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230502150200 +0200" stop="20230502163400 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">La Mambanegra : Music Meeting Festival</title>
<desc lang="fr">La Mambanegra - Music Meeting Festival 2018 - The latin music orchestra, La Mambanegra, combines many musical elements, such as Jamaican or Colombian music, as well as Funk and Hip Hop. Yet, their main musical influence comes from 1970s New York, where during the time Salsa was born. The magic of the genre, however, is given new colours by La Mambanegra: with a series of fantastic adventures in Cali, La Habana and New York, the band's music is inspired by an anonymous and even mythical hero of the Cali's popular neighborhood Barrio Obrero. Consisting of 8 talented musicians, La Mambanegra presents their charming showcase at the Music Meeting Festival in Nijmegen, The Netherlands.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<icon src="https://img.bouygtel.fr/CMS/images/D4B0F3F8A6F2CB76DAF0FF96B710D450.jpg" />
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230502163400 +0200" stop="20230502173300 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">lovelytheband</title>
<desc lang="fr">Formed in West Hollywood in 2016, lovelytheband features former Oh Honey member Mitchy Collins along with guitarist Jordan Greenwald and drummer Sam Price. The band debuted in July 2017 with the Christian Medice-produced &quot;Broken,&quot; a sprightly and infectious single that quickly racked up over three million digital streams. Signing with Another Century Records, lovelytheband released their debut EP &quot;Everything I Could&quot; in September of that year and joined Vance Joy and AWOLNATION on tour. In April 2018, &quot;Broken&quot; was still going strong and hit number one on the Billboard Alternative Songs Airplay chart. That August, lovelytheband returned with their full-length debut album, Finding It Hard to Smile.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Pop &amp; Rock</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230502173300 +0200" stop="20230502194600 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam</title>
<desc lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam - New Cool Collective is one of the foremost Dutch jazz ensembles. Pioneering new blends of music styles since 1993, NCC has performed in various formations, from small combos to larger ensembles and even big bands! The ensemble's high energy is cut out for the dance floors, as dance, Latin, salsa, afrobeat and boogaloo all meet in a jazzy mix. NCC includes saxophonist Benjamin Herman, guitarist Rory Ronde, drummer Joost Kroon, percussionists Frank van Dok and Jos de Haas, pianist Willem Friede, bassist Leslie Lopez, and trumpeter David Rockefeller.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230502194600 +0200" stop="20230502210000 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Live From the Kennedy Center</title>
<desc lang="fr">Live From the Kennedy Center - When Nas was just 19 years old, he composed what would become one of hip-hop's defining masterpieces, Illmatic. To mark its 20th anniversary, Nas delivers a standout performance alongside the National Symphony Orchestra at Washington DC's Kennedy Center. With conductor Steven Reineke taking the orchestra through arrangements of beats by DJ Premier and Large Professor, Nas delivers impassioned renditions of tracks like &quot;N.Y. State of Mind&quot;, &quot;The World Is Yours&quot;, and &quot;Memory Lane (Sittin' in Da Park)&quot;. Between songs, the program cuts away to both archival and new interview footage to document Nas' rise from Queensbridge upstart to influential rap icon.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Pop &amp; Rock</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230502210000 +0200" stop="20230502223700 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Opera Imaginaire</title>
<desc lang="fr">Opera Imaginaire - To celebrate Le Concert Spirituel's 30th anniversary, conductor Hervé Niquet collaborated with the Baroque Music Center of Versailles to build his opéra imaginaire. For this unique project, Le Concert Spirituel presents an original performance of unpublished operas by Lully, Rameau, Charpentier, and many other French baroque composers. You will find yourself captivated by a tearful lover, intrigued by the passage to the underworld, and fascinated by the descents of the Gods. The program includes many favorite passages, such as Lully's Armide, Charpentier's Medea, and Campra's Carnaval de Venise. Experience all the magic of Louis XIV's French opera as Le Concert Spirituel transforms the Théâtre des Champs-Elysées into a true French baroque scene.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Opéra</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230502223700 +0200" stop="20230502233700 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Robin Schulz, Sam Feldt, Afrojack &amp; Alle Farben - Parookaville</title>
<desc lang="fr">Parookaville - Parookaville is a city that comes to life once a year to keep the legend of Bill Parooka alive. It was started as an artistic, free-flowing, wild, and musical place where people could connect with their pure selves, experience real connections, and feel a deep sense of bliss and fulfillment. Step into the darkness if you dare, follow your inner light and immerse yourself in a spectacular world of freedom and love! Only four years since the first event, this festival has already become one of Germany's most prevalent music festivals. This edition features Armin van Buuren, Showtek, Robin Schulz, and W&amp;W.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230502233700 +0200" stop="20230503003800 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Maceo Plex - Audio Obscura x Rijksmuseum</title>
<desc lang="fr">Audio Obscura x Rijksmuseum - The American DJ/producer - known for his enigmatic combinations of grooving, melancholic and ecstatic house and techno - visited the museum for some ground-level inspiration, and will share this during this once a lifetime event under the ever so stunning Rijksmuseum. This is the first time the museum collaborates on a project that revolves around electronic music, matching its vision to inspire visitors and to let them experience art in exciting new ways Initiated by Audio Obscura, this is the next step in connecting world-class artists with legendary, historical locations.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230503003800 +0200" stop="20230503015400 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">At L'Aéronef Lille 2017</title>
<desc lang="fr">At L'Aéronef Lille 2017 - Gossip fans, rejoice: Beth Ditto makes a big comeback! With her new album, the fiery singer launches into a solo career. With the boundless energy, undeniable humor, and legendary generosity that characterize her, the American phenomenon presents brand-new songs. Beth Ditto is more than a singer: she is an inescapable figure of the world's pop culture. As the lead singer of indie rock band Gossip (1999-2016), this young woman pulled off spectacular stage performances and gave hilarious interviews, greatly contributing to her sympathy capital. Her 2017 album mixes blues, pop, country, and rock, paying tribute to her native Arkansas in twelve eclectic and unifying pieces. Experience Beth Ditto as never before in this appearance at L'Aéronef Lille 2017!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Contemporain</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230503015400 +0200" stop="20230503030000 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Caixa Cubo - Da Pá Virada Sessions</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Os Capoeira</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Os Capoeira - Da Pá Virada Sessions - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the bands taking part in this series is Os Capoeira. This ensemble practices the traditional Brazilian martial art from Bahia it is named after, combining elements of dance, acrobatics, and percussive music. Moreover, Os Capoeira runs a cultural center in São Paulo. Let yourself be inspired by Os Capoeira's unique take on Brazilian culture!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230503030000 +0200" stop="20230503034500 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">WOMEX 2018</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Kim So Ra</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Kim So Ra - WOMEX 2018 - Since 1994, World Music Expo (WOMEX) has been attracting musicians, agents, a great number of press agencies, as well as media companies from all over the world. Its main exposition event has been held in various locations throughout Europe, including Berlin, Brussels, Marseille, Stockholm, Seville, Cardiff, and Budapest. In 2018, WOMEX was held in Las Palmas, Gran Canaria. One of its showcase participants, Korean percussionist Kim So Ra, has played the hourglass-shaped, two-headed drum known as janggu since she was a child. Quietly, she has been taking revolutionary steps to modernize perceptions within traditional Korean music.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Musique</category>
<category lang="fr">Musicale</category>
<icon src="https://img.bouygtel.fr/CMS/images/BD1A4F239A69EC884BEAFFB08B575969.jpg" />
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230503034500 +0200" stop="20230503044400 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Caixa Cubo - Da Pá Virada Sessions</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Andre Marques</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Andre Marques - Da Pá Virada Sessions - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the artists taking part in this series is pianist, composer, and arranger André Marques. He has been building a solid career, releasing his music with numerous groups: he is a member of the Latin Grammy-nominated Trio Curupira, the André Marques Sexteto, and he leads the Brazilian music orchestra Vintena Brasileira. In this episode of Da Pá Virada Sessions, André Marques performs an intimate solo piano recital.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230503044400 +0200" stop="20230503054600 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Liran Donin : Music Meeting</title>
<desc lang="fr">Nijmegen has been welcoming the International Music Meeting Festival, or Music Meeting for short, every spring since 1985. From jazz and improvised music to traditional music and unique crossovers: musical encounters and international collaborations are at the heart of this adventurous festival. In 2019, Tel Aviv-born bassist, producer and composer Liran Donin performed here. </desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230503054600 +0200" stop="20230503064800 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Marius Neset : Jazz in Duketown</title>
<desc lang="fr">Marius Neset - Jazz in Duketown - Jazz in Duketown is the largest free outdoor jazz festival in the Netherlands. It's a real gathering for jazz addicts, inviting internationally renowned artists. In 2019, one of them is Copenhagen-based Norwegian saxophonist Marius Neset, who is known internationally for his collaborations with People Are Machines, Kaktusch, JazzKamikaze, and Django Bates' projects StoRMChaser and Human Chain. Neset completed his Master's degree at the Copenhagen Rhythmic Music Conservatory in 2008.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>