<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Bouygues -->
<programme start="20230326050700 +0200" stop="20230326064000 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Jazz à Ramatuelle</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Fred Hersch Trio</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Fred Hersch Trio - Jazz à Ramatuelle - At the age of 63, Fred Hersch is unquestionably one of today's key figures in jazz piano. His music touches upon millions of nuances, contains a keen sense of harmony, and displays an intrinsic knowledge of the standard repertoire. What else made him the teacher of Brad Mehldau and sideman of Stan Getz, Joe Henderson and Art Farmer? Since his recovery from a long coma in 2008, Fred Hersch has experienced a spectacular artistic renaissance. With numerous albums as composer as well as interpreter, he has managed to establish himself as a role model of jazz piano. Supported by John Hebert (double bass) and Eric McPherson (drums), Fred Hersch showcases his unparalleled technique and sensitivity at Jazz à Ramatuelle 2018.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230326064000 +0200" stop="20230326072200 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">City Beats</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Ibiza</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">City Beats - Episode 2 - Ibiza - DJ-producer Carly Foxx is on a musical journey, immersing herself in the life of five iconic European cities to find inspiration for a series of new tracks. In this episode, Carly Foxx travels to the world's clubbing capital to inspire her music track and discovers Ibiza's alternative spiritual side. She starts her journey in San Antonio but discovers this place is mainly about clubbing and drinking - not very inspiring for her music track. The next stop is Old Town, where Carly meets female Ibiza singer Sam Smith, who introduces her to DJ and producer Manu Gonzalez. While talking to him, Carly decides the base of her Ibiza-inspired track should be a Balearic beat, to which she plans to add bongos and castanet samples.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Documentaire</category>
<category lang="fr">Téléréalité</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230326072200 +0200" stop="20230326082300 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Robin Schulz, Sam Feldt, Afrojack &amp; Alle Farben - Parookaville</title>
<desc lang="fr">Parookaville - Parookaville is a city that comes to life once a year to keep the legend of Bill Parooka alive. It was started as an artistic, free-flowing, wild, and musical place where people could connect with their pure selves, experience real connections, and feel a deep sense of bliss and fulfillment. Step into the darkness if you dare, follow your inner light and immerse yourself in a spectacular world of freedom and love! Only four years since the first event, this festival has already become one of Germany's most prevalent music festivals. This edition features Armin van Buuren, Showtek, Robin Schulz, and W&amp;W.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230326082300 +0200" stop="20230326090000 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Classical:NEXT 2019</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Śniedź</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Classical:NEXT 2019 - Śniedź - Śniedź is a voice and electronics duo from Warsaw, Poland who combine extended vocal techniques with improvised, self-named &quot;glitchtronica.&quot; Singer, performer, and sound artist Aleksandra Klimczak frequently breaks boundaries between art genres through cooperating with young artists from different artistic fields. Her work has been awarded from scholarships from the Polish Ministry of Culture and the Capital City of Warsaw. Music curator Antoni Beksiak deals with contemporary crossover, ethnic, classical, jazz, and pop music in his work as an initiator, critic and creator. During this showcase recorded at Classical:NEXT 2019 in Rotterdam, The Netherlands the perform a set list of their own works.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Classique</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230326090000 +0200" stop="20230326111500 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam</title>
<desc lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam - New Cool Collective is one of the foremost Dutch jazz ensembles. Pioneering new blends of music styles since 1993, NCC has performed in various formations, from small combos to larger ensembles and even big bands! The ensemble's high energy is cut out for the dance floors, as dance, Latin, salsa, afrobeat and boogaloo all meet in a jazzy mix. NCC includes saxophonist Benjamin Herman, guitarist Rory Ronde, drummer Joost Kroon, percussionists Frank van Dok and Jos de Haas, pianist Willem Friede, bassist Leslie Lopez, and trumpeter David Rockefeller.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230326111500 +0200" stop="20230326120900 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Caixa Cubo - Da Pá Virada Sessions</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Os Capoeira</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Os Capoeira - Da Pá Virada Sessions - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the bands taking part in this series is Os Capoeira. This ensemble practices the traditional Brazilian martial art from Bahia it is named after, combining elements of dance, acrobatics, and percussive music. Moreover, Os Capoeira runs a cultural center in São Paulo. Let yourself be inspired by Os Capoeira's unique take on Brazilian culture!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230326120900 +0200" stop="20230326131900 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Irène Drésel</title>
<desc lang="fr">Irène Drésel - The world of Irène Drésel can be described as high-colored techno, sensual, and bold. It's a hypnotic world where languid and sporty BPMs rub shoulders with crystalline melodies, foiling the expectations of techno listeners. A polymorphic artist who has left the frenzy of Paris for the calm of the countryside, Irène Drésel tends to her universe down to the smallest details, as evidenced on stage by the roses that gracefully overhang the cold steel of her machines. Irène Drésel composes alone, but she is accompanied live by a percussionist, Sizo Del Givry. Enjoy their 2019 show at Trabendo Paris!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Rap &amp; Techno</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230326131900 +0200" stop="20230326143400 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Lalah Hathaway - Sing Jazz 2018</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Lalah Hathaway</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Lalah Hathaway - Sing Jazz 2018 - Winner of five Grammys in four consecutive years, including the Grammy for best R&amp;B album in 2017, Lalah Hathaway is a force impossible to ignore. The American artist has shared the scene with Prince, Snoop Dogg, Stevie Wonder, Anita Baker, Mary J. Blige, Frank Ocean and many others, an irrefutable proof of her keen musical sense and enormous talent. With a 26-year career, Hathaway is still highly sought after by the biggest names in music. See her transform the 2018 Sing Jazz festival scene into a real R&amp;B club, where she flaunts her voice and stage presence out of the ordinary.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<icon src="https://img.bouygtel.fr/CMS/images/E537F830342471D10D4F174FE9E53A46.jpg" />
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230326143400 +0200" stop="20230326150200 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Cold Storage</title>
<desc lang="fr">Cold Storage - The Finnish dancer and film maker Thomas Freundlich created 'Cold Storage', a short dance film that pays homage to the virtuosic physical performances and melancholy comedy of the classic silent screen. As a lonely ice fisherman discovers his frozen prehistoric soul brother in the ice, multiple levels of time and reality blend together into a cinematic and kinetic exploration of alienation, dependency and friendship. In this choreography by Valtteri Raekallio, Eero Vesterinen and Valtteri Raekallio dance to the music of the internationally renowned avant-garde accordionist Kimmo Pohjonen.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Film</category>
<category lang="fr">Comédie</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230326150200 +0200" stop="20230326162200 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">The Opera Locos</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Opera Locos - In The Opera Locos (&quot;The Opera of Crazies&quot;), a comic opera show from the Spanish theater company Yllana and theatre producer Rami Eldar, five eccentric opera singers perform some of the greatest opera arias. Classical arias from George Bizet's Carmen, W. A. Mozart's The Magic Flute, and Giuseppe Verdi's Rigoletto are combined with classics from the pop and rock repertoire. During the performance, the five characters reveal their hidden passions, personalities, and desires, leading to unpredictable, hilarious situations that audiences of all ages will appreciate. The soloists are Florian Laconi (tenor), Margaux Toqué (mezzo soprano), Michaël Koné (countertenor), Laurent Arcaro (baritone), and Diane Fourès (soprano). This performance was recorded at Théâtre Libre in Paris, France.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Musique</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230326162200 +0200" stop="20230326171100 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Ben Frost</title>
<desc lang="fr">Ben Frost - Australian Ben Frost produces under his Bedroom Community label albums inspired by post-classical electronic music, structured sound art and minimalism. His numerous collaborations testify to his desire to develop an artistic form combining music, texts, technology and performance. In this fascinating concert delivered at the Sónar Reykjavík 2018 festival, Frost once again displays his ingenuity as he presents the pieces of the album The Centre Cannot Hold. The award-winning visual artist MFO signs visual effects and lighting.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Pop &amp; Rock</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230326171100 +0200" stop="20230326180300 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Ramón Valle &amp; Reinier Baas : Music Meeting 2020</title>
<desc lang="fr">Ramón Valle &amp; Reinier Baas - Music Meeting 2020 - Since 1985, the Dutch city of Nijmegen has been welcoming the International Music Meeting Festival every Pentecost. Ranging from jazz and improvisational music to traditional music and unique crossovers, this adventurous festival is all about musical encounters and international collaborations. Disrupted by COVID-19, the festival's 2020 edition had to adapt to new challenges. It now presents this exclusive concert by pianist Ramón Valle and guitarist Reinier Baas, filmed at Concertgebouw De Vereeniging in Nijmegen.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230326180300 +0200" stop="20230326194100 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Jazz à Ramatuelle : Omar Sosa</title>
<desc lang="fr">Jazz à Ramatuelle: Omar Sosa - Experience the incredible richness of our world's music in this performance by the unparalleled Afro-Cuban pianist Omar Sosa! Whilst staying true to Cuban music traditions, Sosa shows an insatiable curiosity: tirelessly exploring music from around the world - from the Caribbean to India and from West Africa to the Arab World - nothing seems to escape his thirst for discovery. A celebration of rhythm in all its forms, this Omar Sosa concert from the French Ramatuelle Jazz Festival promises an intense mystical experience!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230326194100 +0200" stop="20230326200000 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Audience Music</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Imagine Dragons</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Enjoy groundbreaking concerts, in-depth artist interviews, and unique stories with host Ted Stryker. This concert series gives the audience an intimate view of music's most influential artists today. Shot in 4K, host Ted Stryker interviews musicians across all genres, creating one of the most unique music shows on TV today. This episode features the multi-platinum, Grammy Award-winning band Imagine Dragons. They bring their passionately inventive alt-rock sound to a special, one-hour concert, just one month after releasing their hit song &quot;Natural.&quot; &quot;Living in a dog-eat-dog world can bring out the worst in you, and sometimes, the best,&quot; says the band's singer Dan Reynolds.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230326200000 +0200" stop="20230326220900 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Above &amp; Beyond Group Therapy 300</title>
<desc lang="fr">Above &amp; Beyond Group Therapy 300 - Above and Beyond recently made their mark on ABGT300 in an epic way. Live for the 300th edition of Group Therapy Radio, the group broadcast from The Asiaworld-Expo in Hong Kong on September 29, 2018. ABGT300 also saw live performances from Andrew Bayer, Ben Böhmer, Grum, Ilan Bluestone, and Spencer Brown, with the signature set from Above and Beyond as the main event. This year, they wanted to push Group Therapy to the next level. Get ready for some magic moments and excellent music.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230326220900 +0200" stop="20230326230800 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Caixa Cubo - Da Pá Virada Sessions</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Andre Marques</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Andre Marques - Da Pá Virada Sessions - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the artists taking part in this series is pianist, composer, and arranger André Marques. He has been building a solid career, releasing his music with numerous groups: he is a member of the Latin Grammy-nominated Trio Curupira, the André Marques Sexteto, and he leads the Brazilian music orchestra Vintena Brasileira. In this episode of Da Pá Virada Sessions, André Marques performs an intimate solo piano recital.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230326230800 +0200" stop="20230327030000 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Leçons de ténèbres, de Michel-Richard de Lalande</title>
<desc lang="fr">Lalande - Leçons de ténèbres - Harpsichordist and organist Sébastien Daucé conducts Ensemble Correspondances and soloist Sophie Karthäuser (soprano) in a performance of Michel-Richard de Lalande's (1657-1726) sacred music piece Les Leçons des Ténèbres ('lessons of darkness'). To round off the period of Lent leading up to Easter, the congregation sings these Lamentations of Jeremiah in church. With each psalm, one of the candles is extinguished until complete darkness and silence ensues. Whatever one's faith, this tradition is a unique spiritual experience. French baroque composer Michel-Richard de Lalande, an important composer of &quot;grands&quot; motets of unprecedented length, was one of many who wrote music for this religious practice. This performance was recorded at Chapelle Corneille in Rouen, France in 2016.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Classique</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230327030000 +0200" stop="20230327040300 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Marius Neset : Jazz in Duketown</title>
<desc lang="fr">Marius Neset - Jazz in Duketown - Jazz in Duketown is the largest free outdoor jazz festival in the Netherlands. It's a real gathering for jazz addicts, inviting internationally renowned artists. In 2019, one of them is Copenhagen-based Norwegian saxophonist Marius Neset, who is known internationally for his collaborations with People Are Machines, Kaktusch, JazzKamikaze, and Django Bates' projects StoRMChaser and Human Chain. Neset completed his Master's degree at the Copenhagen Rhythmic Music Conservatory in 2008.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230327040300 +0200" stop="20230327050400 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Frequencerz @ Airbeat One</title>
<desc lang="fr">Frequencerz @ Airbeat One - Frequencerz is a Dutch hardstyle duo formed by Pepijn Hol and Niels Koster. In 2009, they signed their contract with the Fusion Records label. Since then, they've released a good number of albums, such as Medium Rare, S.T.F.U. / G.T.F.O, and Phaser. With their performances for huge crowds at Defqon.1, Decibel Outdoor, and The Qontinent, they've established themselves as one of the biggest hardstyle acts of today. Their show at the German Airbeat One festival underlines their reputation. Expect nothing but spectacular light shows, non-stop jumpstyle, and a crazy crowd!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230327050400 +0200" stop="20230327063700 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">China Moses</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">&quot;Whatever&quot; at Jazz à Ramatuelle</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">China Moses: &quot;Whatever&quot; at Jazz à Ramatuelle - In 1988, Dee Dee Bridgewater was one of the first great jazz singers to perform at the Jazz Festival in Ramatuelle. In 2016, the story seems to repeat itself as her daughter China Moses took the stage at Ramatuelle. Over the years, China Moses has become a mature performer with a unique style: rocky voice, sharp sense of swing, and intense/energetic stage presence. After signing compilations dedicated to Dinah Washington and blues, Moses released in 2016 an album of his own compositions, entitled &quot;Whatever&quot;. Get ready for a most entertaining performance combining jazz, soul, and hip-hop.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>