<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Bouygues -->
<programme start="20230501050700 +0200" stop="20230501063900 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Charlie Parker : &quot;Bird with Strings&quot; revisited à la Philharmonie de Paris</title>
<desc lang="fr">Charlie Parker - Bird with Strings Revisited - In the late 1940s, jazz saxophonist Charlie &quot;Bird&quot; Parker expressed his wish to record with a classical string section rather than his usual jazz quintet. This desire was fulfilled in 1949 and 1950 when he recorded two albums with oboe, harp, string section and a jazz rhythm section, released as 'Charlie Parker with Strings'. Fast forward 70 years, when saxophonists Olivier Bogé, Géraldine Laurent, Pierrick Pédron, Thomas de Pourquery, and Jaleel Shaw follow in the jazz legend's footsteps, revisiting the repertoire of those original albums in this 2019 concert at The Philharmonie de Paris. Bastien Stil conducts Christophe Dal Sasso's new orchestral arrangements in this genre-blending concert, which opens with Dal Sasso's very own Overture pour cinq saxophones et orchestra.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<icon src="https://img.bouygtel.fr/CMS/images/F0063316707C2A1E40D1DB5CDC61234F.jpg" />
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230501063900 +0200" stop="20230501072100 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">WOMEX 2018</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Rob Thorne Toi Puo</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Rob Thorne Toi Puo - WOMEX 2018 - Since 1994, World Music Expo (WOMEX) has been attracting musicians, agents, a great number of press agencies, as well as media companies from all over the world. Its main exposition event has been held in various locations throughout Europe, including Berlin, Brussels, Marseille, Stockholm, Seville, Cardiff, and Budapest. In 2018, WOMEX was held in Las Palmas, Gran Canaria. One of its showcase participants, composer/performer/anthropologist Rob Thorne, is a diverse explorer in the newly revived evolution of taonga puoro, traditional Māori instruments, fusing these ancient voices with modern sounds and technology. He creates ethereal and immersive site-specific works as well as contemporary chamber music, born out of in-depth research and respect for tradition.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Musique</category>
<category lang="fr">Musicale</category>
<icon src="https://img.bouygtel.fr/CMS/images/BD1A4F239A69EC884BEAFFB08B575969.jpg" />
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230501072100 +0200" stop="20230501082200 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Fabrizio Rat : Artemix</title>
<desc lang="fr">Fabrizio Rat - Since his teenage years, Fabrizio has worked simultaneously on both classical and electronic music productions. He's definitely not the classical music guy who has just discovered techno. Throughout his apprentice years at the musical academy in Turin, he was working as a producer in dance music studios at the same time, hiding his &quot;double life&quot; to both the professors and the DJs. Arriving in Paris in 2007, his objective starts to take shape. Fabrizio combines the acoustic sounds and weird harmonics of his prepared piano with the acid loops of the TB-303 and the beats of the TR-909. Unsurprisingly, it's in front of the dancefloor, in clubs or festivals, that Fabrizio plays his live sets. With the right hand, he plays repetitive rhythmical patterns while the left one handles the machines and manipulates the piano strings.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Rap &amp; Techno</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230501082200 +0200" stop="20230501090000 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">WOMEX 2018</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Mario Batkovic</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Mario Batkovic - WOMEX 2018 - Since 1994, World Music Expo (WOMEX) has been attracting musicians, agents, a great number of press agencies, as well as media companies from all over the world. Its main exposition event has been held in various locations throughout Europe, including Berlin, Brussels, Marseille, Stockholm, Seville, Cardiff, and Budapest. The 2018 edition of WOMEX was held in Las Palmas, Gran Canaria. One of its showcase participants, Mario Batkovic, aims to explore the sonic possibilities of the accordion, without effects or loops, rather through a mutualist symbiotic relationship between man and instrument. Challenging, hypnotic, and grandiose, Batkovic's single-handed symphonic vision is certainly unique.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Musique</category>
<category lang="fr">Musicale</category>
<icon src="https://img.bouygtel.fr/CMS/images/BD1A4F239A69EC884BEAFFB08B575969.jpg" />
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230501090000 +0200" stop="20230501111500 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam</title>
<desc lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam - New Cool Collective is one of the foremost Dutch jazz ensembles. Pioneering new blends of music styles since 1993, NCC has performed in various formations, from small combos to larger ensembles and even big bands! The ensemble's high energy is cut out for the dance floors, as dance, Latin, salsa, afrobeat and boogaloo all meet in a jazzy mix. NCC includes saxophonist Benjamin Herman, guitarist Rory Ronde, drummer Joost Kroon, percussionists Frank van Dok and Jos de Haas, pianist Willem Friede, bassist Leslie Lopez, and trumpeter David Rockefeller.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230501111500 +0200" stop="20230501121200 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Audience Music</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">The Naked and Famous</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">This series features groundbreaking concerts, in-depth artist interviews and unique stories with host Ted Stryker. This concert series gives the audience an intimate view of music's most influential artists today. Shot in 4K, host Ted Stryker interviews musicians across all genres, creating the most unique music show on TV today. This episode features The Naked and Famous, a band from Auckland, New Zealand. They play a mix of electro pop and alternative rock. The group was founded in 2008 by singer Alisa Xayalith and singer/producer/guitarist Thom Powers. Soon after, they scored their first number one hit with &quot;Young Blood.&quot; Their second single &quot;Punching in a Dream&quot; also made it to the New Zealand hit lists. At the Red Studios in Hollywood, Alisa and Thom are supported by David Beadle and Luna Shadows.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Pop &amp; Rock</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230501121200 +0200" stop="20230501131300 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Mariana Aydar : Da Pá Virada Sessions</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Mariana Aydar</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Mariana Aydar - Da Pá Virada Sessions - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the artists taking part in this episode is vocalist Mariana Aydar, who masters the música popular brasileira repertoire (MPB) like no other. She was born in a family of musicians, and has been dubbed the &quot;hottest singer of the moment&quot; by Veja, one of Brazil's leading newsmagazines. For her performance at Da Pá Virada Sessions, Aydar (vocals and triangle) is joined by Cosme Vieira (accordion) and Feeh Silva (zabumba).</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230501131300 +0200" stop="20230501142800 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Oumou Sangaré @ Jazz Sous Les Pommiers</title>
<desc lang="fr">Salif Keita described her as the &quot;Tina Turner of Mali.&quot; Indeed, Oumou Sangaré is one of Africa's most important female voices. While maintaining her political views as a champion of women's rights in Africa, her vocal talent has brought this singer to shine at some of the most important venues around the world. At Jazz Sous Les Pommiers 2017, Oumou Sangaré presents her latest album, Mogoya. She is accompanied by a group that combines traditional African instruments with a modern band set-up, featuring young French musicians. Recorded in spectacular 4K in a beautiful musical setting, Sangaré will surely make you sing and dance!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230501142800 +0200" stop="20230501150200 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Songbook</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Half Moon Run</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Songbook - &quot;I never heard anyone say that, and yeah, I know exactly what it means. It has to go in there, this has to be a song.&quot; Every song has its own story, and we all think it's a story we've heard before, but we haven't. Songbook finds and captures these intriguing stories by pulling you into the process of writing and composing. Known for its pristine sound, cinematic 4k video and eye for detail, Songbook live-captured episodes emphasize the paramount importance of quality. It addresses the on-the-spot elements of blending song and location at the right moment. Both the magical location and remarkable music interaction will get the attention they deserve. Simply because Songbook isn't just a live music session, it lives.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230501150200 +0200" stop="20230501161800 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Chloé - Trabendo Paris</title>
<desc lang="fr">Chloé - Trabendo Paris - Chloé has, without a doubt, led an entire generation to her electronic music playground - one that goes beyond strictly club and techno. As much a film music enthusiast as an accomplished guitar player, she stumbled into the electronic scene early on, developing an unwavering curiosity for sound machines. Chloé is a composer, and she gives life to artistic ideas. The challenge is to stay unwavering in spite of self-doubt that arises throughout the creative process. It is precisely this inner questioning, this contradiction, that nourishes and motivates Chloé's work. Chloé dedicates a full set to her 2017 album Endless Revisions. At Trabendo Paris, she plays these brand-new songs only a few weeks after the album was released.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Pop &amp; Rock</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230501161800 +0200" stop="20230501170500 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Jacob Karlzon Trio - Open Waters</title>
<desc lang="fr"> Together with the Danish bassist Morten Ramsbøl and the Swedish drummer Rasmus Kihlberg, the Swedish pianist Jacob Karlzon presents the album &quot;Open Waters&quot; in the Hamburg factory of piano builder Steinway. The trained pianist, who shared the stage with Kenny Wheeler, Norma Winstone and Billy Cobham, honors the rich tradition of eclectic Swedish jazz. In 2012 he explored heavy metal, then applied electronics to determine the beat. </desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230501170500 +0200" stop="20230501180500 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Caixa Cubo - Da Pá Virada Sessions</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Filo Machado</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Filo Machado - Da Pá Virada Sessions - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the artists taking part in this series is Filo Machado. Born in São Paulo, this singer, composer, instrumentalist, arranger, and producer has celebrated many musical successes. Filo Machado took part in saxophonist Jane Bunnett's Canadian tour with her spectacular project 'Rendez-Vous Brazil/Cuba'. He has appeared at the jazz festivals of Córsega and Uzeste and opened for the one and only Nina Simone in Cannes.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230501180500 +0200" stop="20230501194100 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Atys en folie</title>
<desc lang="fr">Atys en Folie - Atys en folie is a parody of Jean-Baptiste Lully's lyrical tragedy Atys (1676). Atys, Lully's most famous opera, was a constant subject of parody throughout the 18th century. Stage director Jean-Philippe Desrousseaux drew on several parodies to create this original production for singers, puppets, and musicians to revive the work. Princes, princesses, and kings are relegated to peasants, market gardeners, and fishmongers in the countryside. Among the performers are Alain Buet, Marie Lenormand, and Arnaud Marzorati. Gaëlle Trimardeau, Bruno Coulon and Jean-Philippe Desrousseaux feature as puppeteers. The music is performed by ensemble La Clique des Lunaisiens, conducted by Arnaud Marzorati. This performance was recorded at Teatru Manoel in Valletta, Malta, in 2017.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Opéra</category>
<category lang="fr">Opérette</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230501194100 +0200" stop="20230501201600 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Echoes Series: Black Country</title>
<desc lang="fr">Echoes Series: Black Country - Echoes is a modern live music show hosted by Jehnny Beth (lead singer in the British band Savages). It presents leading and emerging bands and artists from the contemporary scene. The show takes place underneath the Palais de Tokyo museum in Paris, in the club of brutalist architecture, the &quot;Yoyo.&quot; The live sets are 30 minutes long and take place on a customized stage, creating closeness with the audience. The intimate, immersive space lends to the atmosphere of the show. The artistic direction by Antoine Carlier follows a minimalist, refined and pure aesthetic, allowing the artists' energy and emotions to take center stage. This episode features the band Black Country. Their set includes the songs &quot;Science Fair,&quot; &quot;Sunglasses,&quot; and &quot;Opus.&quot;</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230501201600 +0200" stop="20230501210000 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Classical:NEXT 2019</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">reConvert Project</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Classical:NEXT 2019 - reConvert Project - The concept of percussion has been altered significantly by the evolution of the instrument. The methods of the innovative reConvert Project are unique and dedicated to changing the face of the percussionist world, by working actively with composers such as Georges Aperghis, Simon Steen Andersen, Michael Maierhof and Jorge Sánchez-Chiong and premiering over a dozen works written to help train emerging young composers. The reConvert philosophy is based on the re-examination of the aesthetic use of percussion instruments, where musical discourse is analysed and adapted to their creative needs. With numerous works using unconventional instruments and staging, a whole new experience is created for the listener.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Classique</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230501210000 +0200" stop="20230501225800 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Lang Lang au Royal Albert Hall</title>
<desc lang="fr">Lang Lang - If one word applies to the classical pianist Lang Lang, it's &quot;inspiration&quot;. He inspires millions with his open-hearted, emotive playing, whether in intimate recitals or on the grandest of stages. Yet he never forgets what first inspired, and continues to inspire him. Talented artists, above all the great composers - Liszt, Chopin and the others - whose music he now delights in bringing to others. What better place to experience Lang Lang's romantic music than London's beautiful Royal Albert Hall? Chances are you couldn't attend his November 15, 2013 solo concert there - it was sold out within 48 hours! Watch Lang Lang's fast fingers up close, as he effortlessly tackles Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart's Piano Sonatas Nos. 4, 5, 8, after which he indulges in the unmatched, spectacular melancholy of Frédéric Chopin's Ballades Nos.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Classique</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230501225800 +0200" stop="20230501235600 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Nile Rodgers</title>
<desc lang="fr">The popular music performance series Front and Center premiered nationwide on public television in 2016, and now returns for Season 6. The series boasts 22, one-hour episodes and an all-star line-up. This episode features Nile Rodgers. He started his musical career by the end of the '60s. A decade later, he scored a hit with Chic's debut single &quot;Dance Dance Dance,&quot; followed by &quot;Le Freak&quot; from the second album C'est Chic. At Front and Center, Nile Rodgers performs his most well-known songs such as &quot;Get Lucky&quot; and &quot;We Are Family.&quot; In between the songs, Nile Rodgers shares personal stories about his dreams and how they have come true. Enjoy this intimate Front and Center show!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Pop &amp; Rock</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230501235600 +0200" stop="20230502015500 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Tower of Power</title>
<desc lang="fr">Tower of Power - Tower of Power is an American R&amp;B-based horn section and band that has been performing since 1968. The concert shows the legendary band's return to where it all started. Recorded live over two performances at The Fox Theatre in Oakland, Tower of Power celebrates their 50th anniversary with their life-long fans, friends, and family. The lead vocalist in this performance is the electrifying, soulful and compelling Marcus Scott. The show also includes an augmented horn and string section and alumni guests, including Lenny Pickett, Bruce Conte, Chester Thompson, Ray Greene, and Francis &quot;Rocco&quot; Prestia. Celebrate the music of Tower of Power and join these memorable evenings where the band performs their full spectrum of life-affirming funk and soul hits.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230502015500 +0200" stop="20230502030000 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Etenesh Wassie Trio : WOMEX 2018</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Etenesh Wassie Trio</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr"> In 2018 WOMEX took place in Las Palmas in Gran Canaria. One of the participants was the Ethiopian diva Etenesh Wassie with her trio. She mixes the contemporary energy of jazz and punk with her in-depth knowledge of the Ethiopian repertoire. The result is compelling, inspired, and truly unique.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Musique</category>
<category lang="fr">Musicale</category>
<icon src="https://img.bouygtel.fr/CMS/images/BD1A4F239A69EC884BEAFFB08B575969.jpg" />
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230502030000 +0200" stop="20230502042000 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Chaka Khan</title>
<desc lang="fr">Chaka Khan - Chaka Khan, also known as the &quot;Queen of Funk,&quot; has sold about 70 million records worldwide in her nearly five-decade-long career. This unique singer masters many musical genres, including R&amp;B, pop, rock, gospel, country, international music, and classical music. For this concert, the 10-times Grammy Award-winning artist returns to her hometown, where she gives the performance of a lifetime to an appreciative audience. With her nine-piece band and three backing vocalists, she performs a smashing selection of her greatest hits, including &quot;I'm Every Woman,&quot; &quot;Ain't Nobody,&quot; and &quot;Tell Me Something Good.&quot; Join this world-famous superstar in this concert recorded at the Harris Theatre in Chicago, filmed in spectacular 4K.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230502042000 +0200" stop="20230502050500 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Moonlight Benjamin : WOMEX 2018</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Moonlight Benjamin</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Numerous musicians, booking agents, news agencies and media companies from all over the world have been attending the &quot;World Music Exhibition&quot; World Music Expo (WOMEX) since 1994. Over the years, this music fair has settled in several European cities, including Berlin, Brussels, Marseille, Stockholm, Seville, Cardiff and Budapest. In 2018 WOMEX took place in Las Palmas in Gran Canaria. One of the participants was the Haitian singer Moonlight Benjamin. With her band she mixes voodoo blues, Haitian rock and Creole roll into a swirling brew that is thrilling with exciting riffs and heavy grooves. Her powerful voice and fiery electric guitars do the rest.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Musique</category>
<category lang="fr">Musicale</category>
<icon src="https://img.bouygtel.fr/CMS/images/BD1A4F239A69EC884BEAFFB08B575969.jpg" />
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230502050500 +0200" stop="20230502060500 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Mestrinho : Da Pá Virada Sessions</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Mestrinho</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Mestrinho - Da Pá Virada Sessions - Da Pá Virada sessions bring the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the artists taking part in this series is accordionist Mestrinho, seen in performance with Cainã Cavalcante on guitar, Alex Buck on drums, and Carlinhos Noronha on bass. They combine the subtle rhythms of Brazilian music with the leader's instrumental virtuosity.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>