<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Bouygues -->
<programme start="20230410050800 +0200" stop="20230410064500 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Moderat at Stereolux 2016</title>
<desc lang="fr">Moderat at Stereolux 2016 - Since the German bands Modeselektor (Gernot Bronsert and Sebastian Szary) and Apparat (Sascha Ring) joined forces in 2009, they have been hugely successful as the electronic music supergroup Moderat. In 2012, the formation produced the soundtrack of Xavier Dolan's film Laurence Anyways, released as A New Error. According to Les Inrockuptibles, their album II includes &quot;the rhythmic punch of the one (Modeselektor) and atmospheric finesse of the other (Apparat) combine perfectly.&quot; In 2016, the threesome returned with an eagerly anticipated third album, III, which they present in this program, live on stage at Stereolux in Nantes, France.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230410064500 +0200" stop="20230410072800 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">WOMEX 2018</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Norayr Kartashyan &amp; Menua</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Norayr Kartashyan &amp; Menua - WOMEX 2018 - Since 1994, World Music Expo (WOMEX) has been attracting musicians, agents, a great number of press agencies, as well as media companies from all over the world. Its main exposition event has been held in various locations throughout Europe, including Berlin, Brussels, Marseille, Stockholm, Seville, Cardiff, and Budapest. In 2018, WOMEX was held in Las Palmas, Gran Canaria. One of its showcase participants, Norayr Kartashyan, is acclaimed as one of Armenia's finest woodwind masters and composers, an acknowledged virtuoso numerous traditional Armenian instruments. To name a few: the blul and shvi flutes, duduk, the double-reed zurna trumpet, the pku clarinet, and the parkapzuk bagpipe.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Musique</category>
<category lang="fr">Musicale</category>
<icon src="https://img.bouygtel.fr/CMS/images/A5539A1D83657FE964693E3151A5A56C.jpg" />
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230410072800 +0200" stop="20230410082400 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">The Go! Team @ Route du Rock Hivers</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Go! Team @ Route du Rock Hivers - Originating from Brighton, UK, The Go! Team blends garage/indie rock with distorted guitars and a popping brass section. The creative force behind this six-piece band is Ian Parton. According to him, the band samples everything from Bollywood to hip-hop. Although the samples are at the heart of the band's sound, every song is kicked off by the melody. At Route du Rock Hivers 2018, The Go! Team presents its latest album, Semicircle. Its opening track Mayday is built around a drum loop based on Morse code. This is only the beginning of the endless variety of sound effects The Go! Team experiments with. At their 4K show at Rock Hivers 2018, you will enjoy a blend of noisy pop, hip-hop collages, awesome grooves, irresistible soul arrangements and much more!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Pop &amp; Rock</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230410082400 +0200" stop="20230410090000 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Eleanor Dubinsky - Nublu 2019</title>
<desc lang="fr">The music of vocalist, guitarist and cellist Eleanor Dubinsky lives on the narrow ledge where jazz, international music and pop meet emotionally heartfelt songwriting. The musician and her versatile band deliver dynamic compositions that explore the fragile link between human emotions and human responsibility. The core of Eleanor's artistic mission is to enter into dialogue and achieve self-realization through music.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230410090000 +0200" stop="20230410111500 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam</title>
<desc lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam - New Cool Collective is one of the foremost Dutch jazz ensembles. Pioneering new blends of music styles since 1993, NCC has performed in various formations, from small combos to larger ensembles and even big bands! The ensemble's high energy is cut out for the dance floors, as dance, Latin, salsa, afrobeat and boogaloo all meet in a jazzy mix. NCC includes saxophonist Benjamin Herman, guitarist Rory Ronde, drummer Joost Kroon, percussionists Frank van Dok and Jos de Haas, pianist Willem Friede, bassist Leslie Lopez, and trumpeter David Rockefeller.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230410111500 +0200" stop="20230410121600 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Runtown : La Machine de Moulin Rouge</title>
<desc lang="fr">Runtown - La Machine de Moulin Rouge - Enjoy Runtown's first concert in Paris, where the Nigerian superstar brings many guests to his show. One of the most talented Nigerian afrobeat scenes will make you rediscover his greatest hits. Nigeria is a very creative country when it comes to the music scene. Runtown is no exception. His first single, &quot;Party Like It's 1980,&quot; paved the way for &quot;Gallardo,&quot; which caught the entire international scene's attention. Runtown's inspiration comes from the greats, from Salif Keita and Fela Kuti to Otis Redding and Bob Marley. An exceptional event not to be missed.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230410121600 +0200" stop="20230410131900 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Jesse Cook - Follow the Road</title>
<desc lang="fr">Celebrated guitarist, composer, and music producer Jesse Cook has been delivering unforgettable concert experiences to audiences across the globe for over 25 years. As far as he has ventured, Jesse has always been fascinated with the mystique of the road that first led him out of Toronto. In his directorial debut, Cook shows us a concert from a rarely seen perspective: the musician's. Born to film director parents, guitarist Jesse Cook taps into this pedigree, and self-directed this story, his fifth Concert Special. The result is &quot;Follow the Road.&quot; Captured in 4K, during his 31-city cross-Canada tour, we follow the band down the TransCanada Highway, against a backdrop of majestic mountains and stunning natural beauty, as they traverse the scenic splendor of the second largest country in the world.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Documentaire</category>
<category lang="fr">Musique</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230410131900 +0200" stop="20230410143200 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">STUFF. Live at BIRD Rotterdam</title>
<desc lang="fr">With their inexhaustible energy, STUFF is impossible to get off the stage! The band was formed in 2012 when drummer Lander Gyselinck was asked by a local bar to make live music between sets of DJs, and he gathered a number of musician friends. The band is considered an avant-garde jazz band that plays a mix of funk, hip-hop and electro. Andrew Claes (saxophone), Dries Laheye (bass guitar), Lander Gyselinck (drummer), Mixmonster Menno (samples) and Joris Caluwaerts (keyboard) share a fabulous musical connection. The eagerness with which the musicians conquer every stage and the great pleasure with which they do so makes the heart of every music lover melt.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230410143200 +0200" stop="20230410150100 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Songbook</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Violetta Zironi</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Songbook - &quot;I never heard anyone say that, and yeah, I know exactly what it means. It has to go in there, this has to be a song.&quot; Every song has its own story, and we all think it's a story we've heard before, but we haven't. Songbook finds and captures these intriguing stories by pulling you into the process of writing and composing. Known for its pristine sound, cinematic 4k video and eye for detail, Songbook live-captured episodes emphasize the paramount importance of quality. It addresses the on-the-spot elements of blending song and location at the right moment. Both the magical location and remarkable music interaction will get the attention they deserve. Simply because Songbook isn't just a live music session, it lives. This episode of Songbook features Italian singer-songwriter Violetta Zironi.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230410150100 +0200" stop="20230410161500 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Omer Avital Qantar - Jazz in Duketown</title>
<desc lang="fr">Jazz in Duketown is the largest free open-air jazz festival in the Netherlands. Jazz fanatics and other music lovers eagerly look forward to the performances of the many internationally renowned artists every year. In 2019 Israeli-American double bass player Omer Avital is one of them. Together with his quintet, consisting of saxophonists Asaf Yuria and Alexander Levin, drummer Ofri Nehemya and pianist Eden Ladin, he performs a strong repertoire from his album 'Qantar': vibrantly energetic, idiosyncratic jazz with oriental influences.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230410161500 +0200" stop="20230410165800 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Fedde le Grand @ Pacha Festival</title>
<desc lang="fr">Pacha Festival - Fedde Le Grand is considered one of the most important artists of house music, a style in constant evolution. He is known around the world for his simple &quot;Put Your Hands Up For Detroit&quot;, &quot;Rhythm Of The Night&quot;, &quot;The Creeps&quot;, and &quot;Let Me Think About It&quot;. Fedde Le Grand has received countless awards and has offered remixes of the greatest international artists such as Coldplay, Madonna, Will.i.am, Robbie Williams and, more recently, Michael Jackson (&quot;Love Never Felt So Good&quot;) and Faithless (&quot;Insomnia&quot;). His electrifying DJ set at Bali's Pacha Festival thrills the view with his breathtaking lights, fireworks, and delirious crowd!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230410165800 +0200" stop="20230410175800 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Caixa Cubo - Da Pá Virada Sessions</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Filo Machado - New Year's Eve Special</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Filo Machado - New Year's Eve Special - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the artists taking part in this series is Filo Machado. Born in São Paulo, this singer, composer, instrumentalist, arranger and producer has celebrated many musical successes. Filo Machado took part in saxophonist Jane Bunnett's Canadian tour with her spectacular project 'Rendez-Vous Brazil/Cuba'. He has appeared at the jazz festivals of Córsega and Uzeste and opened for the one and only Nina Simone in Cannes.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230410175800 +0200" stop="20230410193700 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Meute</title>
<desc lang="fr">Meute - When the bass sounds and the confetti explodes, there is no doubt that Meute is a different kind of band. The band creates a whole new genre by mixing fanfare music with hypnotic techno. Meute liberates electronic music of the classic model of the DJ console. This group breaks the codes by provoking a real interaction with the audience, who will be unable to do anything but stomp their feet. This brass and percussion ensemble revolutionizes techno music while ultimately bringing it back to its roots. The eleven musicians in their iconic red jackets have already taken over the biggest festivals in Europe! Watch them on Festival 4K with their show at Trianon Paris, 2019.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230410193700 +0200" stop="20230410201500 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Classical:NEXT 2019</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Trio Zukan</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Classical:NEXT 2019 - Trio Zukan - In 2014, Trio Zukan emerged from the combination of three uncommon instruments: accordion, percussion and txistu. The repertoire for this instrumental combination was non-existent at the beginning, so its members decided to promote a project with different composers, with the intention of creating a new repertoire. Today, Zukan has commissioned, revised and released more than a dozen pieces by national and international composers such as: María Eugenia Luc, Mikel Chamizo, Isabel Urrutia, Francisco José Domínguez, Vassilis Filippou, etc. The group is one of the most consolidated groups on the contemporary music scene in the Basque Country. They have performed in Quincena Musical Donostia, Bernaola Festival, Musikagileak Circuit, BBVA Cycle and Attacca Basel, among others.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Classique</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230410201500 +0200" stop="20230410210000 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">WOMEX 2018</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Mario Batkovic</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Mario Batkovic - WOMEX 2018 - Since 1994, World Music Expo (WOMEX) has been attracting musicians, agents, a great number of press agencies, as well as media companies from all over the world. Its main exposition event has been held in various locations throughout Europe, including Berlin, Brussels, Marseille, Stockholm, Seville, Cardiff, and Budapest. The 2018 edition of WOMEX was held in Las Palmas, Gran Canaria. One of its showcase participants, Mario Batkovic, aims to explore the sonic possibilities of the accordion, without effects or loops, rather through a mutualist symbiotic relationship between man and instrument. Challenging, hypnotic, and grandiose, Batkovic's single-handed symphonic vision is certainly unique.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Musique</category>
<category lang="fr">Musicale</category>
<icon src="https://img.bouygtel.fr/CMS/images/BD1A4F239A69EC884BEAFFB08B575969.jpg" />
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230410210000 +0200" stop="20230410230800 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Hardwell and the Metropole Orchestra - Symphony</title>
<desc lang="fr">Hardwell and the Metropole Orchestra - Symphony - During &quot;Symphony: The Global Revolution of Dance,&quot; the global sensation DJ Hardwell, with the world's leading pop and jazz orchestra, The Metropole Orchestra, take the audience on a musical journey through the history of dance music. The spectacular show of legendary DJ and the Metropole Orchestra is characterized by the composition of different music periods, from the '80s to the present. The show features hits from various world stars like Donna Summer, Tiësto, Carl Cox, and Daft Punk.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Classique</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230410230800 +0200" stop="20230410230800 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Fabrizio Rat : Artemix</title>
<desc lang="fr">Fabrizio Rat - Since his teenage years, Fabrizio has worked simultaneously on both classical and electronic music productions. He's definitely not the classical music guy who has just discovered techno. Throughout his apprentice years at the musical academy in Turin, he was working as a producer in dance music studios at the same time, hiding his &quot;double life&quot; to both the professors and the DJs. Arriving in Paris in 2007, his objective starts to take shape. Fabrizio combines the acoustic sounds and weird harmonics of his prepared piano with the acid loops of the TB-303 and the beats of the TR-909. Unsurprisingly, it's in front of the dancefloor, in clubs or festivals, that Fabrizio plays his live sets. With the right hand, he plays repetitive rhythmical patterns while the left one handles the machines and manipulates the piano strings.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Rap &amp; Techno</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>