<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Bouygues -->
<programme start="20230328050000 +0200" stop="20230328060100 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Isle of Wight 2018: Part I</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Isle of Wight Festival, held in Newport, England is a rock-pop music festival that annually serves as the first major event opening the British festival summer. The tradition of the festival first saw the light of day in 1969, opening eleven days after the closing of legendary Woodstock and was regarded as the European counterpart to the legendary &quot;counterculture&quot; festival. In 1970, its line-up was stars-studded with gigs by Jimi Hendrix, The Who, The Doors, Joni Mitchell, Supertramp, Leonard Cohen and many more, establishing the name of the festival. In 2002, the festival was revived after 30 years of silence and brought back the sounds of contemporary musical legends to the Isle of Wight.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Pop &amp; Rock</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230328060100 +0200" stop="20230328073300 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Charlie Parker : &quot;Bird with Strings&quot; revisited à la Philharmonie de Paris</title>
<desc lang="fr">Charlie Parker - Bird with Strings Revisited - In the late 1940s, jazz saxophonist Charlie &quot;Bird&quot; Parker expressed his wish to record with a classical string section rather than his usual jazz quintet. This desire was fulfilled in 1949 and 1950 when he recorded two albums with oboe, harp, string section and a jazz rhythm section, released as 'Charlie Parker with Strings'. Fast forward 70 years, when saxophonists Olivier Bogé, Géraldine Laurent, Pierrick Pédron, Thomas de Pourquery, and Jaleel Shaw follow in the jazz legend's footsteps, revisiting the repertoire of those original albums in this 2019 concert at The Philharmonie de Paris. Bastien Stil conducts Christophe Dal Sasso's new orchestral arrangements in this genre-blending concert, which opens with Dal Sasso's very own Overture pour cinq saxophones et orchestra.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<icon src="https://img.bouygtel.fr/CMS/images/F0063316707C2A1E40D1DB5CDC61234F.jpg" />
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230328073300 +0200" stop="20230328081100 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">IDLES - Echoes Series: Idles</title>
<desc lang="fr">Echoes Series: Idles - Echoes is a modern live music show hosted by Jehnny Beth (lead singer in the British band Savages). It presents leading and emerging bands and artists from the contemporary scene. The show takes place underneath the Palais de Tokyo museum in Paris, in the club of brutalist architecture, the &quot;Yoyo.&quot; The live sets are 30 minutes long and take place on a customized stage, creating closeness with the audience. The intimate, immersive space lends to the atmosphere of the show. The artistic direction by Antoine Carlier follows a minimalist, refined and pure aesthetic, allowing the artists' energy and emotions to take center stage. This episode features the band Idles. Their set includes the songs &quot;Colossus,&quot; &quot;Love Song,&quot; and &quot;Television.&quot;</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230328081100 +0200" stop="20230328090000 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Ensemble Offspring</title>
<desc lang="fr">Ensemble Offspring - Ensemble Offspring is Australia's foremost new music ensemble, based in Sydney, made up of flute, clarinet, violin, cello, piano, and percussion. At Classical:NEXT, the ensemble features a line-up of internationally acclaimed core instrumentalists, Claire Edwardes (percussionist/artistic director), Zubin Kanga (piano), Jason Noble (clarinet), and Lamorna Nightingale (flute). With a 23-year history, the group embraces all modes of adventurous music making, which has brought to fruition the creation of over 200 new works. The 2019 Classical:Next showcase programme Solitude features two works written for the ensemble by Kate Moore (&quot;Fern&quot;) and Andrea Keller (&quot;Love in Solitude&quot;).</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Classique</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230328090000 +0200" stop="20230328100500 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Joris Voorn</title>
<desc lang="fr">Joris Voorn - The Royal Concertgebouw is a night full of the best house and techno, hosted by one of the biggest names from the underground at one of the prettiest locations in the world. Renown as one of the most stunning sites dedicated to music, the Royal Concertgebouw has been transformed into a glorious cathedral of techno for one night only. Audio Obscura is a movement born out of love for cutting-edge underground dance music. Today, Audio Obscura has grown into one of the most sought-after destinations for leading DJs to play, and for partygoers, both young and old, to dance the night (and day) away.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Rap &amp; Techno</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230328100500 +0200" stop="20230328110500 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Mestrinho : Da Pá Virada Sessions</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Mestrinho</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Mestrinho - Da Pá Virada Sessions - Da Pá Virada sessions bring the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the artists taking part in this series is accordionist Mestrinho, seen in performance with Cainã Cavalcante on guitar, Alex Buck on drums, and Carlinhos Noronha on bass. They combine the subtle rhythms of Brazilian music with the leader's instrumental virtuosity.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230328110500 +0200" stop="20230328124100 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Opera Imaginaire</title>
<desc lang="fr">Opera Imaginaire - To celebrate Le Concert Spirituel's 30th anniversary, conductor Hervé Niquet collaborated with the Baroque Music Center of Versailles to build his opéra imaginaire. For this unique project, Le Concert Spirituel presents an original performance of unpublished operas by Lully, Rameau, Charpentier, and many other French baroque composers. You will find yourself captivated by a tearful lover, intrigued by the passage to the underworld, and fascinated by the descents of the Gods. The program includes many favorite passages, such as Lully's Armide, Charpentier's Medea, and Campra's Carnaval de Venise. Experience all the magic of Louis XIV's French opera as Le Concert Spirituel transforms the Théâtre des Champs-Elysées into a true French baroque scene.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Opéra</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230328124100 +0200" stop="20230328132300 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">WOMEX 2018</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Rob Thorne Toi Puo</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Rob Thorne Toi Puo - WOMEX 2018 - Since 1994, World Music Expo (WOMEX) has been attracting musicians, agents, a great number of press agencies, as well as media companies from all over the world. Its main exposition event has been held in various locations throughout Europe, including Berlin, Brussels, Marseille, Stockholm, Seville, Cardiff, and Budapest. In 2018, WOMEX was held in Las Palmas, Gran Canaria. One of its showcase participants, composer/performer/anthropologist Rob Thorne, is a diverse explorer in the newly revived evolution of taonga puoro, traditional Māori instruments, fusing these ancient voices with modern sounds and technology. He creates ethereal and immersive site-specific works as well as contemporary chamber music, born out of in-depth research and respect for tradition.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Musique</category>
<category lang="fr">Musicale</category>
<icon src="https://img.bouygtel.fr/CMS/images/A5539A1D83657FE964693E3151A5A56C.jpg" />
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230328132300 +0200" stop="20230328142400 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Runtown : La Machine de Moulin Rouge</title>
<desc lang="fr">Runtown - La Machine de Moulin Rouge - Enjoy Runtown's first concert in Paris, where the Nigerian superstar brings many guests to his show. One of the most talented Nigerian afrobeat scenes will make you rediscover his greatest hits. Nigeria is a very creative country when it comes to the music scene. Runtown is no exception. His first single, &quot;Party Like It's 1980,&quot; paved the way for &quot;Gallardo,&quot; which caught the entire international scene's attention. Runtown's inspiration comes from the greats, from Salif Keita and Fela Kuti to Otis Redding and Bob Marley. An exceptional event not to be missed.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230328142400 +0200" stop="20230328150200 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Eleanor Dubinsky - Nublu 2019</title>
<desc lang="fr">The music of vocalist, guitarist and cellist Eleanor Dubinsky lives on the narrow ledge where jazz, international music and pop meet emotionally heartfelt songwriting. The musician and her versatile band deliver dynamic compositions that explore the fragile link between human emotions and human responsibility. The core of Eleanor's artistic mission is to enter into dialogue and achieve self-realization through music.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230328150200 +0200" stop="20230328163500 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Jazz à Ramatuelle</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Parisien meets Kühn &amp; Portal</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Jazz à Ramatuelle: Parisien meets Kühn &amp; Portal - Since his first appearance at Jazz in Ramatuelle in 2010, saxophonist Émile Parisien has made his mark among the most talented musicians of his generation. On the soprano saxophone, his favorite instrument, he invented a unique lyrical style. As part of his participation in the 2016 edition of Jazz à Ramatuelle, Parisien invited two European jazz legends to join his ensemble: the German pianist Joachim Kühn (*1944) and the legendary multi-instrumentalist Michel Portal (*1935). Over 80 years old, the latter is an incomparable saxophonist, clarinetist and bandoneonist, a musical adventurer who skilfully combines jazz, classical music and film music.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230328163500 +0200" stop="20230328173000 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Sheryl Crow</title>
<desc lang="fr">Sheryl Crow - Missouri-born country mega-star Sheryl Crow celebrates her return to the stage in an intimate performance at New York City's Iridium. Having sold over million copies of her ten studio albums worldwide over the course of her over three decade-long career, Sheryl Crow has long-established a status of one of America's most successful musicians. With a warm sound made up of elements of country, pop, rock and Americana, Crow has received nine GRAMMY-awards and over thirty nominations.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Pop &amp; Rock</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230328173000 +0200" stop="20230328194300 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam</title>
<desc lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam - New Cool Collective is one of the foremost Dutch jazz ensembles. Pioneering new blends of music styles since 1993, NCC has performed in various formations, from small combos to larger ensembles and even big bands! The ensemble's high energy is cut out for the dance floors, as dance, Latin, salsa, afrobeat and boogaloo all meet in a jazzy mix. NCC includes saxophonist Benjamin Herman, guitarist Rory Ronde, drummer Joost Kroon, percussionists Frank van Dok and Jos de Haas, pianist Willem Friede, bassist Leslie Lopez, and trumpeter David Rockefeller.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230328194300 +0200" stop="20230328210000 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Beth Hart - Front And Center</title>
<desc lang="fr">The popular music performance series Front and Center premiered nationwide on public television in 2016, and now returns for Season 6. The series boasts 22, one-hour episodes and an all-star line-up. Today's guest is Beth Hart, active in the music scene since the '90s, releasing her third live album. Her intimate show showcases her amazing voice, and her piano playing skills, which she proves with the song &quot;Jazz Man.&quot; One of the performance's highlights includes the ballad &quot;Leave the Light On,&quot; as well as the final song &quot;No Place Like Home.&quot; During her performance, Beth Hart is supported by Jon Nichols, Bill Ransom, Bob Marinelli, and Sonny Landreth.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230328210000 +0200" stop="20230328222600 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Sing Jazz 2018</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Incognito</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Incognito - Sing Jazz 2018 - An acid jazz project rooted in the 1970s jazz/funk/soul world, Incognito was originally formed by Jean-Paul &quot;Bluey&quot; Maunick and Paul &quot;Tubbs&quot; Williams. Both were original members of the late 1970s disco/funk group Light of the World. They decided to take a couple of their jams into the studio and debuted with the single Parisienne Girl. Decades later, Incognito's cover of Boz Scaggs' classic Lowdown with Chaka Khan and Mario Biondi saw the band's international status grow more and more popular. At Sing Jazz 2018, Incognito takes a fresh direction on classic musical themes, giving their fans an unforgettable live show!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<icon src="https://img.bouygtel.fr/CMS/images/E537F830342471D10D4F174FE9E53A46.jpg" />
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230328222600 +0200" stop="20230328232100 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">&quot;We Love Ella&quot; : The Amazing Keystone Big Band</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Amazing Keystone Big Band - &quot;We Love Ella&quot; - The Amazing Keystone Big Band performs material from their album &quot;We Love Ella&quot; at this 2019 recording from Salle Pleyel in Paris, France. Led by trombonist Bastien Ballaz, saxophonist Jon Boutellier, pianist Fred Nardin and trumpeter David Enhco, The Amazing Keystone Big Band helps young and adult audiences all over the world discover jazz in all its guises. &quot;We Love Ella&quot; is a reinvention of legendary vocalist Ella Fitzgerald's greatest successes.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<icon src="https://img.bouygtel.fr/CMS/images/7411F2F30A14758717C62E0F1F7D6040.jpg" />
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230328232100 +0200" stop="20230329002600 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Jungle By Night</title>
<desc lang="fr">Jungle By Night - Jazz in Duketown - Jazz in Duketown is the largest free outdoor jazz festival in the Netherlands. It's a real gathering for jazz addicts, inviting internationally renowned bands. In 2019, one of them is the Amsterdam-based Dutch instrumental collective Jungle by Night. The band plays a mix of various styles, inspired by funk, jazz, dub, rock, and others. The ensemble made its debut in 2010 and has played at numerous festivals. Their December 2010 performance with former backing musicians of Afrobeat founder Fela Kuti in Paris saw them hailed as &quot;the future of Afrobeat&quot;.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<icon src="https://img.bouygtel.fr/CMS/images/5E195F7D302BDA1AC6B4E91232CF0B98.jpg" />
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230329002600 +0200" stop="20230329014700 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Rocky Mountain Way</title>
<desc lang="fr">Rocky Mountain Way - The Colorado Music Hall of Fame hosted a concert for the induction of rock 'n' roll legends Joe Walsh and the late Dan Fogelberg, along with the honoring of the famed Caribou Ranch recording studio near Nederland, Colorado, where Walsh and Fogelberg both recorded some of their best work. The concert, dubbed &quot;The Rocky Mountain Way,&quot; took place on Sunday, August 13, 2017, at Fiddler's Green. It featured performances from an all-star list of musicians including The Lumineers, Garth Brooks, Amy Grant &amp; Vince Gill, The Nitty Gritty Dirt Band, Richie Furay, Randy Owen of Alabama, Todd Park Mohr, Michael Martin Murphey, and surprise guests paying tribute to Dan Fogelberg and Caribou Ranch. Joe Walsh reunited his Caribou recording band Barnstorm for the performance.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Pop &amp; Rock</category>
<icon src="https://img.bouygtel.fr/CMS/images/C48609F1056AF07359F069F8FE7DB1AC.jpg" />
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230329014700 +0200" stop="20230329030000 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Creamfields</title>
<desc lang="fr">Creamfields - Having burst onto the ever-growing festival scene two decades ago, Creamfields has secured its spot as being one of the - if not the - biggest weekend dedicated to electronic music in the UK. Currently, the clubbing and raving pilgrimage attracts an impressive 70,000 festival-goers over the weekend. Continuously offering up the very best in EDM, house, trance, drum and bass, grime, and more, Creamfields has hosted some massive names over the past twenty years. This 2019 edition of Creamfields presents Green Velvet, MK, Carl Cox, Deadmau5, Camelphat, Nicole Moudaber, Dimitri Vegas &amp; Like Mike, and many more!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Pop &amp; Rock</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230329030000 +0200" stop="20230329035100 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Mn'JAM Experiment: Live with a Boom</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Live with a Boom</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Mn'JAM Experiment: Live with a Boom - Imagine that visual arts and music are no longer two separate fields; that musicians no longer focus on their instruments only, but also on the visuals of their performance. Such is the premise of Mn'JAM Experiment! Zoom in on their music and you'll find a mix between empirical and rationally constructed elements; between acoustic, electric and electronic instruments; urban rhythms and traditional melodies, vocal loops and guitar solos, turntables and acoustic drums. Zoom in on the visuals of the performance -they are analogously a product of pre-composed material and live manipulation, mostly carried out by the guy behind the turntables.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230329035100 +0200" stop="20230329045100 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Caixa Cubo - Da Pá Virada Sessions</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Filo Machado - New Year's Eve Special</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Filo Machado - New Year's Eve Special - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the artists taking part in this series is Filo Machado. Born in São Paulo, this singer, composer, instrumentalist, arranger and producer has celebrated many musical successes. Filo Machado took part in saxophonist Jane Bunnett's Canadian tour with her spectacular project 'Rendez-Vous Brazil/Cuba'. He has appeared at the jazz festivals of Córsega and Uzeste and opened for the one and only Nina Simone in Cannes.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230329045100 +0200" stop="20230329055300 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">La Fraîcheur</title>
<desc lang="fr">La Fraîcheur - For over a decade now, first in Paris, then Montreal and now in Berlin, La Fraîcheur has been brewing her blend of deep house and techno beats, making a name for herself with her signature sound of emotionally charged and acid techno sets. The queer feminist-activist is a marathon DJ who can go on for countless hours, running the gamut from classics to new songs released just hours earlier. Her craft expanded by producing music ranging from ravy epic techno to dark pumping electro, spacious open-air deep house to melancholic electronica. She wrote her critically acclaimed debut album during an artist residency with the Berlin-Detroit Connection.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Pop &amp; Rock</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230329055300 +0200" stop="20230329065500 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Nilüfer Yanya - Echoes Series: Nilufer Yanya</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Baxter Dury, Wet Leg &amp; Geese Yoyo</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Echoes Series - Episode 6 - Echoes is a modern live music show hosted by Jehnny Beth (lead singer in the British band Savages). It presents leading and emerging bands and artists from the contemporary scene. The show takes place underneath the Palais de Tokyo museum in Paris, in the club of brutalist architecture, the &quot;Yoyo.&quot; The live sets are 30 minutes long and take place on a customized stage, creating closeness with the audience. Once the bands have performed, Jehnny Beth invites everyone to sit at her roundtable for a group conversation. The open discussions in every episode allow the audience to understand the rapport, artistic exchange, and intellectual debates that run through this eclectic musical universe. The intimate, immersive space lends to the atmosphere of the show.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>