<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Bouygues -->
<programme start="20230518050100 +0200" stop="20230518060100 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Nubiyan Twist : Music Meeting</title>
<desc lang="fr">Nubiyan Twist - Music Meeting - Since 1985, the Dutch city of Nijmegen has been welcoming the International Music Meeting Festival every Pentecost. Ranging from jazz and improvisational music to traditional music and unique crossovers, this adventurous festival is all about musical encounters and international collaborations. In 2019, the band Nubiyan Twist performs at the International Music Meeting Festival. This London-based group operates on the intersection of soul and jazz.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230518060100 +0200" stop="20230518073800 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Moderat at Stereolux 2016</title>
<desc lang="fr">Moderat at Stereolux 2016 - Since the German bands Modeselektor (Gernot Bronsert and Sebastian Szary) and Apparat (Sascha Ring) joined forces in 2009, they have been hugely successful as the electronic music supergroup Moderat. In 2012, the formation produced the soundtrack of Xavier Dolan's film Laurence Anyways, released as A New Error. According to Les Inrockuptibles, their album II includes &quot;the rhythmic punch of the one (Modeselektor) and atmospheric finesse of the other (Apparat) combine perfectly.&quot; In 2016, the threesome returned with an eagerly anticipated third album, III, which they present in this program, live on stage at Stereolux in Nantes, France.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230518073800 +0200" stop="20230518081100 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Classical:NEXT 2019</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Tricia Dawn Williams</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr"> Tricia Dawn Williams - Transition is a portrait of the avant-garde piano stretching almost one hundred years. Each piece on the programme breaks new ground as the music navigates through uncharted waters to depict a new profile for the instrument. Transition by Tricia Dawn Williams is a unique experience that transforms the piano recital into an interdisciplinary performance featuring gesture-control technology, video-art, electronic music and extended piano technique. Born in Malta, of Irish and Welsh descent, Tricia Dawn Williams is committed to contemporary music, multimedia and new technologies. Williams is one of the first concert pianists to collaborate with developers and composers internationally on the application of gesture-control technology.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Classique</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230518081100 +0200" stop="20230518090000 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Classical:NEXT 2019</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Śniedź</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Classical:NEXT 2019 - Śniedź - Śniedź is a voice and electronics duo from Warsaw, Poland who combine extended vocal techniques with improvised, self-named &quot;glitchtronica.&quot; Singer, performer, and sound artist Aleksandra Klimczak frequently breaks boundaries between art genres through cooperating with young artists from different artistic fields. Her work has been awarded from scholarships from the Polish Ministry of Culture and the Capital City of Warsaw. Music curator Antoni Beksiak deals with contemporary crossover, ethnic, classical, jazz, and pop music in his work as an initiator, critic and creator. During this showcase recorded at Classical:NEXT 2019 in Rotterdam, The Netherlands the perform a set list of their own works.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Classique</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230518090000 +0200" stop="20230518103100 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Clubbing Experience with Nina Kraviz @ Kappa FuturFestival</title>
<desc lang="fr">Nina Kraviz - When you're into techno, you're into Nina Kraviz. The Siberian DJ and producer has become one of the biggest names of the techno scene. From world famous stages, to intimate shows in smaller venues, Nina's hypnotic style of mixing, combined with her acid-like techno is loved by many. Kraviz went solo and made a splash in 2009, when she issued productions on Efdemin's Naïf, Jus-Ed's Underground Quality, and Matt Edwards' Rekids. Following additional singles on Rekids and Rosa, as well as the Mr. Jones EP in 2013, Kraviz founded the Trip label in 2014. Enjoy her show at Kappa FuturFestival 2019!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Musique</category>
<category lang="fr">Clips</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230518103100 +0200" stop="20230518113200 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Runtown : La Machine de Moulin Rouge</title>
<desc lang="fr">Runtown - La Machine de Moulin Rouge - Enjoy Runtown's first concert in Paris, where the Nigerian superstar brings many guests to his show. One of the most talented Nigerian afrobeat scenes will make you rediscover his greatest hits. Nigeria is a very creative country when it comes to the music scene. Runtown is no exception. His first single, &quot;Party Like It's 1980,&quot; paved the way for &quot;Gallardo,&quot; which caught the entire international scene's attention. Runtown's inspiration comes from the greats, from Salif Keita and Fela Kuti to Otis Redding and Bob Marley. An exceptional event not to be missed.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230518113200 +0200" stop="20230518134500 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam</title>
<desc lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam - New Cool Collective is one of the foremost Dutch jazz ensembles. Pioneering new blends of music styles since 1993, NCC has performed in various formations, from small combos to larger ensembles and even big bands! The ensemble's high energy is cut out for the dance floors, as dance, Latin, salsa, afrobeat and boogaloo all meet in a jazzy mix. NCC includes saxophonist Benjamin Herman, guitarist Rory Ronde, drummer Joost Kroon, percussionists Frank van Dok and Jos de Haas, pianist Willem Friede, bassist Leslie Lopez, and trumpeter David Rockefeller.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230518134500 +0200" stop="20230518150200 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">&quot;We Love Ella&quot; : The Amazing Keystone Big Band</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Amazing Keystone Big Band - &quot;We Love Ella&quot; - The Amazing Keystone Big Band performs material from their album &quot;We Love Ella&quot; at this 2019 recording from Salle Pleyel in Paris, France. Led by trombonist Bastien Ballaz, saxophonist Jon Boutellier, pianist Fred Nardin and trumpeter David Enhco, The Amazing Keystone Big Band helps young and adult audiences all over the world discover jazz in all its guises. &quot;We Love Ella&quot; is a reinvention of legendary vocalist Ella Fitzgerald's greatest successes.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<icon src="https://img.bouygtel.fr/CMS/images/C88B1D8822AE4BC8696F6B6B529F30C3.jpg" />
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230518150200 +0200" stop="20230518171700 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam</title>
<desc lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam - New Cool Collective is one of the foremost Dutch jazz ensembles. Pioneering new blends of music styles since 1993, NCC has performed in various formations, from small combos to larger ensembles and even big bands! The ensemble's high energy is cut out for the dance floors, as dance, Latin, salsa, afrobeat and boogaloo all meet in a jazzy mix. NCC includes saxophonist Benjamin Herman, guitarist Rory Ronde, drummer Joost Kroon, percussionists Frank van Dok and Jos de Haas, pianist Willem Friede, bassist Leslie Lopez, and trumpeter David Rockefeller.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230518171700 +0200" stop="20230518181200 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Sheryl Crow</title>
<desc lang="fr">Sheryl Crow - Missouri-born country mega-star Sheryl Crow celebrates her return to the stage in an intimate performance at New York City's Iridium. Having sold over million copies of her ten studio albums worldwide over the course of her over three decade-long career, Sheryl Crow has long-established a status of one of America's most successful musicians. With a warm sound made up of elements of country, pop, rock and Americana, Crow has received nine GRAMMY-awards and over thirty nominations.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Pop &amp; Rock</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230518181200 +0200" stop="20230518191300 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Maceo Plex - Audio Obscura x Rijksmuseum</title>
<desc lang="fr">Audio Obscura x Rijksmuseum - The American DJ/producer - known for his enigmatic combinations of grooving, melancholic and ecstatic house and techno - visited the museum for some ground-level inspiration, and will share this during this once a lifetime event under the ever so stunning Rijksmuseum. This is the first time the museum collaborates on a project that revolves around electronic music, matching its vision to inspire visitors and to let them experience art in exciting new ways Initiated by Audio Obscura, this is the next step in connecting world-class artists with legendary, historical locations.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230518191300 +0200" stop="20230518202800 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Oumou Sangaré @ Jazz Sous Les Pommiers</title>
<desc lang="fr">Salif Keita described her as the &quot;Tina Turner of Mali.&quot; Indeed, Oumou Sangaré is one of Africa's most important female voices. While maintaining her political views as a champion of women's rights in Africa, her vocal talent has brought this singer to shine at some of the most important venues around the world. At Jazz Sous Les Pommiers 2017, Oumou Sangaré presents her latest album, Mogoya. She is accompanied by a group that combines traditional African instruments with a modern band set-up, featuring young French musicians. Recorded in spectacular 4K in a beautiful musical setting, Sangaré will surely make you sing and dance!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230518202800 +0200" stop="20230518210000 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Classical:NEXT 2019</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Brian Bolger, Pat Brunnock, Tomas O'Durcain &amp; Chien Buggle</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Classical:NEXT 2019 - Dublin Guitar Quartet - Strange to think that until the formation of The Dublin Guitar Quartet (DGQ) there had never been a guitar ensemble that specialised in contemporary classical music. The quartet consists of Brian Bolger, Pat Brunnock, Tomas O'Durcain, and Chien Buggle. Not deterred by the scarcity of repertoire, the DGQ set about creating their own collection of work by focusing on transcriptions and new commissions. Their performances now boast a dynamic mix of celebrated masterpieces by the likes of Philip Glass, Steve Reich, Arvo Pärt and Bryce Dessner alongside new commissions by composers such as Nico Muhly, Michael Gordon, and Marc Mellits.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Classique</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230518210000 +0200" stop="20230518213300 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Audience Music</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Imagine Dragons</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Enjoy groundbreaking concerts, in-depth artist interviews, and unique stories with host Ted Stryker. This concert series gives the audience an intimate view of music's most influential artists today. Shot in 4K, host Ted Stryker interviews musicians across all genres, creating one of the most unique music shows on TV today. This episode features the multi-platinum, Grammy Award-winning band Imagine Dragons. They bring their passionately inventive alt-rock sound to a special, one-hour concert, just one month after releasing their hit song &quot;Natural.&quot; &quot;Living in a dog-eat-dog world can bring out the worst in you, and sometimes, the best,&quot; says the band's singer Dan Reynolds.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230518213300 +0200" stop="20230518223500 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Fabrizio Rat : Artemix</title>
<desc lang="fr">Fabrizio Rat - Since his teenage years, Fabrizio has worked simultaneously on both classical and electronic music productions. He's definitely not the classical music guy who has just discovered techno. Throughout his apprentice years at the musical academy in Turin, he was working as a producer in dance music studios at the same time, hiding his &quot;double life&quot; to both the professors and the DJs. Arriving in Paris in 2007, his objective starts to take shape. Fabrizio combines the acoustic sounds and weird harmonics of his prepared piano with the acid loops of the TB-303 and the beats of the TR-909. Unsurprisingly, it's in front of the dancefloor, in clubs or festivals, that Fabrizio plays his live sets. With the right hand, he plays repetitive rhythmical patterns while the left one handles the machines and manipulates the piano strings.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Rap &amp; Techno</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230518223500 +0200" stop="20230518235100 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Arsenik à l'Olympia</title>
<desc lang="fr">Arsenik - Olympia, Paris - The mythical duo Arsenik is a rap group from France, made up of two brothers, Lino and Calbo. The team performs at Olympia Paris to celebrate their 20 years since their first album, Quelques gouttes suffisent… It's a unique concert: Arsenik plays the entire album with numerous special guests for the first time. The album has sold over 300,000 copies in France. Today it's being considered a classic, and it continues to be cited in the top five of the best French rap albums of all generations. Enjoy Arsenik's live show in Olympia Paris!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Rap &amp; Techno</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230518235100 +0200" stop="20230519005400 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Joris Voorn</title>
<desc lang="fr">Joris Voorn - The Royal Concertgebouw is a night full of the best house and techno, hosted by one of the biggest names from the underground at one of the prettiest locations in the world. Renown as one of the most stunning sites dedicated to music, the Royal Concertgebouw has been transformed into a glorious cathedral of techno for one night only. Audio Obscura is a movement born out of love for cutting-edge underground dance music. Today, Audio Obscura has grown into one of the most sought-after destinations for leading DJs to play, and for partygoers, both young and old, to dance the night (and day) away.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Rap &amp; Techno</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230519005400 +0200" stop="20230519015900 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Dipha Barus</title>
<desc lang="fr">Dipha Barus - Dipha Barus has received several career awards, including the 2014 DJ of The Year at the Paranoia Awards and has been recognized by Rolling Stone Magazine. He has produced several popular hits in Indonesia, and recently released the amazing &quot;No One Can Stop Us&quot; with local star Kallula. Discover this Indonesian platinum star at the Pacha Festival in Bali, with a cocktail in hand, and let yourself be transported under the tropical sun.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Pop &amp; Rock</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230519015900 +0200" stop="20230519024000 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">City Beats</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">London</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">City Beats - Episode 1 - London - DJ-producer Carly Foxx is on a musical journey, immersing herself in the life of five iconic European cities to find inspiration for a series of new tracks. In this episode, Carly Foxx steps outside of her comfort zone to draw inspiration for her music track from urban youths in London's grime scene. With fresh eyes, she explores what makes this city unique to the people who live there. Carly interviews people on the street and asks them about the London music scene, which is very lively and diverse. To better understand the urban music scene, Carly pays a visit to RepreZent Radio, where she interviews grime artists. She records street sounds such as a bus driving by, the ticking against a metal door, and police sirens.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Documentaire</category>
<category lang="fr">Téléréalité</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230519024000 +0200" stop="20230519030000 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">The Entrepeneurs - Songbook</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">The Entrepeneurs</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">The Entrepeneurs - Songbook - &quot;I never heard anyone say that, and yeah, I know exactly what it means. It has to go in there, this has to be a song.&quot; Every song has its own story, and we all think it's a story we've heard before, but we haven't. Songbook finds and captures these intriguing stories by pulling you into the process of writing and composing. Known for its pristine sound, cinematic 4k video and eye for detail, Songbook live-captured episodes emphasize the paramount importance of quality. It addresses the on-the-spot elements of blending song and location at the right moment. Both the magical location and remarkable music interaction will get the attention they deserve. Simply because Songbook isn't just a live music session, it lives.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230519030000 +0200" stop="20230519035600 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Audience Music</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Skylar Grey</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Enjoy ground-breaking concerts, in-depth artist interviews, and unique stories with host Ted Stryker. This concert series gives the audience an intimate view of music's most influential artists today. Shot in 4K, host Ted Stryker interviews musicians across all genres, creating one of the most unique music shows on TV today. This episode features singer/songwriter Skylar Grey, best known for her songwriting skills, as displayed in Eminem and Rihanna's &quot;Love The Way You Lie&quot; (2010). The five-time GRAMMY-nominee and Wisconsin-born pop artist takes the stage to perform some of her most popular songs, as well as some works of her forthcoming album &quot;Angel With Tattoos&quot;. Enjoy Skylar Grey's performance and interview at Audience Music 2019!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230519035600 +0200" stop="20230519050000 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Nilüfer Yanya - Echoes Series: Nilufer Yanya</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">IDLES, Life &amp; Primal Scream</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Echoes Series - Episode 1 - Echoes is a modern live music show hosted by Jehnny Beth (lead singer in the British band Savages). It presents leading and emerging bands and artists from the contemporary scene. The show takes place underneath the Palais de Tokyo museum in Paris, in the club of brutalist architecture, the &quot;Yoyo.&quot; The live sets are 30 minutes long and take place on a customized stage, creating closeness with the audience. Once the bands have performed, Jehnny Beth invites everyone to sit at her roundtable for a group conversation. The open discussions in every episode allow the audience to understand the rapport, artistic exchange, and intellectual debates that run through this eclectic musical universe. The intimate, immersive space lends to the atmosphere of the show.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230519050000 +0200" stop="20230519062700 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Cirque Le Roux : La nuit du cerf</title>
<desc lang="fr">Cirque le Roux - A Deer in the Headlights - Cirque Le Roux, a reunion of six gifted artists, chooses glamour and eccentricity to dress up the acrobatic prowess of its creation. The acrobats master it all, from decor to costumes, and from the most perilous circus numbers to the slightest tremors of an intrigue which combines the eternal themes of love, friendship and the unsaid. Enter the strange and comical world of the Cirque Le Roux company with their disturbing story of A Deer in the Headlights performed on the stage of the Théâtre Libre de Paris. The story features three children, whose mother has died, who meet in the family home to prepare the funeral. The reunion is turned upside down by the irruption of a mysterious shaggy stranger. From now on, the funeral will take a completely different turn.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Cirque</category>
<icon src="https://img.bouygtel.fr/CMS/images/00FC166E621B1CDD9CDC7274E22B544F.jpg" />
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>