<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Bouygues -->
<programme start="20230413050800 +0200" stop="20230413060100 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Live From the Kennedy Center</title>
<desc lang="fr">Live From the Kennedy Center - When Nas was just 19 years old, he composed what would become one of hip-hop's defining masterpieces, Illmatic. To mark its 20th anniversary, Nas delivers a standout performance alongside the National Symphony Orchestra at Washington DC's Kennedy Center. With conductor Steven Reineke taking the orchestra through arrangements of beats by DJ Premier and Large Professor, Nas delivers impassioned renditions of tracks like &quot;N.Y. State of Mind&quot;, &quot;The World Is Yours&quot;, and &quot;Memory Lane (Sittin' in Da Park)&quot;. Between songs, the program cuts away to both archival and new interview footage to document Nas' rise from Queensbridge upstart to influential rap icon.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Pop &amp; Rock</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230413060100 +0200" stop="20230413073300 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Charlie Parker : &quot;Bird with Strings&quot; revisited à la Philharmonie de Paris</title>
<desc lang="fr">Charlie Parker - Bird with Strings Revisited - In the late 1940s, jazz saxophonist Charlie &quot;Bird&quot; Parker expressed his wish to record with a classical string section rather than his usual jazz quintet. This desire was fulfilled in 1949 and 1950 when he recorded two albums with oboe, harp, string section and a jazz rhythm section, released as 'Charlie Parker with Strings'. Fast forward 70 years, when saxophonists Olivier Bogé, Géraldine Laurent, Pierrick Pédron, Thomas de Pourquery, and Jaleel Shaw follow in the jazz legend's footsteps, revisiting the repertoire of those original albums in this 2019 concert at The Philharmonie de Paris. Bastien Stil conducts Christophe Dal Sasso's new orchestral arrangements in this genre-blending concert, which opens with Dal Sasso's very own Overture pour cinq saxophones et orchestra.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<icon src="https://img.bouygtel.fr/CMS/images/F0063316707C2A1E40D1DB5CDC61234F.jpg" />
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230413073300 +0200" stop="20230413081000 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Echoes Series: Ed O'Brien</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Ed O'Brien</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Echoes Series: Ed O'Brien - Echoes is a modern live music show hosted by Jehnny Beth (lead singer in the British band Savages). It presents leading and emerging bands and artists from the contemporary scene. The show takes place underneath the Palais de Tokyo museum in Paris, in the club of brutalist architecture, the &quot;Yoyo.&quot; The live sets are 30 minutes long and take place on a customized stage, creating closeness with the audience. The intimate, immersive space lends to the atmosphere of the show. The artistic direction by Antoine Carlier follows a minimalist, refined and pure aesthetic, allowing the artists' energy and emotions to take center stage. This episode features guitarist Ed O'Brien, a member of rock band Radiohead. His set includes the songs &quot;Mass,&quot; &quot;Olympik,&quot; and &quot;Brasil.&quot;</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230413081000 +0200" stop="20230413090000 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Audience Music</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Sofi Tukker</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Sofi Tukker - Enjoy ground-breaking concerts, in-depth artist interviews, and unique stories with host Ted Stryker. This concert series gives the audience an intimate view of music's most influential artists today. Shot in 4K, host Ted Stryker interviews musicians across all genres, creating one of the most unique music shows on TV today. This episode features a playful performance of the New York City-based electro-pop duo Sofi Tukker. The duo's name is a stylized merge of the birth names of its members Sophie Hawley-Weld and Tucker Halpern. The two started producing music together in 2014, when they met at Rhode Island's Brown University.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230413090000 +0200" stop="20230413103300 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Mötley Crüe</title>
<desc lang="fr">Mötley Crüe, the American rock band formed in the 1980s, was founded by bassist Nikki Sixx and drummer Tommy Lee, who were later joined by guitarist Mick Mars, and vocalist Vince Neil. Mötley Crüe has sold more than 100 million records worldwide, including 25 million in the US. On December 31, 2015, legendary rock icons Mötley Crüe completed their 35-year touring career as a band with a spectacular final concert at Staples Center in their hometown of Los Angeles, CA, just 10 miles from the Sunset Strip where the band's infamous and decadent career first launched. The band thrilled the sold-out arena with performances of mega-hits &quot;Kickstart My Heart,&quot; &quot;Girls Girls Girls,&quot; &quot;Home Sweet Home,&quot; and &quot;Dr. Feelgood.&quot; Directed by Jeff Tremaine and Christian Lamb.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Documentaire</category>
<category lang="fr">Société</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230413103300 +0200" stop="20230413113400 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Isle of Wight 2018: Part I</title>
<desc lang="fr">The Isle of Wight Festival, held in Newport, England is a rock-pop music festival that annually serves as the first major event opening the British festival summer. The tradition of the festival first saw the light of day in 1969, opening eleven days after the closing of legendary Woodstock and was regarded as the European counterpart to the legendary &quot;counterculture&quot; festival. In 1970, its line-up was stars-studded with gigs by Jimi Hendrix, The Who, The Doors, Joni Mitchell, Supertramp, Leonard Cohen and many more, establishing the name of the festival. In 2002, the festival was revived after 30 years of silence and brought back the sounds of contemporary musical legends to the Isle of Wight.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Pop &amp; Rock</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230413113400 +0200" stop="20230413134700 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam</title>
<desc lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam - New Cool Collective is one of the foremost Dutch jazz ensembles. Pioneering new blends of music styles since 1993, NCC has performed in various formations, from small combos to larger ensembles and even big bands! The ensemble's high energy is cut out for the dance floors, as dance, Latin, salsa, afrobeat and boogaloo all meet in a jazzy mix. NCC includes saxophonist Benjamin Herman, guitarist Rory Ronde, drummer Joost Kroon, percussionists Frank van Dok and Jos de Haas, pianist Willem Friede, bassist Leslie Lopez, and trumpeter David Rockefeller.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230413134700 +0200" stop="20230413150200 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Cabaret Contemporain</title>
<desc lang="fr">Cabaret Contemporain - &quot;Cabaret Contemporain&quot;: an explosive performance by musicians, composers, and improvisers who cross all musical boundaries with an innovative approach to the world of sound. Transforming life into dream and music into dance, the acoustic instruments are processed through an electronic filter which combines musical genres and codes. This performance is animated by the search for a new vocabulary of sounds. Enjoy this stunning live performance at the Suona Francese Festival in Rome's amazing Maxxi museum! Featuring Fabrizio Rat (piano), Giani Caserotto (guitar), Ronan Courty (bass), and Simon Drappier (bass).</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Pop &amp; Rock</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230413150200 +0200" stop="20230413171700 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam</title>
<desc lang="fr">New Cool Collective - Melkweg, Amsterdam - New Cool Collective is one of the foremost Dutch jazz ensembles. Pioneering new blends of music styles since 1993, NCC has performed in various formations, from small combos to larger ensembles and even big bands! The ensemble's high energy is cut out for the dance floors, as dance, Latin, salsa, afrobeat and boogaloo all meet in a jazzy mix. NCC includes saxophonist Benjamin Herman, guitarist Rory Ronde, drummer Joost Kroon, percussionists Frank van Dok and Jos de Haas, pianist Willem Friede, bassist Leslie Lopez, and trumpeter David Rockefeller.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230413171700 +0200" stop="20230413181400 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Audience Music</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">The Naked and Famous</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">This series features groundbreaking concerts, in-depth artist interviews and unique stories with host Ted Stryker. This concert series gives the audience an intimate view of music's most influential artists today. Shot in 4K, host Ted Stryker interviews musicians across all genres, creating the most unique music show on TV today. This episode features The Naked and Famous, a band from Auckland, New Zealand. They play a mix of electro pop and alternative rock. The group was founded in 2008 by singer Alisa Xayalith and singer/producer/guitarist Thom Powers. Soon after, they scored their first number one hit with &quot;Young Blood.&quot; Their second single &quot;Punching in a Dream&quot; also made it to the New Zealand hit lists. At the Red Studios in Hollywood, Alisa and Thom are supported by David Beadle and Luna Shadows.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Pop &amp; Rock</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230413181400 +0200" stop="20230413191700 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Joris Voorn</title>
<desc lang="fr">Joris Voorn - The Royal Concertgebouw is a night full of the best house and techno, hosted by one of the biggest names from the underground at one of the prettiest locations in the world. Renown as one of the most stunning sites dedicated to music, the Royal Concertgebouw has been transformed into a glorious cathedral of techno for one night only. Audio Obscura is a movement born out of love for cutting-edge underground dance music. Today, Audio Obscura has grown into one of the most sought-after destinations for leading DJs to play, and for partygoers, both young and old, to dance the night (and day) away.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Rap &amp; Techno</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230413191700 +0200" stop="20230413203200 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Bixiga 70 - BIRD 2019</title>
<desc lang="fr">Bixiga 70 - BIRD 2019 - Stemming from Brazil's São Paulo, Bixiga 70 is an exciting brass and percussion-based instrumental dance ensemble that combines jazz, funk, and Afro-Brazilian music, incorporating elements from dub, reggae, electronics, cumbia, carimbo, Ethio-jazz, and samba. The name Bixiga 70 is taken from a vibrant neighbourhood in downtown São Paulo. Organic, ritualistic, and sometimes even primal, the band's music appeals to those who seek out mental and physical freedom.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230413203200 +0200" stop="20230413210000 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Songbook</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Sorcha Richardson</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Songbook - &quot;I never heard anyone say that, and yeah, I know exactly what it means. It has to go in there, this has to be a song.&quot; Every song has its own story, and we all think it's a story we've heard before, but we haven't. Songbook finds and captures these intriguing stories by pulling you into the process of writing and composing. Known for its pristine sound, cinematic 4k video and eye for detail, Songbook live-captured episodes emphasize the paramount importance of quality. It addresses the on-the-spot elements of blending song and location at the right moment. Both the magical location and remarkable music interaction will get the attention they deserve. Simply because Songbook isn't just a live music session, it lives. This episode of Songbook features Irish singer-songwriter Sorcha Richardson.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230413210000 +0200" stop="20230413213300 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Audience Music</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Imagine Dragons</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Enjoy groundbreaking concerts, in-depth artist interviews, and unique stories with host Ted Stryker. This concert series gives the audience an intimate view of music's most influential artists today. Shot in 4K, host Ted Stryker interviews musicians across all genres, creating one of the most unique music shows on TV today. This episode features the multi-platinum, Grammy Award-winning band Imagine Dragons. They bring their passionately inventive alt-rock sound to a special, one-hour concert, just one month after releasing their hit song &quot;Natural.&quot; &quot;Living in a dog-eat-dog world can bring out the worst in you, and sometimes, the best,&quot; says the band's singer Dan Reynolds.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230413213300 +0200" stop="20230413223200 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Caixa Cubo - Da Pá Virada Sessions</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Andre Marques</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Andre Marques - Da Pá Virada Sessions - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the artists taking part in this series is pianist, composer, and arranger André Marques. He has been building a solid career, releasing his music with numerous groups: he is a member of the Latin Grammy-nominated Trio Curupira, the André Marques Sexteto, and he leads the Brazilian music orchestra Vintena Brasileira. In this episode of Da Pá Virada Sessions, André Marques performs an intimate solo piano recital.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230413223200 +0200" stop="20230413234800 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Lalah Hathaway - Sing Jazz 2018</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Lalah Hathaway</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Lalah Hathaway - Sing Jazz 2018 - Winner of five Grammys in four consecutive years, including the Grammy for best R&amp;B album in 2017, Lalah Hathaway is a force impossible to ignore. The American artist has shared the scene with Prince, Snoop Dogg, Stevie Wonder, Anita Baker, Mary J. Blige, Frank Ocean and many others, an irrefutable proof of her keen musical sense and enormous talent. With a 26-year career, Hathaway is still highly sought after by the biggest names in music. See her transform the 2018 Sing Jazz festival scene into a real R&amp;B club, where she flaunts her voice and stage presence out of the ordinary.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<icon src="https://img.bouygtel.fr/CMS/images/E537F830342471D10D4F174FE9E53A46.jpg" />
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230413234800 +0200" stop="20230414005000 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Nilüfer Yanya - Echoes Series: Nilufer Yanya</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Jane Birkin, Leonie Pernet &amp; Rone Yoyo</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Echoes Series - Episode 5 - Echoes is a modern live music show hosted by Jehnny Beth (lead singer in the British band Savages). It presents leading and emerging bands and artists from the contemporary scene. The show takes place underneath the Palais de Tokyo museum in Paris, in the club of brutalist architecture, the &quot;Yoyo.&quot; The live sets are 30 minutes long and take place on a customized stage, creating closeness with the audience. Once the bands have performed, Jehnny Beth invites everyone to sit at her roundtable for a group conversation. The open discussions in every episode allow the audience to understand the rapport, artistic exchange, and intellectual debates that run through this eclectic musical universe. The intimate, immersive space lends to the atmosphere of the show.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<category lang="fr">Variétés</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230414005000 +0200" stop="20230414015600 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Panorama do Choro : Da Pá Virada Sessions</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Panorama do Choro</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Panorama do Choro - Da Pá Virada Sessions - The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the bands taking part in this series is Panorama de Coro. This ensemble combines jazz and traditional Brazilian music. The resulting music has a festive, almost street-like atmosphere. Panorama de Coro consists of Roberta Valente (pandeiro and percussion), Alexandre Ribeiro (clarinet), Gian Correa (7-string guitar), Henrique Araujo (cavaquinho), João Poleto (flute and tenor saxophone) and Yves Finzetto (pandeiro and percussion).</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230414015600 +0200" stop="20230414030000 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Invisible World : WOMEX 2018</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Invisible World</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">One of the participants was the band Invisible World, which operates at the crossroads where Eastern European and Mediterranean influences come together and break new ground. Invisible World is led by the inventive Czech bassist Tomáš Liška, together with the Turkish violinist Efe Turumtay, the Serbian accordionist Nikola Zarić and the Moravian drummer Kamil Slezák.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Musique</category>
<category lang="fr">Musicale</category>
<icon src="https://img.bouygtel.fr/CMS/images/A5539A1D83657FE964693E3151A5A56C.jpg" />
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230414030000 +0200" stop="20230414035500 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">WOMEX 2018</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">The Garifuna Collektive</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr"> In 2018 WOMEX took place in Las Palmas in Gran Canaria. One of the participants was The Garifuna Collective. These young and old musicians from the Caribbean keep Andy Palacio's legacy alive.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Musique</category>
<category lang="fr">Musicale</category>
<icon src="https://img.bouygtel.fr/CMS/images/BD1A4F239A69EC884BEAFFB08B575969.jpg" />
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230414035500 +0200" stop="20230414050200 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Caixa Cubo - Da Pá Virada Sessions</title>
<sub-title lang="fr">Trio Corrente</sub-title>
<desc lang="fr">Trio Corrente - Da Pá Virada Sessions - Da Pá Virada sessions bring the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian jazz, and beyond. Filmed in São Paulo, each session offers a unique experience by giving a fresh look into Brazil's music scene. The artists for each session are selected in consultation with Stingray DJAZZ's music editor. One of the bands taking part in this series is Trio Corrente, which was formed in 2001, consisting of Fabio Torres on piano, Paulo Paulelli on bass, and Edu Ribeiro on drums. Since then, the trio has been creating an original sound playing the classics of choro and Música Popular Brasileira.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<icon src="https://img.bouygtel.fr/CMS/images/85AF68953696EE583B766546E072B267.jpg" />
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>
<programme start="20230414050200 +0200" stop="20230414062900 +0200" channel="StingrayFestival.fr">
<title lang="fr">Ron Carter : Foursight</title>
<desc lang="fr">Ron Carter - Foursight - An evening with the &quot;Foursight&quot; quartet takes you on a tour of Ron Carter's discography, with two thousand five hundred albums, which is to say the consideration he has received since his debut in 1959. After accompanying Jacky Byard and Eric Dolphy, he joined Miles Davis' legendary VSOP with Herbie Hancock, Wayne Shorter, and Tony Williams, among others. Much more than an accompanist, the double bassist is above all a great soloist, as much in intimate trios as in advanced experimental formations or large orchestras. He will be remarkably surrounded here, during his &quot;Foursight&quot; show at Jazz sous les pommiers 2019.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Spectacle</category>
<category lang="fr">Jazz</category>
<rating system="CSA"><value>Tout public</value></rating>
</programme>