<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Voo -->
<programme start="20230423033500 +0200" stop="20230423043500 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Pilgrimage: The Road to Santiago S5 (3/3)</title>
<desc lang="fr">After 14 days and 364 kilometres, the group finally reach the famous Sanctuary of Fatima.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Découverte</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/06/2156364_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230423043500 +0200" stop="20230423070500 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">This is BBC Two</title>
<desc lang="fr">Highlights of programmes on BBC Two.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/33/1763280_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230423070500 +0200" stop="20230423080500 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Gardeners' World</title>
<desc lang="fr">Frances Tophill reveals some exciting news. After years of dreaming, she finally has her very own garden and can't wait to share her plans and get to grips with bringing this compact space to life. Toby Buckland meets a man who has planted his plot with a wonderful array of fruit and nuts, and there's a gardener in Gloucestershire who is potty about the 500 pot plants she has designed specially to produce a floral firework display. In west London, a community champion is growing a range of unusual produce in the heart of an urban jungle. And there are also more inspiring viewers' videos.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/31/2155083_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230423080500 +0200" stop="20230423090000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Countryfile</title>
<desc lang="fr">Countryfile launches 'Wild Britain', an initiative to galvanize us to help our wildlife.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Mag Société</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/43/2161494_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230423090000 +0200" stop="20230423093000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Beechgrove Garden</title>
<desc lang="fr">Lizzie and Calum provide some top tips for making the garden as productive as possible.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/24/07/1805695_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230423093000 +0200" stop="20230423100000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Landward (3/26)</title>
<desc lang="fr">The team dive into the sea for a marine special, with a guest appearance from a mermaid!</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Nature</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/27/59/1870648_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230423100000 +0200" stop="20230423110000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Sunday with Laura Kuenssberg</title>
<desc lang="fr">Interviews with key politicians and public figures.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/32/1753818_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230423110000 +0200" stop="20230423134000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Morning Session</title>
<desc lang="fr">Coverage from the Crucible Theatre in Sheffield.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/01/05/2176644_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230423134000 +0200" stop="20230423141000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Sign Zone: The Big Cook Out S2</title>
<desc lang="fr">In the final episode of the series, Sam and Shauna travel to the small town of Deri near Caerphilly to celebrate the success of Deri Rugby Club, which has gone from the brink of extinction just four years ago to being crowned league champions. As well as providing a social and sporting focus for the town, the club and its members have also provided some invaluable support to people in difficulty over the years. To celebrate the achievements of the players and the volunteers who run the club, Sam and Shauna cook a huge venison feast with their help. They make smoked steak sandwiches with Caerphilly cheese and a Kentucky-style stew known as a burgoo with grilled venison tenderloin and a broccoli slaw. As part of their mission to promote sustainable meat sources Sam and Shauna take part in a controlled deer hunt to manage the herd.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/08/2158278_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230423141000 +0200" stop="20230423144000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">The Best Dishes Ever S1</title>
<desc lang="fr">Ainsley Harriott introduces a selection of classic recipes from some of the BBC's best-loved television chefs. Today he's serving up dishes that are delicious but also easy on the wallet - good quality and good value. The menu includes a Bake Off masterclass featuring Sussex suet pond pudding, a James Martin tomato soup with garlic bread, the Hairy Bikers' version of a ploughman's lunch and Ainsley's own perfect potato tart.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/07/1752962_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230423144000 +0200" stop="20230423151500 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Songs of Praise (St George's Day)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«St George's Day»Laura Wright celebrates England's patron Saint George on a dragon hunt in London.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Documentaire</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/46/1978317_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230423151500 +0200" stop="20230423160000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Athlétisme : Marathon de Londres</title>
<desc lang="fr">Coverage continues of the 43rd staging of the world-famous London Marathon. There are more interviews with the inspirational people and famous faces competing in this special event, with many of those running to raise money for causes close to their hearts. Commentary comes from Steve Cram, Andrew Cotter, Baroness Tanni Grey-Thompson and Paula Radcliffe, while Jeanette Kwakye, JJ Chalmers, Steve Brown and Sarah Mulkerrins report from around the course.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/08/01/1917713_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230423160000 +0200" stop="20230423181500 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Afternoon Session</title>
<desc lang="fr">Coverage from the Crucible Theatre in Sheffield.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/01/05/2176644_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230423181500 +0200" stop="20230423190000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Flog It ! S16</title>
<desc lang="fr">Flog It! comes from the Boconnoc estate in the Cornish countryside. Antiques experts Jonathan Pratt and Nick Hall uncover a pair of Georgian chairs and a children's pedal fire engine. Paul Martin learns about the creation of the historic south Cornish port of Charlestown and how it led to the downfall of its creator, Charles Rashleigh.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/54/2122567_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230423190000 +0200" stop="20230423200000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">London Marathon Highlights</title>
<desc lang="fr">Gabby Logan presents highlights from the 43rd London Marathon, including all the key moments from the elite men's, women's and wheelchair races. Kenya's Amos Kipruto and Ethiopian Yalemzerf Yehualaw are the defending men's and women's champions respectively, while Switzerland's Marcel Hug and Catherine Debrunner are seeking to retain their wheelchair crowns. Plus inspirational stories from some of the 50,000 mass runners who are all pounding the streets of London with the same goal in mind - to reach the finish line. Commentary comes from Andrew Cotter, Steve Cram, Paula Radcliffe and Baroness Tanni Grey-Thompson, with reporting from Jeanette Kwakye, JJ Chalmers, Steve Brown and Sarah Mulkerrins.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/28/2125609_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230423200000 +0200" stop="20230423210000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Evening Session</title>
<desc lang="fr">Coverage from the Crucible Theatre in Sheffield.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/01/05/2176644_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230423210000 +0200" stop="20230423220000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Countryfile</title>
<desc lang="fr">Charlotte Smith and Hamza Yassin travel to Dumfries House.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Mag Société</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/43/2161494_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230423220000 +0200" stop="20230423230000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Last Woman on Earth with Sara Pascoe (Jordan) S2 (2/3)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Jordan»Sara Pascoe learns Jordan's dying jobs, including herding in the desert with the Bedouin.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Documentaire</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/30/13/2165600_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230423230000 +0200" stop="20230423234500 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">QI</title>
<desc lang="fr">Sandi has a testing time with Susan Calman, Maisie Adam, Josh Widdicombe and Alan Davies.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/12/1745818_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230423234500 +0200" stop="20230424001500 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Colin From Accounts (Benedict Cumbercrapp) S1 (2/8)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Benedict Cumbercrapp»When Ashley makes a mess in Gordon's sock drawer, an impromptu trip to Costco follows.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Série Comédie</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/56/1752524_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230424001500 +0200" stop="20230424010500 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Day 9</title>
<desc lang="fr">Highlights from day nine at the 2023 World Snooker Championship.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/06/58/2092323_A.jpg" />
</programme>