<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Voo -->
<programme start="20230505024500 +0200" stop="20230505033000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Secrets of the Chippendales Murders (The Show Must Go On) S1 (3/4)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«The Show Must Go On»The NYPD investigate multiple leads into the murder of Nick De Noia.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Documentaire</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/31/33/2170211_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230505033000 +0200" stop="20230505042000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Secrets of the Chippendales Murders (The Naked Truth) S1 (4/4)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«The Naked Truth»The FBI are led on an international manhunt for the person behind Nick De Noia's murder.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Documentaire</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/24/28/2164801_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230505042000 +0200" stop="20230505074500 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">This is BBC Two</title>
<desc lang="fr">Highlights of programmes on BBC Two.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/18/1765031_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230505074500 +0200" stop="20230505083000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Bargain Hunt S64</title>
<desc lang="fr">Charlie Ross presents Bargain Hunt from an antiques and collectors fair in Shepton Mallet, Somerset. Helped by experts Kate Bliss and Colin Young, the teams hunt for bargains to sell at auction. Meanwhile, can anyone guess Charlie's mystery item, which played a big part in local industry?</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/58/1626268_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230505083000 +0200" stop="20230505090000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Clive Myrie's Italian Road Trip (Torre Del Greco) S1 (4/15)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Torre Del Greco»Clive spends a night on the Golden Mile, Italy's original millionaire's row.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Documentaire</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/04/1756160_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230505090000 +0200" stop="20230505100000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Gardeners' World</title>
<desc lang="fr">Monty adds some interest to the spring garden. He also sows peas and shallots, has some thrifty tips for petunias, and plants lilies in pots. Carol Klein visits Mothecombe Gardens in Devon, which has been designed specifically for pollinators, with swathes of nectar-rich daisies and lavender. Arit Anderson joins a group of young carers at a community garden in West Sussex, where they go for respite, friendship and fun. Plus more of the films that have been sent in by viewers.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/31/2155083_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230505100000 +0200" stop="20230505130000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">BBC Elections</title>
<desc lang="fr">Ongoing coverage of local elections in England and Northern Ireland.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/32/1753818_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230505130000 +0200" stop="20230505144500 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Politics Live</title>
<desc lang="fr">Jo Coburn is your guide as the votes are counted in 2023's bumper set of elections. BBC correspondents will be at all the key counts around the country. David Wallace Lockhart will crunch the numbers on his giant screen, and Professor Sir John Curtice will assess the underlying electoral trends. Senior politicians and commentators will be on hand to give their verdict on the results.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/22/02/2030147_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230505144500 +0200" stop="20230505153000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Impossible S5</title>
<desc lang="fr">Game show in which players must avoid giving impossible answers to a set of questions.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Jeu</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/04/1660824_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230505153000 +0200" stop="20230505161500 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Countryfile Spring Diaries S3 (5/5)</title>
<desc lang="fr">Jules Hudson looks at the spring dangers outdoors and in homes which could harm pets.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Nature</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/07/30/1765110_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230505161500 +0200" stop="20230505170000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Escape to the Country S19 (5/70)</title>
<desc lang="fr">Ginny Buckley helps a couple to look for a character home in Shropshire.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Télé-Réalité</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/01/02/2153608_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230505170000 +0200" stop="20230505180000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">The Great British Sewing Bee S8</title>
<desc lang="fr">It's Children's Week in the sewing room, and Sara Pascoe invites the sewers to make a cute sailor suit for a toddler. The task requires them to make elasticated shorts and a top with a square collar and ties. For the Transformation Challenge, the sewers turn old school clothes into a cool outfit to be seen in outside school. Then things get scary when mini-models enter the sewing room for a Halloween-themed Made to Measure. Whose costume will go down a treat and win Garment of the Week, and who will leave with a whimper?</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/18/13/2185358_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230505180000 +0200" stop="20230505200000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Diamond League : Meeting de Doha</title>
<desc lang="fr">Coverage of the opening Diamond League meet of the 2023 season, with many of the world's best athletes in action at the Khalifa International Stadium in Doha. All eyes will be on Qatari star Mutaz Barshim, the reigning world and Olympic high jump champion, who memorably shared the gold medal at the Tokyo Games with Italian rival and friend Gianmarco Tamberi. Kenya's Faith Kipyegon will be the woman to watch in the 1500m - the 29-year-old is a double Olympic and world champion in the discipline and holds seven of the fastest 20 times in history over the distance. And Great Britain's Holly Bradshaw, who won bronze in the pole vault in Tokyo, takes on a high-class field featuring world and Olympic champion Katie Moon of the USA.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/21/41/2005129_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230505200000 +0200" stop="20230505203000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Clive Myrie's Italian Road Trip (Capri) S1 (5/15)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Capri»Clive finds himself on stage in the world's most surprising celebrity nightclub.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Documentaire</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/13/1755067_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230505203000 +0200" stop="20230505213000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Les motards poilus : Cooking Trip en Méditerranée S1</title>
<desc lang="fr">The bikers' Corsican adventure begins in Bonifacio. They head straight for one of the best delis in town to scope out the local cuisine, including the legendary sausage figatelli. At the Étang de Diane, a salt-water inlet, the bikers discover that mussels and oysters have been grown in these nutrient-rich waters since Roman times. And the bikers spend their final night in a mountaintop B&amp;B.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/18/13/2185361_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230505213000 +0200" stop="20230505220000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Beechgrove Garden</title>
<desc lang="fr">Ahead of the coronation weeken, there is a slight royal theme to the work going on at Beechgrove Garden. Carole Baxter and Calum Clunie will be planting delphiniums, reportedly one of the favourite flowers of HM King Charles III. Elsewhere in the garden, Carole starts to refresh the planting in the Garden for Wildlife with a selection of varieties known to help pollinators and other species. Calum replants some of his underperforming roses from the end of last year, and Brian Cunningham sends another report on the work he is doing at his garden in Perthshire. And there is the next in Beechgrove's Back to Basics skills guide.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/24/07/1805695_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230505220000 +0200" stop="20230505230000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Gardeners' World</title>
<desc lang="fr">A celebration of the people who give up their time to help others.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/31/2155083_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230505230000 +0200" stop="20230505233000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Wrexham: Hollywood or Bust</title>
<desc lang="fr">Exploring why Wrexham AFC's promotion to the Football League means so much to fans.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Documentaire</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/52/1752444_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230505233000 +0200" stop="20230506000500 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Newsnight</title>
<desc lang="fr">The day's important national and international news stories. With Faisal Islam.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Infos</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/37/1776034_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230506000500 +0200" stop="20230506003500 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">MOTDx</title>
<desc lang="fr">Jermaine Jenas brings you the best of football culture.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Mag Sport</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/17/1749481_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230506003500 +0200" stop="20230506010000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Colin From Accounts (Bubbly Sophie) S1 (4/8)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Bubbly Sophie»Ash and Gordon's awkward sexual encounter causes them to drift apart.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Série Comédie</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/1752367_A.jpg" />
</programme>