<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Voo -->
<programme start="20230530021500 +0200" stop="20230530031500 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">The Great British Sewing Bee S9</title>
<desc lang="fr">Sara Pascoe welcomes 12 sewers to the Sewing Bee in Leeds. Judges Patrick Grant and Esme Young want to see how the newbies deal with 'Classics with a Twist'. For their first Pattern Challenge, the sewers make a top with a twist at its centre, which is a straightforward construction with a tricky brain-teaser. For the 90-minute Transformation Challenge, they take the office uniform - a pencil skirt and blouse - and give it their own personal twist to reflect their style. Finally, in the Made to Measure round, the sewers meet their models for the first time and attempt to perfectly fit a dress that has cut-out details. Who will impress the judges and win Garment of the Week, and whose hopes of staying in the competition won't last beyond week one?</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/18/13/2185358_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230530031500 +0200" stop="20230530041500 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Turkey: Empire of Erdogan S1 (2/2)</title>
<desc lang="fr">Erdogan cracks down hard on dissent, becoming the most powerful leader of modern Turkey.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Documentaire</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/16/1753819_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230530041500 +0200" stop="20230530073500 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">This is BBC Two</title>
<desc lang="fr">Highlights of programmes on BBC Two.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/19/1853151_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230530073500 +0200" stop="20230530080500 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Great Coastal Railway Journeys (Liverpool to Blackpool) S2 (2/20)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Liverpool to Blackpool»Michael Portillo crosses the Irish Sea, bound for the mighty port of Liverpool.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Documentaire</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/08/18/2193914_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230530080500 +0200" stop="20230530085000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Garden Rescue S8</title>
<desc lang="fr">Simon and Nancy would like the team to inject some of the glamour of Tinseltown into the unloved, neglected garden of their 400-year-old cottage. They have recently moved to the UK from Beverly Hills and are desperate for a nice spot to sit with some shade and privacy that reminds them of the home they left behind. Can Charlie and Chris bring their vision to life with £4K?</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/11/19/2195336_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230530085000 +0200" stop="20230530095000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Hidden Treasures of the National Trust S1 (1/6)</title>
<desc lang="fr">Rebuilding a Chinese bridge, saving a 450-year-old table, and a painting with a secret.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Documentaire</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/13/1767479_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230530095000 +0200" stop="20230530100000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Lifeline (Melanoma Focus) (n°2)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Melanoma Focus»Owain Wyn Evans makes an appeal on behalf of Melanoma Focus.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Société</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/24/51/1745779_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230530100000 +0200" stop="20230530120000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Nicky Campbell BBC News Talk</title>
<desc lang="fr">Nicky Campbell takes your calls on the day's talking points, hearing views and experiences from across the UK. Call 08085 909693 between 9am and 11am on weekdays (calls are free from mobiles and landlines).</desc>
<category lang="fr">Autre</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/05/1978623_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230530120000 +0200" stop="20230530131500 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">BBC News</title>
<desc lang="fr">Twenty-four hours a day, the latest national and international stories as they break.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Infos</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/20/27/1880115_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230530131500 +0200" stop="20230530140000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">The Super League Show</title>
<desc lang="fr">The latest rugby league highlights including a meeting of last year's Grand Finalists as Leeds host St Helens. They're the two most successful clubs in the history of the competition and Leeds are amongst the teams hoping to stop St Helens being crowned champions for a fifth consecutive year. Two of the current top three meet as Hull KR face Wigan, the leaders Warrington are at Leigh and Huddersfield host Castleford. Salford play Hull FC and the bottom team Wakefield are away to Catalans Dragons.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/37/2142957_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230530140000 +0200" stop="20230530144500 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Impossible S6</title>
<desc lang="fr">Game show presented by Rick Edwards in which players score points by answering questions correctly. However, they must avoid the impossible answers, otherwise they will be eliminated from the show until the next day. In each episode there are three rounds, and the three highest scorers from each round play against each other in the final. The winner of this battle faces a £10,000 question.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Jeu</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/04/1660824_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230530144500 +0200" stop="20230530151500 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Eggheads S20</title>
<desc lang="fr">Challengers take on probably the greatest quiz team in Britain.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Jeu</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/20/00/2134059_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230530151500 +0200" stop="20230530154500 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">James Martin's Food Map of Britain</title>
<desc lang="fr">Chef James Martin takes to the skies to explore how the beautiful and unique landscape of the British Isles produces distinct and delicious regional ingredients. In this episode he feasts his eyes over the bounty of the West Country, where he gets an understanding of why Devon's milk is so creamy and why a small corner of Cornwall has started exporting tea to China. During his journey he cooks an exotic tea-smoked duck and a decadent clotted cream summer pudding.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/08/13/2193913_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230530154500 +0200" stop="20230530161500 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">A Countryside Summer S1 (7/15)</title>
<desc lang="fr">John Craven shares some top picks of the best beaches in Britain.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Nature</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122122_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230530161500 +0200" stop="20230530171500 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Big Cats About the House S1 (3/3)</title>
<desc lang="fr">Willow an injured cheetah cub needs Giles's help. Maya makes her first tv appearance and becomes a big cat ambassador. In Kenya Giles helps lions in trouble.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Animalier</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/20/29/2198925_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230530171500 +0200" stop="20230530181500 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Back in Time for the Corner Shop (20s, 30s &amp; 40s) S1 (2/6)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«20s, 30s &amp; 40s»The Arderns continue their time travelling journey in the 20s, 30s &amp; 40s. From Izal loo roll to powdered eggs, they learn how life behind the counter reflects 30 years of change.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Histoire</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/19/1853109_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230530181500 +0200" stop="20230530190000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Flog It ! S14</title>
<desc lang="fr">Paul Martin presents from Norwich cathedral in Norfolk, once home to Benedictine monks. Experts Thomas Plant and David Fletcher pick out some items to take to auction. Among them are an old astronomical map and a watercolour by a local artist. Meanwhile, Paul explores the history of the Broads.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/20/12/2122567_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230530190000 +0200" stop="20230530193000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Richard Osman's House of Games S5</title>
<desc lang="fr">Every day this week, celebrity contestants Edith Bowman, Fern Brady, Will Kirk and Martin Lewis take on a series of quiz rounds selected by the host, quiz legend Richard Osman. A daily winner is declared following a quickfire round at the end of each show, and the scores are tallied across the week, resulting in an overall champion being crowned on Friday. Will the winning stars opt for the much-coveted House of Games wheelie luggage, or will they be tempted by the House of Games reusable coffee mug, which is brand new for this series?</desc>
<category lang="fr">Jeu</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/05/1687924_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230530193000 +0200" stop="20230530200000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Great Coastal Railway Journeys (Whitby to Robin Hood's Bay) S2 (7/20)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Whitby to Robin Hood's Bay»Michael Portillo continues his railway adventure at Whitby.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Documentaire</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/08/18/2193914_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230530200000 +0200" stop="20230530210000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Digging for Britain (Ice Age Camp and a Saint with Syphilis) S10 (6/6)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Ice Age Camp and a Saint with Syphilis»An Ice Age camp and the mystery of a medieval skeleton.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Histoire</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/30/2122573_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230530210000 +0200" stop="20230530220000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Springwatch</title>
<desc lang="fr">Featuring a smorgasboard of wildlife: mammals, birds, reptiles, amphibians, inverts and a botany bonanza. Michaela Strachan heads out in search of all six of Britain's native reptile species, while Chris Packham gets into the finer detail of some of our nests on site at RSPB Arne. Iolo Williams meets up with the series's resident botanist as they uncover some rather revealing revelations about our British flora, while Gillian Burke goes in search of some of Snowdonia's brilliant bats.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/18/10/2197863_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230530220000 +0200" stop="20230530230000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Forensics: The Real CSI (Playing with Fire) S3 (3/4)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Playing with Fire»A major factory in Birmingham is burned to the ground.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Documentaire</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/59/1974919_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230530230000 +0200" stop="20230530233000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Colin From Accounts (High Needs People) S1 (8/8)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«High Needs People»Ashley and Gordon must find a new home for Colin so they can go their separate ways.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Série Comédie</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/59/1752384_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230530233000 +0200" stop="20230531001500 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Newsnight</title>
<desc lang="fr">The day's important national and international news stories. With Victoria Derbyshire.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Infos</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/20/21/1805472_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230531001500 +0200" stop="20230531014000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Denmark</title>
<desc lang="fr">When Herb discovers that Danish convicts live a life of luxury, he decides to travel to Denmark and get arrested.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Comédie</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/20/29/2198926_A.jpg" />
</programme>