<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Voo -->
<programme start="20230326012500 +0100" stop="20230326032500 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Elaine Paige at the BBC</title>
<desc lang="fr">Elaine Paige OBE is Britain's biggest and most enduring star of musical theatre, enjoying success for over four decades in the West End, on Broadway, and on TV, radio and the pop charts. This selection of some of her best-loved songs and finest performances at the BBC features huge hits like Don't Cry For Me Argentina, Memory and I Know Him So Well. There are also rarely seen archive gems from the earliest days of Elaine's career, and her own unique interpretation of many musical masterpieces from shows like Chess and Anything Goes' all underline why she has stayed at the very top for as long as she has.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Concert</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/56/1752527_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230326032500 +0200" stop="20230326054500 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Burning</title>
<desc lang="fr">Jong-su's former neighbour introduces him to a man with a mysterious hobby.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Drame</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/19/2162724_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230326054500 +0200" stop="20230326073500 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">This is BBC Two</title>
<desc lang="fr">Highlights of programmes on BBC Two.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/41/1755108_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230326073500 +0200" stop="20230326083500 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Gardeners' World</title>
<desc lang="fr">As plants begin to show their early growth, Monty gets plenty of plants for free when he demonstrates how to make the most of herbaceous perennials. He also cuts back pelargoniums that have overwintered in the greenhouse and makes a start on sowing vegetables. Nick Bailey shares plans for his new garden in Cambridgeshire and shows us how to create a container garden ideal for those on the move. Frances Tophill discovers more ways to use cut flowers as she visits a florist in Dorset. Sue Kent has plenty to do to start the growing season in her Swansea garden as she creates a white border and experiments with an unusual way to grow container vegetables. And Rachel de Thame celebrates the majestic hellebore. Plus more of the films that have been sent in by viewers.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/31/2155083_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230326083500 +0200" stop="20230326093000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Countryfile</title>
<desc lang="fr">Matt Baker and Anita Rani meet the volunteers trying to save the River Wye from pollution.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Mag Société</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/43/2161494_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230326093000 +0200" stop="20230326103000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Pilgrimage: The Road to Santiago (2/3)</title>
<desc lang="fr">Life on the pilgrimage begins to challenge the celebrities physically and spiritually.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Découverte</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/06/2156364_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230326103000 +0200" stop="20230326110000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Weatherman Walking (Talacre to Rhyl) (6/8)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Talacre to Rhyl»Weatherman Derek Brockway is in Flintshire, walking from Talacre to Rhyl.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Nature</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/34/2122125_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230326110000 +0200" stop="20230326123000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Saturday Kitchen Best Bites</title>
<desc lang="fr">The best bits and favourite moments from Saturday Kitchen.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/56/1682723_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230326123000 +0200" stop="20230326130000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Coast to Coast Food Festival (Belfast Mela) S1 (6/20)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Belfast Mela»Colin and Edith join the festivities and try the food at Belfast's Mela festival.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Documentaire</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/56/2122583_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230326130000 +0200" stop="20230326133000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Sign Zone: The Big Cook Out S1</title>
<desc lang="fr">Cookery series in which American smokehouse barbecue chefs Sam and Shauna travel across Wales to create huge outdoor feasts. In this edition, Sam and Shauna celebrate Barry Town United Football Club's promotion to the Welsh Premier League by cooking a whole pig Hawaiian-style in a huge brick firepit.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/24/19/2158278_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230326133000 +0200" stop="20230326140000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Sign Zone: The Big Cook Out S2</title>
<desc lang="fr">Sam and Shauna are on a mission to change the way people cook outdoors and to celebrate amazing communities across Wales. Sam and Shauna kick-off their meaty smoke-and-fire fuelled bonanza at Clwyd Special Riding School in north Wales. For over 30 years, this unique place has helped people of all ages who have additional learning needs or physical disabilities, and it is run almost entirely by an army of volunteers. With over 100 people to feed, Sam and Shauna organise a spectacular cookout of ten huge beef briskets, barbecued Southern-style in a unique giant handmade cinderblock smoker, built with the help of the community. The succulent beef is served with a Lexington red slaw with creme creole and a southern American rice and peas dish called Hopping John, all wrapped up in handmade tacos.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/24/19/2158278_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230326140000 +0200" stop="20230326154500 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">La grande attaque du train d'or</title>
<desc lang="fr">A gentleman crook and a master safe-cracker attempt the first moving train robbery.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Thriller</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/17/40/2160777_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230326154500 +0200" stop="20230326171000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Figure Skating World Championships Highlights</title>
<desc lang="fr">The best of the action from Saitama, Japan, where ice dance duo Lilah Fear and Lewis Gibson hope to win Britain's first World Championship medal for 39 years. The pair took silver at January's European Championships, recording Britain's best performance on the continental stage since Jayne Torvill and Christopher Dean in 1994. Elsewhere, the home crowd will cheer on Shoma Uno and Kaori Sakamoto as they try to retain their individual titles. Uno became the third Japanese skater to win the men's crown last year, capitalising on the absence of rivals Nathan Chen and Yuzuru Hanyu. Sakamoto, meanwhile, produced a personal best score to beat Belgium's Loena Hendrickx to gold 12 months ago. Katherine Downes introduces the action, with expert analysis from 1980 Olympic champion Robin Cousins.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport nl Glisse</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/11/19/2158280_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230326171000 +0200" stop="20230326181000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Mission déco S4 (3/8)</title>
<desc lang="fr">The designers make over a hotel room at a top golf resort on the banks of the River Clyde.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Télé-Réalité</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/43/2161495_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230326181000 +0200" stop="20230326191000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Course sans frontières S3</title>
<desc lang="fr">Five teams set off from Vancouver on a race across Canada.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Télé-Réalité</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/24/2157031_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230326191000 +0200" stop="20230326200000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Flog It ! S15</title>
<desc lang="fr">Flog It! comes from the ancestral home of the Spencer family, Althorp in Northamptonshire. Nineteen generations have lived here, employing local people to work at the house and vast estate. Antiques experts Christina Trevanion and Will Axon find a selection of antiques and collectibles to take to auction. Christina is drawn to a 1950s toy pedal car, and Will finds a Mouseman tray. Paul Martin discovers how the Grand Union Canal was the waterway equivalent of the M1 as he takes to the water on a narrow boat and discovers what life was like for the boat people who ferried cargo from A to B.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/54/2122567_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230326200000 +0200" stop="20230326210000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Les hôtels les plus incroyables du monde (Reid's Palace, Madeira) S4 (2/6)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Reid's Palace, Madeira»Monica and Giles work on a historic hotel situated in the island of perpetual springtime.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Documentaire</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/24/24/2164788_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230326210000 +0200" stop="20230326220000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Britain's Biggest Warship: Goes to Sea (Don't Feed the Birds) S2 (2/3)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Don't Feed the Birds»The next phase of flight testing for the top secret F35 jets is underway. Coping with a rolling, pitching, wind-blown deck is hard enough, but a full- blown hurricane is looming.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/09/2157697_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230326220000 +0200" stop="20230326230100 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">We need to talk about Cosby S1 (4/4)</title>
<desc lang="fr">After spending the early 00s advocating respectability politics, Cosby falls to Earth.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Documentaire</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/24/56/2163653_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230326230100 +0200" stop="20230326234500 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">QI</title>
<desc lang="fr">Hannah Waddingham, Desiree Burch and Jason Manford look at animals that begin with a 'T'.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/12/1745818_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230326234500 +0200" stop="20230327001500 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">The Cockfields S1 (1/3)</title>
<desc lang="fr">Simon's taking girlfriend Donna to meet his family for the first time.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Série Comédie</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/56/1752524_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230327001500 +0200" stop="20230327013000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">The Holy Land and Us - Our Untold Stories S1 (2/2)</title>
<desc lang="fr">Rob and Sarah are joined by two women trying to find out what happened to their families.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Documentaire</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/13/1755320_A.jpg" />
</programme>