<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Voo -->
<programme start="20230529020000 +0200" stop="20230529030000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Question Time</title>
<desc lang="fr">Fiona Bruce presents Question Time with a panel of politicians and other guests facing topical questions from an audience in different parts of the UK each week. Also live on iPlayer at 20:00.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/26/1859241_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230529030000 +0200" stop="20230529040000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Steeltown Murders S1 (2/4)</title>
<desc lang="fr">Paul begins the swabbing operation, but it may not be as straightforward as he had hoped.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Série Dramatique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/20/27/1752528_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230529040000 +0200" stop="20230529074500 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">This is BBC Two</title>
<desc lang="fr">Highlights of programmes on BBC Two.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/19/1853151_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230529074500 +0200" stop="20230529081500 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Great Coastal Railway Journeys (Douglas to Port Erin) S2 (1/20)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Douglas to Port Erin»Michael Portillo begins on another railway adventure across and beyond the United Kingdom.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Documentaire</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/08/18/2193914_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230529081500 +0200" stop="20230529090000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Bargain Hunt</title>
<desc lang="fr">The teams are battling it out in Doune, Perthshire. Natasha Raskin Sharp meets leading tartan historian Peter MacDonald to learn about the origins of the iconic patterned cloth, while experts Roo Irvine and Danny Sebastian are guiding the Reds and the Blues.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/58/1626268_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230529090000 +0200" stop="20230529093000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Coast to Coast Food Festival (York) S1 (10/20)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«York»Sean Fletcher and Edith Bowman go in search of tips and treats at the York Food Festival.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Documentaire</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/46/1754292_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230529093000 +0200" stop="20230529100000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Banjo: Designing the Hebrides (Lighthouse Glengorm) S1 (4/6)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Lighthouse Glengorm»Banjo redesigns a castle turret room and a bedroom at a lighthouse.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Documentaire</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/04/43/1763251_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230529100000 +0200" stop="20230529120000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Nicky Campbell BBC News Talk</title>
<desc lang="fr">Rachel Burden takes your calls on the day's talking points, hearing views and experiences from across the UK. Call 08085 909693 between 9am and 11am on weekdays (calls are free from mobiles and landlines).</desc>
<category lang="fr">Autre</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/05/1752469_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230529120000 +0200" stop="20230529140000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">BBC News</title>
<desc lang="fr">Twenty-four hours a day, the latest national and international stories as they break.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Infos</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/20/27/1880115_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230529140000 +0200" stop="20230529144500 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Impossible S6</title>
<desc lang="fr">Game show presented by Rick Edwards in which players score points by answering questions correctly. However, they must avoid the impossible answers, otherwise they will be eliminated from the show until the next day. In each episode there are three rounds, and the three highest scorers from each round play against each other in the final. The winner of this battle faces a £10,000 question.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Jeu</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/04/1660824_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230529144500 +0200" stop="20230529151500 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Eggheads S20</title>
<desc lang="fr">Teams from all over the UK battle to beat the formidable Eggheads.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Jeu</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/20/00/2134059_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230529151500 +0200" stop="20230529154500 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">James Martin's Food Map of Britain</title>
<desc lang="fr">Chef James Martin takes to the skies to explore how the beautiful and unique landscape of the British Isles produces distinct and delicious regional ingredients. In this episode he flies over the UK's answer to the Mediterranean, the South Coast. He discovers how the forests of Hampshire are home to one of Britain's most prized culinary ingredients, the truffle, and why tomatoes grown on the sunny Isle of Wight are giving those from Italy a run for their money. On his journey he cooks a delicious forest truffle chicken and succulent Isle of Wight stuffed tomatoes.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/08/13/2193913_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230529154500 +0200" stop="20230529161500 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">A Countryside Summer S1 (6/15)</title>
<desc lang="fr">Chris Packham and Megan McCubbin visit Walney Island off the west coast of England.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Nature</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/56/1752521_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230529161500 +0200" stop="20230529171500 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Big Cats About the House S1 (2/3)</title>
<desc lang="fr">Maya the jaguar is now a boisterous toddler and pushes the Clark family over the edge. She pulls through her health issues. Giles visits Costa Rica to see what wild jaguars face.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Animalier</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/20/30/2198307_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230529171500 +0200" stop="20230529181500 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Back in Time for the Corner Shop (Victorian) S1 (1/6)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Victorian»The Arderns start their time travelling adventure running a Victorian corner shop, discovering how life behind the counter reflects two decades of incredible social change.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Histoire</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/20/57/2198924_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230529181500 +0200" stop="20230529190000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Flog It ! S14</title>
<desc lang="fr">Flog It! comes from Ragley Hall in Warwickshire, a beautiful 17th-century Palladian house owned by the Marquess of Hertford. Antiques experts Will Axon and Christina Trevanion find treasures to take off to auction, like a Polynesian paddle and a stunning 18th-century drinking glass. Paul Martin explores the work of famous sculptor and wood carver Grinling Gibbons.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/20/12/2122567_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230529190000 +0200" stop="20230529193000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Richard Osman's House of Games S5</title>
<desc lang="fr">Every day this week, celebrity contestants Edith Bowman, Fern Brady, Will Kirk and Martin Lewis take on a series of quiz rounds selected by the host, quiz legend Richard Osman. A daily winner is declared following a quickfire round at the end of each show, and the scores are tallied across the week, resulting in an overall champion being crowned on Friday. Will the winning stars opt for the much-coveted House of Games wheelie luggage, or will they be tempted by the House of Games reusable coffee mug, which is brand new for this series?</desc>
<category lang="fr">Jeu</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/05/1687924_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230529193000 +0200" stop="20230529200000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Great Coastal Railway Journeys (Middlesbrough to Boulby) S2 (6/20)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Middlesbrough to Boulby»Michael is propelled in search of the unknown universe in Boulby, North Yorkshire.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Documentaire</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/08/18/2193914_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230529200000 +0200" stop="20230529203000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Digging for Britain (1/4)</title>
<desc lang="fr">Professor Alice Roberts re-examines key archaeological sites of prehistoric Britain, from the arrival of the earliest humans to mysterious ceremonies at Stonehenge.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Histoire</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/30/2122573_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230529203000 +0200" stop="20230529213000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Springwatch</title>
<desc lang="fr">Springwatch returns from a brand new location with a star-studded wildlife cast. Chris Packham and Michaela Strachan are broadcasting from RSPB Arne in Dorset, where spring is in full swing and the nest cameras are rigged, so they're ready to capture all the drama of the season. Iolo Williams is out and about exploring, not only RSPB Arne but the wider area of Purbeck, a new and very super NNR. Gillian Burke is embarking on a wildlife exploration of her own as she sets off to explore Snowdonia National Park.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/18/10/2197863_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230529213000 +0200" stop="20230529220000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">University Challenge</title>
<desc lang="fr">It's the grand final of the series. Only two teams remain, but which will lift the trophy?</desc>
<category lang="fr">Jeu</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/28/1764166_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230529220000 +0200" stop="20230529230000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Once Upon a Time Northern Ireland (Do Paramilitaries Lie Awake at Night?) S1 (2/5)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Do Paramilitaries Lie Awake at Night?»A deeply segregated society emerges as the violence escalates.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Histoire</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/52/2122893_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230529230000 +0200" stop="20230530012000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Les affranchis</title>
<desc lang="fr">Martin Scorcese's iconic gangster film, based on the true story of Henry Hill.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Thriller</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/17/04/2197781_A.jpg" />
</programme>