<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Voo -->
<programme start="20230526022500 +0200" stop="20230526032500 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Forensics: The Real CSI (To Catch a Rapist) S3 (2/4)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«To Catch a Rapist»A young woman is raped by a total stranger on a quiet residential street.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Documentaire</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/59/1974919_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230526032500 +0200" stop="20230526035500 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Iolo's Borderlands S1 (3/4)</title>
<desc lang="fr">Iolo Williams discovers curlew, linnets and dragonflies in Montgomeryshire.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Nature</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/12/2122122_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230526035500 +0200" stop="20230526042500 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">MasterChef S19</title>
<desc lang="fr">It's the last quarter-final, with this week's most talented four cooks returning to fight for a place in Knockout Week. They face a single intense challenge. They must cook two courses that will excite not just John and Gregg but also some of MasterChef's most inspiring winners, finalists and contestants, who have all gone on to careers in the food industry. Their fate is in the hands of two MasterChef champions, 2014's Ping Coombes and 2015's Simon Wood, and one of the finalists from 2020, Claire Fyfe. With just two Knockout Week places up for grabs, these amateurs need to show real flair and ambition to edge closer to the MasterChef 2023 trophy.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/29/56/2166894_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230526042500 +0200" stop="20230526071500 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">This is BBC Two</title>
<desc lang="fr">Highlights of programmes on BBC Two.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/41/1755108_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230526071500 +0200" stop="20230526081500 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Homes Under the Hammer S26 (26/30)</title>
<desc lang="fr">Featuring properties in Birkenhead, Ramsgate and Hull.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Télé-Réalité</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/43/2161497_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230526081500 +0200" stop="20230526090000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Money for Nothing S14 (6/20)</title>
<desc lang="fr">The team upcycle a chest of drawers, some utility chairs and a set of trestle table bases.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Documentaire</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/05/2125890_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230526090000 +0200" stop="20230526100000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Gardeners' World</title>
<desc lang="fr">Monty is busy planting umbellifers and making some changes to the dry garden. He also sows peas and pots his dahlias. Carol reveals exciting plans for an ambitious show garden she's designing for the RHS Hampton Court Palace Garden Festival. And with a ban on peat in compost on the way, Arit investigates what that means for the industry and gardeners alike. Plus an ecologist who takes a scientific approach to gardening for wildlife and more of the films that have been sent in by viewers.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/31/2155083_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230526100000 +0200" stop="20230526120000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Nicky Campbell BBC News Talk</title>
<desc lang="fr">Nicky Campbell takes your calls on the day's talking points, hearing views and experiences from across the UK. Call 08085 909693 between 9am and 11am on weekdays (calls are free from mobiles and landlines).</desc>
<category lang="fr">Autre</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/05/1978623_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230526120000 +0200" stop="20230526131500 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">BBC News</title>
<desc lang="fr">Twenty-four hours a day, the latest national and international stories as they break.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Infos</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/20/27/1880115_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230526131500 +0200" stop="20230526140000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Politics Live</title>
<desc lang="fr">Highlights of the week's proceedings at Westminster and the regional governments.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/03/1752432_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230526140000 +0200" stop="20230526144500 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Impossible S6</title>
<desc lang="fr">Game show presented by Rick Edwards in which players score points by answering questions correctly. However, they must avoid the impossible answers, otherwise they will be eliminated from the show until the next day. In each episode there are three rounds, and the three highest scorers from each round play against each other in the final. The winner of this battle faces a £10,000 question.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Jeu</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/04/1660824_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230526144500 +0200" stop="20230526151500 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Eggheads S20</title>
<desc lang="fr">Teams from all over the UK battle to beat the formidable Eggheads.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Jeu</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/20/00/2134059_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230526151500 +0200" stop="20230526154500 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">James Martin's Food Map of Britain</title>
<desc lang="fr">Chef James Martin takes to the skies to explore how the beautiful and unique landscape of the British Isles produces distinct and delicious regional ingredients. He explores Northern Ireland to get an understanding of why the beef from the miniature native cattle, the Dexter, has such a rich and unique flavour. He also visits the east coast and discovers why its lobsters are so prized by chefs. On his journey he creates a Goan lobster curry, and a fillet of Dexter beef served with a garlic and parsley risotto and caramelised onions.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/08/13/2193913_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230526154500 +0200" stop="20230526161500 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">A Countryside Summer S1 (5/15)</title>
<desc lang="fr">Marcus Wareing seeks inspiration from an expert herb grower in Bristol.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Nature</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/06/1752481_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230526161500 +0200" stop="20230526171500 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Big Cats About the House (Episode #1.1) S1 (1/3)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Episode #1.1»Big cat expert Giles Clark adopts Maya a jaguar cub and hand raises her at home while raising funds for wild cats. But Maya's health deteriorates and her life hangs in the balance.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Animalier</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/16/26/2197004_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230526171500 +0200" stop="20230526181500 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">La face cachée d'Istanbul (Athènes) (2/3)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Athènes»Dr Michael Scott uncovers the invisible ancient treasures of Istanbul, Turkey.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Histoire</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/12/29/2195492_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230526181500 +0200" stop="20230526190000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Flog It ! S14</title>
<desc lang="fr">This episode comes from the RAF Museum at Hendon in London. Antiques experts Michael Baggott and Mark Stacey find some real gems among the bags and boxes to take to auction. There's a nautilus shell that lights up the saleroom and some Superman film memorabilia that goes sky high. And Paul Martin explores the history of one of Britain's most famous tourist attractions; Highgate cemetery.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/20/12/2122567_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230526190000 +0200" stop="20230526193000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Richard Osman's House of Games S5</title>
<desc lang="fr">Every day this week, celebrity contestants Mehreen Baig, Clare Balding, Jamie Laing and Mike Wozniak take on a series of quiz rounds selected by the host, quiz legend Richard Osman. A daily winner is declared following a quickfire round at the end of each show, and the scores are tallied across the week, resulting in an overall champion being crowned on Friday. Will the winning stars opt for the much-coveted House of Games wheelie luggage, or will they be tempted by the House of Games reusable coffee mug, which is brand new for this series?</desc>
<category lang="fr">Jeu</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/05/1687924_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230526193000 +0200" stop="20230526200000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Great Coastal Railway Journeys (St Bees to Maryport) S2 (5/20)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«St Bees to Maryport»Michael meets a lifelong fan of Alfred Wainwright's famous guidebooks.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Documentaire</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/08/18/2193914_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230526200000 +0200" stop="20230526203000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Beechgrove Garden</title>
<desc lang="fr">Carole Baxter and Diana Yates are at the garden outside Aberdeen where they are continuing to mark the show's 45th anniversary by planting blue-themed varieties. This time, it's container planting. At the garden, they demonstrate how to produce homemade fertiliser using comfrey. In Bellshill, Calum Clunie helps a new gardener set up an allotment in order to have a steady supply of homegrown produce. George Anderson has an update from his own garden in Sunny Joppa, and Beechgrove's head gardener, Scott Smith, has a back-to basics guide on how to spot when your seedlings are ready for potting on.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/24/07/1805695_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230526203000 +0200" stop="20230526210000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Villages by the Sea (Ravenglass)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Ravenglass»Archaeologist Ben Robinson goes in search of the Romans in the village of Ravenglass.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Nature</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/34/2122125_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230526210000 +0200" stop="20230526220000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Chelsea Flower Show</title>
<desc lang="fr">At the end of the week, Monty Don and Joe Swift are celebrating in style the winner of the coveted BBC RHS People's Choice Award. Actor and passionate gardener Caroline Quentin gives us an exclusive in depth look at her glorious garden in Devon. Carol Klein reveals her guilty pleasure plants from the competition that deserve to be loved again. And Adam Frost takes a look behind the beauty to reveal how designers are using plants and materials to create stunning sanctuaries whilst making our gardens resilient to the changing climate.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/08/16/2193915_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230526220000 +0200" stop="20230526230000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Hidden Treasures of the National Trust S1 (3/6)</title>
<desc lang="fr">Restoring Paul McCartney's childhood home and uncovering a special trove of photos.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Documentaire</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/13/1767479_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230526230000 +0200" stop="20230526233000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Detectorists S3 (6/6)</title>
<desc lang="fr">Andy and Lance have a last day on the farm, one last chance to find that gold.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Série Comédie</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/37/2122580_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230526233000 +0200" stop="20230527000500 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Newsnight</title>
<desc lang="fr">The day's important national and international news stories. With Victoria Derbyshire.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Infos</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/20/21/1805472_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230527000500 +0200" stop="20230527003500 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">MOTDx</title>
<desc lang="fr">Jermaine Jenas brings you the best of football culture.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Mag Sport</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/17/1749481_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230527003500 +0200" stop="20230527013500 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Strike: Inside the Unions S1 (1/2)</title>
<desc lang="fr">State of the Unions.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Société</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/29/1974840_A.jpg" />
</programme>