<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Voo -->
<programme start="20230324011500 +0100" stop="20230324021500 +0100" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Becoming Frida Kahlo (Tout pour Diego) S1 (2/3)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Tout pour Diego»Now married and living in 1930s America, Frida sees the ugly side of capitalism.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Société</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/11/1755081_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230324021500 +0100" stop="20230324030000 +0100" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Rip Off Britain: Holidays S11 (8/10)</title>
<desc lang="fr">Which airlines are being stingiest with their free luggage allowance?</desc>
<category lang="fr">Documentaire</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/10/2125897_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230324030000 +0100" stop="20230324040000 +0100" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Inside the Autistic Mind (1/2)</title>
<desc lang="fr">Chris helps an autistic comedian connect with her mum and a non-speaking man find a voice.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/03/1752424_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230324040000 +0100" stop="20230324073000 +0100" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">This is BBC Two</title>
<desc lang="fr">Highlights of programmes on BBC Two.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/41/1755108_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230324073000 +0100" stop="20230324090000 +0100" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Saturday Kitchen Best Bites</title>
<desc lang="fr">The best bits and favourite moments from Saturday Kitchen.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/56/1682723_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230324090000 +0100" stop="20230324100000 +0100" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Gardeners' World</title>
<desc lang="fr">Monty Don plants tender annuals for high summer colour, as well as sharing his tips for growing cherries and pruning blackcurrants. Arit Anderson discovers a paradise garden in Cambridge that has become a focal point for the local community. Adam Frost heads to a beautiful walled garden in West Sussex that is both ornamental and productive, and Frances Tophill meets an enthusiast in Devon who grows a huge variety of perennial veg. Also, how one gardener transformed the alleyway behind his house into a relaxing space full of plants, as well as a grower from Suffolk sharing her obsession with tomatoes. There's also another look at some viewers' films from their own gardens.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/31/2155083_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230324100000 +0100" stop="20230324110000 +0100" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">BBC News</title>
<desc lang="fr">The latest headlines, breaking news and sport from the BBC newsroom.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Infos</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/32/1913999_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230324110000 +0100" stop="20230324131500 +0100" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">BBC News</title>
<desc lang="fr">Twenty-four hours a day, the latest national and international stories as they break.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Infos</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/32/1913999_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230324131500 +0100" stop="20230324140000 +0100" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Politics Live</title>
<desc lang="fr">Jo Coburn presents highlights of parliamentary proceedings from across the UK.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/05/1752469_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230324140000 +0100" stop="20230324144500 +0100" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Impossible S4</title>
<desc lang="fr">Game show in which 24 players compete across the series, scoring points by answering questions correctly. However, they must avoid the impossible answers, otherwise they will be eliminated from the show until the next day. In each episode there are three rounds, and the three highest scorers from each round play against each other in the final. The winner of this battle faces a £10,000 question.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Jeu</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/04/1660824_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230324144500 +0100" stop="20230324151500 +0100" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Eggheads S20</title>
<desc lang="fr">A new team of challengers take on what is probably the greatest quiz team in Britain.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Jeu</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/19/11/2134059_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230324151500 +0100" stop="20230324154500 +0100" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Eggheads S20</title>
<desc lang="fr">A new team of challengers take on probably the greatest quiz team in Britain.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Jeu</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/19/11/2134059_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230324154500 +0100" stop="20230324161500 +0100" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Hairy Bikers' Best of British (Recession) S1 (5/30)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Recession»Si and Dave discover how necessity often forced British cooks to pull out all the stops.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Documentaire</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/41/2043461_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230324161500 +0100" stop="20230324171500 +0100" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Eat Well for Less? S8</title>
<desc lang="fr">Chris and Jordan help a convenience-loving family cook one meal for all and save money.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/07/00/2156367_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230324171500 +0100" stop="20230324181500 +0100" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">The World's Most Extraordinary Homes (Spain) S2 (5/8)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Spain»Piers and Caroline visit a house made up of 11 specially crafted steel boxes.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Documentaire</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/10/22/2157702_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230324181500 +0100" stop="20230324190000 +0100" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Flog It ! S17</title>
<desc lang="fr">Today, Flog It! comes from Dover Castle in Kent. Antique experts James Lewis and Jonathan Pratt search for items to take off to auction. James finds a hefty hunting club, and Jonathan unearths a lighter that is also a ruler. Paul Martin uncovers the story of author Ian Fleming, who created James Bond.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/54/2122567_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230324190000 +0100" stop="20230324193000 +0100" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Richard Osman's House of Games S5</title>
<desc lang="fr">Every day this week, celebrity contestants Hugh Fearnley-Whittingstall, Jodie Kidd, Jamali Maddix and Suzi Perry take on a series of quiz rounds selected by the host, quiz legend Richard Osman. A daily winner is declared following a quick-fire round at the end of each show, and the scores are tallied across the week, resulting in an overall champion being crowned on Friday. Will the winning stars opt for the much-coveted House of Games decanter, or will they be tempted by the House of Games kitchen composter?</desc>
<category lang="fr">Jeu</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/05/1687924_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230324193000 +0100" stop="20230324200000 +0100" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Coast to Coast Food Festival (York) S1 (10/20)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«York»Sean Fletcher and Edith Bowman go in search of tips and treats at the York Food Festival.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Documentaire</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/07/1752962_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230324200000 +0100" stop="20230324210000 +0100" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Your Home Made Perfect S3</title>
<desc lang="fr">In 2017, Lei Ying and her husband, David, snapped up a Belfast house after seeing the amount of space it could offer them. However, three years later and with their children growing fast, they have discovered that having lots of space is not always a good thing - especially when it's all in the wrong place. The layout means that mealtimes are spent in a tiny, stressful corner of the ground floor, and when they want to relax, the cavernous lounge is too big to be cosy. They are lucky enough to have a garden, but access to that is also problematic, with a tight chicane of corridors and a dangerous staircase the only route. Lei Ying dreams of a perfect kitchen, whilst David hopes for a cosy home and a safe route to the garden. Can architects Laura Jane Clark and Will Foster solve all these problems on a £25,000 budget?</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/26/2157708_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230324210000 +0100" stop="20230324220000 +0100" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Gardeners' World</title>
<desc lang="fr">As plants begin to show their early growth, Monty gets plenty of plants for free when he demonstrates how to make the most of herbaceous perennials. He also cuts back pelargoniums that have overwintered in the greenhouse and makes a start on sowing vegetables. Nick Bailey shares plans for his new garden in Cambridgeshire and shows us how to create a container garden ideal for those on the move. Frances Tophill discovers more ways to use cut flowers as she visits a florist in Dorset. Sue Kent has plenty to do to start the growing season in her Swansea garden as she creates a white border and experiments with an unusual way to grow container vegetables. And Rachel de Thame celebrates the majestic Hellebore. Plus more of the films that have been sent in to us by viewers.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/31/2155083_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230324220000 +0100" stop="20230324230000 +0100" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Becoming Frida Kahlo (A Star Is Born) S1 (3/3)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«A Star Is Born»Dangerous politics and turbulent love shock Frida's world.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Société</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/11/1755081_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230324230000 +0100" stop="20230324233000 +0100" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Cunk on Britain S1 (1/5)</title>
<desc lang="fr">Philomena's mockumentary series taking us right up Britain's history. Starting from the very beginning with the Big Bang. Written by Charlie Brooker, starring Diane Morgan.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Documentaire</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/36/1757419_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230324233000 +0100" stop="20230325000500 +0100" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Newsnight</title>
<desc lang="fr">The day's important national and international news stories. With Faisal Islam.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Infos</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/37/1776034_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230325000500 +0100" stop="20230325003500 +0100" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">MOTDx</title>
<desc lang="fr">Another selection of football, music and lifestyle from around the Premier League scene.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Mag Sport</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/17/1749481_A.jpg" />
</programme>