<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Voo -->
<programme start="20230514020500 +0200" stop="20230514030500 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Pride Hits at the BBC</title>
<desc lang="fr">A musical celebration for Pride, with a collection of the BBC archives' biggest stars.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Musique</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/56/1752527_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230514030500 +0200" stop="20230514044000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Celle que vous croyez</title>
<desc lang="fr">A woman creates a fake profile on social media with unintended consequences.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Drame</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/05/51/1760684_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230514044000 +0200" stop="20230514073500 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">This is BBC Two</title>
<desc lang="fr">Highlights of programmes on BBC Two.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/11/1853150_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230514073500 +0200" stop="20230514083500 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Gardeners' World</title>
<desc lang="fr">A special programme from the first big flower show of the season - the RHS Malvern Spring Festival. Rachel de Thame and Nick Bailey explore show gardens packed full of ideas and discover the newest varieties of plants and flowers that are hot off the potting bench. There are the herb specialists from Gloucestershire who believe that edibles are just as important as ornamentals in the garden, and a nursery famed for its foxgloves that also has an impressive collection of tree peonies. Toby Buckland celebrates spring colour at Aberglasney Gardens in Carmarthenshire, and Arit Anderson spends the day with a charity group that gives horticultural work experience to vulnerable people and those with learning difficulties.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/31/2155083_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230514083500 +0200" stop="20230514093000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Countryfile</title>
<desc lang="fr">Countryfile returns to the New Forest community helping Ukrainian refugees.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Mag Société</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/43/2161494_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230514093000 +0200" stop="20230514100000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Beechgrove Garden</title>
<desc lang="fr">Blooms, veggies and fruit all get the expert treatment from George Anderson and Calum Clunie. George is trialling new blueberry bushes, and Calum is demonstrating even more garden produce to plant at home. One of Scotland's favourite flowers - the sweet pea - gets planted out, ready to bring colour and fragrance wherever they are cultivated. Lizzie Schofield starts working with a family that has just moved into a new-build estate, with a new house and a new garden that needs to be turned from turf to terrific.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/24/07/1805695_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230514100000 +0200" stop="20230514103000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Landward (6/26)</title>
<desc lang="fr">Dougie visits Mar Lodge Estate in the Cairngorms to see the regeneration of the forest.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Nature</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/27/59/1870648_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230514103000 +0200" stop="20230514120000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Saturday Kitchen Best Bites</title>
<desc lang="fr">The best bits and favourite moments from Saturday Kitchen.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/56/1682723_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230514120000 +0200" stop="20230514130000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">The Big Family Cooking Showdown S2</title>
<desc lang="fr">The three remaining families must volunteer a family member to cook a salted caramel tart.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/29/32/2190464_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230514130000 +0200" stop="20230514133000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Food and Drink S3</title>
<desc lang="fr">Chef and pub landlord Tom Kerridge plays host to some of the best cooks in a series highlighting all that is excellent in food and drink. This edition is all about the best of British food. Tom is joined by Hugh Fearnley-Whittingstall - a passionate champion of British dishes. He cooks a classic roast chicken to go up against Tom's stew and dumplings. Oliver Peyton puts cured meats from Blighty under the spotlight, and drinks expert Joe Wadsack tastes a wine made in London, before we find out whether Tom's stew or Hugh's chicken is the best British dish.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/56/2122583_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230514133000 +0200" stop="20230514141500 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Talking Pictures</title>
<desc lang="fr">Celia Imrie takes a look at some of the leading ladies who've proved time and again, year after year, that they are amongst the very best of British talent. These are our acting Dames, who've earned the respect and affection of cinema audiences - and the royal seal of approval, too. Using BBC interviews and archive footage, those featured include Emma Thompson, Diana Rigg, Julie Walters, Elizabeth Taylor, Maggie Smith, Judi Dench and Helen Mirren - all of whom prove unquestionably that the song was right - there IS nothing like a Dame.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Mag Culture</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/50/1752955_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230514141500 +0200" stop="20230514160500 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Un thé avec Mussolini</title>
<desc lang="fr">Florence 1935. Luca, part-raised by English ladies in Florence, re-enters their lives.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Comédie</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/05/07/1937186_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230514160500 +0200" stop="20230514170000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Flog It ! S13</title>
<desc lang="fr">This episode comes from Southwell Minster in the town of Southwell, near Nottingham, where experts Caroline Hawley and Mark Stacey find antiques and collectables to take to auction. Paul Martin finds out how Southwell Minster has had a cavalcade of historical figures pass through the doors, from Cardinal Wolsey to Charles I, at some dramatic moments in British history. Paul also explores Newstead Abbey, the country seat of poet and renowned lothario Lord Byron, and finds out there is more to him and his relationships than meets the eye.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/54/2122567_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230514170000 +0200" stop="20230514180000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Course sans frontières S3</title>
<desc lang="fr">The five pairs meet up again to reflect on the adventure of a lifetime.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Télé-Réalité</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/24/2157031_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230514180000 +0200" stop="20230514190000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Commando: Britain's Ocean Warriors S1 (4/4)</title>
<desc lang="fr">Would-be mountain leaders are pushed to the limit in the frozen wilds of northern Norway.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Société</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/05/22/2192598_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230514190000 +0200" stop="20230514200000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Les motards poilus : Cooking Trip en Méditerranée S1</title>
<desc lang="fr">On the final leg of their Mediterranean journey, the Hairy Bikers are travelling through Southern Spain in the footsteps of the Moors, heading for Costa del Sol. They begin their exploration of the Moorish influence on the culture and cuisine of Spain in Valencia. The bikers head straight for the market to taste a local speciality, horchata, a non-alcoholic drink made from tiger nuts.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/18/13/2185361_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230514200000 +0200" stop="20230514210000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Inside the Factory (Mints) S7 (9/10)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Mints»Gregg visits a factory that churns out 32 million mints per day.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Société</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/28/15/2189975_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230514210000 +0200" stop="20230514220000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Antiques Roadshow</title>
<desc lang="fr">Judith Miller is intrigued and just a little terrified by a collection of 1970s dolls with eyes that change colour, made by the short-lived Blythe's Boutique company. Mark Hill is thrilled to see an early Louis Vuitton trunk, while Wayne Colquhoun admires a pair of vintage Guinness signs from the wall of a popular pub. Justin Croft challenges Fiona to put three books by famous Irish authors in order of value, while jewellery specialist John Benjamin is captivated by an unusual black opal. Mark Smith gets a rare chance to see medals awarded to participants in the Easter Rising in Dublin in 1916, while Fiona meets the Armagh Rhymers, a folk group who dress in bizarre wicker costumes and preserve the ancient tradition of storytelling known as mumming.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/14/2162908_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230514220000 +0200" stop="20230514230000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Simon Reeve's South America (Brazil) S1 (n°2)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Brazil»Simon travels through Brazil, from the heart of the Amazon to the city of Rio de Janeiro.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Documentaire</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/05/05/12/2102387_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230514230000 +0200" stop="20230515010500 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Désigné coupable</title>
<desc lang="fr">Based on a true story of Mohamedou Ould Salahi, a Mauritanian citizen who was detained at Guantánamo Bay detention camp without charge from 2002 until his release in 2016.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Drame</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/04/05/10/2121755_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230515010500 +0200" stop="20230515015000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">The Chris &amp; Rosie Ramsey Show S2</title>
<desc lang="fr">Filmed in front of a live studio audience, the always up-for-a-laugh, always startlingly honest husband and wife presenting duo will be joined by another celebrity couple to poke fun at life, relationships, annoyances, parenting and absolutely everything in between, as well as sharing their relationship highs and, let's face it, most importantly, their 'beefs'. Other popular elements include Please Keep Me Anonymous, where a well-known face reads out some terrifying audience confessions, and It Goes Or I Go, where audience members compete to rid themselves of something their loved one just refuses to remove from the house.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/53/1753750_A.jpg" />
</programme>