<!-- racacax\XmlTv\Component\Provider\Voo -->
<programme start="20230402021500 +0200" stop="20230402035500 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Wild Men</title>
<desc lang="fr">Comedy about a man in the midst of a midlife crisis who decides to live in the wilderness.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Comédie</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/24/26/2164795_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230402035500 +0200" stop="20230402072500 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">This is BBC Two</title>
<desc lang="fr">Highlights of programmes on BBC Two.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/19/1853151_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230402072500 +0200" stop="20230402082500 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Gardeners' World</title>
<desc lang="fr">With spring gaining momentum, Adam Frost gets to work on his veg plot and plants his first lot of potatoes. He introduces roses to his borders, and in a quest to increase biodiversity, has a radical plan for his lawn. Joe Swift meets a garden designer who, facing the challenge of two awkward, adjoining plots, transformed them into wonderful, cohesive spaces. And Rekha Mistry demonstrates how to grow the perfect onion from seed and has a go at growing cotton. Plus more of the films that have been sent in by viewers.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/31/2155083_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230402082500 +0200" stop="20230402091000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Countryfile</title>
<desc lang="fr">Joe Crowley is in Aberystwyth to meet scientists behind some of the biggest new developments in farming and food security, from insect brownies to the revival of historic crops and why some South American visitors could be the saviours of upland farming. Charlotte Smith is in the Lea Valley, home to 3,500 acres of glasshouses providing 75 per cent of the UK's home-grown salads, to investigate why what's known as London's salad bowl is on the brink of collapse. Adam Henson finds out why the shift towards sustainable farming could mean boom time for native breeds, while Adrian Chiles discovers what the future of sheep farming could be in his final report from the Welsh mountains.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Mag Société</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/43/2161494_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230402091000 +0200" stop="20230402101000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Pilgrimage: The Road to Istanbul (3/3)</title>
<desc lang="fr">With the end of their pilgrimage looming, the celebrities get a taste of monastic life.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Découverte</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/06/2156364_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230402101000 +0200" stop="20230402114000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Saturday Kitchen Best Bites</title>
<desc lang="fr">The best bits and favourite moments from Saturday Kitchen.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Magazine</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/56/1682723_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230402114000 +0200" stop="20230402121000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Coast to Coast Food Festival (Anstruther) S1 (12/20)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Anstruther»Edith Bowman introduces Colin Murray to her home town of Anstruther on a food adventure.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Documentaire</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/56/2122583_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230402121000 +0200" stop="20230402124000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Sign Zone: The Big Cook Out</title>
<desc lang="fr">Sam and Shauna try something completely different as they take on an epic vegetarian cookout, by celebrating the Indian Gujarati community in Grangetown in the heart of Cardiff. This vibrant community carries out valuable volunteer work, including feeding the homeless every month with fresh, home-cooked food. Gujaratis are strict vegetarians, which means that meat-loving Sam and Shauna have to come up with some innovative ideas for their big cookout. They learn how to make an avocado and mango chutney using a recipe from one of the community members that has been handed down through the generations, and to complete the menu, they make a black bean and jackfruit chilli and demonstrate the best way to make vegetable kebabs.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/28/08/2158278_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230402124000 +0200" stop="20230402131500 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Sign Zone: The Big Cook Out S2</title>
<desc lang="fr">In this episode, Sam and Shauna head west to Ferryside, a small but close-knit coastal community just eight miles from Carmarthen in south west Wales. They want to celebrate the work and achievements of Ferryside Lifeboat, a completely independent organisation run entirely by volunteers from the local community. They decide to lay on a huge fishy feast on the beach. Sam and Shauna get the whole community to help them make a show-stopping Cajun seaweed bake, where lobster, mussels, sea bass, potatoes and corn are steamed for hours in a massive firepit in the beach as the sun goes down. Sam and Shauna also teach the Ferryside Lifeboat community how to make a New England-style fish and cockle chowder served with laverbread, and mackerel smoked on sticks over an open fire on the beach, served with an African-style zingy chermoula dip.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/28/08/2158278_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230402131500 +0200" stop="20230402153000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Arsenal / Manchester City</title>
<desc lang="fr">Coverage from the WSL as Arsenal host Manchester City.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Football</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/27/1868494_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230402153000 +0200" stop="20230402180000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">England v Italy</title>
<desc lang="fr">Live rugby union as England continue their quest for a fifth straight Women's Six Nations title, with last year's Grand Slam winners hosting Italy at Franklin's Gardens, Northampton. England enjoyed a comfortable 74-0 victory in Parma last year, which formed part of their incredible 30-match winning streak that only ended at the hands of New Zealand in the World Cup final.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Sport</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/13/2158277_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230402180000 +0200" stop="20230402190000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Course sans frontières S3</title>
<desc lang="fr">The teams head into the heart of the Yukon towards former gold rush boom town Dawson City.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Télé-Réalité</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/22/24/2157031_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230402190000 +0200" stop="20230402200000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Flog It ! S11</title>
<desc lang="fr">In this episode, Flog It! comes from the Imperial War Museum at Duxford in Cambridgeshire. The experts will be greeting hundreds of visitors and trying to find items to take off to auction. Meanwhile, Paul Martin finds out more about the Hawker Hurricane, famed for its role in the Battle of Britain.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Divertissement</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/54/2122567_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230402200000 +0200" stop="20230402210000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">The Boleyns: A Scandalous Family (Ambition) S1 (1/3)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Ambition»Thomas Boleyn, the patriarch of the Boleyns, is determined to elevate the family name. His ambitions for his three children will take them to the heart of the Tudor court.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Histoire</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/52/1755596_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230402210000 +0200" stop="20230402220000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Britain's Biggest Warship: Goes to Sea (Manhattan Ahoy!) S2 (3/3)</title>
<desc lang="fr">«Manhattan Ahoy!»With just a few weeks to go before HMS Queen Elizabeth arrives in New York in spectacular style, the F35 jets try a method of landing never attempted before.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Doc Sciences</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/23/09/2157697_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230402220000 +0200" stop="20230402230000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Simon Reeve's Return to Cornwall</title>
<desc lang="fr">Simon Reeve returns to Cornwall to see what life is like when the summer crowds have gone.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Documentaire</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/13/1756161_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230402230000 +0200" stop="20230403004000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">Les fils de l'homme</title>
<desc lang="fr">In a future where children are no longer born, a loner helps a pregnant woman to safety.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Science-Fiction</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/03/24/27/2164797_A.jpg" />
</programme>
<programme start="20230403004000 +0200" stop="20230403011000 +0200" channel="VOO.be">
<title lang="fr">The Cockfields S1 (2/3)</title>
<desc lang="fr">The family are visiting Aunty Rose in the nursing home, and Donna offers to make tea.</desc>
<category lang="fr">Série Comédie</category>
<icon src="https://images.voomotion.be/Events/2023/01/12/47/1752362_A.jpg" />
</programme>